Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Right in the middle of his battle
with the terrifying Artificial Humans,
Goku is assaulted by the
symptoms of his heart ailment.
Goku was in an absolute pinch.
It was Vegeta who came to Goku's aid.
At length, Vegeta had become
a legendary Super Saiyan as well.
I was left shaking from the joy it gave me.
I had overcome Kakarrot,
and the time had come for me
to return as Prince of the Saiyans!
Regardless of what you may
have changed yourself into,
you are still no match for us Artificial Humans.
"No. 20's Defiant Smile...
The Secret of Doctor Gero."
Yeah, I guess that's about the level you'd be.
I failed to mention something...
When we become Super Saiyans,
our ferocity increases somewhat.
We become lightly over-excited.
You guys don't feel pain, do you?
How lucky for you.
So strong!
What's wrong?
Have your rummage sale
puppet calculations gone awry?
Well, weren't you put together well?
Is that blood there? Or is it oil?
I've got you!
I won't let go until I've
absorbed all of your energy!
Oh, no!
Kicking won't do any good.
I absolutely will not let go.
Absolutely, you say?
Don't you let go!
Goku, it's okay.
Everyone else will take care of those guys.
We will change history.
Sure enough.
You guys really do suck
energy out through your hands.
Then you take that energy
and add it to your own.
You expect me to let go?
You absolutely will not let go of me.
Absolutely not!
So then, this is the area on your palms...
...that you used to absorb your energy, is it?
I've had quite a bit drawn out of me,
but I figure you won't be doing that any more.
You feel fear, do you,
even though you're an Artificial Human?
Why, you...
Not so fast!
After I'm finished with him,
then I can take all the time I need against you!
What is it?!
Take this!
It's Super Vegeta's Big Bang Attack!
Huh? What's that smoke there?
I know!
That island must be where everyone
is fighting the Artificial Humans!
Hey! Don' tell me yer fixin'
to take us down to that island?
Naturally, of course I am.
You idiot! Don' you dare!
–What do you think you're doing?
–Cut that out!
With all this shouting, you've made him cry!
When that baby gets in a bad mood,
he tends to wet himself, so watch out!
Fool! I'm tellin' ya to turn back!
We certainly appear to have miscalculated.
But, as before, there is no
possibility of you coming out victorious.
I've been considerably drained
of energy by that other one.
If you're going to beat me, now is your chance.
Bring it on.
Does he... have some sort of strategy here?
You were ranting to
yourself just now, weren't you?
About how we have absolutely
no chance for victory?
I can't say I feel the same way.
What did you mean by that?
I meant that no matter how unimaginably
strong you may have become,
it still is not enough to
defeat the Artificial Humans.
So it's nothing more than you
being a poor loser then, is it?
He-He's running away!
He's planning on hiding himself in those rocks!
Hey, Kuririn!
Give me one of those senzu!
Eh?
But...
Hurry it up!
Do you want him to get away?
Give it to him, Kuririn.
All right.
Here!
Could you have made that any less snappy?
You stupid idiot!
All right!
You guys go on home...
...and have yourselves a
relaxing glass of milk or whatever.
Just stay out of my way!
Damn him! Where does he get
off telling us to go drink milk?!
He actually allowed himself
to lose quite a bit of his power.
He purposely let the fight go
on long enough to confirm...
...that the Artificial Humans
draw in energy through their palms.
If he had fought with
that No. 20 guy just now,
he likely would have lost.
Instead, he came across like he
had something more up his sleeve.
Vegeta really does have a gift for battle.
He might have even surpassed... Goku.
Regardless, I'm going after them!
Even if it's just to confirm with my own eyes...
...that the Artificial Humans are finished.
Me too!
I'm going too!
If we stop now,
then I won't understand why
I went through all that training!
All right then.
But do not attempt to fight.
That guy is more than any of you can handle!
He will be using the rocks to conceal himself.
Since he's an Artificial Human,
you can't count on being
able to sense him, either.
If you find him, let Vegeta
or myself know immediately.
And be extremely cautious over there.
–Right!
–Let's go!
Where are you?! Come on out!
You coward!
Show yourself!
Dammit.
He's using this topography
to his advantage, all right.
In that case, I'll just have to drive him out.
I'll just blow all of these rocks away!
Stop! The rest of us are down here too!
Take this!
I accept your energy!
Shoot!
Damn you–!
Dammit. He's a lot faster than I thought.
Looks like he's gotten too used...
...to using an opponent's
ki to follow their moves.
I am able to follow your movements quite well,
but I doubt you'll ever find me.
On the other hand,
who would have thought
Vegeta could be so strong?
What am I going to do?
I don't have a chance against him.
Looks like I have no choice
but to return to the laboratory.
I wanted to avoid the
laboratory, if at all possible...
He's here too?
There's plenty of targets creeping
around that I can steal energy from.
I'll drain all of their energy,
and add it to my own!
Then I can beat Vegeta!
The cunning Artificial Human No. 20...
If left unchecked, something
terrible is bound to happen.
And what is happening at
Doctor Gero's laboratory?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
What did you say, Trunks?
These are different from the
Artificial Humans you know?
That's impossible.
Then, who is this guy we're fighting now?!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"A Reality More Terrifying than the Future!?
Trunks' Suspicions."
What in the world is going on?
"Next time"
"A Reality More Terrifying than the Future!?
Trunks'Suspicions"