Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Goku and Cell had reached their full power.
The highest level of battle had begun.
You've suddenly appeared
and vanished before, as well.
Instantaneous Movement. I can do it.
And when it comes to speed,
I'm pretty sure of myself.
Although, I can't keep up
with Instantaneous Movement.
"Defeat or Death!?
Goku's Turnabout Ploy."
Awesome! They're ridiculously fast!
W-Wha–What a fight this must be...
Goku!
Th-They've vanished...
W-Where... where could
the two of them have gone?
All in all, those guys are
incredibly fast, both of them!
You're pretty good, really.
I honestly didn't think you
would entertain me this much.
Me, too.
This is the way a fight has to be.
Now then, I think it's about time we got going.
Over there!
That broken up area there!
They're hiding there,
using some camouflage as a trick!
A-Ah, so that's it!
No matter what tricks they
may use, they cannot fool my eyes!
That's our Mister Satan, the
greatest combat sportsman in the world!
O-Over there...
They're up there, huh, Mister Satan?
Cameraman! Above us! Above us!
R-Right!
–We can't see anything!
–What is this? We can't tell what's going on!
What happened to Satan? Where's Satan?!
We want to see Satan defeat Cell!
Put Satan on! Satan!
Yeah, yeah!
Their battle is already beyond the
point where a TV camera can capture it.
Yes. Previous Kami-sama also stood there often,
observing status of Lower Realm.
Is that so?
Yes.
No need strain yourself.
Previous Kami-sama also concentrated
until clearly understood Lower Realm situation.
Use less force. Feel out ki,
like differentiating quiet sounds.
Goku-san is fighting. It's an incredible fight...
Yes. Now you got it.
W-Watch out!
F-Father...!
This is a magnificent fight!
I would hate to let it end
due to an out-of-bounds defeat.
Let's remove the out-of-bounds
defeat from the rules.
It doesn't hold any meaning for us.
What...? What do you intend to do?
Everybody! Get away from the ring!!
Phew, that was close...!
Th-Thanks so much...
You guys should go home already.
You're in the way here.
W-We can't very well do that.
After this, our Mister Satan
is going to be fighting, after all.
Right, Mister Satan?
Satan-sama?
O-Of course I am!
But then, maybe we should watch
from a little bit further distance.
Now, the whole land is our ring.
Whoever loses will now be determined
only by surrendering or dying.
I get it. You want to fight all-out.
That is what is most appropriate
for a fight between you and I.
All right.
Now then, what do you say we
make full use of this expanse right away?
C-Cameraman, move forward
some more. More, more, more, more!
R-Right...!
What are they doing?!
We can't see anything!
N-No, there's no malfunction, our
courageous announcer and cameraman
are providing special coverage from the site...
Yes... yes... if you could
please just wait a little longer...
No, that's not what I meant... Yes...
Yes, Z-TV...
S-Such extraordinary shockwaves!
W-What in the world could this be?
Satan-sama...?
T-Tricks! Tricks...
I-It's trembling... The ground is trembling!
Mister Satan, could this be a trick, too?
I-Incredible!
It's not just speed, neither one of
them is falling behind on power, either!
Incredible, incredible,
incredible, incredible, incredible!
No, hold on–don't!
Not like that, there, there, there!
You got him! No, not like that! Got him!
That's the way! That's the way! Go! Go! Go!
Go–
You're here, are you?
How long have you...?
What a fierce battle.
What's more, even though a good deal
of time has passed since the fight started,
neither one of those two's
ki has dropped hardly at all.
If Cell is a monster, then
Son Goku is also a monster.
G-Goku... what are you planning
to do from way up that high?
Ka... me...
It's a Kamehame-Ha!
Is Goku thinking of launching
a Kamehame-Ha at full power?!
You can't shoot a
Kamehame-Ha from that position!
If you did, it would be a disaster for the Earth!
Th-There's no way he would shoot it.
If he did so from that position,
it would destroy the Earth.
ha... me...
H-Hey...!
F-Father is planning to fire it!
Y-You wouldn't...!
Holy–!
Ha!!
Finally, Goku's full power
Kamehame-Ha bursts forth!
The goddess of victory has smiled upon Goku.
Or has she?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Cell is back up. Rats,
sure enough, he's still alive.
I knew that I'd beaten him too easily.
I'm sorry to say it but Goku can't win.
What's more, it looks like he
knows that while he as fighting.
I don't know what he has in mind.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"A Conclusion to the Deathmatch!!
Goku's Declaration of Surrender!?"
It can't be! Father, why?
"Next time"
"A Conclusion to the Deathmatch!!
Goku's Declaration of Surrender!?"