Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
In the face of the overwhelming
power boasted by the Saiyans,
Yamucha, Chaozu, and
Tenshinhan had been defeated.
Elsewhere, Son Goku, who had
finally made his way back to Kami-sama,
spurred Kinto Un to rush to the field of battle.
Kinto Un!
"Leave it to Me!
Gohan's Great Burst of Anger."
Looks like Kakarrot has decided to lay low.
What a coward.
F-Father is not a coward!
D-Dammit...
What's become of you, Goku?!
Hurry, Kinto Un!
Go, go, go! Go!
At this point, it looks like we'll have
to fight them with just the three of us.
You know what to do. Let's go with that plan.
Y-Yeah.
First, I draw his attention as much as I can.
I'll find an opening, and grab
his tail, the Saiyans' weakness.
Once his power fails, and he can't move...
I-I rush him as hard as I can.
That's right. Watch yourself!
What are you all mumbling
about? It won't do any good.
What can you guys do against me?
We'll show you what we can do, right now!
All right!
Here goes!
He's started charging me all of a sudden!
Keep his attention!
Now!
Why, you–!
Gohan!
We did it!
You fools!
I-Impossible!
P-Piccolo-san!
Whoa, don't you die, now.
We still have to have you
tell us about the Dragon Balls.
I-It can't be!
Hell of a miscalculation, huh?
Did you think we would leave
our weak spot untrained forever?
That's too bad. The best
that this planet had to offer,
and this is what happens to him after one blow.
P-Piccolo-san!
Shake it off! Piccolo-san!
Piccolo-san! Piccolo-san!
I-It's hopeless now...
Now then, while he has gone beddy-bye,
I think I'll toy around with the little squirts.
I'll start with Kakarrot's son.
Hey, you've inherited
the blood of a true Saiyan.
You'll be able to amuse
me for a little while, right?
You know, your old man is pretty cold, huh?
Letting his own son die like this...
Dammit, what's going on here?!
The TV isn't showing anything!
Come on, come on, come on!
It's no use.
I'm sure that things aren't going so smoothly
that they can provide us with a TV broadcast.
Y-You don't think that everyone
has been killed already, do you?
Don't you say anything dire like that again!
Ch-Chichi, what are you
doin', gussied up like that?
T-Those are Lunch-san's...
I can't take it anymore!
I'm goin' to rescue Gohan!
D-Don't be ridiculous! If you
go now, you're goin' to be killed!
I don't care! I'm goin'
to die together with Gohan!
H-Hold on, now!
Chichi! Calm down!
Let me go, Pa! Let me go!
Let go of me! I-I'm goin'!
Pa! Let go of me! I'm goin'!
I'm goin'! I'm goin'! I'm goin'!
Now see here, Chichi!
You're goin' to get killed!
–I'm tellin' you no!
–I'm goin' to go rescue Gohan-chan!
–Come on, re-think this!
–I'm goin' where Gohan is!
Chichi!
Tenshinhan...
Yamucha...
Son-kun...
I believe in you.
I'm sure... I'm sure
you're going to save the Earth.
Hey now, don't you snuff it
just yet! Amuse me a little longer.
That's more like it!
Stop!
Ho, at least his moves are pretty good.
You dirty brat! Bounce around, will you?!
Let me show you something I've been saving.
Kienzan!
What a worthless technique!
Nappa! Get out of the way!
That idiot! Can't he tell
what kind of technique that is?!
D-Damn!
W-Why, you–!
How dare you wound my face!
Away with you!
K-Kuririn-san!
Now to finish you!
Y-You bastard!
A-Are you awake already?!
Looks like you're having
a hard time with them, Nappa!
Don't you... don't you
look down on Earth, Saiyan!
W-W-Why, you! Now I'm mad!
I was holding back against you,
since we can't kill you
because of the Dragon Balls.
But don't get too full of yourself!
You're the one who's too full of himself!
W-What ki is this?!
T-There's an incredible ki
coming this way from far off!
I-It's true! A-An amazing, yet familiar ki!
N-No doubt about it. I can feel it.
You guys are all just
spouting nonsense! What is this?!
It could only be him. It's Son Goku!
Just a little farther, Goku. Hurry! Make haste!
It's Son Goku! Son Goku is coming!
I knew he was sure to come!
Damn that bastard, making us wait for him!
F-Father! Father really is coming! Hurry!
G-Goku...
Kakarrot?
Where is he?
These guys have the unusual
ability to sense someone's presence.
Is it Kakarrot? Let's see...
I'm close. I can feel them.
There are two enormous ki,
two even more enormous ki, and one small ki...
That number ain't right. Has somebody died?
Kinto Un, please hurry faster!
Vegeta-sama!
Is what these guys are saying true?
Is Kakarrot really headed this way?
I don't know whether it's Kakarrot or not,
but someone will be
here in about four minutes.
Someone with a battle power of five thousand.
Five–five thousand?! That's impossible!
It's definitely a reading
that makes it unthinkable
that this is the same Kakarrot as before.
What's more, these guys
are able to alter their readings.
That means it's at least five thousand.
T-That can't be! It must
be some kind of mistake!
It's unusual to see this guy panicked.
Nappa! Kill them! If all four of them
team up, it could be a problem for us!
It will also serve as a warning to Kakarrot!
What?!
But what about the Dragon Balls?
I don't care! I have an idea.
If we go to Planet Namek,
the home world of that Namekian,
I'm sure that there will be Dragon
Balls that are even more powerful.
I thought they were just worthless stories,
but if Kakarrot really has come back to life,
then those legends are true after all.
I get you. But Kakarrot being five thousand
has to be a mechanical malfunction.
Well, it doesn't matter. It doesn't
change the fact that I get to kill them all.
I'll start with you!
P-Piccolo-san, run!
I'll stop him one way or
another until Father gets here!
What?!
After all, if you die, Piccolo-san,
then Kami-sama dies too,
and the Dragon Balls will...
You're talking nonsense! There's
no way you can stop him by yourself!
Stop me, you say? Me?
I-If this keeps up, there
won't be any going back...
I-It's no use... I can't move...
Don't make me laugh, you brat!
No!
I-Incredible! D-Did he get him?
Why, you brat! This is where it ends!
N-No!
Goku...
Die!
Who–who are you?
They're sour!
Piccolo leaps in to rescue Gohan from his pinch.
What will be Piccolo's fate?
Hurry, Goku!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Sorry to keep you guys waiting!
You're going to pay, you Saiyans!
Ha! You just had to stroll on by, huh?
There's no way you can stand up to Nappa-sama–
Ungh! What?! T-That's impossible!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Ferocity of the Saiyans!
Kami-sama and Piccolo Both Die."
Father, you're incredible!
"Next time"
"Ferocity of the Saiyans!
Kami-sama and Piccolo Both Die"