The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Gohan-san, I'm impressed. You really came, huh?
I mean, it's not as though... ummm...
Huh? A m-movie?
I'm so happy!
Okay, let's go, let's go!
U-Uh... er...
Gohan-san!
The Great Saiyaman appears!
All right...
The Great Saiyaman, a justice-loving new hero...
His activities have become the
subject of rumors in Satan City.
And, taking an interest in the
true identity of Great Saiyaman,
was Son Gohan's classmate and
Mister Satan's daughter, Videl.
"Gohan, Scramble! Save Videl!!"
I'm off!
Big Brother!
Big Brother, come back soon!
Goten, you've gotten
good at riding Kinto Un, huh?
Big Brother, you're looking cool, too.
Okay then, off I go!
Bye-bye.
This is a big help.
Thanks to this transformation device,
I don't have to worry about being late.
Isn't that...?
Great Saiyaman...?
It's Videl-san. I can't go to school like this.
I've got no other choice...
You think you're getting away?
What do you think you're doing, Videl-san?
Chasing after me like I'm some villain...!
Today's the day when I find out who you are!
Aw... I've gotten pretty far away
from school while she was chasing me.
If I don't hurry, I'm going to be late.
Morning.
Good morning, Videl-san!
Way to figure out where I am.
With that garish outfit of yours,
I could tell right away.
Say, just who exactly are you?
W-Well... like I said before...
I am he who does not abide evil,
the champion of justice,
Great Saiyaman!
Stop yanking me around.
N-No, I'm not yanking anything...
You may look nerdy, but you can fly,
and your strength is something else.
It's hard to believe that
you're just a regular person.
If we're going to live
normally among regular people,
it won't help if they find out how strong we are.
So it's a secret, no matter what?
Yes, no matter what.
Saying so makes me want to
know who you are that much more.
Hold on a second, you!
I'm sorry about this.
What are you doing?!
What do you mean by this?!
Forgive me, but I'll just leave this here.
Okay then, see you later–er, I mean, farewell!
I'm going to find out who you are for sure!
Sensei, I'm sorry I'm late.
Oh, Videl-kun, that's okay.
Your position is a very busy one, after all.
Now then, hurry up and take your seat.
Right.
Was there some kind of
incident this early in the morning?
Mm-hmm, I guess you'd say.
Well, you can't help it, Videl,
but it's unusual for Gohan
to be tardy as well, huh?
Huh? Gohan-kun, too?
He just barely got here.
Ah, yeah, I just overslept a little bit.
Come to think of it,
it seemed like the Great Saiyaman
was heading toward the school...
Uncanny...
Today, thanks to the
actions of the Great Saiyaman,
precious lives were saved.
Indeed, Great Saiyaman is
the new hero of Satan City.
Hmph. How is he a champion of justice?
Compared to me, Satan-sama,
he's still on a small scale.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you know?
Come on, come on, what's the problem?!
Chief, the cops in Satan City are nothing special.
Yeah. If the boss was to come here,
there's nothing they could do about it.
How about we inform the boss right away?
Hey, misters, you can't go
around driving recklessly!
Who are you?
Chief, it's a high-schooler.
You're pretty sassy for a kid.
You mess with the Red Shark Gang, who
are bad enough to silence crying children,
and you're gonna pay for it!
Gohan-kun!
You shouldn't use force.
Shut up!
I guess I've got no choice now...
Videl-san...!
Now you've done it!
Chief!
Th-That's...!
Dammit! We won't forget this!
Gohan-kun!
Are you okay?
Stupid jerk!
Yeah, nothing wrong with me.
But it looked like you took
that incredible punch square-on...
Oh, that? Apparently, the guy
didn't have all that much power.
I'm sorry. I just looked on, thinking
that if you were the Great Saiyaman,
you should be able to take
care of them easily, Gohan-kun.
Huh? Me?
It was my misunderstanding.
If I had been a little later,
you could have been terribly hurt.
But I'm really glad that you weren't injured.
S-Sure!
That was close, that was close!
I came this close to
revealing myself to Videl-san!
Chief, that girl is Mister Satan's daughter.
The stories about her being
pretty strong are true, huh?
It's true, that girl's kick did hurt,
but as for my hand, which hit that kid–
cripes, it feels like I cracked my bones!
Damn, that bastard had one hard mug!
And so then, we went to the
same store we always go to,
and when we got there, those boys–
Yes, this is Videl.
Bad news! A band calling
themselves the Shark Gang
has taken the mayor of Satan City hostage!
You guys bring Mister Satan here, fast!
Otherwise, the mayor is dead!
W-What on earth do you
guys want with Mister Satan?
Our boss is here to challenge him to a duel.
What? A duel?
Mister Satan, I don't care if you
are a hero who saved the Earth,
you can't go swaggering around forever.
I, Rock-sama, am going to kill you!
And then, Boss,
this city will belong to us,
the Red Shark Gang, right?
I think I'll change its name to Rock City, too.
What do you think, Mayor?
Unless you want to watch your mayor get killed,
bring Satan here immediately!
Where is Mister Satan?
We've been trying to
contact him for some time now,
but he appears to be out,
and we can't reach him.
For crying out loud, you get famous,
and hotheaded guys like these show up.
I'd like to get out there
right now and knock them flat,
but they've got firearms.
It is my duty as a hero to
avoid this kind of danger.
I hate to say it, but all
I can do is wait this one out.
If you dawdle around, we'll kill you all, too!
Sensei, I'll be back in a jiffy.
Thank you for your efforts. Be careful, okay?
Sensei...
Yes?
E-Excuse me, but could I go to the restroom?
Again?
Son-kun, you've said that many times before,
and never come back, haven't you?
I don't care if your grades are
excellent, I will not allow it today.
Poor Gohan-kun.
He's here, is he?
You guys let the mayor go!
Boss, that's Mister Satan's daughter.
She looks pretty capable, huh?
But I have no business with his daughter.
I'm here to defeat Mister Satan.
Every once in a while,
there are guys like you that show up,
wanting to beat Papa and
make a name for themselves.
But Papa is busy, so in cases like this,
I'm the one who takes them on.
What?
It's true. Videl-san is so strong,
she rivals even Mister Satan.
Oh, so you're saying that if I defeat this girl,
it's as if I had defeated Mister Satan himself?
Very well! If you say so,
then that's another story.
Still, for being Mister Satan's daughter,
you're pretty cute, aren't you?
But I'm not going to hold back.
You appear to be a little stronger
than everyone else up to now.
I'm going to shred that cute little face of yours!
Her opponent's ki is incredible.
Videl-san is in danger!
But how do I get out of this classroom?
"...sister poet dear, brother poet, too...
"...wanna be with you,
'cause I need to spend my body.
"I'm a music makin' man, and
no peace can be released in life..."
What to do? Isn't there
some clever way out of this?
"...like this amplifier can.
"...your boy is doin' fine.
"And the energy you gave him
keeps me cryin' to the wind...
"...'cause I sing a natural
rhythm, play a magnetic chord...
"...the summer sun is high in the sky,
and love that's in everyone's eye..."
Ah! An earthquake!
Everyone, take shelter under your desks!
Now!
Transform!!
You're pretty good, aren't you?
Videl-san!
How cowardly of you!
Who are you?
My name is...
...he who does not abide evil...
...the champion of justice...
...they call me...
Great Saiyaman!
Videl-san, that's my line.
Hold on, you! This is my job,
so stay out of my way!
Nobody ever called you!
Y-You don't mean...?
W-What are they doing?
It's all right, just go someplace else!
Y-You sure are stern, Videl-san.
Shut up!
Hey, dispose of that weird bastard, too!
Why, you...!
Are you okay, Mayor?
Th-Thanks.
Die!
You wench!
Videl-san!
Maybe I was wrong to worry.
She's got extraordinary strength.
All right, come on, get in!
Okay then, Videl-san...
Wait!
Thanks.
N-Not at all.
Now I want to know your
true identity even more.
I'm sure to discover it before long.
Well, good luck.
Huh? Gohan-kun did?
Right after you left, there
was that earthquake commotion,
and during that, he disappeared.
He came back just a little before you did, Videl.
I knew it! Gohan-kun!
Huh?
He was right behind us a second ago...
Good grief, he's a master of escape!
Today, because of the Great Saiyaman's
actions, evil has been defeated.
However, Gohan is thinking that no
matter how invincible a hero may be,
there are still opponents
who are hard to deal with.
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
There are some awful folks out
there–kidnapping baby monsters,
and putting them on display like that, huh?
You, a Champion of Justice,
are planning to steal that monster?
Great Saiyaman, I won't
allow you to get away with that!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"A Case of Robbery!!
The Culprit is Saiyaman!?"
Videl-san, this is no
time for us to be fighting.
"Next time"
"A Case of Robbery!!
The Culprit is Saiyaman!?"