Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Dende, who Goku brought
from the planet of New Namek,
has become the Earth's new Kami-sama.
The Dragon Balls were restored.
All right. Well, I'll go and gather them up.
That's two that I've found...
This is boring.
Perhaps when I said
ten days, that was too long.
The opening of the tournament of
terror, the Cell Games, is coming soon.
"A Hard Problem for Goku!?
Take Back the Dragon Balls."
Gohan, are you studying there?
Yeah. It's what Mother tells me to do.
No matter where you are,
if you have any free time,
do as many drills as you can, she says.
Yeah? That's pretty commendable.
Actually, I brought some drills myself.
I'm going to do mine, too!
Huh? You've got drills and
stuff on Planet Namek, too?
Of course we do!
You have to study if you want
to be an outstanding Dragon-type.
It's all in Namekian, so
I can't understand a thing.
Aw, this is awful.
With you two suddenly
starting to study like this,
it makes me look like a slacker, you know?
I think I'll go to the Kame House.
Short time left before Cell Games.
Has Goku gathered Dragon Balls?
People of the world!
The combat sports champion,
Mister Satan's demonstration is about to begin!
Satan!
Satan! Satan! Satan! Satan!
And now, our hero, Satan,
is about to enter the stadium!
Oh! Satan is pulling along
four buses all by himself!
What monstrous strength!
Not that man again...
Hm? Mister Satan has produced something.
What could he be planning to do now?
Oh, my! They're phone books!
What's more, he has three volumes!
What could he be doing
with those phone books?
D-Don't tell me...
Don't tell me he intends to tear them apart!
He did it! He's done it!
Er, Mister Satan,
would you tell us what your
plans are for the Cell Games?
Miserable Cell, you're going to regret this!
You will share the same fate as this bus!
Oh, as we might have expected of Mister Satan!
Satan is indeed our one star of hope!
He will definitely give Cell
an out-and-out thrashing!
I-I can't pull my hand out...
Satan! Satan! Satan! Satan!
I can't watch.
There sure are some
incredible people in this world, huh?
That's four that I've found!
D-Dad, how did it go?
Huh? Two of the Dragon Balls
are together, and they're moving.
Who's there?
It's me.
Oh, Tao Pai Pai-sensei.
I've been waiting for you.
Sensei, have you brought
the goods you promised me?
Right here.
So there are Dragon Balls, which are
said to be able to grant any wish, huh?
It was hard work.
I will let you have them for
one hundred million Zeni each.
As long as I have these,
it means that I, Vodka-sama,
the emperor of gangsters, will survive,
even if that monster
Cell does destroy the Earth!
That is correct.
I see. After Cell is gone, I will
place my wish with the Dragon Balls,
and create a gangster empire!
In every age, it is the people who have
the money and the power that prosper!
So... when will you bring me
the remaining Dragon Balls?
Don't be so hasty, I will bring
them here right away, you'll see.
Is that right?
I'm counting on you, Sensei.
And here I just happened
to find those by accident...
It looks like they're around here.
Who's this guy?
A D-Dragon Ball!
What?!
They're inside here, all right.
It seems we have a pigeon
who has come right to us.
Pigeon?
Where? Where?
Let's pluck him right away.
Ahh, right you are!
Pigeon...?
Huh?
I'm letting myself in!
Now that he's inside my mansion,
I can dish it out any way I want to!
We got him!
Banzai! Banzai! Banzai!
Huh? I broke it!
I wonder if I've done something wrong.
W-What's the meaning of this?
Have you been performing periodic inspections?
Well, how about it?!
N-No!
You stupid bastards!
You've got to perform those inspections,
or they won't be of any use
when the time comes, you know!
W-We're sorry!
All right. We'll bring him
into this room, surprise him,
and get his Dragon Ball away from him!
Hm? I'm getting closer.
How nice of you to come in.
Now that you're in this room–
Hey! Over here!
Huh?
Over here, over here.
The Dragon Balls!
How nice of you to come in.
Now that you're in this room–
you'd better leave your Dragon
Ball and get out of here right now,
unless you want to get hurt!
If it ain't Tao Pai Pai!
What?
It's me! It's Son Goku!
Son Goku...?
You may have been a bad guy,
but this sure does take me back!
Aw, crap...
Where have you hidden it, eh? This pigeon...
You've brought one, haven't you?
Pigeon?
–Pigeon?
Don't play stupid!
The one we're going to pluck!
I don't know who you mean.
I-In any case, hand over that Dragon Ball!
What are you doing?!
Dammit...!
Why, you ruffian!
Whoops, I inadvertently
put too much power in that.
Shoot him!!
H-He's a monster!
Sorry, sorry, are you okay?
B-Boss!
D-Don't panic, you idiot!
I thought that something
like this might happen,
and I've taken every defensive measure!
B-B-Boss!
Hurry! Hurry!
Oh, you sure did it, huh?
I'm sorry, Boss!
Do you know what this is?!
This, see...
...is a barrier!
No matter how strong you may be,
I doubt you can break through this barrier!
I win!
S-Sensei! This is where we
must call upon your strength!
N-No... I'm not feeling... so good... today...
This is a fix, huh?
I absolutely need to have these Dragon Balls,
but it looks like you guys are
working hard to gather them, too.
And there's nothing we
can exchange in their place.
I know, Goku-kun! How about we do this?
If you can solve all three of these
puzzle rings by daybreak tomorrow,
we will give you these Dragon Balls.
If you cannot solve them,
we will take all of the
Dragon Balls that you have.
Puzzle rings, huh?
Oh! That's our Tao Pai Pai-sensei!
To think that you would be
hiding puzzle rings in there!
I suppose so.
You never know when and where
something might happen, after all.
Gotcha! I ain't ever done this,
but all I have to do is
solve them by morning, right?
It's decided, then.
Henchman A-kun, provide
a chair for Goku-kun here.
R-Right...
Here, take off your coat and relax.
All right...
Having us here watching
you must be distracting.
We will retire within.
Hm? Yeah...
We'll leave this man here.
If you need anything at all,
please let him know.
Very well, then...
Hold on...!
This sure is pretty difficult...
We should get as far away as we can, now.
Impressive indeed, Tao Pai Pai-sensei.
I've done it!
Two more to go, huh?
This is difficult...
You should pull that thing through there.
Don't talk, okay? I'll be the
one who solves this. Geez...
O-Okay...
One more to go...
I did it...
I'm done!!
Congratulations!
Having come this far,
it's unlikely that Son Goku
will come chasing after us.
This is all thanks to you, Sensei.
Huh?
Where do you suppose Boss
and the others could have gone?
Hey, no worries.
S-Son Goku!
Look! I solved them.
I-Indeed you have...
Well, I'll be taking the
Dragon Balls with me now, okay?
S-Sure. Be my guest.
Thank you.
Finished at last.
I've got all seven together now!
And thus, the ten days
passed in the blink of an eye,
and the Earth greeted
the fated day of M the 17th.
Only one hour is left until the Cell Games.
We are ready to die if necessary
in order to bring you this exclusive,
live broadcast account of the battle with Cell.
Cell does not move.
He has not budged an inch.
Will the monster Cell be
the one who wins the Cell Games?
Will it be the composed Goku?
Or will it be...?
The final battle is in one hour.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
At last, it's the start of the Cell Games.
I'm going to be the first one to go at him.
Don't go making your own order,
and leave out the world champion,
Mister Satan, you bunch of amateurs!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Those Who Would Challenge Cell!!
The Curtain Rises on the Battle."
Huh? Is that Satan man
actually serious about fighting Cell?
"Next time"
"Those Who Would Challenge Cell!!
The Curtain Rises on the Battle"