Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
In order to return Chichi and the others
who had become demonic back to normal,
Gohan and Kuririn headed off to
the Temple of the Heavenly Realm.
However, there was already
someone there waiting to face them.
Piccolo-san!
We meet again, kid.
You're faster than we thought,
I'll give you credit for that.
Dammit.
They got Piccolo-san too.
"Direct Confrontation with Piccolo!!
An Angry Masenko in the Heavenly Realm."
Even your beloved Piccolo-san here...
...has become Garlic Jr.-sama's
obedient servant.
He has become one of us Demon Clansmen!
Just like your mother has.
Son of Son Goku...
...or, as I recall, you have the name Gohan...
...I have a question for you.
It's a simple question. You'll answer me, yes?
Where is your father?
Father?
That's right! Son Goku, the
man foolish enough to oppose me!
You and your father caused
me to suffer a severe disgrace.
I intend to take that humiliation
and return it to you many times over.
What?!
The world is already in the palm of my hand.
However, without taking revenge against you,
I cannot declare my victory complete.
So, tell me, where is Son Goku?
Where is he hiding himself?
Why hasn't he shown himself?
Father is neither running nor hiding!
He just doesn't know
you bad guys are around!
He doesn't know? How do you mean?
I'm going to...
I'm going to take care of you!
If you don't want to talk, that's fine too.
As long as you're around,
Son Goku will show himself eventually.
You... miserable... brat!
You brat! Your power is not greater than mine!
What was that power just now?
Father!
You won't get away with this!
I will not let you get away with this!
If you can shoot him, then go ahead!
If Kami here dies, Piccolo dies too.
So long as you don't mind.
Kami-sama...
Gohan!
Whoa, there!
I will be your opponent!
Garlic Jr.-sama, can I ask that
you leave these two up to us?
Wait just a moment.
Very well. Until Son Goku arrives,
you may thoroughly amuse yourselves.
However...
I strike the finishing blow.
Hurt them, but do not kill them!
You hear that?
He's given us his permission! Get ready, kid!
Hey! Save some of that for us, too!
Don't get reckless and kill them, now!
Yeah, I'll try to be as careful as I can.
Well, kid, bring it on!
As for you, the previous Kami-sama,
feel free to observe this as well.
What's the matter, kid?
If you aren't going to start this, then I will!
Gohan!
Whoa, I told you that
I was going to fight you!
What's wrong with you?
Is this all the power you have?
Come now, you're
supposed to be Son Goku's son.
Don't you die from just that!
Gohan...
Gohan!
Hey, what's the matter, let's get going!
I see, you've already had it.
In that case, I'll just finish you off!
Gohan!
Kuririn-san!
You fool!
A-one, two, three, four,
and one, two, three, four,
A little more, one, two,
one, two, and three, four...
This side, the other side, a-one, two...
How lucky you had these
clothes in a place such as this!
One, two, ah, they're so nice!
A-three, four, a-one, two...
I hope you like them.
If you need anything else, just tell me.
I am a great, great sage after all.
I sure will!
Say, Yajirobe, this young miss...
...doesn't seem to be paying me
quite enough respect, does she?
Quite enough? She ain't payin' none at all.
Um, Yajirobe and Kitty-chan...
Excuse me, I do have the name Karin-sama.
It doesn't matter what your name is.
I'm so hungry! Make me something.
Huh? Us?!
That's right. Hurry, okay?
Sure, but, when it comes to
cookin', we, uh, that is... right?
Pretty please?
'Kay!
Right away!
Hey, Yajirobe, can't we do
something about that little lady?
You're jus' too indulgent with her, Karin-sama.
Can'tcha be more tough with her?!
But I'm a kind and gentle sage.
I couldn't do that, could I?
Kind an' gentle sage, huh? Yeah, right.
Without your help, she'll
never come to respect me.
'Kay then, I'll do everythin' I can.
Excuse me, Kitty-chan?!
Yes?!
Ain't no way he can get
her to respect him like that.
Kuririn-san! Kuririn-san!
This is from me having
slacked off in my training lately...
I couldn't move around the way I wanted to...
Kuririn-san!
Gohan, never mind about me...
You've got to get your hands on that
Ultra Holy Water by tomorrow morning...
Otherwise Piccolo, your mom, and
everyone else can't be returned to normal!
What is it? What am I lacking
to become a Super Saiyan?
Why was Kakarrot able to become one?
Why? That oversoft scum!
Why?!
T-This ki...
A Super Saiyan ki...
Kakarrot?
It is! I've found you at last, Kakarrot!
There! On top of that rock. He's there all right!
What?!
Is this all?
What, was it an illusion?
No. That was no illusion.
This land used to be flat, but he blew
this away with his ki, leaving this mountain.
The only one who could have done
this was you, Kakarrot, as a Super Saiyan!
Good. Apparently you've
raised your skill level again.
Well I'll raise mine even higher!
You just wait, Kakarrot!
Why, that kid! He's got
even more power than before!
He's got such power!
It's no use. Let's get to it.
But Garlic Jr.-sama's orders were to not–
It's nothing to worry about.
Either way, he's just as dead.
I guess you're right.
W-Why those two–
It's all right! Let them go.
Die!
G-Gohan!
Gohan...
Masenko!
Rotten brat!
Miserable fool!
You lousy punk!
Don't get too full of yourself!
Piccolo-san!
Most interesting. Piccolo, squash him!
Pic... colo-san...
Gohan is in an utter pinch!
At last, there is a direct confrontation
with the demonified Piccolo.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
If we don't get Kami-sama back from Garlic Jr.,
Gohan and the others ain't
gonna be able to fight all-out.
At this rate, everyone on Earth
is gonna be turned demonic!
Kami, behold as Piccolo
himself lays into your follower!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Retrieve Everyone's Minds!!
The Ultra Holy Water Resting in the Temple."
Even Kuririn has turned demonic!
"Next time"
"Retrieve Everyone's Minds!!
The Ultra Holy Water Resting in the Temple"