The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Look, don't get so depressed.
I'm surprised at this myself.
To think that I would be able
to make this big a fool out of you!
Y-You piece of crap! In that case...
Now, go, my ghosts!
Super Ghost Kamikaze Attack!!
That's what you get for looking
down on them as child's techniques,
you wretched fool!
You're the one who's the fool.
You should have realized it sooner!
Goku and Vegeta have merged,
giving rise to the ultimate warrior Vegetto.
With his ultra power, Vegetto
has beaten Majin Boo soundly,
until finally he had him cornered.
What are you going to do?
Do you plan on continuing still?
All right!
Hey, do you like coffee candy?
"A Hero Lost!? Vegetto is Absorbed."
I-It can't be...!
J-J-Just a minute now, Kaio-sama!
You wouldn't possibly
tell us to go after him, right?
I doubt there's any choice.
You guys are the only ones
now that can fight against Boo.
That was the reason I had Yama-sama
leave you your bodies in the first place.
Even if that's so,
there's a whole different dimension
of strength between us and Majin Boo.
And Kaio-sama, you don't seriously
think that we could possibly win, do you?
W-Well, as far as that goes...
I, for one, refuse. I am not about to
be eaten by Majin Boo again. No way!!
Hey, how's it going? Things should just
about be settled by now, shouldn't they?
I feel so refreshed!
Yamucha! Where have you
been during this emergency?
Emergency? I'd exercised, so I went
to use the showers. So refreshing!
Even so, this is quite a dull place, huh?
There's no one but tough guys here.
I wonder if there are any
cute, bubbly girls around.
That does it. Maybe leaving
them with their bodies was a mistake.
I did it! I finally did it!
How pathetic, becoming a hard candy!
You truly are helpless now!
Well, don't get too discouraged!
I'll be eating you soon enough!
Little by little, little by little,
I'll slowly dissolve you in my mouth,
and once you've gotten small enough,
I'll crunch down and chew you up!
My fault, my fault!
Still, too bad for you, Majin Boo.
What?
This is impossible!
My appearance may have been altered,
but apparently my strength hasn't changed.
How about that? My speed is the same too.
But without arms and legs,
it's hard to stay in form.
Okay, now what are you going to do?
Your opponent is the strongest
hard candy in the universe!
Don't be absurd!
Even if you can move, you're
still nothing more than hard candy!
And as a hard candy, what can you do?!
Are you sure you want
to ask something like that?
Besides, are you sure it's not too dangerous?
Being this small, it'll be
hard for you to attack me.
Attack you? Where is the
necessity in me doing that?
I'll just catch you and drop you
into my mouth! That's all there is to it!
Is that so? Well then, by all means, here I go!
Didn't I tell you so?
My strength hasn't changed!
I'm taking a breather.
What's wrong? Weren't you
going to catch me and eat me?
If you won't come at me, then I'll go at you!
Now I'll eat you!
Damn you, whizzing around like that!
My, my, that was inexcusable.
You wanted to eat me so badly,
I decided I would let myself be eaten,
but instead I went right through you.
What will you do now?
Shall we do this some more?
Return!
Huh?
That's all for the hard candy, huh?
You did what you could, but in the end, it
looks like it was impossible for you to eat me.
Thank goodness! I thought that
was going to take years off my life!
You moron!
So long as he hasn't defeated Majin Boo,
there won't be any exceptions to the
lifespan of every living thing in the universe!
Th-That's right...
How inexcusable of me!
E-Enough! We all know
quite well that you are strong!
So please, please, hurry and end this!
For a time there, I was
wondering what would happen.
That's fine to say, now
that he's returned to normal.
What were you planning to
do if he were still a hard candy?
Well, it could be that he took into
account that this might have happened.
After all, half of him is
that fighting prodigy Vegeta.
Still, you're lucky that
Vegeta, with his high pride,
would do as you say, and
decide to fight Majin Boo, huh?
Well, yeah! It goes without saying,
that's one of the virtues I possess.
W-Who do you think I am? I am Great
King Yama, you know! Great King Yama!
Hey, Yama! What the hell is the meaning of this?
Oh, you're here?
I asked you what the meaning of this was!
Don't shout like that. As you can see,
I have returned your spirit to your body.
Of course, it is forbidden for me to do
such a thing to someone such as yourself,
who has piled up so many crimes,
but in an emergency situation
such as this, I have little choice.
What are you planning?
Wouldn't you like to fight
Majin Boo one more time, Vegeta?
What?
As you know, Majin Boo,
whom you tried to defeat in
exchange for your own life, is still alive.
If you were to die as such,
it will be no more than a dog's death.
For a warrior as high in pride as
yourself, you couldn't bear dying so.
That's why I'm telling you
that I'll give you another chance.
How about that? Won't you try?
In order to defeat you, I'm going to
make sure you can't restore yourself,
by blowing you to tiny bits!!
You said mine was a dog's death, didn't you?!
H-Hey! What are you...?
Hey, Vegeta...
Very well! I'll do it!
This time for sure, I'm going
to kill that tubby bastard!
Provoking him awkwardly
like that was a mistake.
I wonder if Kaio-sama will
put up the repair costs for me.
See here, what's wrong?
Don't tell me you're thinking of ending
this before I've even gotten serious!
You're the strongest in
the universe, aren't you?
Goku-san!
Th-That didn't hurt!
That doesn't appear to be the case.
What?
Even for you, you've taken too much damage,
and it seems your
regeneration can't keep up, huh?
Now then, I've grown tired of messing
around with you, and it's about time I end this.
W-What did you say?!
You're going to finish me–?
Shut up and listen to me.
You can't be so stupid as to not
realize the difference in our two powers
after I've made this big a fool of you.
I know!
Ten! I will wait until I've counted
to ten before I eliminate you.
You should pray good and hard, or whatever.
Well, I'm starting to count!
One...! Two...!
Three...! If you want to rush
your death, you can come at me!
I'll wipe you out in an instant! Without a trace!
Four...! Five...!
Six...!
Damn. How could my techniques
be all but useless against him?
At this point, the only thing
I can do is absorb him. But how...?
Is that...?
That's it! That's what he broke off earlier!
Seven...!
Eight...!
So he's finally noticed it?
This was the whole reason
I cut off that tail-like thing
growing out of his head, after all.
All right! He's letting his guard down...
Nine...!
Now then, just how well is this going to work?
Ten...!
Barrier!!
I did it!
No way...
I-It can't be... Goku-san! Vegeta-san!
How can this be?! He's been absorbed!
Now everything is finished!
I did it! Serves you right, you
stupid bastard! That's for acting so big!
But now, it's all over! You rotten piece of crap!
At length, even Vegetto has
been absorbed by Majin Boo.
There are no other
warriors that can defeat him.
What in the world will become of
Earth, and the rest of the universe?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Huh? What's going on?
Once we made our way inside
Boo, our merging came undone.
It doesn't make any difference!
We have to hurry up and find
the others that Boo absorbed!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"A Demonic Maze!!
What Is There Inside Boo's Belly!?"
I wonder how the insides
of Boo's body are set up.
"Next time"
"A Demonic Maze!!
What Is There Inside Boo's Belly!?"