Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
I will now show you the true power of the Saiyans.
Indeed, you certainly do have marvelous power.
You have well surpassed me.
However, you cannot beat me like this.
Absolutely not!
Speak hollow boasts to me, will you?
We'll see about that.
"Super Trunks Has a Weakness!!
Cell's Shocking Bombshell Declaration."
Dammit!
Going even higher, are you?
It's no use. You cannot beat me.
H-Hey, are you okay, Vegeta?
I have to hurry and give him his senzu.
Over there is good.
H-Hey, Vegeta!
Here's a senzu. Swallow this for me.
Vegeta! Have you come around?
Miserable Cell...!
E-Extraordinary power!
He's completely surpassed Cell! U-Unbelievable!
S-Say there, who has?
You guys! Don't talk so muddled,
explain things so I can understand more easily!
Trunks, of course!
Trunks has? Hooray! You're sure strong, huh?
Anger! Anger makes me a Super Saiyan!
When did he get that strong?
This ought to be fun.
Something really incredible might come of it!
Father has been just sitting
there every day lately like that.
I'm sure it must be pretty hard to go
beyond even Super Saiyan, after all.
All right, then...
T-That's an incredible ki!
Father! That's incredible!
You've gone beyond, Father!
You've already gone beyond Super Saiyan!
There's still another stage
of transformation possible.
Y-You did it!
T-This is extraordinary power, Father!
You can't lose to anyone like this!
You can surely beat Cell!
Damn!
I-Impossible! This is impossible!
Why can't I hit him?
I'm disappointed at you, too.
You are no test to the
strength of my perfect form like this.
What?!
D-Dammit!
It's the same, no matter
how many times you do it.
You cannot possibly win against me.
Why?! Why, when I'm supposed
to be powered up this much?
Father, you can surely win! For sure!
I can't beat Cell like this... most likely.
H-How come?
My form is awesome. So is my power.
But with my muscles bulging out this much,
even though my power has gotten
huge, my speed has been sacrificed.
Great power ain't good for nothing
if you can't hit your opponent, right?
I couldn't beat that monstrous Cell like this.
Besides that, my energy
consumption was too severe.
As far as balance goes,
the regular Saiyan size is best.
That much I know for sure.
Gohan...!
Yes?
From now on, except when you're asleep,
stay in your Super Saiyan
form as much as you can.
Come to think of it as your natural state.
We'd better start by eliminating that feeling...
...where we have no composure
when we become Super Saiyan.
After that, we start our basic training over.
It may seem like a roundabout
way, but I think it's best.
Right!
All right, I'll do it, Father!
You're such a greenhorn.
For you to say you're
going to show your true power,
and then undergo a transformation
that relies on even more power!
That transformation is a simple matter.
However, the transformation
to achieve this sort of power...
...does not give rise to anything!
Nothing at all!
Anyone would know something like that.
Even your father, Vegeta.
You are a fool.
I-Is that right?
Dad was able to make this transformation.
He didn't do it anyway.
He knew this is what would happen.
What a fool I've been!
Any chance I had of winning
is completely gone. Kill me.
That I will do.
T-Trunks' ki has gotten extremely small!
W-What's wrong?! What's the matter?!
C-Cell's ki is still enormous...
Has Trunks been beaten?!
He said he could win, though...
Dammit, that miserable Cell!
Hey, what are you planning to do?
There's only one thing to do–kill Cell!
Y-You...
Shut up!
Good grief, those Saiyans are
one outrageous warrior race.
You just can't keep up with them.
S-Say, there, has Trunks won yet, I wonder?
He's incredible!
Is he all that incredible–Trunks?
No, it's Cell in his perfect form that's incredible.
Trunks is going to be killed!
You've got to be joking!
Look, isn't there anything
you can do? Do something!
I have been considerably disappointed,
both by you and your father Vegeta.
I was expecting this to be more enjoyable.
I have one final question.
Never mind that you were decisively beaten by me,
you and Vegeta both upped your powers
dramatically in a short period of time.
Just what was it that you did?
You don't want to talk?
In that case, I'll alter the question for you.
If you had more time, is it possible
you could up yourselves even more?
How about it?
How should I know?
I couldn't tell unless I tried it.
But why would you ask such a thing?
So then, it's not impossible, huh?
Very well, next question.
What is Son Goku doing?
Why hasn't he shown up here?
Goku-san is in the middle
of training to defeat you!
Knowing Goku-san, he will
defeat you, and fulfill our wishes!
I'm convinced of that!
That is a good answer.
In that case, I will hold
a martial arts tournament.
Martial arts tournament?
What?! What was that?!
What is it? Don't tell me Trunks has been killed...!
N-No, Cell just said he would
hold a martial arts tournament!
A martial arts tournament?
I'll hold it in ten days, free of charge!
Get as strong as you can
and entertain me, if you would.
W-What the hell are you talking about?
You probably wouldn't know, but in the past,
there was a martial arts tournament,
called the Tenkaichi Tournament.
I'm saying I'm going to hold one again for you!
However, I alone will be your opponent.
The fights will be one-on-one.
If I win, then the next
person will fight me, once again.
Any number of you will be fine!
The more people you have there,
that's just how much the
greater your advantage will be.
Have as many people as
you can get to assemble there.
I'll let you know the location
and other details in a short while,
via a television broadcast or something.
What?!
It seems like a good way to kill some time.
So then, you'd better
prepare a good deal of senzu!
W-Wait, Cell!
What is the purpose of
this martial arts tournament?
And what is your ultimate goal?
I-I don't understand this at all!
Are you out to rule the Earth–no, the universe?
The purpose of the martial arts tournament...
...is to confirm the strength of my perfect form,
as well as to plunge
the whole world into terror.
Besides that, it will serve as an
exercise to further draw out my strength.
I don't particularly have any ultimate goal.
I have no interest in such
base things as conquest.
The original purpose for which
I was created–to kill Son Goku–
does not hold any great
meaning for me as of now.
If I had to say, enjoying
myself is my goal, I suppose.
My biggest aim, of course,
is to see the faces of humans, struck with terror!
Yes, yes! That's the sort of face.
Well, then...
What is this? Cell holding a Tenkaichi Tournament?
Just where do Cell's intentions lie?
And can Goku, now in the middle of his
training, obtain the power to defeat Cell?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
A Tenkaichi Tournament, huh?
Cell sure did come up with an interesting idea.
We'll have to do our best to train for it!
Hold on a minute! Muten Roshi-sama,
why are you getting worked up?
Don't tell me you're thinking of entering, too!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"A Final Battle Closes In on Goku!!
The Mystery of the New Tenkaichi Tournament."
I wonder what sort of battle awaits us.
"Next time"
"A Final Battle Closes In on Goku!!
The Mystery of the New Tenkaichi Tournament"