Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
He's been forming that up in the sky?!
Where did he find that
much remaining power?!
You were planning to
take me by surprise with that?
You're so pathetic!
Too bad!
Be gone!
Piccolo!
Goku, hurry up and complete
this "Genki Dama" of yours!
Are you still lurking about,
you miserable Namekian?!
"The Incredible Destructive Force of
the Genki Dama!! Who Will Survive!?"
All of you sneaking around
like this, you're like pestering flies!
Aren't you done yet, Son Goku?!
Haven't you completed the Genki Dama yet?!
That Freeza creep is
quite thoroughly pissed off!
I-It's no good! This is still
going to take some time!
Shoot it! Shoot it, already!
I-It's no use... Just a little longer...
For someone too stubborn to die...
Are you still hanging around here?
I'll show you the power of
someone too stubborn to die!
Piccolo-san...
Piccolo may be intent on dying.
He probably used up the greater part of
his power in that blindside attack earlier.
He's risking his own life to buy
time for Goku to finish the Genki Dama!
Piccolo-san!
Wait, Gohan!
Goku, please hurry!
That was useless.
Didn't you get it when
I told you it was useless?
Apparently, you wish to die early.
Goku! Hurry...
hurry and complete the Genki Dama!
Piccolo...
Tenshinhan...
These guys pushed Vegeta
around like he was a baby! Be careful!
Here goes!
Oh, look out!
Save me!
You guys,
Attack! Attack, I say!
That's easy for you to say!
They're even... stronger...
guys than... Vegeta was!
Dammit, I'll do it!
What?
You're weaker than we thought, aren't you?!
What?!
We can win this!
All right, me too!
I get it! It's not that they're
weak, it's that we're strong!
This is the result of our training!
The fruits of having received
Kaio-sama's judicious training!
They're better than I thought.
Hey, if we get serious, they'll be no problem!
Hey, ReaCoom, shake it off!
Nice! This is how it ought to be!
I am totally up for this!
ReaCoom Body Attack!!
All right...!
Hey!
Ginyu Special Corps' Red Magma, Jheese!
Ginyu Special Corps' Blue Hurricane, Butta!
Now!
Goku, isn't the Genki Dama ready yet?
Still longer, Goku?
I've just about reached my limit.
Just a little longer...
Just a little longer, and it will beat Freeza...
As you wish, I'll kill you first.
Those guys, they scraped that
together with what little ki they had left!
That there should still be some
flies there that had not run away...
You folks really are
good at annoying someone...
This is as far as it goes!
I'm going to trash you,
along with the whole planet!
Goku! Still not yet?!
Okay, it's finished!
Do it, Goku!
Father!
O-Oh, crap!
Get down!
I-I'll just take this and...
I'll take this and...
Oh, what's this?!
H-He did it! Goku beat
Freeza... He beat Freeza!!
Yeah, he really beat Freeza!
He did it! He did it!
–He beat him!
–Goku did it!
Has Freeza-sama lost?
I-Impossible!
It's a lie!
Goku has won!
He did it!
Kuririn-san!
Yo! You all right?
Y-Yes!
It's all completely changed.
Yeah.
Where's Father?
Where's Uncle Piccolo?
The super-giant Genki Dama finally detonates!
Has Freeza really been laid to rest?
And what of Goku? What of Piccolo?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
How dare you kill Kuririn! Freeza,
I will make sure you pay for that!
I may have taken some damage,
but that doesn't mean
I can't still put you guys away.
The little brat is next.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Transformed At Last!!
Son Goku, the Legendary Super Saiyan."
In Father's rage,
his hair is being colored
by the light he's giving off!
"Next time"
"Transformed At Last!!
Son Goku, the Legendary Super Saiyan"