Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
W-What in the world was that?!
Bulma-san, I'm taking the Dragon Ball with me.
Hurry! This way now!
Hey, what exactly is going on?!
Gohan-kun!
Hold on!
For crying out loud!
Really, what do they think they're–
W-Wasn't that Vegeta with them just now?
In the face of an enormous foe,
Kuririn and the others have temporarily
joined forces with Vegeta. However...
ReaCoom!
Butta!
Jheese!
Ghurd!
Ginyu!
To-geth-er we are...
The Ginyu Special Corps!
"Goku on Final Approach!
Smash Through Freeza's Dragnet."
Well done, everyone.
I have been expecting you.
Thank you very much, Freeza-sama.
Please tell us what our mission is this time.
The traitor Vegeta has taken the
Dragon Balls that I had gathered, and fled.
Vegeta...
Hey, that's that Saiyan, right?
I hear he's quite the arrogant bastard, for
someone who doesn't have that much power.
Vegeta has betrayed Freeza-sama...
However, for whatever reason, his battle
power is starting to rise higher and higher.
Although, he should still be no match for you.
Please rough him up so as not to
kill him, and bring him back here.
I would like to force him to tell me
where he has hidden the Dragon Balls.
That will be a simple task.
Our Scouters are already tracking Vegeta.
He appears to be traveling at
high speed not too far from here.
What is the matter?
Who might these other
two who are with him be?
They appear to have a fairly high battle power.
Two of them? Ah, those must be
the two children who interfered earlier.
So they have teamed up
with each other, have they?
What are we to do with them?
You are to kill them.
–Lucky!
–Hooray! Hooray!
Understood. Let us go
thoroughly enjoy ourselves.
At the heart of it all,
you are no more than just a Saiyan
monkey, kneeling under our rule.
Don't go thinking you're
on an equal level with us,
just because Freeza-sama
has taken a liking to you!
As perfect as Freeza-sama
might be in everything else,
there's still one thing that I can't comprehend.
And that's how someone as useless as you are
has been admitted into the Ginyu Special Corps.
What?! Try saying that again!
Don't breathe next to me.
It stinks so bad, I can't stand it.
I'll show you whether or not I'm useless!
This is no time to be playing around...
...Vegeta-san.
A very nice planet has been found.
It should sell at a high price.
Let us go see it–just the two of us.
As you wish.
Looks like you got away with
your life. You're a lucky one, at least.
That miserable Vegeta...
Oh my, what's the matter,
Ghurd? Do you have to go potty?
No, it's nothing.
Freeza-sama, the Scouters
you ordered are in this case.
Well done.
Well then, we will be off.
Special Corps!
Ginyu! Fight!
They've started moving.
T-They're fast! Hurry!
They're going to overtake us!
These strong guys are coming
at us, one after the next...
There's nothing we can do! Father!
20 minutes to arrival at Planet Namek.
All right...
Oh yeah...
Kaio-sama didn't have
to send me so many of them.
Someone even more
incredible than Vegeta, huh?
Stay alive, everyone.
Ten more minutes...
It's funny. I don't feel any fear.
What am I so relaxed for?
There's going to be someone
unbelievable out there...
...and yet, nothing.
Maybe training in all that
outrageous gravity has made me crazy.
Over there!
We've got them all!
Come on!
What's the matter?! Get over here, now!
Why, you!
Gohan, no matter how
I think this through, it's not right.
How can we let this guy have eternal life?
Don't give me that now!
Hurry up and turn over your Ball!
We don't have time to dawdle!
Yo, Veggie-chan.
It's been a long time, huh?
Dammit! And I was so close!
They're fast! They were so fast,
I didn't even know they were approaching!
By any chance, is that one
of those Dragon Ball things?
There are five of them lying over here.
This is all because you were so slow!
H-How can you say that?
Freeza-sama will be overjoyed by this.
You have to get all seven
Dragon Balls together, right?
There are five of them behind us,
and you've got two of them.
That's all of them, isn't it?
W-What Vegeta said was true.
I'm no match for them!
And that guy is exceptionally
amazing, even among these guys.
Y-You think we're going
to just hand them over to you?!
You seem to have it all wrong.
Without Freeza-sama's power,
you can't do anything!
Watch what you're saying!
What?!
Come on! Come on!
That guy... that guy alone
is really not all that tough.
W-Why is that guy mixed in with them?
Stay back! You smell so bad, I can't take it.
–Die!!
–Whoa!
Don't go acting on your own, Ghurd.
It's not like we've decided
that he's your prey yet.
Why don't you hand that
over right now, Vegeta?
Although, even if you do hand it over quietly,
we have no intention of
turning a blind eye to you.
You guys may be able to search
for people with your Scouters,
but I doubt you can search for these.
What of it?
This is what!
I'm back.
That's too bad. It looked like
you were trying to throw it far away.
Unfortunately for you, Butta's
speed is the fastest in the universe.
T-That's impossible!
Now then, the other one...
Destroy it!
Damn it all!
The Dragon Ball...
H-How?
So the rumors were true, were they?
What do you mean, rumors?
They say that Ghurd is
able to control and stop time,
momentary though it may be.
T-That can't be true...
It's true, all right.
Well then, that makes all of them.
Now, for your turn. We're going to
give you plenty of tender loving care.
And when he says tender loving care,
he doesn't mean patting your head,
and tossing you up in the air.
He means we're going to hurt you.
You don't have to explain that!
Vegeta, is fighting them
the only thing we can do?
You must have realized
running away would be futile.
Having you guys around is better than nothing.
Even knowing the extent of your power
you showed me on Earth will be
useless, I'll still be counting on it.
I'll take Vegeta.
You guys decide who gets the other two
unknown pipsqueaks by rock-paper-scissors.
–Why do you always do this?
–That's not fair!
–You can't do that, Commander Ginyu!
–Yeah!
You took the tastiest piece
last time, too, didn't you?!
You can't do that!
Let me have him! I owe him one!
I guess I've got no choice.
All right then, I'll take the
Dragon Balls to Freeza-sama.
You guys take care of the rest on your own.
Hooray!
I'm nice to you, aren't I?
Yeah, you're the best!
Well, first will be Vegeta,
second will be...
Those guys are a set.
All right, let's go!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Tie, go again!... Tie, go again!...
Couldn't we get away now?
Hooray! I get Vegeta!
D-Damn it!
Cheer up. It's better than
him not getting killed at all.
Understand, that's how it goes.
But I'll let you strike the finishing blow.
Now Freeza-sama will be
able to gain youth immortal.
I won't let you have them!
Stop! Don't waste your energy!
Right now, concentrate
only on defeating these guys,
instead of worrying about him, you idiot!
Hey, come here a minute.
Oh, oh, a strategy meeting, huh?
That Ghurd guy that you'll be
fighting has a low battle power,
but he uses supernatural abilities.
Don't let your guard down.
Yeah.
By the way, is Kakarrot
really not here on this planet?
No, he's not. But he is headed here.
Hurry and get here!
He may be an infuriating bastard,
but if we can get another ally, it will
add some to our potential for battle.
Why in the world did we even
come here to this faraway place?
Far from being able to get
the Dragon Balls together,
we're instead letting the bad
guys get eternal life! Darn it!
Huh? This is disappointing, huh?
Ghurd, you go first.
Tch... What am I, some kind
of battlefield garbage-collector?
What can I do? But ReaCoom,
make sure you really save some for me!
They're the same ludicrous bunch as ever!
Gohan, remember the image
training we did on the spaceship.
This looks like it's
going to be over in no time.
All right, let's go!
Release your ki!
What's this?
A full-power leadoff attack...
A fierce, all-out battle, the likes of which
had not been seen before, had begun at last.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
This is a surprise. Time-stopping
and paralyzing techniques?
Even Kuririn and Gohan
are at risk against those.
It's just not my lucky day,
having to go against these kids.
I have to beat them quick,
or ReaCoom will take Vegeta for himself!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Super-Magic or Just a Trick!?
Mr. Ghurd is Angry!"
Father! Hurry! Hurry!
"Next time"
"Super-Magic or Just a Trick!?
Mr. Ghurd is Angry!"