The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Having slipped inside Boo's body,
Goku and Vegeta have escaped
with Gohan, Piccolo, and the others.
However, Majin Boo then transformed into a
Boo with no self-control, the essence of evil!
It's hopeless! I can't do Instantaneous
Movement in such a brief amount of time!
It was at that time when Kaioshin
instantaneously moved from the Kaioshin
Realm and saved Goku and the others.
However, the Earth was in the end
destroyed, as were Piccolo, Goten, and Trunks.
"Boo's Assault!!
A Conclusion in the Kaioshin Realm."
Th-The Earth...!
It's been wiped out.
It's been blown to bits.
Then, what about Piccolo,
and Gohan and the others?
Unfortunately, they went
together with the Earth.
Th-The Earth has been wiped out?
What sort of nonsense are you talking about?
It's right here, isn't it? Right here!
You're just a geezer who says funny things.
H-How can you say that?! Be quiet!
Those gentlemen are Kaioshin-sama! Probably.
Kaioshin-sama? What's that?
In short... Now listen, above
Kami-sama, there are Kaio-sama,
and above that, there
is the Grand Kaio-sama.
Above even that, at the very top
stand those two, the Kaioshin-sama.
And this is not Earth, but probably
the holy land of the Kaioshin Realm!
You're taking this joke too far!
If those geezers are so awesome, then
why don't they do something about Boo?
W-Well, they...
He sure gets you where it hurts, huh?
And I thought it was suspicious
that someone like you would
be Kami-sama in the first place.
So that's it!
I finally figured it out!
It's a dream!
This is a dream!
That's it! A dream!
Ah, I get it! Here I thought
that things were weird!
After all, there's no way that anyone
stronger than I, the World Champion,
could exist in this world, is there?
There really is no Majin Boo,
and these guys are just
strange characters in my dream!
That would be consistent!
I thought that things starting
with the Tenkaichi Tournament
were weird right from the beginning!
U-Um...
That's right! If this is a dream,
I think I'll try to fly through the air, too!
U-Um...!
Listen well, Majin Boo!
This may be a dream, but how
dare you kill my cute daughter Videl,
and blow the Earth away!
I, Mister Satan, will fly
into space, and put you down!
I'm going to fly!
Th-That hurt!!
It hurt! It's a dream,
yet it still hurt! It hurt!
He's quite an amusing fellow, huh?
Kakarrot!
You let Piccolo and Gohan and the others,
who we worked so hard to rescue,
die instead of that big idiot!
There's no bringing them back!
Our last hope, the Dragon Balls,
were wiped out along with Earth, after all!
Look at this!
After being blown to pieces,
Majin Boo is returning to normal!
Dammit!
It's him, all right!
If any fragment of Majin Boo remains,
then no matter where he is, he will recover.
Where did he go?!
It looks like Boo instantaneously
moved to another planet.
This is terrible!
He immediately grasped onto Kibit's
instantaneous movement technique.
What the hell is he...?
He's searching for you guys.
He's seeking out any strong ki
he can find in the vastness of space.
And because of us, he deliberately
continues that meaningless destruction?
That's the kind of guy Boo is.
Again, many lives throughout
the entire universe are being lost.
And even if we are able to
defeat Boo, we can't return Earth,
or those other planets,
back the way they were.
Th-That's it!
There still are some Dragon Balls!
There are, aren't there? If we
go to my home planet of Namek,
I'm sure the new Elder-sama will
still have the Dragon Balls made!
They can be returned!
The Earth, and the other planets!
And all those many people
who were killed by Boo, too!
–Th-That's it!
–No, hold on!
Dende, Planet Namek is pretty far away, huh?
The ki from Planet Namek ain't all that large,
so it would be kind of impossible to get
there with my Instantaneous Movement.
There are no spaceships anymore, either...
I-I see...
–Damn!
–Uh...
I don't know the slightest about
what these Dragon Ball things are,
but I can instantaneously
move from this Kaioshin Realm
to all the planets in the lower realm!
You just saw it a moment ago, right?
This is Kibit's forte technique.
Great! That does it!
In that case, once we defeat
Boo, things will work out fine!
H-Hold on!
You must not use those Dragon Balls!
They invite confusion into the natural order!
They are only permitted to the
somber Namekians, and possess,
as it were, capability that runs afoul!
Long ago, they were advised to
only use them on Planet Namek!
In fact, the old Namekians would absolutely
not use them on matters of other planets!
Don't be so rigid, old timer!
You know what? If things go well,
I'll take some steamy,
dirty photos of a woman I know,
and give you the unedited prints!
D-Dirty photos?
There, see? You want them, right?
She's not all that young,
but she still has her bounce!
But this woman has been killed, right?
That's why we should bring her back to
life with the Dragon Balls, shouldn't we?
Hey, Kakarrot!
Yes?
This woman–don't tell me you're
talking about Bulma, are you?
S-So it is, huh?!
Why, you! Use other people's
wives as you like, will you?!
You can give him those of your
own wife–photos of Chichi's chi-chis!
N-No... she ain't got any more
bounce left, and I'd get killed!
J-Just a moment!
Boo is about to move again! He is
seeking out Goku-san and Vegeta-san's ki!
Bravo!
Yamucha! Let's go!
Come on, Kuririn!
It's...!
M-Majin Boo!
W-Who is he?
Has he come to train?
What's the matter, Kaio of the North?
It's Majin Boo!
So, he's finally come here, huh?
Boo has at length gotten
to the Grand Kaio's World.
If he's coming, let him come!
Hey, give your Potara
over to Goku and Vegeta.
If they unite once again, they
will beat that guy easily, right?
R-Right!
Here, Goku-san, Vegeta-san.
Please use these Potara and
defeat Majin Boo for sure this time!
No, we won't need these.
I'm giving it back.
After all, these, you see, just ain't suited for us.
I appreciate the offer,
but I want to fight by myself.
G-Goku-san!
I'm sorry, asking to be
selfish at a critical time like this,
but after all, he ain't merged any more either.
Y-You idiot! What are you
saying, at a time like this?!
Y-You guys aren't in a
sport–fighting match with Boo here!
Th-That's right, Goku-san!
Well said, Kakarrot!
I don't need this any more either!
That's the very essence of
the warrior Saiyan people!
C-Can you beat Boo like that?
He has gone back to the original,
most difficult, powerful Majin Boo!
It's okay. We'll manage
something! I'm sure of it!
That bastard! How could he?!
Damn it all! I wish he would
hurry and go somewhere else!
I'll be turned into chocolate again...
S-Stop! Stop!
What are you so worked up over?
New arrival, huh? If you've
come to train, I'll be your partner.
The training here is pretty tough!
If you're going to give up, now's the time.
You don't have a ring over your head.
If you get him angry, it will be terrible!
Why are you keeping quiet?
How about saying something?
It's too late!
Dammit! P-Pull a ridiculous
stunt like that, will you?!
All right! I'll pound into you
just how tough the training is!
Got him!
Who is that guy?!
W-What?! Has he not come here for training?!
Damn! Shall I test out the
results of my training here?
Kien-zan!!
I got him!
Kuririn! Hurry!
Get out of there!
Awesome!
–Kuririn, are you okay?
–Yeah...
He's not the kind of opponent
we can stand up to in the first place.
See here! What are you
planning to do? Stop that! Stop that!
Boo is planning to destroy
the Grand Kaio's world too!
Th-That's bad! Kuririn and
Yamucha have already died once!
If they die again, then this time,
they'll be completely eliminated!
All right! Instantaneous Movement!
Wait, Kakarrot!
Let's call him here!
It won't be so easy, in this holy Kaioshin
Realm, for everything to be destroyed!
We can fight as much as we want!
But how do we do that?
We're the ones he's after! We'll raise
our ki and let him know that we are here!
Th-That's it! All right!
No matter how much we do it, it's no use!
Damn! I'll turn into chocolate, or a
biscuit, or anything you want, just stop!
S-Stop!!
It's all over!
You've had it!
I-It vanished...!
Boo!
It hurts! It hurts!
At last, Majin Boo has come
to the holy Kaioshin Realm.
Having tossed the Potara aside,
will Goku and Vegeta be able to
defeat Boo without merging together?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Boo, we have to defeat you,
for the sake of the universe.
Vegeta, let's play Rock-Paper-Scissors
to decide who goes first.
You idiots! Can't you both fight together?!
This is Majin Boo you're fighting!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Seize the Future!!
A Decisive Battle with the Universe at Stake."
Father's full-power battle has begun!
"Next time"
"Seize the Future!!
A Decisive Battle with the Universe at Stake"