Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Proving Goku's full-power
Kamehame-Ha to be in vain,
Cell had been restored.
Their high-level battle continued on.
Your attack was good enough that it
caused me to have to raise a barrier.
I took on more damage than I expected.
I give up! I surrender!
W-W-What was that?!
In a shock to the entire
world, Son Goku has lost!
"He Who Takes Over as Strongest...
His Name is Gohan."
S-Surrender?
U-Unbelievable!
Surrender?
Son Goku, are you
thinking of ending this fight?!
That's right. I lose.
W-What did that young man say?
Over the long-range mike,
he clearly said he surrenders.
Well, he hung in there pretty well.
That's probably all that young man could do.
You're so right, Mister Satan!
After all, if it were anyone else but you...
Son Goku! Do you realize
what those words mean?
Yeah.
If there is no one left to
fight in these Cell Games,
then every last human on Earth
will be wiped out by my hand!
Cell, don't get me wrong.
It's not as though there
ain't anyone left to fight, right?
It's the same difference.
Vegeta, Piccolo and Trunks
all have to be inferior to you,
no matter how much
they've raised their powers.
They are no match for me.
So, Mister Satan, your
turn has come around again!
You've had plenty of time to rest, and all.
This time, please be sure
to take care of him for good!
Satan-sama, may you have a magnificent fight!
Yes indeed, Master!
R-Right! Why don't I go on
over and make him quake?
M-M-Mister Satan...?
Satan-sama, what's the matter?
Ee-yow-ow-ow-ow!
H-Here I want to go fight,
and there's no way I would lose to that guy...!
B-B-But with my stomach like this...!
Please do not worry, Satan-sama!
This is a fast-acting medicine for stomachaches!
Just swallow one capsule,
and your stomachache will recover on the spot!
You fool! I don't need that!
What a shame! If only I didn't
get these stomachache spells...!
And here I wanted to send that bastard flying...!
Well, would it be okay if
I called on the next person to fight?
You really intend to give up?
W-What does he think he's doing?!
There's no one else who can beat Cell here!
The Cell Games will probably
end after the next person fights.
If he loses, then there ain't
anyone else around who can beat you!
But I'm now absolutely
convinced that he will defeat you.
What?
That's why I've surrendered,
and left everything up to him.
Which means that he's stronger
than you are, not to mention myself?
Yep.
Ridiculous!
There is no one stronger
than me in the whole world.
Yes, there is.
Well then, let's hear the name of
this person who couldn't possibly exist!
He's about to say the name.
A-All right...
He's planning to say "Mister Satan."
H-Hey...
Go tell him for me that my
stomach hurts, and I cannot fight.
It's your turn, Gohan!
What?!
That idiot! Is he trying to get his
own son killed right before his eyes?!
G-Goku-sa! What are you thinkin'?!
Son-in-law!
G-Goku-sa is goin' to make Gohan-chan...
Gohan-chan face that terrible opponent!
–What is he thinkin'?! Gohan! Gohan! Gohan!
–Calm down, Chichi!
H-He said it was time for "gohan."
[gohan: a meal]
So that's it!
He's saying he's going to take a short break,
and have a bento lunch or something, huh?
They sure are happy-go-lucky at a time like this.
You can do it, Gohan.
M-Me, and Cell?
He's jerking me around!
Of all the people he could have
named, he went with Son Gohan?!
Don't be crazy, Son!
There's no way he can fight!
It's true, Gohan's strengths have risen
to the point where I hardly recognize him,
but he'd be facing Cell, an opponent
not even you could stand against!
Piccolo, Gohan has an unbelievable
power, even greater than you or I thought.
Think about it.
Ain't it true that from
the time he was a little kid,
he's been fighting just like the rest of us?
When I was a kid his age,
I wasn't anything special.
B-But still, even though
he may be a Super Saiyan,
this is a little sudden, right?
Inside the Room of Spirit and Time,
there was a dormant power,
sealed deep, deep down within
him, that started to be released.
How about it, Gohan?
After watching the fight
between your dad and Cell just now,
did you think it was too
incredible for you to keep up with?
N-No, I didn't think so.
But then, Father, neither you
nor Cell was fighting all-out, right?
I don't know about Cell,
but your dad was fighting all-out.
In other words,
to you, it felt like I must
have been holding back, right?
I-Is that true, Gohan?
Yes.
W-What?! That fight?!
Impossible! A kid like him...?!
What nonsense.
Okay, let him have it, Gohan.
Bring peace back to the world.
You wanted to be a scholar, right?
Understood! I'll give it a try!
Gohan...
Gohan-chan!
How absurd.
What in the world could be happening now?
They said it was time for "gohan,"
and yet another unnamed
boy has come forward!
I know! That boy sells bento lunches!
So that's it! Since it's time for "gohan,"
that's the reason a bento
salesboy has come forward.
He sells bento lunches!
A bento salesboy has emerged!
Oh? Now it's Chichi-san's kid.
They said he's got a job sellin' bento lunches.
And he was workin' so hard to be a scholar, too.
Now he's dyein' his hair color.
He's gone and become a delinquent.
Must be hard on poor Chichi-san,
havin' both her husband
and her son go bad like that.
Definitely.
G-Gohan?
Hmm, no matter what happens,
I doubt that Gohan can compete with Cell.
Kuririn, you've got the senzu beans, right?
Could you give me one?
Yeah.
Ah, thank you.
Cell!
That there's a senzu. Eat it.
Y-You idiot, Goku! What are you trying to do?!
It's all right, ain't it?
He has used up his strength.
It ain't fair to let Gohan beat him like this.
W-What are you talking about?!
Since when was there any of
this "fair" crap in this situation?!
You miserable fool!
You're trying to play it up too much.
You don't seem to understand that
such indulgence will cost you your life.
I will not hesitate to accept this senzu.
Son Goku! You will come to
utterly regret this very soon.
D-Damn...!
I see. Those are nice, aren't they?
W-Whatever happens now, it's not on me!
Son! No matter how you look at it,
what you just did was reckless!
W-What's the deal with that boy?!
It doesn't look like he's selling bento lunches!
Is that... Gohan's ki?
It just might be possible
that Gohan has surpassed Goku.
Gohan...!
Th-That's Gohan?! Our gentle little Gohan?!
Th-That kid...? How did he
get that much battle power...?!
It appears that Son Goku was
not entirely bluffing in what he said.
However, the part about
you being able to beat me
would appear to be an overstatement.
You impudent brat!
You really mean to go at it, do you?
But then, this might turn
out to be fortunate for you.
You'll be dead before you ever
experience true terror, after all.
Attaboy, Gohan!
G-Gohan...!
Gohan-san!
The boy, whom we thought
was selling bento lunches,
has suddenly begun to fight!
He appears to be hanging in there quite well.
However, he is up against Cell.
Will he be able to last
longer than one minute?
You're a nimble little runt.
Now then, let me increase
my speed like I really mean it!
Sure enough, this was reckless.
G-Goku...!
G-Gohan! Gohan-chan! Stop that! Stop that!
Goku-san!
Hey, Goku! Hey!
Gohan, having accepted
Goku's call, now faces the Cell Games.
Goku, are you saying that
Gohan can really beat Cell?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Get angry, Gohan! If we're going
to defeat Cell, all we can do now
is count on the power you
release when you're angry!
Look how wrong you were, Son Goku!
Thanks to your misdirected
thinking, your dear son will die!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Become Enraged Gohan –
Call Forth Your Dormant Power."
I really don't want to fight.
"Next time"
"Become Enraged Gohan–
Call Forth Your Dormant Power"