The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Several years had passed
since peace had come to Earth.
Gohan was coming to Satan City
in order to attend high school.
He was trying to draw as little
attention to himself as possible,
while still living the life
of a high-schooler. However...
Immediately, stories
about a golden-haired warrior
became the talk of the town.
G-Good day.
I'm Son. Son Gohan. Nice to meet you.
I'm Eraza. Nice to meet you.
This girl here is Videl. Videl's Papa, you see,
is Mister Satan, of all people!
Mister Satan?
This is suspicious, all right!
"For Love and Justice –
Enter the Great Saiyaman."
You want to undergo a complete transformation,
so that your identity is not revealed?
Yes. I thought that you would
surely have some good ideas, Bulma-san,
so I stopped by on the way home from school.
Are there any good ways of doing this?
Sure there are. I am a genius, after all.
Basically, I'd just need to convert
a transformation suit into particles,
like we do for capsules, so
that you can put it on at any time.
Really? By all means,
if I could ask you to do that...
It's just like you to not be able to keep quiet
and turn a blind eye to evil, Gohan-kun.
Sure, I'll make one for you.
Wait here for a couple of hours.
You can do it in two hours?
How kind of you. Thank you very much.
Okay, just wait around for a bit.
Um, where's Trunks-kun? It would
be boring to just sit here waiting.
Trunks is probably in the gravity room,
being put through the wringer by Vegeta.
By Vegeta-san?
He says he's just about the right
age to be starting full-fledged training,
so he's teaching him some fighting moves.
It appears that he wants to make Trunks-kun
even stronger than you, Gohan-kun.
That's frightening, isn't it?
Yo, Trunks!
Ah, Gohan-san! When did you get here?
I just barely arrived.
Say, I hear you're getting
training from your father.
Uh-huh!
Good afternoon, Vegeta-san.
Forgive the intrusion.
Yeah.
Gohan, you've gotten soft.
Never mind how peaceful
it has become, keep training!
Right.
Say, what should we do to play?
Gohan-kun, it's done!
I just need to press this red switch, right?
Right, right.
How nice! Mother, make one for me, too!
This looks pretty cool, doesn't it?
Doesn't it, though?
Good! This is extremely good!
I won't be needing one after all.
Okay, thank you very much!
Come again! Bye-bye!
Bye-bye!
Home, if you please, Kinto Un.
We're late, so go at full speed.
Now I can get by without
people suspecting it's me.
You know what? If I can fly to
school in my transformed outfit,
I can go anywhere faster,
without people knowing who it is.
If you think I'm kidding,
Kinto Un, let's have a race!
Here goes!
All right, start!
Come on, come on, Kinto Un! I'm speeding up!
Look how far ahead I am already!
No one will realize it's me.
Reckless driver spotted!
Come on, come on, come on,
come on! Move it, move it, move it!
Floor it! Floor it!
I'm already transformed, but anyway...
Transform!!
Y-You dirty scumbag! You wanna die?!
W-Why, you! Where did you come from?!
This reckless driving will not do!
You almost ran someone over.
Promise me that from now on,
you will drive safely through the city!
Do what? With that ridiculous outfit on,
what are you talking about,
you perverted bastard?!
Who do you think you are?
W-Who am I...? Yeah... Let's see...
What's with this guy?
He's a weirdo.
I know...!
I am... he who loves justice...
the Great Saiyaman!
Great... Saiyaman...?
You're who?! Not only is your
outfit corny, your name is corny, too!
Th-This guy really is a weirdo!
Let him have it! Let him have it!
Stop making fun of me!
I thought as hard as
I could thinking up that name!
I-I'm sorry. Now that I think
about it, that is a very nice name.
From now on, we will drive safely.
Goodbye, Great Saiyaman, was it?
Drive safely, drive safely.
Right, right.
You understand now, young people of the city?
What is that outfit, Gohan?!
Mother, don't you like it?
For cryin' out loud, how
old do you think you are?!
You're just like your father in that regard.
I'm home, Mother. Wow!
Big Brother, that looks cool!
You think so, Goten?
Okay, I'm leaving!
Big Brother, come home soon.
Gohan, don't rush. Watch out for airplanes.
Right.
That's neat, all right. Big Brother, you look cool!
Don't I? Before long, your
Big Brother will ask Bulma-san
to make one for you, too, Goten.
I'm off!
Goten, you can take care of Kinto Un!
Your brother sure seems happy.
He's transformed over and
over again since yesterday.
Big Brother, you look cool!
Gohan's younger brother, who
looks just like Goku, is named Goten.
He is Goku's second child, who was
left behind before the battle with Cell.
This is great! I should be able to get
there in about twenty minutes like this.
This is great.
Now I'll be able to sleep in a little longer.
...and, as a result, this new element
of energy is extremely complex...
Hey, did you know there was a new
champion of justice who appeared yesterday?
It wasn't the Golden Warrior, either.
Mm-hmm, I heard, I heard.
They're talking about me.
His outfit is awfully lame, but
he's supposed to be pretty strong.
I hear his name is "Great Tireman."
No, it's not! It's "Great Saiyaman"!
W-Why would you know something like that?
Well, I... heard it from
someone who saw him personally.
Would it be okay if I continued
with the lesson, Son Gohan-kun?
Yes!
Yes, this is Videl.
There has been a busjacking
at the eastern bus terminal!
A group of three robbers has taken over
a senior citizen group's sightseeing bus,
and are making ransom demands.
Request immediate–
Hurry up and bring us the ransom!
Otherwise, the old men
and women here are dead!
Request assistance!
Copy! I'll be there at once!
Sensei, I'll be back in a bit!
G-Good work.
What's going on with Videl-san?
Videl's pastime is being a champion of justice.
Champion of justice?
See? She sure does act like the daughter of
Mister Satan, the man who saved the world.
She's strong, so the police
often call on her and stuff.
She is...?
Don't sell Videl short.
Her strength is far higher than my own.
In fact, she has enough
power to rival even Mister Satan.
Strength to rival Mister Satan...?
She could be in trouble, if
she's the same as Mister Satan...
–Hey, you!
–Bathroom!
Transform!!
W-Where is this bus terminal?
Boss, we're done loading it on.
As you demanded, we
have handed over the ransom!
Now, release the hostages!
You fools!
Get us moving!
Don't shoot! You'll hit the hostages!
Yahoo!
We've finally gotten underway.
I wonder where they're going to take us.
Who knows? At any rate, the busjackers
do have a great deal of money, so...
Yeah, it could be a long trip, huh?
Gangster-san, let me
take a souvenir photograph.
Look over here.
Be quiet! You're a hostage!
Ready, "Cheese!"
Y-You dumb bastard, keep your eyes forward!
Dammit!
That's Videl-san's heli!
–Videl-san!
–Go get them!
Boss! Above us! Above us!
What?!
It's that champion of justice, Videl-san!
Grandma, take a picture! Take a picture!
There they are.
She's pretty good.
Damn!
Go get them, Videl-san!
Let them have it!
Videl-san's knockout blows landed!
One shot, for a souvenir?
The bus...!
It couldn't be...
That was so much fun.
It was a hell of a tour, huh?
Knock on wood, knock on wood.
Who are you?
I am... he who does not abide evil...
the champion of justice...
Great Saiyaman!
I nailed it! I nailed it good!
That was so uncool.
This is the champion of justice, Great Saiyaman?
Well then, farewell, Videl-san.
Why does he know my name?!
A new hero is born!
His name, the champion
of justice, Great Saiyaman.
His true identity...
won't ever get found out, will it...?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
This is unusual, Gohan.
You're walking around the city with a girl.
Is this one of those "date" things?
Of all things, Gohan-kun's secret got out,
and to keep her from revealing it,
he has to go out with her.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Gohan's Frantic First Date!?"
Dates are even tougher
than putting down bad guys.
"Next time"
"Gohan's Frantic First Date!?"