The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Vegeta stalled for time so that Goku could
store up enough ki to defeat Majin Boo.
However, there was nothing Vegeta
could do before Boo's spectacular strength.
But then...
...the gentle Boo, who had been
absorbed by Boo, was revived.
I hate you! Don't you pick on Satan!
Aren't you done yet?! Aren't
you done gathering up your ki?!
M-My power... My power is d-dropping off!
But what's this? After storing up his ki,
Goku suddenly returned to
normal from being Super Saiyan!
"Vegeta's Secret Plan!!
Polunga and the Two Wishes."
H-Hang in there, Boo!
Y-You stupid bastard! You let all
that pain I went through go to waste!
What do you think you're doing, Kakarrot?!
S-Sorry, Vegeta...
D-Damn it all! It was never
any problem when I was dead...
It appears that being Super Saiyan 3 in a
living body eats up quite a bit of ki after all...
We've had it. We really have had it.
Boo!
You bastard! How dare you do that to Boo!
Let go! Let go of him!
You dirty runt! Come on, let go!
You turn into choco!!
Th-This is bad. He's going
to be done in like that.
Kaioshins! Dende! Can you hear me?!
You've got to be watching
what's happening on that ball, right?!
Can you hear me? If you can
hear my voice, then answer me!
Yeah, we hear you...
All right! Now then, go immediately
to the restored Planet Namek
and scrounge up the Dragon Balls!
U-Um, how exactly are...
Stop nattering and get on with it!
We're running out of time!
Th-The Dragon Balls, huh?
I'm sure Vegeta-san has
some sort of idea! Let's go!
Still, those things, you know...
This is no time for you to be so particular!
How is it wrong to use
them for something legitimate?
I-I get it. I get it!
Let's go! To Planet Namek!
It would seem they've gone.
V-Vegeta, what are you doing?
It's still too soon to be using the Dragon Balls.
Kakarrot, how many times have
you saved the Earth up to now?
What's this, all of a sudden?
I asked you how many times you've saved it!
Let's see, how many times has it been?
It's time to let the folks on Earth
take the responsibility for a change.
So this is Planet Namek?
Y-Yes... It's supposed to be...
It is Planet Namek! There's no
doubt about it! H-However, it's...
What do you think, Dende?
It's just the way it used
to be, even on this planet!
–Welcome back!
–You've certainly grown up!
Y-You guys!
It has been so long! Elder-sama,
I'm so glad you're looking well!
Dende, you're looking good too. And
you've become quite Kami-sama-like!
N-Not at all!
I'm still very inexperienced, and
there is much I still have to study.
I'm sorry to interrupt your touching
reunion, but there isn't a moment to lose.
Th-That's right! Elder-sama,
I have a favor to ask!
Would you please gather the
Dragon Balls right away for me?
We need the power of Polunga!
The Dragon Balls, you say?
Has something happened to the Dragon Balls?
Kaioshin-sama, we know the
entire situation. Now, let us hurry!
Yeah. So you've already gathered them?
Thank you very much!
Vegeta-san...
Vegeta-san, can you hear me?!
Vegeta-san! All seven Dragon Balls
have already been gathered!
Dende?
Summon Planet Namek's Polunga immediately!
There are two wishes I want granted.
First, I want the Earth that has been
destroyed returned to the way it was!
Next, I want everyone who has died since
the day of that Tenkaichi Tournament,
except for the really bad ones, to
be brought back to life! Those two!
R-Right now? Those wishes?
That's right! Right now!
B-But, isn't that...
Dende, it looks like
Vegeta has some sort of idea.
Sorry to trouble you,
but could you just do it?
Y-Yes, understood!
So, what about the third wish?
After those first two, anything's fine!
Do whatever you want!
Vegeta, about that second wish...
Wouldn't it have been easier
to just ask for everyone who had been
killed by Boo to be brought back to life?
Hmph, idiot! If I'd done that,
then even Babidi and Dabura
would be brought back to life.
Besides, that way, the group that
I killed at the tournament grounds
would not be returned to life.
You sure thought this out, huh?
That won't work, Vegeta-san!
Come to think of it,
with Polunga here, we can only
bring people back to life one at a time!
W-What?!
N-Now that he mentions it, that's right, Vegeta!
W-What do we do?
We can't bring everyone
on Earth back to life like this!
Such worries are unnecessary!
After the incident with Freeza,
I had Polunga's wishes powered-up!
Does that mean he can
do any number of people?!
That's right.
Th-These guys are making a
mess of the natural order of things!
Vegeta-san! They said it would be all right!
Great. Now, get started!
Come forth, Polunga!
W-What the...?
Th-This is... Polunga?
So then, you may speak your wishes!
I shall grant thee any three wishes.
Okay, tell him the wishes! Do you
still remember the Namek language?
Yes.
Polunga! The faraway planet Earth has
been destroyed, and has disappeared.
Please, if you would, return
it back to the way it was!
Okay! That is a simple task.
E-Earth really has returned back to...
We did it! We did it!
I have granted your
first wish. Now, the next one.
You may speak your second wish.
Let's see, how should I say this...?
Um, please bring back to
life everyone who has died
since Madoshi Babidi arrived on Earth,
leaving out the really bad people.
Understood. However, thou must briefly wait.
Their numbers are many,
and it will be demanding.
Right!
W-What's this? Is he capable of even this?
Why, you runt! Why, you...! Why, you...! Let go!
Come on!
Come on! Let go, you stupid runt! Why, you...!
Satan!
This is precarious! Have you noticed, Kakarrot?
Yeah.
That chubby Boo is beginning to lose power.
With them both being
Boos, he's taking damage.
Aren't you done yet, Dende?!
Haven't those wishes been granted yet?!
What a pest! Stop squawking at us!
Polunga is going to a lot of trouble!
Thank you for waiting.
Your second wish has been granted.
He did it! He's done it!
Both the Earth and everyone on it have
been brought back to life, Vegeta-san!
Is that right?
W-What is it you're planning to do?
Vegeta, the ring over your head is gone!
This sure is great for you!
You ain't thought of as being really bad!
Th-Then, I wasn't killed by Boo?
Goodness! What in the world does this mean?
–But I was sure...
–So then, we didn't die?
Huh?
What's going on here?
I'm certain I was turned into chocolate,
and then I was eaten by Majin Boo,
and then I went to Heaven...!
I get it, Vegeta!
You wanted to bring
Gohan and Gotenks back to life
so we can have them fight too, right?
Wrong!
We're starting! Get ready!
Ready? For what?
Get ready to make a Genki Dama!
A-A Genki Dama? A Genki Dama?!
W-What's this?! Vegeta's secret
plan was to use a Genki Dama!
Come on, everyone who has been resurrected!
Share your Genki with Goku,
and then, defeat Majin Boo!
A Genki Dama, you say?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
I'm impressed, Vegeta.
If I can collect a bunch of earth's
Genki energy, we just might win.
Listen up, earthlings!
We're collecting your energy to defeat Boo!
Unless you want to die again,
raise your hands, now!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"A Last Hope!!
We'll Make a Huge Genki Dama."
No, Vegeta-san, you can't
ask them in such a rude manner!
"Next time"
"A Last Hope!!
We'll Make a Huge Genki Dama"