Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Unable to do anything before
the overwhelming power of Freeza,
Vegeta thoroughly loses his will to fight.
Until finally, Vegeta's death draws near.
At that moment...
Son Goku finally rises!
"Such Regret...!!
Vegeta, Pride of the Saiyans, Dies."
Damn...
Piccolo-san!
All right, they're very close.
My apologies, I'm coming now!
Something might just become of this!
How dull. You've utterly
lost the will to fight back.
It's a little soon, but
maybe I should finish you off.
So then, the identity of that
huge ki was Piccolo after all.
S-Son!
Nice. You were brought back
here with the Dragon Balls, huh?
Father!
Are you all right now?
Yeah. Thanks to you guys,
I've recovered from all that damage.
You've stuck it out well,
Gohan! Leave it up to me now.
What?!
Leave it up to you? What, are you
planning on taking that freak on by yourself?
Yep.
Father!
A-Are you really Goku?
There's something different about
the way your ki has felt up until now...
S-Son!
Is that Son? He's got an
unbelievable strength of ki.
There's no comparison
to when he was on Earth.
So you're Freeza?
You're much more of
a runt than I'd imagined.
So there's still another one of you scum left?
Vegeta has promised to fight with me.
Don't you interfere!
You... It's like I've seen you before...
K-Kakarrot, it's you...
K-Kakarrot? But that name is Saiyan.
It's him!
Freeza! Get out here!
I won't let you get away with this!
He looks just like that last Saiyan who
opposed me when I destroyed planet Vegeta.
I won't let a single one of you Saiyans live.
Don't you see, you would do
well just to tremble before me.
Maybe so.
H-He's not the same Kakarrot as before...
He's at last climbed over
the wall of his limitations...
W-Which means...
Are you ready, then?
Yeah.
W-What was that?
Did Goku just do something?
Unreal!
Not even I could see that clearly.
He's exceeded Freeza's speed!
Oh, no! Get out of the way, Goku!
You're an impudent one!
It can't be! He deflected every
one of them, and with just one hand!
Freeza, you'd better fight like you mean it!
H-He's the very thing you fear most...
A Super Saiyan!
That's right!
The strongest warrior in
the universe, a Super Saiyan!
Freeza, you're finished now! Serves you right!
Vegeta!
You knew, Vegeta, that I hate
such petty jokes, didn't you?
Vegeta!
Hey! Vegeta was in a state
where he couldn't even move!
There was no reason to
finish him off on purpose!
The Super Saiyan is nothing
more than a frivolous legend.
He wouldn't stop going on about it.
I hate it when people get tedious.
–K-Kakarrot...
–Vegeta!
Are you... still reciting that soft crap?
Are you not a Super Saiyan?!
Wait!
You foolish scum! Get cold-hearted!
If you had only discarded your
leniency, you would surely already be...
...a Super Saiyan!
I just don't see how I could
act as cold-hearted as you do.
And as for this Super Saiyan
business, I don't know what you mean.
A-A Super Saiyan is...
How wonderful!
Look at it, Zarbon-san, Dodoria-san!
Behold such beautiful fireworks!
L-Listen well, Kakarrot...
And here I've pierced his heart.
What nerve. Are you going to keep talking?
Your... our planet of birth,
Planet Vegeta... was not destroyed...
i-in a collision with a giant meteor...
Don't say any more!
You're just hastening your death!
Freeza did it...!
This after we Saiyans...
served as his hands and feet...
working exactly as he ordered...!
Everyone besides us was killed...!
Your father... and my
father, the king, as well...!
Freeza... was afraid that as
the Saiyans gathered strength...
a Super Saiyan would be born among us...
Just listen to you.
Vegeta!
I-I beg you...! Freeza... defeat Freeza...!
Please... by your Saiyan hand...
Vegeta...
Has he finally croaked?
Well, shall we reconvene
this Show of Terror, then?
For you to cry...
For you to beg of me, must
have been awfully difficult, I bet.
I understand.
It wasn't that your fellow Saiyans
had been killed that was rough on you–
Having to do as he told you must have
been worse than anything you could stand.
I hated you so much...
...but you had your Saiyan pride.
And now I too will share in
some of that pride of yours.
I am a Saiyan raised on Earth!
For all the Saiyans who were killed by you...
...as well as for all the Namekians here...
I am going to beat you!
Such drivel.
Son Goku opens his eyes to his Saiyan pride.
Just how great is his terrible anger?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Freeza! Don't go messing up
other people's planets so much!
What will you do once you break it?!
These Saiyan characters are strange ones.
There's no upper limit to his strength.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Curtain Rises over the Ultimate
Battle!! I Am Going to Defeat You."
Father is strong! The strongest in the universe!
"Next time"
"The Curtain Rises over the Ultimate Battle!!
I Am Going to Defeat You"