Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
In order to combine with
Artificial Humans No. 17 and No. 18
and become his perfect form,
Cell continues to murder over and over again!
Cell masks his ki,
evading Piccolo and the others'
pursuit as if to make fun of them.
As this goes on, Goku finally recovers!
Don't worry! I ain't fighting yet.
If Vegeta can't win against
them now, I can't win either.
That's why I'm thinking of
aiming for something higher, too.
Higher than Super Saiyan!
"Hasten Your Training, Saiyans!
In the Room of Spirit and Time..."
Yeah. I'm thinking of aiming for
something higher than Super Saiyan.
A-Aiming for something
higher than Super Saiyan, you say?
Is such a thing possible?
I don't know.
However, if I ain't as much as that,
I can't possibly win against this opponent.
I'll train for a year,
and if it's no use, I'll give it up.
One year? If it takes that long...
It's okay.
It'll be a year, but there's a
place where it will only take a day.
Chichi, I want to take
Gohan with me too, is that okay?
Y... Y...
Y-You've gotta be kiddin'...
...is what I was goin' to say,
but it's no use, so I'm stoppin'.
There's no helpin' it,
so if you're goin' to do it at all,
make him good and strong!
Chichi...
However, once this fightin'
with the Artificial Humans is over,
I won't let you get in the way of
Gohan-chan's studyin', no matter what.
She certainly is the wife of
the strongest man in the world,
and not just a "Spartan Mama!"
She sure has nerves of steel.
On top of that, I'm goin' to
have you go to work, Goku-sa.
Thank you!
Mmm, how nice.
Well, I'm off.
He vanished! How'd he do that?
Goku-sa...
Haven't we reached the city where he is yet?!
Nope.
If we don't do this quick,
he'll run away on us again!
If we don't do this quick, he'll run away on us.
If only Goku were here.
Goku!
Yeah, if Goku were here...
You see, with Goku's Instantaneous Movement...
Father!
Whoosh! We'd be... oh?
Yo!
Right, just like that, he
could appear anywhere... huh?
Go-Go... Go...
Yo, Kuririn!
Goku!!
Goku! I've missed you!
Man, have I been waiting
for this! When did you wake up?
You're all better then?
Yeah. My stomach's on empty, though.
Your stomach?
That's just like you, Goku!
You really are better, huh?
Yeah, I'm okay now.
Father!
Kamiccolo-sama!
What?
Don't merge the names together.
My base is mostly Piccolo,
so you can just call me Piccolo.
Oh, really? Well then, Piccolo...
What is it?
The way I am now,
there ain't no way I can win against
the Artificial Humans or this Cell guy.
So I'm taking Gohan with me,
and we're going to go train.
To the place where we can train
for a whole year in just one day.
What was that?
You want to go to the
Room of Spirit and Time, then?
I see now.
However, there hasn't been anyone that
was able to spend an entire year in there.
It was all you could do to
spend a month in there so long ago.
I'm taking Vegeta and Trunks with me too.
They're sure to be able to take it.
In that case, hurry and go, Goku.
Cell is rapidly killing people,
and rapidly becoming stronger.
If he combines with No. 17 and
becomes his perfect form on us,
there's going to be trouble.
Right!
Goku, let me ask you something.
Now that an enemy even more
incredible than Freeza has appeared,
are you scared?
Or instead, are you happy?
Both.
He's sure an imprudent one!
Here we are at a time when people are
being killed and the Earth is about to perish.
This is great! It looks as
though Goku hasn't given up yet!
A little bit of hope has come into view!
He really just might go beyond Super Saiyan!
Goku-san!
How are the results of your training?
It's no good.
Dad only sees me as a nuisance.
I ask him to train with me,
but he only persists in saying
I'm in his way and to get lost.
And far be it from training,
Dad has just stood there
motionless for the last three days.
As might be expected of Vegeta.
Apparently he's starting to faintly
see what lies ahead of Super Saiyan.
You're in the way, Kakarrot. Get lost.
Don't say that, I know a good place to train.
There's a room in the temple at Kami's home
where you can get a year's
worth of training in just one day.
Really?
Yeah. Come with me.
I ain't necessarily saying
you'd have to train with me.
However, the room has a capacity of two.
There ain't much time, so
I'll have you go in with Trunks.
Fine, provided that I go in first.
Yeah.
Provincial clothes...
Provincial house.
Son Goku lives in a place like this?
Indeed, Son Goku isn't here,
nor anyone else. They've fled.
So it seems.
Can you tell, No. 16, where he is now?
I can't sense Son Goku's power on my radar.
However, assuming he's gone
to one of his friends' places,
there's either the Capsule
Corporation in Metro West,
or Muten Roshi's small
island in the southern F region.
Makes sense. So, which one is closer?
Muten Roshi's house.
About 2700 kilometers southeast of here.
Okay, let's go.
My, my!
Dammit, are we too late?
And I thought for sure we were
going to take him down this time!
It's him!
Got it. Come.
There is tub, toilet and food.
Good luck with training.
Kakarrot, why are you
encouraging me to train, too?
My final objective is you, you know.
Our opponent this time probably
ain't the kind of opponent
one of us can beat alone.
You must have realized this too.
You may come to regret doing this.
Here. Who will use first?
Vegeta and Trunks will go in ahead of us.
Okay.
Enter.
Excuse us, Goku-san.
Hang in there, Trunks. Make nice with Vegeta!
Good luck!
It's hot! And the air is thin, too!
The gravity is many times greater as well!
What is this?!
There's nothing here! Nothing but white space!
It's impossibly vast!
This is what Goku-san
couldn't bear for a month's time
before he started not feeling right?
Yes indeed. This is fine.
A year with Dad in a place like this?
It didn't work, huh?
Damn him suppressing his ki!
This just isn't any good.
There's any number of
places he can hide, after all.
This is bad. By now, he
must be getting quite strong.
And we don't know when
he'll combine with No. 17
and the others to become his perfect form.
At this point, the only
thing we may be able to do
is hope Goku and the others
really do go beyond Super Saiyans,
and then together,
defeat No. 17 and the others.
And so, after just about one
whole day had passed from the time
Vegeta and Trunks entered
the Room of Spirit and Time...
This mysterious devil continues
to strike as ubiquitously as ever,
–and his victims are now said to
number several hundered thousand.
–Dammit, enough already, Cell!
–Meanwhile, the whole world continues
to live in terror of this devil.
–Why, you...!
Blasted Cell!
Yo. Is Son Goku here?
D-Damn! Is this good timing, or poor?
Son Goku does not seem to be here.
Is that so?
Wake up! We've got visitors of the worst kind.
What? What is it?
Go on back right now! Son Goku is not here!
So it seems.
Well then, why don't we
have you tell us where he is?
H-How did they know about this place?
Do you think we would just dutifully tell you?
Well, I'm not sure.
If you don't tell us, we
intend to force it out of you.
T-They're the Artificial Humans I've heard about?
I see. Well, you can try.
There's an island over there
with no one on it. Let's do it there.
Dear, dear, you never learn...
You guys stay here.
You have to know you would be of no use.
Say, do you think he can win?
It's impossible! He's got three opponents!
It's just about time for
two of the four among Goku
and the others to finish their training!
Until then, we'll have to rely on you, Piccolo!
Unless you say something,
I'll kill you for sure this time.
Understood?
It won't be as easy as it was last time.
At last, No. 17 and Piccolo's fight begins!
Just how great is Piccolo's true power,
now that he's combined with Kami?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
An awesome battle between
No. 17 and Piccolo has begun.
It's up to you, Piccolo.
You're the only one who's a match for him now.
If I can defeat No. 17, at least,
I can prevent Cell from
becoming his perfect form.
I accept this fight!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Next time"
"The Gekiretsu Kodan That Split the Heavens!!
Piccolo vs. Artificial Human No. 17"
Hang in there, Piccolo-san!