Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
During his brutal battle with Cell,
Vegeta nearly decided everything
at once with his overwhelming power!
It seems that even with you really
putting out all the power you've got,
this is what your level is.
How damned disappointing! You pantywaist!
Here I came, wondering what
an exceptional guy you must be...
Killing you has become a frivolous matter!
Damn it to hell!!
"I'm So Distraught!!
Kuririn's Handiwork in Destroying No. 18."
N-No. 18 is in the area!
I-I can still...
...use this controller!
But where in the world is she?
I-I have to find No. 18 right away!
If she's found by Cell...
Damn it all!!
I-Incredible...
I-If only I could become my perfect form...!
If only I could become my perfect form,
t-the likes of that guy would be...!
So, what?
You're saying that if you
could become your perfect form,
you wouldn't be losing to me?
That's right! I absolutely would not lose!
Power, speed, techniques,
brains, mental strength...!
In all things, I will achieve a perfect existence!
That's what the computer told me!
Dammit!
If only I could become my perfect form...!
Damn it all!!
Incredible...
When he fought with me,
could he have been purposely
pretending to be weaker?
No, there isn't any reason why
he would have had to do that.
Something has happened
during these last few days.
Something?
What the hell could have happened
where he would change that much?!
T-There she is! In a place such as this?
H-Haven't they realized it?
Either Cell or Vegeta?
Or Trunks?
With this, once I've shut
down No. 18's functions,
and then destroyed her,
Cell will be unable to
become his perfect form,
and we'll have beaten No. 18 as well!
However, you have to draw to within 10 meters,
or it won't have any effect,
okay? Within 10 meters!
All right!
I-If only I could absorb No. 18...!
The man, No. 17, wasn't there.
Has he alone been absorbed?
That's how Cell has transformed
and powered up, I'll bet.
There they are! Somehow, I have to get closer–
within 10 meters of
them–without them noticing...
If I'm seen, it's all over.
What am I thinking here,
at an important time like this?!
What a start! Don't scare me like that!
Ah, you fool! The Artificial Humans are there!
Despite the obvious gap between us,
you're saying that if you became
your perfect form, you would beat me?
I-I would unmistakably beat you!
If you're at that level, that is...
D-Dad, don't tell me...!
H-He can't mean to...!
No. 16, what's the matter?
No. 18, do not worry about me,
run away at any time!
You seem to be considering it...
How about it, Vegeta?
You Saiyans are a warrior
race through and through!
Fighting is your passion!
However, the stronger your opponent,
the greater the joy you take in fighting!
Isn't that so? Am I wrong?
You'd like to try fighting, wouldn't you...
against me, in my perfect form?
You must want to!
You are the prince of the
warrior race, the Saiyans, after all!
Within 10 meters...
within 10 meters... just a bit farther...!
All right...
E-Even if I use this controller to stop No. 18,
unless she's destroyed,
she'll be absorbed by Cell...!
I think I can destroy her...
No. 16 doesn't hardly
seem able to move, and all...
T-This is the only chance there is!
No. 18 was originally just a cute human girl...
If she hadn't been
reconstructed by Doctor Gero...
I even feel sorry for her!
I wouldn't really have to destroy her...
No! If she is absorbed by Cell,
and then Cell becomes his perfect form,
people all over the world might be killed!
Destroy her...
Don't destroy her...
Destroy her... Don't destroy her...
Destroy her... Destroy her...
–The water's just right, huh Gohan?
–Yes!
My fatigue feels like it's flying away!
So, I wonder how Kuririn-san
and the others are doing right now.
Not knowing what's happening in the
world out front sure makes you uneasy.
Don't worry about it.
More importantly, be sure you massage
yourself well here in the hot water.
It takes the exhaustion away.
Right!
You know something, Gohan,
you're keeping up pretty good!
It's been just about two
months since we've come in here.
Even so, Father,
in the world outside,
only four hours have gone by!
It really is wondrous, huh?
This Room of Spirit and Time.
Yeah, it sure is.
Okay! I'm going to work hard
to become a Super Saiyan soon,
and become an opponent for you, Father!
Now you've done it!
All right, Gohan!
Once we get out of the tub,
we'll eat, and then it's more training!
Right!
Destroy her... Don't destroy her... Destroy her...
See ya!
Bye!
She was originally just a cute human girl...
You're...
That couldn't be... an
emergency shutdown controller?
Why would he...?
Don't you want to try
fighting me in my perfect form,
prince of the warrior race?
You certainly do understand Saiyans well.
Your cells are also included
within my body, after all.
That must be what it is...
That is indeed what it is.
Very well!
I will intentionally fall into your trap!
You may become your perfect form. Go!
Dad!
I would not be proud of
myself if I defeated you
the pathetic way you are now.
Dad! You can't!
If you let him do that...
That's you're greatest fault, Dad!
Shut up, Trunks!
I'm not above fixing it so that you'll
never take that insolent tone with me again!
You should know better than anyone
how incredible the power
beyond Super Saiyan that I have is!
So, get going!
I'm looking forward to this, Cell.
Dad may have let you go,
but I will not let you escape!
Bulma-san, you went to all that
trouble to make this for us. I'm sorry.
Get away safely!
No matter what, don't
get absorbed by Cell! Please!
Why?! Why did you break the controller?!
It must have been your
chance, right? To destroy me?
T-That's...
Kid, move it!
If you have the time to interfere with me,
why not help out in searching for No. 18?
There will be no more need
for you to search for No. 18.
–What?
–You are going to be
defeated by me, here and now!
What was that, you punk,
with your ass still blue?
Trunks! Do not interfere!
I thought I said I was going to squeeze
the life from you, right here and now!
How about you just accept that and fight?!
Trunks! I told you to stop!
It's like Dad explained it–
I also possess nearly as
much power as he does!
With your power now, you
will not be winning against me!
Give it up!
H-Hey, Vegeta!
Do something with this guy, will you?
No. 18! I-I've found you!
No!!
At last, No. 18 has been discovered by Cell!
Will Kuririn's affections turn to their harm?
And what will be No. 18's destiny?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
No. 18, Cell has spotted you!
Get out of there, fast!
I will prevent him from
getting his perfect form,
even if I have to defeat you, Dad.
I've had enough hellish futures!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"A Shock to the Entire Universe!! Cell's
Spectacular Evolution Toward His Perfect Form."
Oh, no! No. 18 is going to be absorbed!
"Next time"
"A Shock to the Entire Universe!! Cell's
Spectacular Evolution Toward His Perfect Form"