Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Just as Trunks had foretold,
the Artificial Humans No. 1 9
and No. 20 have appeared.
E-Everybody!
M-My power...
And so, the first casualty
of their massacre is Yamucha.
Is this the terrible power of the Artificial Humans?
"The Cold-Blooded No. 20's Hideous Atrocities!!
Goku's Super Transformation of Anger."
There's a large ki in distress,
and it's growing smaller! Whose is it?
Is that Yamucha-san?
They've shown themselves!
Yamucha!
Aw, damn.
Kuririn, Yamucha is still alive.
I left the senzu back where we were earlier.
Take him there and feed him one.
You got it.
We're counting on you, Kuririn!
Yeah.
So you're the Artificial Humans?
About time you showed your faces.
Strange. How did you know
we were Artificial Humans?
What's more...
you seemed to know we would
be appearing here on this island.
Why don't you tell me how you knew?
Well now, how about you try
to force the answers out of us?
That we will.
Wait! There'll be too many casualties here!
Let's relocate to someplace
where nobody's around!
You guys okay with that?
Someplace where no one else is?
Very well.
However, we need not
trouble ourselves with relocating.
Stop it!!
What was that? What's happened?
It's them. They did this.
How awful!
Mommy!
Why you...
I thought I would make us a
place where no one else was around.
Apparently you still don't like it here.
Come with me!
I'm going to smash the both of you!!
You cannot defeat us.
Dammit!
Very well. We will follow you.
Choose the place you wish to die, Son Goku.
How did you know Goku's name?
We know who you are as well.
Piccolo and Tenshinhan, isn't it?
We'll talk about this later.
Let's go!
It's Father, and the others!
And those two guys are with them.
What?
I get it, they must be changing locations.
This is bad! I've got to warn Goku!
Those guys suck the power out of you!
Oh, yeah!
This is a special newscast.
We've just received word
that the city on Amembo Island,
nine kilometers southwest of Metro South...
has been attacked by an unknown party,
and has in large part been leveled.
He said southwest of Metro South, right?
That's where Ten-san went!
So then... they've actually appeared.
Artificial Humans from the Red Ribbon Army.
Currently there is no
communication with the city,
and there is concern for
the safety of its inhabitants.
Ten-san!
Hey, there's nothing to worry about.
This time Goku's been there from the start.
This is sure to be an easy
victory for them, you know.
That's right! Goku is a Super Saiyan,
the strongest warrior in the universe!
Yeah, you're right.
Goku, we're all counting on you.
Yamucha-san, you say
they can suck out your power?
Yeah. I don't know how they do it,
but just by him grabbing me,
I could feel my power rapidly fading.
If that's right, then Doctor Gero
has invented quite a fearsome device.
This is terrible! We have to hurry
and go warn Father and the others!
To be honest, I don't even want to go.
I want nothing to do with it.
After all, I was helpless to
stop them from nearly killing me!
Gohan!
Yamucha-san, I'm going.
I have to take them the senzu.
You guys! None of you understand...
...how terrible these Artificial Humans are!
Dammit! I'm not going to do anything!
I'm just going to watch now!
Heh. Whatta fool he is.
Say, aren't you going?
Of course I ain't goin'.
"Ain't goin'?" Aren't you
supposed to be pretty strong too?
At a time like this, we need
as many guys as we can get!
Your friends, the Earth,
everything's caught in this pinch.
Yeah, prob'ly.
"Yeah, prob'ly?!"
You don't care about
anything at all! How very shabby!
I can't fly, y'know.
Sorry.
Enough is enough, Son Goku!
How far were you thinking of going?
Right here is fine. I'm making this the spot.
You have no claim over
us to choose the location.
A tableland, but surrounded
on all sides by rocks.
If it becomes necessary, they figure they
can fight us while hiding among the rocks.
These guys have thought this out.
So, before we start fighting,
tell us how you know so much about us.
What's going on? Goku's out of breath.
All we've done so far is fly here.
Why is that?
Very well, I'll tell you.
Afterward, you'll probably
wish you hadn't asked.
Son Goku, you've been
under constant surveillance,
through the use of miniature,
grub-like spy robots.
During the Tenkaichi Martial Arts Tournaments...
...as well as your battles
with Piccolo and Vegeta.
The research has been ongoing from the
time you destroyed the Red Ribbon Army.
How could Son Goku be defeated?
What kind of Artificial
Human would be necessary?
This was to get even with me?
Yes it was.
Because of you, the Red Ribbon Army's
dream of world conquest was shattered,
and only Doctor Gero remained.
The way you say that, it almost
sounds as if you were Doctor Gero himself.
Don't be absurd.
I am No. 20, an Artificial Human
constructed by Doctor Gero.
Doctor Gero has died,
and is no longer of this world.
I see. So did you guys spy on me during
the fight on the planet Namek as well?
There was no need. After your fight with Vegeta,
we had a complete knowledge
of your strengths and abilities.
Of course, should you
become more powerful still,
taking into account your age...
...it was calculated that there could be no
more tremendous increases in your power.
This is bad!
Looks as though no one's started fighting yet,
and everyone is still suppressing their ki.
We'll never find them like this!
Where are you?! Where are you?!
It looks as though you've failed...
...to investigate the most
important thing about me.
You guys lose!
What?
It will cost you your lives not to
have known about the Super Saiyan.
Super Saiyan?
This way!
What an incredible ki!
Can his power really be this great?
You two stay out of this.
It would appear I'm the
one they want most, after all.
You certainly have achieved
quite an increase in power.
No. 20, this seems to be a
technique different from the Kaio-ken.
It's an unusual technique.
These readings are far
higher than what was calculated.
However, it is still not enough to overpower us.
To say nothing of myself,
at your level, it is unlikely
you could defeat even No. 19.
Oh really? Well, why don't I have
you show me this strength right now?
The day of battle at long last arrives.
However, even as they face a
Goku who has turned Super Saiyan...
...what do these surprisingly at-ease
Artificial Humans have planned?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Damn, my body is acting funny.
Did those guys drain out my ki?
Good, No. 1 9's maximum power just shot up!
On the other hand, Son
Goku's energy is starting to fall off!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Goku's Double-Shock!!
Caught Between Illness and Adversary."
Oh, no! How can he get sick now?!
"Next time"
"Goku's Double-Shock!!
Caught Between Illness and Adversary"