The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Using every means of destruction,
Majin Boo has indiscriminately attacked
and destroyed cities and
villages all over the world.
Elsewhere, Goku had placed
his hopes with Goten and Trunks,
and returned back to the Other World.
There, Goku was told by Great King
Yama that Gohan is still alive.
Sensing Gohan's ki, Goku
has come to the Kaioshin Realm.
There, he was reunited with Gohan,
Kaioshin, and the resurrected Kibit.
"You're Kidding, Right!?
The Z-Sword is Broken."
–Fu-sion!
Once again!
–Fusion Ha!
No, no!
How many times do I have
to say this before you get it?!
Match your timing together!
Listen! Fusion is a merging technique.
No matter how well you learn the pose,
unless you make your breathing as one,
you will not master Fusion.
Yeah, but Goten's being too slow!
Am not! Trunks-kun is too fast!
–What was that?!
–Oh, yeah?!
Enough already! We don't
have any time for this!
If you want to fight, you can do it all
you like, after you defeat Majin Boo!
All right. Let's continue training!
Right...
Fusion Ha!
Once again!
My, my, and they were
doing so well with it, too.
Yoink!
Okay...
So do you really suppose
they'll be able to merge together?
It's okay, they'll do it!
There's no reason Son-kun would lie to us.
Awesome, awesome!
You've done good to be able to wield it
that well in just a day! Incredible, Gohan!
Indeed, quite wonderful, Gohan-san!
So, I'm sure it's awfully sharp, that Z-Sword.
Say, let's test it out a bit!
Very good!
Let's see... okay...
First will be this rock.
All right, here goes, Gohan!
Try cutting this clean in half!
I'm sure it will cut right through it like tofu!
If I know the Z-Sword here!
You did it, Gohan-san!
Yes...
Wow! That's awfully sharp!
Goku-san...
Let's try something even harder this time.
Goku-san, here.
Oof... what's this?
This is katchinko, said to be
the hardest metal in the universe.
Whew, that's hard!
As long as you're doing this, try it with that!
That's great!
All right, Gohan, here goes!
Leave it to me!
Ready, set...
Go!
Y-You're kidding! It broke!
I-I-It can't be! Th-Th-The Z-Sword!
Th-The strongest blade ever...!
Look at that! Kaioshin-sama, this is your fault
for telling us to try testing it
against something that hard.
B-But, it's said that whoever takes it in hand
will hold the greatest power in the world!
Th-Th-The Z-Sword was the
legendary blade of this holy region!
It appears it was something
of an exaggerated legend, huh?
B-But still, because of it, my
strength has risen considerably.
That Z-Sword was incredibly heavy, after all.
See? Perhaps it meant that if you
came to be able to use that sword,
you would have the greatest
power in the world, maybe.
Th-That's it! If you've gotten that
much power in your regular state,
once you turn Super Saiyan, you should
experience a considerable power-up!
That's it! That's the legendary
greatest power in the world!
But whether that power is greater
than Majin Boo's... I don't know...
B-But Goku-san, there isn't any other way.
That's not so-o!
Huh? What's with the old guy?
U-Um, and you are...?
Me?
You'll be so surprised
to hear this! I'm, y'know...
Who am I, who am I, but your, y'know...
15-generation-previous, y'know, Kaioshin here!
F-Fifteen-generations previous?!
K-Kaioshin-sama?!
U-Um... Great King Yama-sama?
"Great King Yama-sama"
What is it?
Er, can we please ask you
to allow us to go home, oni?
What?!
We have been working so
long now without any rest,
and hardly any time for meals.
If this keeps up, I fear we will find
it hard not to get in line ourselves.
I'd like to get some rest right along with you,
but we can't very well leave
these dead people here, right?
Oni...
Passing judgement on these lost dead
and then leading them to the
world they are to proceed to is our duty!
G-Great King Yama! This is terrible!
What's wrong?!
A-Another million-and-a-half
dead have just arrived from Earth!
What did you say?!
Just what in hell is happening on Earth?
Fifteen-generation-previous–
Kaioshin-sama?!
That's right.
Long, long ago, y'know, there was this
terribly strong, y'know, bad guy, y'know.
Well, not so bad as this Majin Boo now.
So this guy, y'know, sealed
me up inside that sword, here.
I'm sure, y'know, he was all nervous by how
fearsome I am, y'know, so he did it. Mm hmm.
Finally, I've been allowed out!
He doesn't look like that
awesome an old guy. Right?
Not really...
Say, should we put him to the test?
Huh? I'm not too sure...
–H-Honorable forefather!
–A-Are you all right?!
–Please, shake it off!
–Honorable forefather!
You ignorant fool!
What are you doing?!
You dung dangle! You tinkle trickle!
Dimwit! Scum! That you could
do that to a majestic Kaioshin!
And you have an outie, too!
He's just a blowhard old man after all.
He's not that strong at all, is he?
It wasn't my power, y'know,
that made my opponent nervous!
It was the fearsome ability
I have that he was nervous about!
–Fearsome...
–Ability?
What's that?
Nyah nyah nyaaaah!
I'm not telling you any mo-ore!
I guess there ain't any choice.
If that's the case, I'll give you a dirty
book next time I see you, so tell us!
F-Father!
Goku-san! How could you say that?!
Hmph! I don't have to see
any book! With my godly eyes,
I can see gals bathing and change
their clothes and stuff just fine, you know!
H-Honorable forefather!
Well, in a little while, I'll let you
touch a real woman's boobs and behind!
R-Really?!
Yeah! Sure thing!
That's got him! I knew it, he's the
same type as Old Man Turtle Hermit!
Father, when you say that,
what do you intend to do?
What will I do?
Since I can't go down to
the Lower Realm any more...
You've got a girlfriend,
right, that girl Videl?
I hate to ask, but for just a bit,
have her let him touch her.
W-W-What are you saying?! That isn't funny!
Oh yeah? This is a problem...
Still, with Super Saiyan 3
and Fusion and everything,
circumstances are getting far beyond
anything on a dimension we can handle, huh?
It looks as though we won't
get a turn... this time around.
That's not so! I'm sure
there's something we all can do.
And that's the game! Ta-da!
Say, would it be okay if she's
kind of a middle-aged woman?
Well, if she's sexy,
I suppose that would be fine.
All right! Let's make it Bulma!
You explain the situation to
Bulma and ask her to do it for me!
I-I have to ask Bulma-san to do such a thing?!
So, this ability, can it beat Majin Boo?
Well, I can't say absolutely,
y'know, but I think it will.
See? Just by allowing him to
touch someone's behind and boobs,
the Earth–no, the whole
universe can be saved!
Isn't that sexual harassment?
And besides, I'm the one
who has to ask her, right?
Even if the universe does get saved,
I'm going to get killed by Bulma-san!
Fine! Okay!
It's settled then.
So, what is this "ability" then?
I, y'know, can take anyone
who's good at what they do,
y'know, and with my mental power, y'know,
draw out their hidden power wa-ay,
wa-ay past their limits, here.
Ever heard of such an incredible ability?
Hey, that's an ability you
hear about rather often, ain't it?
What are you talking about?!
Past their limits, you know, past their limits!
There's absolutely no one else like that!
N-Now that you mention it, I guess not.
Hey, you're the one that
pulled that sword out, aren't you?
Go stand over there.
Right.
If anyone was able to pull that sword out
and be able to swing it around, y'know,
once I set him up, y'know, he's sure
to be the strongest in the universe.
However, y'know, I had thought that
whoever pulled out that sword, y'know,
and let me out, y'know,
would have been a Kaioshin.
Who would have thought that
I would be saved by a human?
What is the world coming to?
M-My sincere apologies...
All right! Stand there, and
you can't move too much!
Right!
Okay then, here goes. Go defeat Majin Boo!
Um, is that–?
Quiet!
We're in the middle of an important ceremony!
Ceremony? This?
S-Say, uh, how long does this take?
The ceremony is five hours.
To power him up takes another twenty hours.
I'm going to go take a
little nap. Hang in there, Gohan!
Th-This can't be...!
I-It wouldn't do for us to
not stay awake, would it?
Indeed.
Th-This is lousy.
Fusion Ha!
All right! Good, you're just about perfect!
Okay, it's about time when we can
see whether or not you can do this.
All right, you two make
your ki exactly the same!
Right!
A-Am I really going to be
able to merge with this guy?
Unbelievable. It sounds fishy to me.
Okay, begin!
Right!
Has Fusion been mastered at last?
And can Gohan really power
up through the mental abilities
of the 15-generation-old Kaioshin?
The annihilation of the Earth is
drawing close before our very eyes!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
All right, you've got
the Fusion down perfectly!
Now for the birth of the
warrior who will defeat Majin Boo!
Now, see here! I don't
care how strong you are!
Don't go off after Boo without
even turning Super Saiyan!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Birth of a Superhuman Warrior!!
His Name is Gotenks."
Gotenks? Even his personality is different.
"Next time"
"Birth of a Superhuman Warrior!!
His Name is Gotenks"