Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
At last, Cell had become
his ultimate, perfect form.
Miserable Vegeta! Take responsibility!
I knew it. Even if it is his perfect form,
it doesn't appear to be anything special.
Damn it all!
How dare you take No. 18?!
Kuririn-san!
Don't you move, Cell!
Kienzan!!
Kuririn-san! Please, get away!
The first casualty is Kuririn.
The overture to the collapse of the Earth–no,
the whole universe–has already begun!
"Super Vegeta in Peril!!
An Absolutely Perfect Terror Closes In!!"
K-Kuririn-san...
H-He's too awful!
T-This is a first.
There wasn't even time to feel pain.
I-I'm still falling to pieces.
Kuririn-san!
Such a fortunate man,
to be the first to taste of this perfect power.
Stay with us, Kuririn-san!
Here's a senzu. Can you eat it?
Please, swallow it somehow.
Did it make you happy to pick on that scum?
Just as I thought, it would
appear that even in this perfect form,
you're nothing special.
You'll have to excuse me.
Now then, would you assist me in warming up?
Very good. I will finish you off as you warm up.
If you please...
Thank goodness! Kuririn-san...
That was a close call!
I thought you might have had it.
Kuririn-san?
This isn't good! Vegeta's going to get killed!
I'm certainly not much at all
when compared to you Saiyans.
However, I more-or-less know
the strength of this opponent.
I-I know... I know how terrible he is!
To him, he probably
did no more than tap me,
but I learned how terrible he is!
C-Cell has truly gotten stronger.
However, Vegeta still
exceeds him in every way.
Y-You can't take the ki you
can feel now as a reference.
He's hiding a much, much
more phenomenal power!
Just like you are, Trunks.
You knew?
It seems the power-up from
this perfect form of yours...
...was not altogether
an exaggeration after all.
Vegeta is that sort of guy,
so maybe he didn't realize it,
but somehow, I could tell.
You've been sort of... reserved toward Vegeta.
You've overcome the wall
that Vegeta could not overcome.
Am I wrong?
What's the matter? Is this all
the power of your perfect form?
Dad has gone beyond
the limits of Super Saiyan.
It would appear that you have
become able to fight a bit more decently.
But you're still a long way
from being a match for me.
Sure enough, this is the
power-up you would have gotten
from absorbing those
flea-market Artificial Humans.
Maybe so.
Smile, will you?
He achieved outstanding power,
such as the strength he has now.
However, one day,
I went beyond even that world.
I realized that this must have
been what Goku-san was speaking of.
I couldn't tell Dad about it!
I couldn't tell Dad, not
with his towering pride!
Trunks...
Dad should have defeated Cell as he was!
Vegeta is sure impressive.
He's fighting toe-to-toe
with the perfect form Cell.
Toe-to-toe, you say?
Vegeta is getting frantic.
With someone of equal–no, perhaps
even greater ability before his eyes,
his rational judgment has dropped.
Hey, there!
How long are you two going to
be enjoying this all by yourselves?
You let me know just
what's going on as well!
I mean, really...!
Nice going, Gohan.
That's it! You've just
about got your ki under control!
This is smarting just as I expected.
At this pace, you'll soon surpass me!
Mock me, will you?
You can't get away!
Just as I expected, Vegeta.
That attack just now was pretty good.
Don't you make light of me!
Take this!!
Dad...
Vegeta there has lost his composure.
To think that by absorbing No. 17 and No. 18,
Cell's power would rise this much...!
Dammit!
What sort of monster has
Doctor Gero given rise to?
D-Don't you toy with me!
D-Dad...
You mean there's that much
difference between their powers?
You miserable jackass!
You're not taking this seriously, are you?!
I did say this would just
be warming up, didn't I?
What?!
H-He's saying everything up
to now was just warming up?
Fight like you mean it!
After that catastrophic beating
from me, you must be angry, right Cell?
You've become your perfect form,
but nothing has changed in the least.
You're just the same as you were
when you were getting beaten up!
If that bothers you,
then show me the power
of this perfect form of yours!
Well, maybe just a little bit.
When I have become
Super Vegeta, do not mock me!!
H-He connected!
W-What?
Super Vegeta, huh?
That should have connected...!
Vegeta's kick had to have connected
perfectly with Cell's vital point!
And yet, there's been no damage at all!
He really is a monster!
Trunks, aren't you going to help,
with that hidden power of yours?
Dad...
Dad would look upon being
helped by myself or Goku-san
to be much more humiliating
than being defeated by Cell.
That's just the kind of person Dad is.
B-But still...!
He'll be beaten! Vegeta will be beaten!
Before the perfect form of Cell, the
power of Super Vegeta is of no avail.
What will you do, Vegeta?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
All the fight has gone out of Vegeta.
If one of us doesn't step
in to help, he'll be killed!
Trunks, it's now or never!
Now is the time to become that
outrageous level of Super Saiyan!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Breaking Through the Boundaries of the
Super Saiyan!! Trunks Summons a Storm."
Trunks-san has begun
an incredible transformation!
"Next time"
"Breaking Through the Boundaries of the
Super Saiyan!! Trunks Summons a Storm"