Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Goku flew all around the Earth,
seeking the Dragon Balls that were
restored by Dende, the new Kami-sama.
I've got all seven together now!
And so, the day of the
Cell Games drew ever closer...
The battle begins in one hour!
"Those Who Would Challenge Cell!!
The Curtain Rises on the Battle."
All right, I guess I better go.
Be careful, Goku-sa! Don't go dyin'.
Yeah, I know.
Gohan-chan's not fightin', right?
U-Um...
Promise me you won't let Gohan-chan fight!
Well, I'm off!
Now, look here!
H-He might be fightin'... Gohan-chan...
Father!
He's here, he's here!
It's just about time.
Huh? Where's Vegeta?
He left a moment ago.
Is that right? Vegeta must be all
fired up. I bet he's improved himself.
What is it with everyone?
What are you so gloomy about?
Are you nervous?
Goku, something bad has turned up.
It's the Dragon Balls.
We had them made so that we could bring a
lot of people back to life with one wish, right?
Yeah.
By doing that, they're like they were before,
where if someone has already died
once, they can't be returned to life.
I'm sorry. I should have said so from the start.
Hey, don't let it bother you, Dende.
We're fine, as long as we don't die, right?
A-As long as we don't die? We're taking on Cell!
It's okay, it's okay.
Let's hurry and get going,
or we won't make it by 12 o'clock!
It's just about time! Come quickly, Son Goku!
Just over twenty minutes remain
until the start of the Cell Games,
which will decide the fate of the Earth!
As might be expected,
there are no spectators in the area,
perhaps for fear of being caught in the battle!
As you can see,
Cell has just been standing in
the middle of the ring, unwavering.
Our hero, Mister Satan,
who will be taking Cell down,
has not yet shown himself.
Oh, what car is this?!
Oh, it is indeed Satan!
Mister Satan has arrived!
Oh, he has turned toward the
camera, holding his fist high!
He is responding to the warm
backing of the people of the whole world!
Satan!
Oh, my! Mister Satan is
already declaring his victory!
It's just like Satan, the combat
sports champion of the world!
It looks as though, when faced
with the strongest man on earth,
not even Cell is able to conceal his anxiety!
What's with this piece of trash?
And so, only twenty minutes remain
until the start of the Cell Games!
Cell vs. Satan!
In my own personal estimation,
Satan has a slight lead on Cell!
Mister Satan, with his stately, heroic spirit,
is burning in anticipation of victory!
Oh, my! Satan is about
to enter the ring already!
There is plenty of time still
before the matches are to begin,
but he is driven!
Just what you'd expect of the
most dependable man on earth!
C-Could he be telling us to come on down?
Th-This is most... er...
V-Very well! Let's go!
We are pros as well! Let's have
everyone see just how brave we are!
B-Besides which, no matter what else,
Mister Satan is here, so we can be at ease!
P-Please take a close look at these
images, overflowing with tension!
Right now, toward the ring which will
indeed determine the fate of the world,
the most courageous announcer
in the world is approaching!
Um, should we come up into the ring as well?
I am with you. Do not worry.
V-Very well then...
Could you share with us,
Mister Satan, how you feel right now?
I have sympathy for Cell here,
whose reckoning has gone awry.
He couldn't possibly have known
that there was someone in
this world as strong as I am.
Yes, yes...
He went and talked like a bigshot,
and now, it is too late for him to
get off with just saying "I'm sorry."
Listen to me, Cell! Your secret is out!
The way you destroyed
our capital's military forces
was through using tricks involving explosives!
But that isn't going to work on me!
H-He's pretending he can't hear you.
He's so nervous, he doesn't know what to say!
In that case, let's make
contemptuous faces at him!
And I'll give him a good spanky-spanky!
It might be okay if he does get killed...
It's Yamucha-san, with Tenshinhan-san!
We're going too.
We probably won't be
joining in the fighting, however.
All right. Come on, everyone!
I'm gonna pound your head!
Mister Satan is composed!
He's overwhelming Cell with his composure!
Even before this fight has begun,
Mister Satan's victory is a foregone conclusion!
What's that...?
Is something the matter?
W-What in the world is that...?
Vegeta...
So you've come, in spite
of what happened before?
I'm sure you've improved yourself, as well.
Um... a strange man has just appeared.
I-It looked as though he
flew here, through the air...
It's a trick, all right.
Could he possibly be planning to
enter into the Cell Games as well?
Let's ask him. So, who are you?
If you've come to watch,
it's too dangerous for you to be this close.
Get lost, and don't ever talk to me again.
Oh, my...
He's nothing more than a slightly crazy person.
His hairstyle is strange, too.
Those are the kinds of guys
who make the most trouble,
by getting in the way.
And so, in five more minutes,
the Cell Games, focus of
attention for the entire world,
with the fate of the Earth
at stake, will commence!
As I expected, Mister Satan is the
only one who will be fighting Cell!
However, that is only to be expected!
Mister Satan is the all-out
combat sports champion of the world!
He alone is all that will be needed!
A-Again, it appears someone has flown in...
H-He's using a trick, too.
This is a surprise. No. 16, huh?
I'm surprised you even still exist.
What's more, your damage
has been repaired, hasn't it?
The only ones who could have repaired
that robot are Bulma and Bulma's father.
This isn't their concern...!
C-Cell just muttered something, right?
Perhaps he knows that man?
Who knows? In any case,
he doesn't look all that tough.
So, it appears you've finally come, Son Goku.
I've been waiting for this!
S-Say there, look at that...
What?
I see them! Over there!
All right, let's go!
W-Who are those guys?!
Stay out of Satan's way!
G-Gohan-chan!
C-Cut that out! Gohan! Don't fight! Gohan!
–Gohan-chan, I say! Gohan-chan!
–Chichi! Calm down! Chichi! Settle down!
Don't go fightin'! Don't die!
Don't go dyin', Gohan-chan!
Gohan-chan, stop that! Cut that out!
Welcome, all of you!
A whole slew of them came!
I-It looked as though all of them flew here...
I-It appears this trick of theirs is in vogue.
No. 16! Are you all better?
I wanted to express my gratitude.
Thanks, Kuririn. Thanks to you, I'm all fixed up.
Is that so? That's great, huh?
Let's all hang in there together, okay?
Son Goku, I was built in order to kill you.
Do not forget that.
This guy sure is grim, ain't he?
I'm not getting any attention...
Has fight started?
Not yet, it appears.
Now, then...
Maybe you should let me fight first.
We don't necessarily need you
to fight right off the bat, Goku-san.
It's okay with you, right Vegeta?
Do as you like.
Either way, I will be the
one who finishes him off.
D-Don't you go making your own order!
Um, by any chance,
were you fellows thinking of
competing in the Cell Games here?
That's right. Not all of us, though.
That's enough of your foolishness!
This is not a game!
You guys don't understand anything!
You're the one who doesn't understand.
This is a surprise.
To think that there should
still be some shameless yokels,
who don't know about me, Mister Satan,
the number one name in
the world of combat sports!
Now listen! Satan here is the
world combat sports champion!
He's the strongest man in the whole world–!
All right, then, as a special
free service, I will explain it to you.
How about that?!
I-Incredible! That's our Mister Satan! Incredible!
Th-They're not at all surprised...
Goku, it's okay, just let them go first.
F-Fine with me...
It's time!
The Cell Games, the tournament of
martial arts tactics, is about to begin.
Will Goku and the others be able to defeat Cell?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Huh? Here come some more weirdoes.
Satan's number-one and number-two pupils?
And now, two new challengers have arrived!
Caroni the Swift, and Piroshiki the Mighty!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Just a Moment!!
The Satan Squad Goes On the Rampage."
I hope those people don't get hurt.
"Next time"
"Just a Moment!!
The Satan Squad Goes On the Rampage"