Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
After Goku had defeated ReaCoom, and
then Butta, Ginyu had appeared before him.
Elsewhere, having gathered
all seven Dragon Balls together,
Freeza was speeding
toward the Grand Elder's location,
in order to learn the
password to have his wish granted.
You guys use the Dragon
Radar to locate the Dragon Balls.
Vegeta, you take care of the other one.
Now that you've recovered
from being near death,
your power should be greatly increased.
He's no longer an unbeatable opponent.
You knew about that, huh?
We're off!
Good luck, Goku!
All right, we're up, too.
This is going to be a more interesting
fight than any I've ever had before...
"Incredible Force!!
Did You See Goku's Full Power?"
Vegeta!
Your guard is down!
He got him!
Yow... Damn that Vegeta...
I see now, you're a lot better than I expected.
And having Vegeta run off on
you like that must have hurt too.
I have to end this quickly.
Otherwise, what little
hope we have will be lost.
This is a nice development. From what I saw,
Kakarrot and Ginyu both have
about the same level of ability.
If I'm lucky, the two of them
might just take care of each other.
If that happens, I can't fail!
As soon as I get the password to
have my wish granted out of those runts,
I'll take care of them, too.
Then, once I make myself immortally young,
I'll have a chance of
beating even Freeza in battle!
Gohan, no matter what it takes, we have
to borrow the Dragon Radar from Bulma-san,
and find the Dragon Balls before Freeza
gets the password from Grand Elder-san.
Right!
You certainly have
impressive speed for a Saiyan.
Ginyu Special Corps Commander, Ginyu...
...Super Fighting Pose!!
Like this?
F-Fool! Your feet are reversed! Your feet!
Oh, really?
You know, you guys all
pose in the strangest ways, huh?
I've never seen anything like it.
W-What?! Can't you grasp the
splendor of the Ultra Fighting Pose?!
It doesn't matter to me
either way, I'm running out of time.
Sorry to interrupt your big entrance,
but I have to end this right now.
Oh, aren't you the confident one?
This is the first time that I,
Ginyu-sama, have heard such insolence.
If you had dared to come off to me like that
while we were sizing each other up earlier,
I would not have hesitated
to knock you off your perch.
You see, like yourself,
I'm the type of fighter who can
change his level of battle power at will.
That's the Commander Ginyu
I know so well. He's not at all agitated.
That's no surprise, I guess.
Even if that guy's battle
power really is around 60,000,
then Commander Ginyu's
maximum fighting power is much higher.
Yikes!
Geez! What could everyone else
possibly be up to while I'm here,
struggling by myself like this?
How do I know they
haven't all forgotten about me,
and are just goofing around now?
Good grief, first my spaceship gets all broken,
and I can't go back to Earth.
Then my transmitter gets all broken.
Nothing is going right.
All right, it's fixed!
That certainly did take
up a lot of time and effort.
W-What was that just now?
A-All seven of them are in
the same place, aren't they?
I-I'll just bet they were
going to leave me behind,
while they went and made
their wish to Shen Long! All right!
But suppose the person who has
gathered the Dragon Balls is Vegeta, instead?
Not again!
W-What is it with this planet anyway?
I know! Even if it is Vegeta, I can just say,
"Send me back to Earth" first!
Hey, that's simple enough, isn't it?
With that settled, I'm off to the Dragon Balls!
Let's go!
All right...
He's fast! He might have the edge on speed!
Oh, crap!
I managed to bottle you up there pretty good!
Dammit!
Commander! He's all ours now!
Damn... he's got incredible
power! I can't get free!
Commander! You can shatter his
bones any time now, and finish him off!
I-I'm out of options! At this
point, I'll have to use Kaio-ken...
Wha–?
C-Commander!
Who asked you to help, Jheese?
If you pull anything uncalled-for
like that again, consider yourself dead!
Yes, sir.
And as for you!
You're still hiding your
true power level, even now!
Did you really think I wouldn't be able to tell?
Perhaps you were planning on saving
that energy for a battle with Freeza-sama.
Don't you dare take me so lightly!
I'm itching for a good fight, the
kind I don't get to enjoy every day,
so cut out your silly charade!
Okay, you got it. I'll show you my true power.
Very good. I doubt you'll
be able to rest in peace
if you're killed without
using all of your power.
Use that device of yours that
reads your opponent's power,
and take a good look at my rating!
I won't even need to look at my Scouter.
Your rating should only rise to around 85,000.
Kaio-ken!
90,000!
95,000!
100,000... 105,000...
106,000... 107,000...
108,000!
I-Impossible!
109,000...
110,000!
110,000! It can't be!
I-It's still going up!
Incredible, Goku!
His power continues to rise,
not knowing where to stop...
Just what is Goku's true power?
Exactly how much is it?
And what is Ginyu's true power?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Did you witness my power, Ginyu?!
1-180,000?! U-Unbelievable!
That's your true power?!
I hate to say it, but
there's no way you can beat me.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"What of the Battle's Outcome!? Freeza's
Evil Hand Closes Around the Grand Elder."
Father, Freeza has finally...!
"Next time"
"What of the Battle's Outcome!? Freeza's
Evil Hand Closes Around the Grand Elder"