Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Goku's spaceship was
racing toward Planet Namek.
Piccolo, Tenshinhan and the others
had begun their training under Kaio.
Kuririn was rushing to the Grand
Elder, under the guidance of Dende.
Elsewhere, a fierce battle between
Vegeta, burning with ambition,
and the evil minion Zarbon, was unfolding.
Ha! To think that you'd
be so helpless at this level!
You've surprised me. You have
indeed made magnificent progress.
But as a result, you have
awakened my true power,
which has been dormant for many years.
"Nothing but Goosebumps! The Handsome
Warrior Zarbon's Devilish Transformation."
What?
You say I've awakened your true power,
which has been dormant for many years?
That's correct.
That's a hilarious joke!
I will tell you why I have let my true
power lie dormant and unused before you die.
In order to display my true
power, I must transform myself.
However, my transformed
appearance is unattractive.
As someone who prefers
beauty, I cannot abide it.
But I will choose to
transform before I choose death.
Transform, you say? The way we Saiyans do?
Those who are cornered will say the
most absurd things out of desperation.
Unlike a Saiyan, I do not transform
into something larger than is needed.
My power just increases.
Overwhelmingly so!
Show me!
You need not ask.
I will show it to you, now!
W-What is this?!
My appearance isn't the
only thing that has transformed!
Don't be too terrified by my power!
Dende, aren't we to the Grand Elder's place yet?
It's a little bit farther ahead.
We have to do something while
Vegeta and that other guy are fighting.
You know, I get the feeling
that a lot of time has passed
since we landed on this planet,
but it doesn't look like the sun is
setting one bit, huh? Why is that?
The sun doesn't go down.
After all, we have three suns,
and they all come out in turn.
Then, you don't have night on your world?
No, we don't.
Well, okay...
D-Dammit!
That's my limit...
I've got to have a little rest...
Still, I've conquered this fifty-times
gravity a lot faster than I thought I would.
Looks like that duel with
Vegeta wasn't altogether useless.
I wonder if Tenshinhan and those
guys are training under Kaio-sama.
Listen to me, Goku. This is an order from Kaio.
Do not go near him.
I'm not just saying this for your own sake.
I'm saying this for the sake
of everyone on Earth, Namek,
and many other planets as well.
If you launch some shoddy
attack on Freeza and get him angry,
something terrible is going to happen.
You have to leave that guy alone.
I can't go resting now! All right!
Hold it!
Hold it! Hold it!
"Rice catch!" Get it? That was a great pun!
Hold it!
Dammit, I'm not about to lose!
No matter how you might
struggle, you cannot beat me!
Incredible! Even as far away as we
are, I can feel the ki from their battle.
My power now doesn't even compare
to what it was before I transformed!
I-It's no good...
Even after I powered up on Earth...
I'm not going to let you die easy!
Vegeta, is that all for you?
You're not showing yourself, huh?
Looks like you weren't able to
move, and now you've drowned.
You did give me a hard time,
and even forced me to take
on my loathsome transformation.
Now then, I guess I should
go report this to Freeza-sama.
Why did I come to this planet, anyhow?!
We can't get the Dragon Balls,
and our spaceship has been wrecked!
I'm surprised that you can be so calm.
It's just a little while longer. When Father
gets here, he'll manage to do something.
I hope Son-kun gets here soon.
If I'm forced to stay cooped up in a
place like this for too long, I'll go crazy!
I wonder if Kuririn-san has
found that Grand Elder person.
The ki have subsided.
The fight is over.
Which one of them won?
I don't know.
Whichever one of them won,
it's all the same. Let's hurry.
Which way? Should we just
keep going straight like this?
Um, a little more to the left.
There it is. You see that
tall rock over there, right?
T-That one, huh?
Whew, that sure was a long way.
Grand Elder-sama is inside that house.
I'm surprised it's still even here.
As conspicuous a location as this is,
it's only a matter of time
before those bad guys find it.
He hasn't already been killed, right?
He couldn't be...
Nail-san! Thank goodness! You're all right!
H-He looks exactly like Piccolo!
Glad you're here, Dende.
Visitor, Grand Elder-sama is roughly
familiar with the course of events.
Then, Grand Elder-sama
does know what is happening?
T-That will spare us the
time of explaining, then.
Both of you, come inside.
Grand Elder-sama will see you.
Um, if he already knows
what is generally going on,
why hasn't he left this unsafe location?
Grand Elder-sama has grown too aged.
He is aware that his death is approaching.
The only thing he could do is to remain
here quietly, with me here protecting him.
I had heard that his death was near,
but I didn't know it was so close.
Come, inside.
That guy is capable.
I can sense quite a bit of power from
him, compared to the other Namekians.
Up.
Right.
Grand Elder-sama, Dende and a visitor.
H-He's huge!
Welcome. You are an Earthling, correct?
First, I would like to offer my gratitude
for rescuing my child Dende here. Thank you.
N-Not at all. We didn't
do anything all that great.
That miserable Zarbon! T-This isn't over yet!
I'm going to become even stronger!
And then, I'm going to
defeat both Zarbon and Freeza!
I-I'm not about to turn over
the Dragon Balls to anyone!
Vegeta was alive.
However, the hidden power possessed
by Freeza and Zarbon was fearsome.
And after finally meeting him,
would the Grand Elder be of
any help to Kuririn and the others?
The tangled battle of good and evil
surrounding the Dragon Balls yet continues.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
This hyper-gravity training
is exhausting even me.
Goku, we got the last Dragon Ball!
Thanks to the Grand Elder, I'm
now brimming with my latent power!
Who is this "Grand Elder" guy?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Defend the Star of Hope!!
Kuririn's Astonishing Power-Up."
Father, fate is starting to turn our way.
"Next time"
"Defend the Star of Hope!!
Kuririn's Astonishing Power-Up"