The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
He is the fearsome Majin Boo,
who has destroyed as much as 80 percent
of the Earth's people and cities. However...
W-Why is it you kill people
and destroy buildings and such?
Because it's fun!
I-It won't do to have you
killing and destroying and so on!
N-No, that's fine! That's all
fine, if you find it to be fun!
You think it's wrong for me to do?
Y-Yeah, well...
Okay, I'll stop!
Y-You're not going to kill anyone any more?
Mm-hmm.
Y-You're not going to
destroy anywhere else?
Mm-hmm.
I did it!
Just as a subtle change was starting
to take place within Boo's heart...
A single bullet fired by an
idiot has chilled the mood.
"Run Away, Satan!!
An Angry Majin Boo Emerges."
W-Who did this...?
That's one down!
W-What are those imbeciles doing?!
We didn't need this!
Oh?
Y-Young master!
That guy over there together with
Majin Boo, isn't that Mister Satan?
Why would the hero Mister Satan
be together with Majin Boo?
Hmph! Is that any concern of mine?
I'll just blow them both away at once!
We will become new
heroes, in place of Satan!
Burn in hell!
Take that! I blew them to pieces!
You sure did it, young master!
This is the birth of a new hero,
who saved the Earth from Majin Boo!
H-Hey! H-He's still standing!
He's not blown to bits!
He moved! He's still alive!
D-Damn that guy!
W-Why you...!
You're gonna pay!!
You're gonna pay for this!!
W-What?!
You stupid piece-of-crap jackass!!
You're gonna...!
You're gonna...! You're gonna...!
Get the hell out of here!
Scum of the earth!
Dammit, what a cruel thing to do...
M-Majin Boo-san! He's still barely alive!
Quickly! Quickly!
How about it? Can you heal him?
If he's not dead, I can heal him.
We did it! We did it! We did it!
We did it, we did it, we did it!
We did it, we did it, we did it,
we did it, we did it, we did it!
We did it, we did it, we did it, we did it!
W-What's going on here? Why are
that blowhard and Majin Boo together?
I-It could be that we can get
through this without fighting!
But still...
The fact that he's in danger has not changed.
Great!
Bravo, bravo!
All finished!
How splendid!
I was sure to make a room for you, too.
Thank you so much!
And now, come see this.
This is your home.
How nice for you, huh?!
Okay, now, spread those legs!
One-two! One-two! One-two! One-two!
Right, one more time! One-two! One-two!
One-two! There now!
See you again next week!
I wonder if the Earth is okay
while we're here doing this...
You were just thinking if everything
is okay while we're doing this, right?
I told you at the beginning,
the power-up requires 20 hours.
Just relax and sit there.
Have you forgotten that there is
no reason why a Kaioshin would lie?
–No!
–In that case, fine.
Right.
Now then...
Is this Bulma or whoever girl a fine woman?
Your father made me a promise, you know.
Once I draw your power
out beyond your bounds,
this Bulma or whoever middle-aged woman
would let me touch her
on the boobs and behind.
Kaioshin-sama, shouldn't
you be concentrating harder?
I'm no amateur at this!
If I couldn't concentrate while doing
this little, I couldn't be a Kaioshin!
Well, how about it?
Sure, she's a downright beauty.
Th-That so? This is no time for
us to be carrying on idly, is it?
A downright beauty...
I have to hurry and power you up!
Just as you'd expect from our honorable
forefather. He's found his concentration.
Really?
With him in that manner,
everything is all right.
Yo! Is the yummy stuff done yet?
I'm finishing now, please
wait just a moment longer.
Yo-o!
Boo has the innocent nature of a little
child, huh? He won't be killing anyone now!
Thank goodness,
thank goodness, thank goodness!
Yo! Ready yet?
Yes, right now!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
It's absolutely delicious!
You'll eat with me too?
Y-Yes!
Where have you been off playing?!
We weren't off playing, we
went to Majin Boo's place.
I'm telling you that once your Fusion comes
undone, you are to return here immediately!
Piccolo-san, did you watch us?
I didn't have to watch you.
Everyone here at least knows that
after thirty minutes, you return to normal!
We don't have time right now for
you to be doing anything uncalled-for!
Do not do anything else on your own!
Shall I wash your back?
You get in with us!
It's all right for me to get in with you?
Don't be so restrained. Get in!
Right! Very well then,
if you'll pardon the intrusion...
S-S-Sorry about that!
Fun, huh?
Y-Yes, and the water is
just the right temperature.
Fun! Fun!
Fun, huh?
Y-Yes!
That bath was just right!
Er, if it is all right with you, could you
let me take a picture together with you?
Please, as a memento.
That's it! A little more like...
please, sprawl yourself out.
Like this?
Pardon me, but taking
pictures like this is in fashion!
I guess I took advantage of Boo's innocent
heart and wasn't very scrupulous about this.
I don't need this!
I've gotten hungry!
Cook something yummy for me!
He just ate a little while ago.
Okay, okay! I'll cook something right away!
Something yummy! Something yummy!
For dessert, the chocolate you brought
will be fine! They're yummy, after all!
Right!
You miserable traitor!
You pose as a champion of justice,
and then go and become Boo's underling?!
W-Why you...!
Yo! Isn't it ready yet?
Miserable traitor!
Die!!
Serves you right!
Satan...!
Boo! Don't think this is over yet!
Still alive...
U-Unbelievable! Y-You saved me!
Thank you, Boo-sama!
B-Boo-sama?
Boo-sama! Is something the matter?
Run... away... with the dog... far... away...!
Y-You'll die!
Die? What do you mean?
Hurry up!!
R-Right!
Farther awa-ay!
Right!
What is it?!
W-What's this?
T-This isn't any trick...!
As a result of Majin Boo's intense anger,
the evil portion inside him has swelled
up and sprung out as another Majin Boo!
That is to say, he has divided
into a purely evil Majin Boo,
and a naive Majin Boo.
Why you...!
P-Piccolo-san, w-what's happening?
Two Majin Boos. The Earth
may never return to normal now!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
A battle between the two Boos has begun.
The way things are going ain't good.
There's no way the first Boo can win.
The other one took most of his strength!
How can this be? That new Boo is a mass of evil!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Which One Will Win!?
A Good-and-Evil Boo-Boo Confrontation."
Ah! The first Boo got turned into chocolate!
"Next time"
"Which One Will Win!?
A Good-and-Evil Boo-Boo Confrontation"