Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Before the overwhelming
might of the Artificial Humans,
Piccolo and the others endured a total defeat.
However...
Damn those Artificial Human
bastards! Toy with me, will they?!
They're going to regret turning me,
Vegeta-sama, back without finishing the job!
I am a demon clansman! Don't you ever forget–
I'm just using you to
help me take over the world!
I think he's lying about taking over the world.
I'm sure Piccolo...
...has gone to become his
original self with Kami-sama,
thereby becoming a Super Namekian.
The time when Piccolo and
Kami-sama reunite has finally come.
"Walking Weapons of Mass Destruction!!
The Artificial Humans Draw Near Goku."
K-Kami-sama...
You must know why it is I've come to this place.
Yes, I know.
Originally, me and you–or more accurately,
your father–were a single person.
I imagine I understand
what it is you are thinking.
In that case, I won't waste my breath.
Quite honestly, I did not
think the day would come...
...that our destinies should come together again.
We won't be fusing together.
You will serve only as the means
for a super power-up for Piccolo.
The only justification you have for your
existence any more are the Dragon Balls!
I-It can't be!
Your words... are true indeed.
Before I had realized it,
you had opened up a great
difference between our powers.
As you faced one great
opponent after another,
my powers were becoming all but inadequate.
K-Kami-sama, that not true!
Kami-sama has duty as Kami-sama!
It's quite all right, Mister Popo.
Even Trunks, who was able to bury
Freeza and his father in a moment's time.
As well as Trunks' father Vegeta, possessed
of an even greater ability than Trunks...
...were brought to such a terrible
state by the Artificial Humans.
Even when Son Goku
recovers from his affliction,
he will likely meet with similar results.
It appears the time for Kami and Daimao...
...to become one again has come after all.
That's right. What the Earth
needs right now is not a Kami,
it's me, coupled with the super
power I need to defeat those guys.
Provided that... we observe
events for a short while longer.
What's that–? Observe?!
Correct. To determine whether or not
those three will bring harm to the Earth.
How can you say such a leisurely thing?!
After the way they–
You were the ones who picked that fight!
Besides which, they did
not attempt to kill any of you.
You disgust me.
While you were up here,
looking on at the world from afar,
did you not hear what Trunks came to say?
He told us that the future
lies in ruins because of them!
I also heard that the future
Artificial Humans that Trunks knows...
...are somewhat different from
these current Artificial Humans.
I don't suppose you're thinking that
these guys might actually be little darlings?
I'm not saying anything of the sort.
But if this is to be the last
judgment I make as myself,
then I would like a
conclusive reason to proceed.
You worthless coward!
Fine, very well then.
I'll be waiting right here.
Waiting until the irrevocable happens,
and you finally make up your mind.
Hey, Kuririn!
I'm going to go pick up
Chaozu and continue our training.
You are?
If the situation gets
bad once again, I'll be back.
Not that I think it'll help, but anything I can do...
Gotcha. We'll take Goku and move
him to where Muten Roshi-sama is.
We should be able to buy
him quite a bit of time there.
Tell Goku for me not to overdo it.
Don't overdo it. He's right, you know.
This time, not even Goku has a chance.
How could history be
turning out this differently?
The Artificial Humans weren't
supposed to be this incredibly powerful.
And there were only
supposed to be two of them.
How should I know why?
At any rate, this time around, this is the reality.
Here, Goku-sa...
A car! We finally found one.
We're fine! Why don't we just keep on flying?
There's no reason for us
to hurry. We have the time.
Well, well...
You're just pulling my leg.
No, it's true. I was shocked.
These packages are in the way.
Hey, you! What do you think you're doing?!
Well then, we're off.
First stop, Son Goku's home.
Before that, I said I wanted some new clothes.
All right, all right.
What am I, dreaming?
Could be.
Damn it all!
Think I'm going to let this go?
No! This isn't over until I make
you Artificial Humans realize...
...that I am the strongest warrior in the universe!
Hey, what have we here?!
Hey, boss! There's a girl up here!
Hey there, cutie!
Ride along with us, and
we'll have ourselves some fun!
You heard the man.
Well, maybe we will have a little fun.
They've got a lot of guts to challenge
the Invincible Lords of the Highway!
Let's get them!
Scum! You won't make a fool out of me!
Say, No. 17, how'd you like
to try some of their clothes?
Stop kidding around!
Those ridiculous outfits?!
Thought so.
Damn you!
So, they're finally giving up?!
What?! You want some of this?!
The cops! Guess you guys get to live!
Stay where you are!
Don't make any funny moves!
There's no mistake!
This is the stolen vehicle, all right!
Okay, then.
We're taking you in for questioning.
Hey, you, get out! Come out of there!
Don't try anything!
Why you! Are you resisting?!
He calls that resisting.
You know what, Officer?
If you want to see someone resisting...
Hey, hold it! What are you doing?
Doing something like this...
...is called resisting.
Shall we go?
There it is! That's Goku's home!
Say, can I ask you something?
T-Those Artificial Humans... You're
sure they're all rotten to the core?
They're unbelievably cold-blooded.
At least they are in my era. Why do you ask?
Oh, yeah, well, I was just thinking,
it'd be great for us, you know, if they weren't...
I think you're better off not
entertaining such dubious hopes.
Y-Yeah, of course, you're right.
I was just thinking, that's all.
See ya!
Gohan-chan?!
Oh, it's Kuririn-san.
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Nice to see you.
It's Goku's wife.
N-Nice to meet you.
Kuririn! You're all right!
Thank goodness, we've been worried!
How's Goku?!
He's okay. He took the
medicine and he's sleeping now.
You're the one from the future...
I get it! You beat the
Artificial Humans for us, right?
N-No.
I'll fill you in on everything later.
Right now, we have to hurry and
move to Muten Roshi's place. All of us.
What?
There are three new, even
more terrifying Artiicial Humans,
and they'll be here any time.
T-This is terrible.
Gently, now! Gently!
So these new Artificial
Humans are all that strong, then?
Yeah. And "strong" just doesn't cover it.
Now we just have to wait for Gohan.
He took Bulma home, right?
He's back!
Gohan-chan!
Huh?
Why is everyone here?
Thank goodness! Thank
goodness you came back unhurt!
H-Has something happened?
I'll tell you later, hurry and get in the plane.
For the time being, a temporary
evacuation has been accomplished.
However, even then, the sound of a new mystery...
...was about to make itself known to Bulma...
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Guys, I'm sorry I'm worrying you,
but my heart is getting much better.
What did you say, Bulma-san?!
Another time machine,
just like mine, has been discovered?!
Who in the world could have come here in it?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"An Ominous Foreboding!
Bulma Unveils a Mystery."
What could have happened in the future?
"Next time"
"An Ominous Foreboding!
Bulma Unveils a Mystery"