Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
So then, I will hold a martial arts tournament.
A martial arts tournament?
In the past, there was a martial arts tournament,
called the Tenkaichi Tournament.
I'm saying I'm going to hold one again for you!
After word from Cell that he
would hold a martial arts tournament,
Kuririn and the others grew restless.
To accommodate them,
Cell carried out step-by-step
his preparations for the martial arts tournament.
It is a bit plain, but I'll think of something later.
Now then, how about I head
over to the television station?
"100% Ratings!! The Cell Games Call for
Death with an Exclusive Live Broadcast."
Oh? Hmm?
That's odd... I don't get this...
Apparently, your construction
is completely different
from these human-based Artificial Humans.
I am completely machine based,
and was built from nothing.
Which would mean... this
won't serve as any reference, huh?
Then, you cannot repair me?
Hey, don't you worry.
Once Bulma gets back, we'll manage something.
Bulma knows more about you guys than I do.
This cake truly is tasty!
Isn't it, though?
There's still plenty more, so
partake of as much as you like!
I'll take that huge choco crème one this time!
Hey, I had my eye on that one!
Me first!
The early bird gets the worm, you know! Nyah!
That goes for me too!
Enough! Stop poking around,
you're getting everything dirty!
–Hey now, this is mine here!
–I-I really have to separate
Gohan-chan from the likes of them soon!
Oh, my! I'm so pleased that
you're enjoying eating it so much!
I still have plenty more, if you like...
–Hey, that's mine!
–I called this one already!
Good grief, Oolong and the
others are so easygoing right now.
Yeah...
–Stop it! Old guys like you
shouldn't have so many sweets!
–You just shut up!
Damn. What is Cell dallying around for?
If you're going to show up,
then hurry and show up!
Trunks, he really told you he'd let
us know the details via television?
Yes, I'm sure of it.
Yamucha-sama!
Pu-erh, once Cell appears on the TV, let me know.
I'm going outside to work out.
Right, Yamucha-sama!
There are only nine more days
until Cell holds his tournament.
I can't let even a second go by wasted.
That's the way it is, all right.
Yamucha-san, let me come with you.
Thank you, Kuririn.
Not at all!
In a tournament where there
are rules, there won't be any dying.
It's been a while since
I could show off what I've got!
Lately, I haven't been
called on for anything, after all.
And you guys won't be called on this time either.
As long as I'm there, it will be enough.
I'm not going to allow Kakarrot,
or anyone else to get in my way!
You've got a big mouth for someone
who got beaten to a pulp by Cell, don't you?
What was that?
Once I go train in the Room
of Spirit and Time another day,
I'll settle everything!
There won't be any place for scum like you!
Scum, you say?
I call you scum only because you are scum.
Dad!
Trunks! Trunks!
Trunks!
What's this, you're alive and kicking, aren't you?
I heard from Piccolo that you'd
gotten away without being killed,
but I came flying back,
worried that you'd been terribly hurt!
I'm quite sorry about that.
Indeed! You shouldn't worry your mother like that!
I'm sorry for making you worry so.
Mom...
H-Hey, now! Let go!
C-Come on, now! Let go!
Trunks can't bear to tear himself away from Trunks!
–Come on!
–My, is that boy also named Trunks-chan?
What a coincidence!
Come on, let me go, Trunks!
Come on, let me go. Come on...
Where are you doing the
programs that are being broadcast
all over the Earth?
O-On the top floor, S-Studio B...
Thanks, miss.
Yamucha-sama slipped on
Kuririn-san's smooth head!
Kuririn! You can use
that head against Cell, too!
Yamucha-san, please don't make fun of me like that!
Still, that head of yours is quite slick.
You could have that
slipperiness as a secret technique!
M-Maybe I'll go over to Cell's side!
Here comes!
What are those two doing?
Are they going to be able to beat Cell like that?
This is tops!
Pafu-pafu, pafu-pafu...
You are the biggest dirty old man!
This is the program he likes the most.
It sure is!
A-wiggle-waggle! That's nice, nice, nice!
Cell!
Yamucha-sama! It's Cell! Cell showed up!
Miserable Cell!
And now, up next, world news.
W-Who are you?!
What are you doing?
Is this the top floor, Studio B?
T-That's right. C-Call the guard!
I will go beyond!
I will go beyond Super Saiyan!
Gohan?!
Gohan!
Gohan-chan! Gohan-chan!
Mother, what are you doing here?
I don't need a reason to be here!
How long are you plannin' on stayin'
in here without doin' any studyin'?!
But, Mother...
You're goin' to be a
great scholar in the future!
But if you do nothin' but trainin',
then instead of bein' a scholar,
you're goin' to become
a delinquent like Piccolo!
Mother, Piccolo-san isn't a delinquent...
Delinquent! Delinquent!
Absolutely he's a delinquent! Delinquent!
Piccolo's a delinquent!!
Sorry, Gohan...
I had stopped her, but she forced her way in.
Goku-sa!
Goku-sa!!
I get it. He's hidin' somewhere, huh?
You haven't even been makin'
Gohan-chan do a little bit of studyin',
and now you're feelin'
guilty and won't come out, huh?
Goku-sa?
Cell, is it?!
M-Mother...
Piccolo-san!
Gohan... Gohan... Gohan!
What's wrong? Get a hold of yourself!
Mother! Piccolo-san!
Did you have some kind of bad dream?
Dream?
It's down quite a bit.
You had an incredibly high fever,
and for the last two days,
you've done nothing but sleep!
Sorry.
It ain't something to apologize for.
Lately we've had nothing
but continuous harsh training,
so it couldn't be helped.
Okay, get some more sleep now.
And then, once I get up,
there's more training, right?
Of course there is!
Training is strict business!
You don't like it?
Don't be silly.
This time for sure,
I have to protect Mother and
Piccolo-san from that Cell guy...
Good morning, ladies
and gentlemen of the world.
Now, for just a moment,
I have decided to intrude into your television.
As it happens, I have brought wonderful
news to you ladies and gentlemen,
as you enjoy living your lives in peace.
News that will allow you to live out
your days filled with even more fun,
and even more thrills.
My name is Cell.
Ladies and gentlemen, I'm certain you are well aware
of the incidents where many people have
been wiped out by a monster every day.
I am that monster, having evolved and transformed.
For contributing so much life
energy to me then, I thank you.
You may be at ease. I no longer
have the need for such life energy.
I have decided to hold a martial
arts tournament, called the Cell Games.
The location will be due northwest
of the metropolis, at 28-KS-5.
I have prepared a ring there.
It will be different from the Tenkaichi Tournament,
in that if the warriors representing you,
ladies and gentlemen, are to lose,
then the next warrior will take their place.
This gives you the advantage.
Even as great as I am,
if I go through too many matches,
I may become tired, after all.
The rules will be just about the
same as in the Tenkaichi Tournament.
If you concede, or if any part of your
body touches outside the ring, you lose.
And, although it is my intent to hold back,
if you are killed, it too constitutes a loss.
In the event that all representative
warriors are defeated by me...
What?
...I have decided to kill
every last person in the world.
I will gaze upon the looks of terror on your faces,
acting thoroughly, sparing not a single one of you.
That rotten Cell!
And with that, I would like many of you
who are sure of your strength to come participate.
If you don't want things to end up like this, that is.
And so, I will be looking forward to this.
T-That guy is despicable!
H-He said he would kill
every person in the world!
What power! I was too hopeful,
thinking that we wouldn't
get killed because of the rules.
Yamucha-sama!
Who could possibly fight against a guy like that?
Even Vegeta and Trunks
were no good against him!
And as for Goku...
Are you going somewhere, Vegeta?
I don't care how many Earthlings may die,
but I won't be content if I don't kill that scumbag.
I'll go as well!
Trunks, before you go, I'll cut your hair for you.
It must be a nuisance, right?
Thank you for your trouble.
Cell's announcement quickly
spreads terror throughout the world.
Further, it is clear to everyone's
eyes that, in a peaceful world,
he is a foe that the weakened
military and police forces
are powerless against.
The people had forgotten that long ago,
there was a small boy who
fought against Piccolo Daimao.
What's more, the people were
unaware that there was a warrior
who fought against Vegeta and
the Saiyans, as well as Freeza...
Unaware of the existence of Son Goku.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Sorry to keep you waiting, everyone.
Our training is finally done.
It sure is a relief out here, huh?
Gohan, I hardly recognized you!
So, how about it, Goku?
Do you think you can beat Cell?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Goku and Gohan... The Hero
Father and Son's Ultimate Level-Up."
My training is over; I wonder if
I'll have to start studying again.
"Next time"
"Goku and Gohan... The Hero
Father and Son's Ultimate Level-Up"