Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
It isn't dead, it's a shell that's been cast-off.
This is probably from whatever came
out of the egg back in the time machine.
It must have started
growing, and then shed its skin.
Whatever came out of here,
it must have just barely happened.
A strange egg is discovered
inside the deteriorated time machine,
as well as the discarded
carapace of a mysterious life form.
Very shortly, something awful
is going to happen on Earth.
And yet, it won't be the same kind of
crisis that has occurred so many times before.
"To Face an Unprecedented Foe...
Birth of a Super Namekian!!"
Trunks-san...
Trunks-san?!
Er, yes?
What do you suppose that
strange shedding was, anyhow?
I-I don't know.
For one thing, we don't have
creatures like that in my era, either.
You said it came back a whole
year earlier than the time you arrived
three years ago,
which makes it a full four years
ago that it arrived in this era, right?
Yeah.
That's what the chronometer
inside the time machine indicated.
So without anyone realizing it,
a creature that came from a
good 23 years into the future...
...has been growing and developing
on our earth for the last four years.
Yeah.
Who could possibly have sent
that creature, and for what purpose?
These are the best clothes the store has?
Yes, quite so.
They look very flattering on you.
How do you like them?
How do you think I like them?
They're the absolute worst.
But considering how rural this place is,
I guess I'll have to make do for now.
See you.
E-Excuse me, ma'am, you haven't paid!
Hey!
Hey now, see here!
How... frightful!
Hello, is this the police?
My store has been robbed!
T-They drove away in...
It's the police again.
They're sure starting to get bothersome.
Don't you find this a little
painful to just be dreaming?
We interrupt this program to
bring you this late breaking news.
About an hour ago,
we took a number of calls from
Gingertown, a suburban area of Metro West.
We immediately dispatched
an investigate crew to the scene,
but according to their report,
the town's citizens seem to
have all suddenly vanished,
and there is no sign of anyone.
Gingertown?
The cause for this unexpected state of affairs
is currently under investigation, as we...
That's near where that other time machine was!
C-Can it be?
Yes, hello?
Hello? It's Bulma. Who's this? Kuririn?
Yes, it's Kuririn.
Gohan and Trunks?
No, they haven't come back yet.
Okay, turn on your TV there.
It's probably on every channel by now,
but I'm watching it on channel 872.
Has something happened?
Just hurry!
What's the matter? Who is it?
It's Bulma-san. She wants us to watch TV.
What is she telling us to watch?
Knowing Bulma, she's probably on right now.
Could be.
We've just received some new information.
According to the investigation
of our on-the-scene crew,
the clothing of the apparent
victims of this incident
is being discovered in great numbers.
Our camera crew has just arrived in the area,
so let's go there for a live update.
W-What could this be?
I've just arrived here in Gingertown,
where over 15,000 residents
have suddenly vanished.
We have just made a new discovery.
15,000 people...
There are many sets of clothing here.
It appears as if the people
inside them simply melted away.
As you can see in these images,
from the outlay of the clothing
and the presence of the rifles,
it appears they were
fighting against something...
W-What's this?
T-The Artificial Humans!
So, they've finally started!
I don't think so.
And I think that Gohan-kun
and Trunks will say the same thing.
Which means,
you think there might be some
kind of link to the other time machine?
I don't think there can be any doubt.
When Gohan-kun and Trunks get
there, have them tell you everything.
Right.
Goku-sa's sleepin' tight now.
He seems to be restin'
a lot easier than before.
Muten Roshi-sama!
Forgive the intrusion.
Uh, Kuririn-san?
G-Guys, come watch this news,
then answer me a question–
News?
What's this?
We heard a scream just a moment ago.
Gunfire! We're hearing gunfire.
It appears that the investigative team
or the police in this direction are agitated!
It's become quiet once again.
We're going to move in
as close as we can to see–
What is it?!
What is happening?! Come on!!
K-Kami-sama!
W-What is it? What is that monster?
Did you say monster?
What do you mean, monster?! Say something!!
What?
Change it to a different channel!
Right.
Help us!
The screaming has stopped.
Enough already!
Stop keeping it all to yourself!
You're going to tell me exactly what you saw.
Hey!!
V-Very well.
All right, start talking.
What kind of monster did
you see in the lower realm?
There's no need for me to bother speaking.
What's that?
Once you and I merge and become
one being, you'll know what it is I saw.
K-Kami-sama!
So, you've finally made up your mind, then?
You must have seen some
kind of monster, all right.
Let's hurry this up.
We cannot allow there to be any more victims.
All right!
We will be fundamentally
based on who I am now, got that?
That will be fine.
You are much younger than I,
and have a far greater power.
It is a matter of course.
I serve as nothing more
than a means to power up,
and to contribute my vast wisdom.
Now, since you are to be the base,
you will place your hand upon me.
Right.
K-Kami-sama!
The time is upon us, Mister Popo.
Right now what the Earth needs is not a Kami...
...but rather, the mighty.
Piccolo has changed.
The evil in his heart has mostly disappeared.
Once we merge, it is unlikely
we will ever need to divide again.
Thank you for all your help, Mister Popo.
K-Kami-sama!
F-Farewell, Kami-sama. Don't die.
I am neither Kami nor Piccolo any longer.
I'm a Namekian who has long
since forgotten his real name.
So then, I'm off.
We have received no
further reports from the scene.
In all likelihood, our own staff members
have become victims of this same incident.
So, you think it's because of whatever
monster came out of that shell, then?
Yeah, probably.
That's what I think.
The locations are pretty close, and all.
I'm going to go make sure.
Whoa!
Hold it!
It's okay.
I can become a Super Saiyan.
The ones we should really be
fearful of are the Artificial Humans.
M-Maybe so, but...
I-I'm going too!
You can't go!
Goku-sa is still sleepin' up there!
Why can't you behave a little better?!
Mother, it's exactly
because Father is sick that I...
No way!
Even if the whole universe is
blowin' up, you'll stay at my side!
You mean...?
I'll go by myself.
Gohan-san, if anything happens,
you and the others have to be here,
to protect Goku-san from the Artificial Humans.
Right. Very well.
Hey, don't do anything crazy.
If it gets dangerous,
come back here quick, okay?
Yeah, he's right.
You're an important part of our resistance force
against the Artificial Humans!
Right. Now then, I'll be back.
So, you've shown yourself, you beast.
The mysterious monster finally reveals himself.
The world slips into a state of
hopelessness previously unknown.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Hmm? That ki is Freeza's...
What's more, Vegeta's and
Piccolo's are also all combined into one.
What on earth is going on?
What exactly are you, monster?
You're going to tell me everything,
even if I have to use force!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Kamehame-Ha!?
The Monster Who Possesses Goku's Ki."
I can't believe I'm sensing
Father's ki from that thing!
"Next time"
"Kamehame-Ha!?
The Monster Who Possesses Goku's Ki"