The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Gohan has at length pulled out the Z-Sword,
the legendary blade of the Kaioshin Realm,
said to be able to defeat even Majin Boo.
On Earth, as part of Babidi's plan
to call out Piccolo and the others,
Majin Boo continued over and over
to turn people into candy and eat them.
Let's do this Fusion training properly!
To defeat Majin Boo,
Goten and Trunks have decided to
master the Fusion merging technique.
"Metro West is Targeted!
Stop, Majin Boo!!"
Okay, there ain't much time!
Goten, Trunks, let's begin!
Hm? What's wrong?
So, is this Fusion thing
really an awesome technique?
You'll see once you try it!
Somehow I don't expect
much from this old guy.
I mean, he was unconscious
as Papa was getting killed!
Quickly, both of you become Super Saiyan!
O-Okay.
All right. Now, raise
your ki to their upper limits!
Full-blast, now.
Okay, let's surprise them, Goten!
Yeah!
W-What?
What's this?
These ki... Goten and Trunks? Incredible!
Naturally! He's Vegeta's son, after all!
Those kids could do it. Fusion.
Yes.
Ho, when did they get as strong as this?
All right, that's full-on, right?
Y-Yeah...
Trunks, your ki is just a little bit larger.
For you to do Fusion, you have to
completely match your ki together.
Trunks, hold your ki down just a little bit
and make it the same as Goten's.
Th-The same?
About like this?
That's too small.
Raise it a little more...
a little more... a little more...
Stop! That's it! Remember
the size of that ki well.
Okay, go back to normal.
That sure is hard.
Why is it that I'm the one
who has to match up with Goten?
Sorry, Trunks-kun.
It can't be helped, you know. Don't complain,
you're a whole year older than Goten, right?
Hold on there, Son-kun!
I heard that just now!
Don't you go doing
anything to stunt Trunks' talents!
Bulma-san!
Out of my way!
You can't interfere in their training!
Let go of me!
Look, just leave this up to Goku and Piccolo!
What are you doing?!
Good grief!
Put me down! Kuririn!
Kuririn!
Let Goku handle this!
Yeah, I know!
I just wanted to take a
second to say that! Indeed!
Trunks-kun, I'm going to try hard,
so let's do it one more time!
Hm? Okay.
Fusion, huh? If it were me and Goku...
Kuririn, that's too big! Match up with Goku!
Goku! Hurry and become more like me!
Well, who's to say that
wouldn't have happened?
That's right! The only one left that
can protect the Earth is me, Satan!
I don't mean saving little fish,
and I don't mean saving big fish!
I'm here to save the Earth,
where all of you live!
You'll see, I will surely save us
from the hands of Majin Boo!!
This I now swear to you!
–Way to go, Satan!
–We're counting on you!
Good luck!
And now, ladies and gentlemen,
I now return to my harsh, bitter training!
However, I will endure any
training, no matter how harsh!
And so, briefly, until we meet again,
ladies and gentlemen, farewell!
Satan! Satan! Satan!
That went over so well it scares me.
But you know, if Majin Boo were to
come while I'm in the middle of training,
I'm screwed.
I won't be able to
teach them any lessons.
But, since I'm in training, there's
nothing I'll be able to do about it.
–I'll get him!
–Satan! Satan! Satan!
The terrible Majin Boo
threatens to destroy the Earth!
And yet, where are Ma Junior,
Trunks, and Son Goten,
whom Majin Boo and Babidi seek,
and what are they doing?
This isn't any laughing matter!
If they don't show themselves quickly,
it'll mean trouble for us!
Trunks?
Trunks! Knock a hole in his
dumb-looking face right away!
It couldn't be! Not that hateful little brat!
I don't want to die over that brat!
I have to hurry and tell where he lives!
Mama, I'm sure his house is in Metro West!
Really?
Yep.
Okay then. Idasa-chan, Ikose-chan, listen up.
Everyone concentrate together.
Where shall we go now?
Babidi! Babidi! Can you hear me?
What's this?
Trunks lives at the Capsule
Corporation in Metro West.
I want you to quickly go and
put him to some terrible fate!
Who is this?
Me? I'm on the board of the PTA.
I don't usually tattle on people like this,
but that uncouth, snotty little turd
cheated during his matches earlier today.
In those matches, both Idasa-chan
and Ikose-chan were running fevers,
and not in their best condition.
Otherwise, there's no way my refined
sons would have lost to those brats!
Shut up! I'm grateful for your information,
but just you try talking to me
in that shrill voice of yours again!
I'll kill you!
Well, I never! And after I told
him everything! How dreadful!
Okay, next, raise your ki all the
way to the top in your regular forms.
Starting out with Fusion as
Super Saiyans is pretty hard, after all.
People of Earth!
I just received some significant information.
It seems that one of those three urchins, Trunks,
lives in a house called the
Capsule Corporation, in Metro West.
Perhaps we should go and see him.
You'd better come on out!
Otherwise, the city where
you live will cease to exist!
Damn! Who ratted me out?
Grandpa and Grandma are still at home!
Trunks-kun...
Son-kun, did you hear that just now?
Papa and Mama are going to be killed!
It's okay, we can bring them
back to life with the Dragon Balls.
Metro West is also going to be destroyed!
We can return that to
normal too, with the second wish.
No, we can't.
After using the first wish to bring a
large number of people back to life,
only one more wish will remain.
Now that you mention it, that's right.
In that case, you could just tell Shen Long
to "Return everything back the way
it was" or something, couldn't you?
There you go.
Yeah? How about that?
No, wait! I'm not sure
things would go too smoothly.
Son-kun, it really will be
bad if Metro West is destroyed!
The Dragon Radar will also be lost!
That is a problem.
Okay. Trunks, you return
home as fast as you can,
get the Radar, and bring it back for us!
I will delay Majin Boo
and Babidi for a little while.
W-Will you be all right?
Uncle, can you delay them?
Won't you get beaten right away?
Well, if it's just for a little while,
I can manage something.
Never mind me, hurry! Or else
they'll reach Metro West first!
Trunks, be careful! If it gets
dangerous, come right back here!
Okay!
Trunks-kun, good luck!
Got it!
Is everything really going to be all right?
Oh well.
All right, time to fly!
Trunks is going to come
back safely. Don't worry, Bulma.
But still...
He'll be okay, I said.
He's your and Vegeta's son, after all.
Son-kun...
Now then, where are those two?
Goten, just sit tight for a bit, okay?
Right!
That's a good boy.
Okay, there they are.
Hey, see here! You're flying too fast!
I'm almost falling off, you know! You moron!
Idiot! Don't get sidetracked, go to Metro West!
Why did you suddenly stop?!
Yo!
You!
So that's it. Here I thought
you'd been killed by Vegeta,
but you're still alive, huh?
You know, I have to thank you.
As you can see, thanks to you,
Majin Boo has returned!
Both Vegeta and I looked
too lightly upon you.
How could we have known that
Majin Boo would be this awesome?
We didn't think this could be possible.
Of course he is! My Papa made him, you know!
So, what is it? Why have you come here?
I know, you've come to
tell me where those three are!
You can't mean that.
One of the three is my own son.
I just came to give you a warning.
Warning? A warning, you say?
To us? This is most amusing.
I know, why don't I let
everyone on Earth hear this.
Listen here, those three are definitely
going to show themselves in the near future.
I promise.
So just wait until then!
Stop the unnecessary destruction
and picking on the weak!
Why should we wait?
Are they planning something?
Yeah. They're in special
training in order to defeat you.
To defeat us, you say?!
They could train for a thousand
years and nothing would come of it!
Sure about that?
You expect us to wait for that?
They can come here right now!
Otherwise, we keep killing Earthlings!
After all, we're enjoying
these acts of destruction!
I'll bet. That's what I thought you'd say.
Well then, you'll have to let
me oppose you for just a little bit.
Interesting! Boo, show him
just how terrifying you are!
He seems to want to
die just as Vegeta did!
What's wrong?
Why, you...
Hey, Majin Boo! What are
you doing?! Go, get him!
Come on, show him
your power! Hey! Come on!
Okay, okay.
What's wrong with you?
You're that strong, yet you're
still under Babidi's thumb?
Majin Boo! Quiet, you!
Don't go saying anything funny!
Majin Boo is my servant!
Of course he listens to what I tell him to do!
W-What? Do you want me to use
the spell and seal you up again?
If you seal me up, you're
gonna be killed by him!
W-Why you, when did you come
by such uncalled-for wisdom?
But I'll kill him for you.
I hate him for acting goody-goody.
Sheesh, guess there's nothing left to do.
How should I kill you?
Watch very closely, Earthlings!
We're about to show you what happens
to any fool that tries to go against us!
Here goes!
Is this... Father's ki?!
That's right! Your father is one incredible guy!
I-It can't be...
Th-That old guy and Papa have
about the same amount of power!
Awesome!
Useless! Useless!
Vegeta did that, and he still got killed!
Well, shall I see about going
once more beyond a Super Saiyan
that's gone beyond Super Saiyan?
Go even beyond Super-whatever
that's gone beyond Super-whatever?
Goku... What are you talking about?
What's this? Go beyond even a Super
Saiyan that's gone beyond Super Saiyan?
Can Goku obstruct Majin Boo
until Trunks reaches Metro West?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Majin Boo, Babidi, this is the
transformation beyond Super Saiyan
that's already gone beyond
Super Saiyan, Super Saiyan 3!
Stop, Goku! If you do that,
your remaining time on earth will disappear!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"An Astounding, Great Transformation!!
Super Saiyan 3."
F-Father, that is some
unbelievably incredible power!
"Next time"
"An Astounding, Great Transformation!!
Super Saiyan 3"