Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Goku and Gohan were living
life in their Super Saiyan state.
Unable to control their ki, they
made a mess of the inside of the house!
"Happy Birthday"
As the days leisurely went by,
their family ties grew deeper.
However, the fated day of the
Cell Games was drawing ever closer.
"Seek Out Kami-sama!!
Goku's Great Instantaneous Movement."
Sheesh! What are you
dragging this out for, scum?!
Or have you gone and
kicked the bucket in there?!
S-Still time before 24 hours up.
Dammit!
Just you try going even one second over!
I'll drag you out of there, even if
I have to knock down the door to do it!
Ah! He's coming out!
Hmph! So you've finally come out, huh?
Now then, it's my turn.
Piccolo-san's power has risen exceptionally!
What's with you? You haven't changed at all.
What were you, napping or something?
Just you watch, Kakarrot!
I will surpass you! Count on it!
Everyone throughout the world,
our Royal Defense Force is determined...
...to use all of its power to put a halt
to the monster that calls itself Cell.
Please, do not panic, but rather wait calmly–
There's no way an army can
win against him, don't you know?
All we can do is rely on
Son-kun and the others.
You know, this really is incredible.
I was surprised just by you
having an even greater superpower
than No. 17 and No. 18,
but you even have a device that can detect ki.
What's more, I have absolutely
no idea what it's made of.
Oh, there's one, there's one! See there?
There are some huge fish in this lake!
S-Say, Father?
Are you sure it's okay for
us to be taking it so easy?
Indeed! What are you so relaxed for?
Don't worry, I tell you!
Something will turn up, most likely.
M-Most likely?
It's all right, we can win!
I told you, didn't I,
that there ain't any meaning for us to
train any harder than we already have?
We've gone right up to our limits.
R-Right...
Well, Goku, if you're the one who says so,
I guess we'll just have to believe it.
You guys! Our lunches are ready!
Oh? Thank you!
Now then, don't worry about it,
just take it easy, and let's enjoy ourselves!
It sure looks good!
Still and all, I wouldn't have expected this.
Goku, when did you get your driver's license?
You know what?
It was three years ago, together with Piccolo.
W-With Piccolo...?
Yup! But you know what?
The two of them were really wild,
and they upset their instructors.
At first, they didn't pass.
I-I think I get the idea.
But you know what?
I pleaded as hard as
I could to the instructors, right?
And he finally got it!
So, what about the written exam?
I stayed up all night
drillin' Goku-sa on it.
I should have known!
And as a result,
it's so nice that we can have
Goku-sa take us out for a drive like this!
I'm so happy about it!
It's almost like I'm havin' a dream!
Goku-sa, you really
are one sharp husband!
I know!
Let's stop off at Muten Roshi-sama's
place on our way home!
Yeah.
Hey! What's taking so long?! I'll flatten you!
Shut your trap,
or you're gonna get eaten by Cell!
That's one incredible traffic jam.
Everyone's runnin' away from the cities.
You can't blame them.
You'd have to think that the
rural areas would be safer, after all.
That could be it, I guess.
None of the stores are open, huh?
Everyone is closed.
That's what happens when you
might die in another seven days.
Nobody's gonna work.
Aw, this makes shoppin'
for anything impossible!
And here I wanted to buy a present
to take to Old Man Turtle Hermit.
We interrupt this program
for a special news bulletin.
Oh, there's someone who's working!
In order to defeat the
monster who calls himself Cell,
the Royal Defense Force
is heading to 28-KS Mark 5.
It appears that the
attack is just about to begin.
What?!
Ladies and gentleman, please observe.
This is the vast army of
the Royal Defense Force,
with all of its power concentrated together!
No matter how great a monster he may be,
I doubt there is anything
he can do against this force!
D-Did he say army?
Idiots! What are they thinking?
Don't they know they're
just going to get killed in vain?!
My, my... has the army of fools arrived?
Prepare to attack!
H-He's running away!
Idiot. I just don't want the ring
I went to such trouble to make to get destroyed.
Don't let him get away!
Fire! Begin an all-out attack!
An incredible barrage has begun!
Listen to the sound of that!
I-It's a tremendous assault!
It's still... still going on!
After taking this kind of attack directly,
there can scarcely be
any hide or hair of him left!
G-Get out of there...! Hurry!
All right! Cease fire!
Stop! That's enough!
Stop shooting!
How's that? Serves you right!
I-It can't be...!
I-Impossible...
He's still alive! He's a monster!
The foolish must be given their punishment.
U-Unbelievable! He's still alive!
C-Cell appears to be completely unaffected!
S-Stop! Cell, don't kill them!
Stop!!
D-Damn it all...!
That did at least kill some time.
Sorry about this, but you
all go on ahead without me.
I have to go see Piccolo about something.
S-Say, what could he have to see Piccolo about?
Beats me...
Goku!
Huh? Piccolo,
by any chance, did you go into
the Room of Spirit and Time too?
That's right.
I knew it! I can tell, the way
your very level has increased.
How about being candid with me?
I may have become stronger,
but it still won't be of
any use against Cell, right?
Nope. It's no use, all right.
You really do put it candidly.
So, what have you come here for?
Tell me, can you split into two again,
like how you were before
you merged with Kami-sama?
What?
See, when Kami-sama
and Piccolo merged together,
the Dragon Balls disappeared, right?
There are a lot of people who Cell has killed
that somehow need to be brought back to life,
and I think that we're going
to need them after this, as well.
I get you. But unfortunately, it's not possible.
Once we've united together,
we can never become a pair again.
Otherwise, Kami wouldn't have
hesitated so much over uniting.
Is that right?
So that won't work, huh? Sure enough...
Say, I heard from Gohan
that the surviving people
from Namek went off to
some other planet, right?
Maybe I can go seek them out.
What?
If possible,
supposing one of them doesn't mind
staying here on Earth for a long time,
then both Kami-sama and the
Dragon Balls can be restored! Right?
I'm going to head out for a bit,
in search of Namekians!
If you find new Kami-sama, Popo happy too!
But Goku, how are you
going to get them to come?
We don't even know
what planet they went to.
It's going to take too much time.
What are you talking about?
I've got my Instantaneous
Movement ability, ain't I?
All I have to do is search out a ki
that's very similar to yours, Piccolo,
and that will be the planet
where the Namekians are...
Can you sense ki
that are that far away?
Probably.
As long as it's not too far
away, I think I'll be all right.
Let's give it a try, right now.
Be quiet for me for a bit...
Sorry, no good! Now what do we do?
I-I know!
I might be able to search for
them from where Kaio-sama is!
Let's see, Kaio-sama, Kaio-sama...
I've found you!
Do you think this is going to work?
I don't know whether we
can count on him or not.
Let's see, where are you, Kaio-sama...?
There you are, there you are!
Yo, Bubbles! It's been too long. How are you?
Kaio-sama, could you wake up for a second?
It's me, Son Goku.
...how pesky... Goku?
Oh, Goku!
So, that's Super Saiyan, is it?
What are you doing here, out of the blue?
Are you here to pass some time?
Geez, what is it with you?
You sure are laid back.
Don't you know that there's
something terrible happening on Earth?
There is no longer anything
mankind can do against the devilish Cell.
However, how is it that Goku can be so calm?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Dende, if you become Earth's new Kami-sama,
I'm sure Gohan will be thrilled.
Yeah. He may not look like it,
but he is an outstanding fellow.
Now, let's see the new Kami-sama in action.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Dende's First Task!!
The Dragon Balls Restored."
Hooray! Now I'll be able to see Dende again,
and the Dragon Balls will return to normal!
"Next time"
"Dende's First Task!!
The Dragon Balls Restored"