The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
The third match of the Tenkaichi Tournament,
a fight between Videl and Spopovitch,
went contrary to expectations,
as Videl nearly has her life taken from her
before Spopovitch's overwhelming power.
Why you... You're going to pay now.
You damned bastard!
The goofing around ends now, Spopovitch!
I don't believe this is
what we came here to do.
R-Ringout! Contestant Spopovitch wins.
What exactly is it that Yamu
and Spopovitch came to do?
There's something slithering behind
the scenes at the Tenkaichi Tournament.
"Exposed!! The Saiyaman is Son Gohan."
Still?
Father's been awfully long.
Yeah, with his Instantaneous Movement,
he should have been right back.
It might be that Karin Tower
didn't have any senzu.
Oh, no, Kuririn-san!
I'm going to go see how
Videl-san is doing again.
If Father comes back, that's where I'll be.
You know, Gohan...
I hate to say, but this looks like more to me
than simply worrying over a friend, you devil.
Videl! Videl!
Hey, are you sure she's okay?
She's all right. It will take some
time, but there's no mortal danger.
If anything happens to Videl,
someone's going to answer to me!
Mister Satan! Mister Satan!
This is Nathie, the Reporter.
Forgive me for intruding
during your misfortune,
but what is the prognosis for Videl-san?
Please excuse us!
H-How is Videl-san?
Videl is the daughter of the
World Champion Mister Satan!
Her method of training is not like that of others.
There's no cause for concern, so get lost.
I won't be giving any more autographs today.
Er, do you have any words
for Contestant Spopovitch?
I, Mister Satan, will avenge my daughter!
Tell Spopovitch to get ready for me!
I'm going to pound him into a quivering pulp!
Please, another moment,
Mister Satan! Any other comments?
There's so many people there.
Getting into the infirmary doesn't look possible.
I'm not going to concede!
Videl beaten by Spopovitch?
What's going on? I can't believe it!
Satan! Satan! Satan!
Spopovitch-kun, for you to have to
come against me in the first round,
your usual conduct must be pretty poor.
You have to learn more by watching me,
and becoming a better example
of a good boy to everyone!
What?! Don't make me laugh!
Have you had enough yet?
Dammit!
Contestant Mister Satan wins!
Videl, you must have
taken Spopovitch too lightly,
and just underestimated him, right?
I've told you since long ago that
carelessness is your greatest enemy,
indeed what else could I do?
D-Don't tell me this is because
you've started associating
with that weakling boy!
I absolutely will not allow it!
Gohan-kun!
What?!
I hope Videl's okay.
Lousy Great Saiyaman! Who the hell are you?!
If only my camera hadn't broken back then!
I did it! I may not have seen
clearly with my naked eye,
but my camera has surely
captured his uncovered face for me!
I, Shapner-sama, have uncovered
the Great Saiyaman's true identity!
Damn, this time I'll uncover
his true identity for sure!
Shapner! Shapner!
Do you think Videl is okay?
Sure she's okay.
I'm going to uncover his identity for sure!
It's the Great Saiyaman!
Shapner, doesn't the Great
Saiyaman resemble somebody?
I'll uncover his true identity!
Is Father still gone?
Yeah. What could he be doing?
He'd be more charming if he
acted like the dead man that he is
and held back on his appetite a bit.
What a remarkable guy!
The food in the Other World
ain't all that yummy is all.
Guess that's limited to the Lower Realm. Yum!
Goku, get back quickly! I have
a really bad feeling about all this.
Me too.
There's these guys named Spopovitch and Shin,
and so much seems about to happen!
Looks like it's going to get interesting!
Spopovitch, it may be
these next two. Look sharp!
It's all right.
As long as we have this, we'll know in a flash.
I want to get this settled quickly.
Yeah.
Kibit, I'll be relying heavily on you.
Right.
"1) Kuririn 2) Punta 3) Shin
4) Ma Junior 5) Videl 6) Spopovitch
7) Kibit 8) Great Saiyaman 9) No. 18
10) Mister Satan 11) Goku 12) Vegeta"
Next is finally Gohan, right?
His opponent is a guy
named Kibit or something.
Doesn't matter to me if he's
Kibit or Shibit, My Gohan will win!
[Shibit: dead]
That's true. Gohan-kun will win easily.
He's the prospective victor, after all.
Goku-sa is also a prospective victor!
That prize money'll be comin' to our house!
Gohan! Hang in there!
Chichi-san, Gohan-kun
being the Great Saiyaman
is supposed to be a secret, right?
Oh, no! I completely forgot!
Continuing on, we now hold the fourth match!
Ahem...
Before that, we have an announcement!
This concerns Contestant Videl,
who was here moments ago.
Apparently, although she has
sustained considerable injuries,
there is no danger to her life.
As such, those of you who
are Videl fans, please be at ease!
And now, the fourth match!
Contestants, please enter the ring.
The fourth match is between
Contestant Kibit and Contestant Great...
Er, pardon me...
Can I ask you to wait a little while longer?
It doesn't matter if it's just a moment or two,
but there's a miraculous
medicine that can heal Videl-san.
My Father should be
bringing it back with him now.
Ah, is that so? V-Very well,
if it'll only be a moment.
I beg your pardon.
We're sorry for the delay,
but please wait one moment.
Father, please hurry!
Father, were there any senzu?!
Yeah. Lately there ain't been any made, I guess,
but there were three of them there.
Thank goodness!
Here, feed one to that girl.
Thanks!
Excuse me, please wait just
a moment. I'll be right back!
This Kibit guy ain't your average type either.
We don't know how deep
the bottom is on that Shin guy.
Piccolo said our dimension
was too different, though.
Hmph, whoever these guys
may be, it doesn't matter to me.
How long have I been waiting for this day?
All I need to do is fight with Kakarrot and win!
Hey, Goten, what did
your dad just bring with him?
Gee, I don't know for sure.
Seems to be some kind of
medicine for that Videl lady to take.
That lady sure did get it good.
She does pretty well, though.
I wish they would start this already.
Our fight isn't until the seventh match.
I'm getting tired of waiting.
I think I'm the one who's
getting tired down here.
Videl! Videl!
Papa?
Oh, Videl, you're coming to?
Excuse me, please let me through!
Excuse me, I'm coming in!
Videl-san, I brought you something good!
See here! Videl needs her rest, you!
Who said you could come in?
Pardon me, I'm in a hurry.
W-Why you...!
G-Gohan-kun, I...
It's okay, it's okay. Can I coax
you into trying to eat this bean?
Sonny, sonny, this won't do!
We can't have you going around
giving the patients strange things!
Are you an idiot?! This is no
time to be giving her candy!
You'll feel better right away.
I said no, and I mean no!
I'll take it.
Knowing you, something amazing
is sure to arise out of this, right?
Yep.
V-Videl, don't listen to
what this guy is telling you!
Hey! Doctor, say something!
R-Right! Um...
Now see here!
S-Spit it out, Videl!
Okay. Everyone's waiting for you.
Sorry!
Damn, that kid... I'm going to
show him some pain later on...
Videl...
I-I'm healed!
Sorry to keep you waiting! Everything's fine!
Ladies and gentlemen in the
stadium, we apologize for the delay.
And so, let's have them begin!
Contestant Kibit and
Contestant Great Saiyaman!
Haven't we seen the
Great Saiyaman somewhere...?
Huh? Isn't that Son Gohan?
What?! Hey, let me borrow those for a second!
That hairstyle is a perfect match.
It really is Gohan! He's kidding, right?
He's the Great Saiyaman?!
No way, he couldn't be.
Surely he's just borrowing the
name so he can secretly enter in.
Why would it be necessary
for him to enter secretly?
Look, the kid is really
self-conscious, isn't he? That's why!
But can he really perform in hand-to-hand?
Let's root for him! I know it
won't do any good, but still...
Gohan! Good luck!
Fight, Gohan!
The championship may be out of the question,
but win at least one round!
Still, who would have
thought Gohan would've been...
I-I've been completely found-out!
That's it! The thing I had wrapped
around my head got taken off.
And I worked so hard to disguise myself!
Way to go, Gohan!
You look better without the sunglasses!
N-Now what do I do?
It's Gohan! For us to
discover his identity so easily...
Give me back the money for that camera!
Apparently there have been some
issues, but is everything all right?
In that case, begin the fourth match!
Sorry...
I-I'm all messed up now.
If they learn my true power,
it'll turn into a big deal,
and it will become harder for
me to go to school and places,
like Bulma-san said.
That's why I had the disguise...
He doesn't seem to be
the kind of opponent I can
get to let me win with
the right kind of trickery...
Turn yourself into this
Super Saiyan business!
I want to test you,
to see if you will be of help
to us if the situation arises!
Huh? H-How do you know about Super Saiyans?
A-And what do you mean, be of help to you?
You will know the answer
to that in any case shortly.
First, I must see the abilities of a Super Saiyan.
So, it begins...
Y-You've got to be kidding me!
Become a Super Saiyan in
front of all these people?!
What is it? What are they talking about?
He told him to become a Super Saiyan.
How about it, those two?
No, it's not them. Their energy is too low.
Gohan!
Piccolo-san...
What, Piccolo? Is something up?
I don't know what exactly, but...
You must allow us to make use of
Gohan-san. My humble apologies.
And now, no matter what may happen,
I would ask that you please not move from here.
If you would be so kind...
What?!
What is this about?
Well, turn!
Damn, I-I have no choice.
I guess I'll give up school.
I don't listen to those I know nothing about.
Tell us who you are!
Th-This being is the Kaioshin-sama!
He is the Kami over all Kaio,
including the Grand Kaio!
Ah! I've heard about you,
from Kaio-sama! Kaioshin...
You're Kaioshin-sama?
What are you doing, you idiots?!
How long are you two going
to just gape at each other?
Start the match, already!
You're wasting my time!
Ahem, the match has begun.
You all shut up! Somethin'
awesome is about to happen here!
You just watch, ya morons!
Gohan finally commits to
turning into a Super Saiyan.
What is it Yamu and his companion are after?
And what is Kaioshin's goal?
What could possibly be beginning here?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Yamu and Spopovitch are
staging an attack on Gohan
after he turned Super Saiyan.
Why isn't anyone going to help him?
If we don't do something,
Gohan-kun will be killed!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"A Slithering Conspiracy!!
Gohan's Power is Stolen."
I-I'm losing my power...
"Next time"
"A Slithering Conspiracy!!
Gohan's Power is Stolen"