The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
With the Fusion being broken,
and as everyone began to wonder
if this was the end of the Earth...
Big Brother! It's Big Brother!
...at last, having completed
his training in the Kaioshin Realm,
Gohan had returned!
Hey, don't tell me you intend to fight me!
No, I'm going to kill you!
You retard.
Will the extraordinarily powered-up
Gohan be able to completely defeat Majin Boo,
and become a true savior?
"Has He Done It!?
Majin Boo's Great Explosion."
Retard, you say? Retard?!
H-He called him that?!
H-He's gotten too carried away, regardless!
Y-You called me a retard?!
You can't win!
So, that was you after all?
What?
What do you mean?
I knew it! Ever since I was fighting those runts!
Far, far, in a very faraway
place, I felt a strong power.
I will not stand for any
power stronger than mine!
So that's it. You were
testing me, just to make sure
that I really was greater than you...
That's too bad, huh Majin Boo?
Y-You mean that even
during the height of that battle,
he had already become
conscious of Gohan's existence?
I-In that case, what in the world was
the meaning of that fight with Gotenks?!
Listen, and listen well!
I will not stand for you! Absolutely not!
Absolutely not, absolutely not!
I won't stand for you!! I'll kill you!!
Kill me, you say?
You must know better than anyone
else that such a thing is impossible.
I'm looking forward to this!
Watch out!
I'm so thirsty...
B-Beer!!
Looks so good!
Hold on, hold on, I'll find some milk for you.
W-We owe you one, Gohan. You saved us.
Not at all.
Whew! That was close!
T-To think he would blow himself up!
Big Brother, you're incredible! Way to
know that Boo was blowing himself up!
Is Boo dead, then?
No.
He blew himself up, didn't he?
He tried to take you with him, Gohan-san!
If he had been trying to take me with him,
he would have made it even bigger–
so much so that there
would be nothing left of Earth.
What does this mean?
Has he fled? I don't feel his ki!
He is capable of muffling his ki.
S-So he's hiding,
looking for his next chance!
I don't know. But it does seem
as if he's planning something.
Ha! Even if he is really
alive, there's no problem!
That jerk was powerless to stop Gohan-san!
He's as strong as we were as Super Gotenks!
Even stronger!
Really? Yeah, just a little.
Tell me, Gohan, how is it
that you've become so powerful?
Wow, such an incredible old man, huh?
By the way, Piccolo-san,
who has the Dragon Radar?
Ah, we gave that to Piccolo-san!
Y-Yeah. It's true that I do have it.
However... with Dende having been killed,
the Dragon Balls are mere stones now.
The Dragon Balls are what?!
It's okay. Dende is alive. See?
You can faintly feel his ki, right?
What?!
I-It's true! I feel him!
–Yeah! I can tell too!
–He's over that way!
Come on! Let's go locate Dende while we can!
We don't know when Boo
will appear again, after all.
All right! Let's go!
That jerk! He really has killed everyone!
There isn't a single person anywhere!
Yeah...
What? Do you see something?
Yes. Isn't that...?
I-I want some beer...
water would be okay too...
It's Mister Satan! Why is he
the only one who has survived?
He's sure a tough one. Let him be, let him be!
No, let's bring him with us.
Even given all that, he's
still a good person at heart.
He did try to save the Earth, in his own way.
Juice... Cola... Oolong tea...
Huh? You're...!
Good day.
G-Good day...
Still, why is it that Dende alone survived?
Boo had plenty of time. Enough
for him to seek him out and kill him.
Father said that you were fighting
in the Room of Spirit and Time,
and that Boo was the first to come out, right?
That's right.
He broke through the wall between dimensions.
Even so, Piccolo-san, afterward you all
came out as well, almost immediately, right?
One day here is the same
as a year within the room,
so Piccolo-san, you and the others
came out just one moment later, didn't you?
Th-That's right!
How can this be?!
I got so distracted that I've
misunderstood everything! That's right!
It was completely the opposite!
You sure do get reckless
sometimes, Piccolo-san!
Th-Thanks...
Oh! Kami-sama!
Everyone!
How good of you to have
gotten away, Dende! Well done!
P-Popo-san said that I at
least absolutely must not die!
When it looked like everyone
was going to be eaten by Boo,
he immediately flung me
toward the Lower Realm!
I choose choco!!
Kami-sama at least must not die!
He was right. If you had died, the
Dragon Balls would be ordinary stones.
The Earth would have remained a ghost town.
That's our Mister Popo!
He's made an excellent determination!
H-Hey, who is he? That kid over
there with the sickly complexion?
Now see here! What do you mean, kid?!
That's Kami-sama! Kami-sama!
W-What did you say?
Whew, thank goodness!
Um...
What are these Dragon Balls that you
have been talking about for a while now?
Never mind that, what in the
world does Majin Boo plan to do?
There's no way he can win!
W-W-W-What?!
V-V-Videl has been killed?!
B-Boo killed V-Videl?!
Th-Th-That can't be!! Videl! Videl!
Hey, you! Why didn't you
protect Videl?! Why didn't you?!
I'm sorry...
It's okay, Pops! They can
come back to life, after all!
C-Come back to life? Really?
Videl can come back to life, right?
Really! Really! Really!
You're not lying to me, are you?
If you're lying, I'll make
you swallow a thousand needles!
It's Majin Boo!
What?! Boo, you say?
Th-That can't be! Is he
already intent on fighting again?
What could have changed in
just the hour or so that has gone by?
I'll finish him off this time for sure!
Everyone, be careful not
to get caught in between us!
Okay, show me what has changed!
Boo!
Why have you killed everyone?!
You promised me, didn't you?
That you wouldn't kill any more?
Boo! Don't you know who I am?
It's no use! He's not the
same Boo he was before!
L-Look! This is the cute little guy
you saved! See how lively he's gotten?
I told you, it's useless! Stop it, already!
You'll get in the way of Gohan's fighting.
What does he want me to do? Damn...
Strange. I don't think there's a
single thing about him that has changed.
What is it with him?
What the hell is he thinking?
Yeesh! He's bluffing, he's bluffing!
He's just going to go
right off running away again!
Hey, pipsqueaks!
Come on out! I want to fight you!
What?
You've got it backward, Boo!
I'm your opponent now!
First I'm going to settle things with
the pipsqueaks! I'll fight you afterward!
Why?! Why do such a roundabout thing?
You wanted to defeat me, didn't you?!
What's the matter, pipsqueaks?
Are you afraid to fight me?
What happened to all those
high spirits you showed earlier?
Once again, Majin Boo challenges
Trunks and Goten to a fight.
Just what exactly do you have planned?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Oh, no! Gotenks and Piccolo
have been absorbed by Boo!
What do you think, Gohan-kun?
This is a moment which will never come again!
The birth of the mightiest of Majin!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Boo's Worst Foul!! Gotenks is Absorbed!?"
That was dirty, Majin Boo!
"Next time"
"Boo's Worst Foul!! Gotenks is Absorbed!?"