Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Damn it all!
Planet Namek has been destroyed.
They say the Namek Dragon Balls
can bring people back to
life any number of times!
In other words, both Son-kun and
Kuririn can be brought back to life!
It is you folks that don't know anything.
Goku and Kuririn will
return to life on Planet Namek.
However, Namek is no longer there,
it's just the vacuum of space.
The moment they return to life,
death awaits them again.
"Son Goku Survived –
The Z Warriors All Resurrected!!"
W-Why is it Father and
Kuririn-san cannot come back to life?
It appears to be okay if, like Chaozu-kun,
your body is regenerated by Kami-sama
and you're at Kaio-sama's place.
Otherwise, it seems you return
to life at the place where you died.
But Son-kun and Kuririn
died on Planet Namek,
and Planet Namek isn't there any more,
right? There's just the emptiness of space.
On top of that, Kaio-sama
doesn't appear to have jurisdiction
over the area of Planet Namek's location.
I-It can't be...
How about using your heads a little bit?
I don't know about spirits or whatever,
but you can always bring them back to
life after moving them here to Earth, right?
Probably, anyhow.
That's it! Just like he said!
You say some pretty good things, don't you?
Thanks a lot!
Don't get carried away!
All I want to do is see for myself
Kakarrot's strength as a Super Saiyan.
And then, sometime,
I will defeat him! That's for sure!
Pardon me, madam of Earth.
Once the Namek Dragon Balls reactivate,
we intend to locate a suitable
planet and then relocate ourselves there.
Would you please direct us to a nice
place where we can stay until that time?
I guess you're right.
In that case, you can come live at my place!
Are you sure that is all right?
It's awfully big, so don't worry!
Besides, for our part, we'd like to trouble
you to use the Dragon Balls a little bit more.
Just do it, okay?
Okay, Dende-kun?
Y-Yeah...
With so many of you here,
if you were found out by anyone,
there would be a big fuss over you!
That's certainly true.
We accept your kind assistance.
And um, Vegeta-kun, wasn't it?
Vegeta-kun?!
Why don't you come too?
After all, you don't
have any rent money, right?
I'll provide plenty of food!
You must be like Son-kun,
and eat an awful lot, I bet!
However, no matter how
attractive you might say that I am,
you can't do anything naughty!
W-What a vulgar woman!
To say that with such a loud voice!
Okay, everyone! Wait just a moment.
I'll go hunt down a telephone
and have my dad come get us.
A-Ahem, Bulma-san?
Could I stay over at
your place too, Bulma-san?
Gohan-kun, you have a home, don't you?
You should go home!
Your mother must be worried and all!
See, that is...
I forgot to do my homework,
and Mother will be angry at me...
The repairs to the spaceship
are complete, this time for sure.
Without fail, you will arrive on
Namek in five days. Are you all ready?
Gohan, sit tight!
Your Ma is comin' to save you!
And so, the countdown...
4... 3... 2...
1...
Ah, that's right! A moment ago,
I got a phone call from Bulma.
She says everyone has returned to Earth.
As such, are you still going after all?
Can't you speed this
thing up any more?! Huh?!
T-This is it...
He's here! He's here! Down here!
Here, here, here!
Gohan-chan!
Where is he?! Gohan-chan?!
Mother, I'm home...
And so, the Namekians were carried
to the Capsule Corporation,
which is run by Bulma's father.
This is my home. What do you
think? A pretty cool place, huh?
My, my! How good of you to come!
Is this gentleman your boyfriend, Bulma?
What a handsome young man, and so trendy!
T-Trendy?
Is that...?
This is a space capsule that I repaired.
The fourth time around, it's perfect.
However, I still haven't decided
where to place the stereo.
So that's it. It's the thing
Kakarrot came in.
Vegeta-san! I've prepared something cold.
Come drink with everyone else!
As it turns out, the Namekians would live
at Bulma's home until
the Dragon Balls reactivated.
And so, in no time at all, 130 days had passed.
The Namek Dragon Balls
reactivate in 130 days, then?
That's correct. On Planet Namek,
one year is 130 days, you see.
Compared to Earth, that's one-third!
Isn't that nice?
Let's make our request of
Super Shen Long-san right away!
J-Just a moment!
Gohan and the others aren't here yet...
Hey, wait a second!
Hey, Gohan!
Pardon us! My Juku school ran long!
Are you going to Juku again? Such hard work!
I want to have my
Gohan-chan studyin' a whole lot,
and have him become a great scholar!
Well, we were just about to begin!
Okay, Dende-kun, if you would?
Right!
So this is the home-grown Shen Long?
Wow, this is incredible!
Indeed!
–It suddenly got dark!
–What's happening?!
What's that?!
It's a monster!
Wait, wait! It's coming out of
Dr. Briefs' Capsule Corporation!
It must just be some new invention!
Oh, is that it?
Everybody, this is an experiment
of the Capsule Corporation!
Please, do not worry!
–What a surprise!
–Thank goodness.
Thou who hast gathered
the seven Dragon Balls,
I shall grant thee any three wishes.
Ladies and gentlemen of Earth,
next time will be fine with us.
Have your own wishes granted!
Thank you very much, Grand Elder-sama!
In that case, I'll make our wishes.
First, please call the spirits of Son Goku
and Kuririn, who died on Planet Namek, here.
Understood. I shall attempt it.
I have summoned the spirit of
the being named Kuririn here.
However, I canst not summon the
spirit of the one called Son Goku.
T-That can't be! Why not?!
Because Son Goku is alive,
I canst not summon only his spirit.
A-Alive...?
W-What's this?
D-Don't tell me... how did he...?!
–Hooray!
Hooray!
If he's alive, I wonder
why he hasn't come home.
His spaceship is probably
broken or something.
Well, if that's the case, you
can have Shen Long call him here!
I-I guess so, huh?
Okay, now, the second wish!
Please return Kuririn back to life!
Go! Go! Go!
Huh?
Kuririn-san!
So that's it! I've come back to life!
Hooray!
I have returned his dismembered body to
its original state as a special free service.
You may have a frightening face,
but you sure do good work!
And now, this time, at last...
Bring Son-kun here to us!
Hooray!
Goku-sa!
It is no good.
It hath been refused.
This man called Son says he shall
return shortly of his own accord.
R-Refused? Why?
I know!
He's afraid of his wife-san!
So the greatest in the universe is
the Super Saiyan Son Goku's wife, is it?!
J-Joke! That was a joke!
F-Father won't come home?
He says he'll come back on his own shortly.
He's definitely coming home.
So that's it!
He's gone to another planet, intending to
pile on more training and power up even more!
I can't just stay in a
place like this taking it easy!
My, my, my, my, my, my!
Pay him no mind!
Let's continue. Instead of Son, bring
back to life someone at Kaio's place.
Yeah, okay.
I wonder who I should call back.
They're saying they
want to call one of you back.
What do we do?
I want to continue
training here a little longer.
I-I want to be with Ten-san.
Very well, Yamucha, you may go.
Me first, huh? Excuse me.
All right. Now then...
Bulma! Bulma!
Bulma, it's me. Do you know who?
Kaio-sama?
Tenshinhan and Chaozu
will stay here a little longer.
Return Yamucha to life, if you would.
Yamucha, right? Okay!
And now, our third wish, once more please!
Bring Yamucha back to life!
Very well, understood.
I have returned the one
named Yamucha to life.
W-Where?
Where? Where?!
I have granted all of thy wishes. Farewell.
J-Just a minute, now!
He left! Where is Yamucha?!
H-Here!
Yamucha-sama!
–Yamucha-sama! Yamucha-sama!
–Pu-erh!
Yamucha!
As long as you were returning me anyway,
I wish you had chosen a better place.
And then, another 130 days passed.
With the first wish, Chaozu–
and with the second wish,
Tenshinhan was resurrected.
Ten-san...
Ten-san! Ten-san!
Chaozu!
And then...
So, Dende, it is about time to take our leave.
Right.
Everyone, thank you all so much!
T-Take care, okay?
Gohan-san, goodbye. It was most enjoyable!
Dende...
I shall grant that wish!
Goodbye.
Goodbye!
G... G...
With the third wish, the Namekians
transferred themselves to another planet.
Let's see...
And after this manner, the
Earth was peaceful for a short time.
However...
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
This is a surprise! Kuririn has a girlfriend?!
I sure hope nothing bad comes of it.
The Demon Clan has
been becoming active lately.
Gohan, watch out! Garlic Jr. is back!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Terrible Happenings in Heaven!!
Garlic Jr. to Become Kami!?"
Oh, no. I won't have any time to study!
"Next time"
"Terrible Happenings in Heaven!!
Garlic Jr. to Become Kami!?"