Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Having merged with Nail, and
benefiting from that great power-up,
even Freeza finds himself in a
close battle against Piccolo. However...
Every time I, Freeza, transform
myself, my power substantially grows!
And I still have two more
transformations remaining!
What's that?!
Shall we put an end to
this playing around, then?
The second transformation of Freeza brings
with it astounding battle power and speed.
Stop it!!
"Fear Me!! Freeza Does Battle
with a Third Transformation."
What?
Someone like you deserves to...
...Die!!
G-Gohan!
Full power!
That brat...
Hang in there, Gohan!
Thank you, Piccolo-san!
Quite strange.
That little one should not
have such a battle power.
After recovering from near-death, it is
as if he is a different person altogether.
That's it! The little one is a Saiyan!
But whose child is he?
Twenty years ago,
with the exception of Vegeta, Nappa and Raditz,
the Saiyans were supposed
to have been exterminated.
So whose is he?
He doesn't look like either Vegeta or Nappa...
So he's Raditz's child?
There is something there
that reminds me of him.
T-That blast that just got bounced back...
You've gotten stronger, Gohan.
I'm so glad.
But it was no use.
I put everything I had into that,
and it still didn't connect against Freeza!
That brat...
He is indisputably drawing
closer to becoming a Super Saiyan.
You!
You must have figured it out!
After coming one step away
from death, when we Saiyans recover,
our strength increases!
Now listen!
Before Freeza makes his final transformation,
you must render me half-dead!
Well? Do it now!
The blood of the Saiyans
must be completely cut off.
Not because I believe in ridiculous
legends, such as the Super Saiyan,
history's greatest warrior, but because
I do not feel well with them around.
It is the principle of it all,
with the little one and Vegeta
growing stronger so quickly.
If I injure myself, there will be no effect!
You must do it!
B-But my power isn't enough
to bring you to near-death!
Don't worry.
I'll lower my battle power as low as it will go.
Your power will be enough.
We're just lucky that Namekian kid
down there can heal people instantaneously.
No matter how much I may hate you, how can I?
Besides which, it's just
about time for Goku to recover.
Kakarrot is a lowest-class warrior!
He won't get any stronger than that!
Very well.
It would be a simple matter to blow
you all to pieces in this current form,
but before I kill you, I will have you
witness the terror of an ultimate power,
even more frightening than death!
Ultimate... what now?
H-How can it be?
I do you a great service!
You will experience a terror
even greater than that of Hell's.
And so, gaze upon my final transformation!
My true form!
You rotten...
P-Piccolo-san!
If you do it now, there's still time. Hurry!
What?! What's wrong with this planet?
It's all over! I'm going to die here!
If I'd known Son-kun were coming,
I could have left searching
for the Dragon Balls up to him!
Gohan-kun is a fool! Kuririn is an idiot!
I hate you, Son-kun!
Freeza's ki is rising again.
Am I going to get out of here in time?
Hurry up! This is the only way!
It can't be...
There's no other choice!
Can't you even do that,
you good-for-nothing fool?!
That's not good enough!
You have to shoot a stronger ki!
T-That's good...
I'm at last going to become... a Super Saiyan...
W-Why did Kuririn-san shoot Vegeta?
G-Gohan! Get out of here!
Right!
Are you okay, Piccolo-san?
I can't say that I am...
I know! It's all right,
we can heal those injuries!
There's a Namekian named
Dende that can heal injuries!
I'll go get him.
Gohan!
Kuririn-san, where's Dende?
What?! You say you can't heal me?
T-That's right!
You're saying you could
heal the others, but not me?
You killed many of my friends as well!
I cannot heal someone like that!
Y-You brat! So long as you don't
heal me, Freeza will not be beaten!
I won't!
H-Hurry up... I'm starting
to lose consciousness...
I... I... I...
I'm going to save the other one.
Damn...
You... brat...
Vegeta and the other Saiyans gain a whole
lot of strength once revived from near death.
You knew that, didn't you?
Y-Yeah.
And so, he had me blast him on purpose.
It sounded like he was
sure he could beat Freeza!
So that was why?
–Dende!
Vegeta!
They said... you can
heal injuries. Is that true?
Y-Yes!
Dende...
I see, so that's it!
Unbelievable! Do I have the same ability?
No. You, like Nail-san, are a warrior-type.
More importantly, Dende,
I know how you feel,
not wanting to heal Vegeta.
For now, without him,
there isn't anything we can do!
He...
He's just like Freeza!
He's also killed so many Namekians!
Go heal him for me.
I can beat Vegeta now,
but I can't possibly beat Freeza.
What now? Freeza is...
He's finishing his transformation!
Ah, hell. All this time, we should have
masked our ki and hidden somewhere.
If we had done something like that,
he would just blow us away,
planet Namek and all!
He doesn't have any more use for this planet!
T-That is one impossibly huge ki.
T-The incredible beast is about to appear!
Dende, please! Heal Vegeta!
Dende...
We can see him now!
You little turd!
You just be grateful that
I didn't kill you right here!
So that's Freeza's battle power?
Looks like he's revealed his true self.
Freeza, or anyone else, bring it on!
I have now become a Super Saiyan!
So this is Freeza? Such an incredible ki!
At last, Freeza completes
his third transformation.
Is there any hope left for Gohan and the others?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
After Dende resuscitated Vegeta,
he powered up something incredible.
Has he really surpassed Freeza?
I've decided to see for myself the
power of history's greatest warrior,
the legendary Super Saiyan.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Death of Dende...
Come Forth! Intense, Wide-Open Power."
Avenge Dende's death, Vegeta!
"Next time"
"The Death of Dende...
Come Forth! Intense, Wide-Open Power"