The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
The fierce, final battle between
Goku and Majin Boo continued.
However, not even Goku's arduous
attacks were of any use against Boo.
Here I'm wanting to obliterate him,
but I have to gather ki
for about a whole minute.
All right! I'll keep him in
check somehow for one minute.
You start gathering ki immediately!
As Goku gathered up his ki,
Vegeta took his place,
risking his life to fight Boo.
However, even after the
necessary one minute had gone by,
Goku's ki had not been stored up.
What in the world is the matter, Goku?
"Don't You Pick On Satan!!
The Original Boo is Revived."
This is strange... I should have
long since had enough ki gathered...
Vegeta!
Hey, there! Where are you planning on going?
It's obvious, isn't it? I am
returning to the Kaioshin Realm.
Y-You're what?
Unquestionably, between Majin Boo and I,
there is too much difference in our
powers, and I will be no match for him.
However, even I should be
able to buy them some time.
At this point, even if it's only for one second,
we have to buy enough time to
let Goku-san gather even more ki.
Right now, Goku-san is
our only remaining hope.
Just a minute!
I'm going too!
Not you, too!
I am not a fighter-type, but
even so, I should be of some use!
Dende-san...
This is a crisis for the whole universe.
At a time like this, I can't
just sit here doing nothing!
Thanks!
Well then, let's go!
Right!
J-J-Just a moment, now!
For the love of... would
you settle down for a second?
If you boys could go and buy time,
I would have long since let you go!
You boys must know well enough
that this situation is one where
we can no longer do anything!
I know how you're feeling anxious,
but there's nothing we can do any more.
The only thing we can do...
is believe in those two,
and watch over them.
Knowing those two, I'm sure they'll
manage something. Isn't that right?
Vegeta!
Stay back...!
Stay back! Of all the...
Who is it you think I'm
going through all of this for?!
You hurry up and gather your ki!
This is bad!
No matter how tough Vegeta is,
there ain't no way he can stand up to that!
I can't stand it any more!
Boo!
Yo, yo, yo! I watch on silently, and
you get carried away with yourself!
Did you think that the world combat
sports champion Mister Satan-sama
would quietly overlook your brutality?!
I am going to punish you! Prepare yourself!
You will soon regret having an
opponent you can't deal with!
We didn't need this! He should
have just quietly stayed in hiding!
He's nervous, he's nervous!
You're getting a spankie spankie!
Yo, yo, yo! What's the matter?!
Hurry up and come at me!
Or are you afraid of Mister Satan here?
You miserable coward!
I-I nailed that! I nailed that so
hard, it's a shame this is a dream!
Y-You want to go?!
E-Even in a dream, this is scary!
I-I'm sorry!
I-I didn't mean any harm!
I just wanted to show off a little!
I was only playing around,
and I couldn't help myself!
Satan dodged Boo's attack!
Nice going! I have to
give you more credit, Satan!
I'm so sorry!
W-What is it? What in the world is wrong?!
C-Could it be that he's in awe of my resolve?
I did it, I did it! I did it!
Yo, yo, what's the matter?!
Come on, come on! Suffer some
more from the power of my resolve!
W-Why is this?
Why is it that ever since Mister
Satan appeared, Boo has been...?
C-Could it really be a result
of Mister Satan's resolve?
K-Kakarrot!
What the hell are you doing?!
This is our chance! Gather
your ki now, while you can!
Yeah, you got it!
B-B-Boo!!
W-What's this?
W-What's happening here?
I-I know! That chubby Majin Boo
was friends with Mister Satan!
With that Boo inside his body,
he was undergoing rejection, and
was incapable of attacking Satan!
I see, so that's why he spat him out, is it?
Well, even if that Satan fellow is
done in, it won't have much of an impact.
H-How could you? He may
have a number of character issues,
but he is the last survivor of the human race...
for the time being...
Boo!
Boo! Hey! Come on!
Snap out of it! Boo!
Boo...
Hey, come on...
B-Boo...
B-Boo... And you were such a nice guy, too...
How... How awful...!
How dare you do this to Boo!
You'll pay! You're going to pay!!
Why, you...! Brace yourself!
I, Mister Satan, will beat you to a pulp!
W-What's with this guy?
You really want to fight?!
I'm warning you, y-you'd better quit!
To put it frankly, I'm too strong for you!
V-Very well!
If you want to get hurt
that badly, I'll let you have it!
Come on!
This is my dream, after all...
So it's only natural that
I'm the one who will win!
How's that? Have you learned your lesson?
H-How can this be?!
Even in my dream, this still hurts!
W-Why, you...! Cut that out!
Are you trying to get me really angry?!
Do you really want to get hurt that badly?
If you're going to apologize, now's the time!
W-Well, that's okay!
Maybe I'll just let you off. Mm-hmm!
I might have been partly in the wrong as well.
What?!
B-Boo...
I hate you! Don't you pick on Satan!
Boo! Y-You're alive?
How long is this going to take,
Kakarrot?! Still not yet?!
I-I know! But it's strange...
I've gathered up ki to just about my full power,
b-but the stored-up ki is starting to decrease!
I-It's what?!
Kakarrot, enough already!
How long will this take?!
That fatso isn't going to hold out that long!
Aren't you done yet?!
Aren't you done gathering up your ki?!
Damn it! Damn it! This ain't...
This ain't supposed to be happening!
M-My power... My power is d-dropping off!
W-What's this?!
Th-This can't be...!
Boo...!
Th-Thank goodness!
That's my Boo! Hang in there!
Bust that guy's chops!
Th-This is trouble. I can't really win.
Looks like this has
become the worst of all games.
Far from storing up ki,
Goku has instead powered down.
Is there no way left to defeat Boo?
The universe is meeting its greatest crisis!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
The way things are headed,
the chubby Boo is done for!
Super Saiyan 3 ain't
getting the job done, either!
Dende, Kaioshin, bring back
Earth right now with the Dragon Balls!
It's time the people of
earth pulled their own weight!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Vegeta's Secret Plan!!
Polunga and the Two Wishes."
All right! Everyone has come back to life!
"Next time"
"Vegeta's Secret Plan!!
Polunga and the Two Wishes"