Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
In order to meet Kaio-sama, the man said
to be the strongest in all of the Other World,
Goku ran as hard as he could.
However, he slipped off of the Serpentine
Road and fell into the depths of Hell!
With great difficulty, he finally
located a secret cave and returned.
G-Great King Yama-sama?
It was Great King Yama's office.
Having come back to the beginning,
Goku ran off to the Serpentine Road.
Thanks to the Enseiju fruit,
the mysterious item he
had eaten while he was in Hell,
Goku's speed had been powered-up.
Eight months remain until
the Saiyans' assault. Hurry, Goku!
"Such Sweet Temptation!
The Snake Princess-sama's Hospitality."
Oni?
Something's coming oni.
Watch out oni! Stop oni!
I thought he had fallen off
the Serpentine Road earlier oni.
Be that as it may, it looks
like he's a lot faster this time oni–
Ah oni!
Uncle Piccolo is awesome!
Well, with this many of us members
here, I'm not at all afraid of those Saiyans.
I can't wait to see what kind of
training Kami-sama puts us through.
Thanks to my eating that fruit,
I've already come this far in a flash.
What's that?
I wonder if this is Kaio-sama's residence.
What is this?! What is this?!
Welcome to our lobby, honored guest!
Snake Princess-sama, we have a visitor.
What? A visitor?
My!
Such a handsome gentleman!
He's just my type!
The Snake Princess-sama approaches!
Then Kaio-sama, you're...
...a woman? You're cute, huh?
Cute, you say?
Such a gallant gentleman!
For some reason, my heart is all a-flutter!
The Snake Princess-sama
hasn't been this worked up
since Great King Yama-sama, has she?
Yes! He was quite handsome too!
It's been nearly five hundred years, I'll bet.
F-Five hundred years?!
Well, no matter. Never mind that,
Kaio-sama, teach me some martial arts.
M-Martial arts?
How about instead, we dance the tango?
This is so romantic! Surely we
were destined to come together.
The tango is a lot like the
dance we did at my wedding.
So this is Kaio-sama's
martial arts technique.
I get it! This is a technique to get your
opponent off their guard, then clobber them!
–Ee-yow!
–Kaio-sama is a lot weaker than I thought...
What are you doing?! She is not Kaio-sama!
This is the Snake Princess-sama,
who shone in the glory of victory
at the Other World Beauty Contest!
What? You ain't Kaio-sama? I'm leaving.
G-Goodness, no!
Please wait!
I'm in a hurry!
A-At least have dinner before you go.
D-Dinner? Come to think of it...
...I ain't eaten anything since that
piece of fruit. I guess I'll eat before I go.
I'm so happy! Okay, okay, you guys,
quickly prepare something for dinner!
–Right!
You guys understand, right? We'll do
whatever it takes to keep that man here!
After all, he's the kind of nice man
we haven't had for five hundred years.
I won't have him get away from us!
Snake Princess-sama, if I mix this
sleeping potion in with the cooking,
it will bring on an irresistible urge to sleep,
he'll doze off, and won't leave here!
Well, it's not a very elegant
method, but what choice do we have?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
We have foie gras, made
from the bird of paradise,
sauté of bear's paw, from Needle Mountain,
baked crocodile, taken from the
River Sanzu, and mussels au gratin.
Let's dig in!
Yes, yes, be my guest!
Help yourself to as much as you like.
All right, I'm eating!
I-If you like, help
yourself to my serving as well.
Really? Thanks!
Okay, then... I'll take it...
I'm full, I'm full!
Well then, I guess I should go.
Please, wait! Are you not sleepy?
I ain't got time to sleep. I've got
to go meet Kaio-sama and everything.
You're sure you put
the sleeping stuff in, right?
Yes, plenty of it.
Thanks for dinner. Okay then, I'm going.
You guys!
Please, wait. We have a bath warmed up.
How about if you took a bath before going?
Kaio-sama dislikes dirty people.
Yeah, maybe I am a little sweaty.
Maybe I should freshen up before I go.
–Yes, yes!
This feels great.
How is the water?
Fine. It's a little bit hot, but it's okay.
This originally comes
from the steam baths of Hell.
He should be warmed
clear through to the bone!
Okay.
Huh? Suddenly it's become night.
Goku-sama, there are so many stars.
To think that I should be together with
you on such a wonderful evening, Goku-sama,
it makes the Snake Princess so happy...
Say there, Goku-sama?
Goku-sama?
Oh, my...
T-This is terrible!
He's been boiled alive!
98... 99... 100!
Oh, that's refreshing!
How embarrassing! But
still, what a manly figure he has.
Wow, that was revitalizing!
Okay then, I'll be going.
Ah, wait!
Hey you guys, stop him!
–Just a moment!
–What is it? I'm in a hurry!
I have to hurry and see Kaio-sama,
and learn martial arts from him!
In that case, then we have
just the thing! How about this?
A thrilling, spine-tingling
game of Russian Roulette!
You can help train your
mind to overcome fear with this!
Russian Roulette?
How does it train your mind?
First, you take one bullet
and place it into the pistol.
Then you spin it round and round.
The chances of the bullet
being shot are one in six.
When it does, that's the end of the story.
It's a game brimming with
thrills, in exchange for one's life!
That ended all too easily, huh?
I ain't doing anything that dangerous.
Thank you for waiting! It is now showtime!
Yes, yes, please leave
after you've watched this show!
Is this martial arts too?
Yes! It is a new martial art.
Snake Princess-sama,
this time I made sure to use
all the sleeping potion we had left.
Make it good.
Here, have some specially prepared juice.
Wow, thanks.
Yummy!
For this guy to have eaten and drank
that much sleeping potion and still be alive–
what is he, a monster?
We did it! He should be asleep
for three days and nights like this!
He's pretty tough, huh?
Yes. He is no ordinary person.
But you know, he has such
a lovely face when he's asleep.
He really is my type.
Chichi... Gohan...
He's having some kind of dream.
Bring the dream-viewing mirror.
Right.
This will reflect whatever dream he is having.
Chichi... Gohan...
–Father!
–Goku-sa!
What's this? A woman and a boy?
Ah, apparently they are his wife and child.
He's not single?!
He still looks delicious, though!
Are you going to eat this one too?
I wonder if there will be any for us this time.
After all, the only one to get out of
here safely has been Great King Yama.
Good, Gohan!
Once you've finished doin' those
drills, your studyin' is done for today.
Mm-hmm. I want to
hurry up and go out and play.
W-Who are you?!
I'm scared! Father!
Goku-sa!
Gohan!
Chichi!
Oh, it was a dream,
was it? Did I fall asleep?
He's awake already, isn't he?
Yeah...
That's right! I was on
my way to see Kaio-sama!
Please, don't go!
Sorry, but I'm going. Everyone on
Earth is waiting for me to come back.
You're going, no matter what?
Yeah, no matter what.
Why, you–!
I am the Serpentine Road Goddess,
who has lived on the Serpentine Road
for a thousand and five hundred years!
How dare you bring disgrace upon me!
Now listen to me! You will
never return home from here!
What is this?
If you cannot realize my charms,
then you can just dissolve away!
This is bad! I've got
to get out of here quick!
Dammit...
That was close!
Why, you...!
You're not getting away!
Damn! In that case...
Ka... me...
No, I won't. She did
feed me all that food, after all.
Hey, let me pass!
I have to hurry and go see Kaio-sama!
No way! If you want to
live, you'll have to defeat me!
Damn... I know!
Wait up!
See you! Thanks for the meal!
And the bath, too!
This is so degrading!
The journey to Kaio-sama is still far.
The Saiyans' assault is drawing near.
Hurry, Goku! Run the
length of the Serpentine Road!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
What? Gohan ran away?
You can't blame him.
Piccolo's training is too harsh!
I can't turn back now. I've got to tough it out.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Escape from Piccolo!
Gohan Summons a Storm."
It's okay. I'm just going to go
see my mother for a little while.
"Next time"
"Escape from Piccolo!
Gohan Summons a Storm"