Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
I give up!
I surrender!
Son Goku had lost to Cell.
And then, the man who Goku
named as the strongest man was...
It's your turn, Gohan!
What nonsense.
Let him have it, Gohan.
Bring peace back to the world.
You wanted to be a scholar, right?
Understood! I'll do it!
I'll kill him immediately!
Look how wrong you were, Son Goku!
Thanks to your misdirected
thinking, your son will die!
Goku-san!
Hey, Goku! Hey!
Gohan can win this. I'm sure of it!
"Become Enraged Gohan –
Call Forth Your Dormant Power."
Yours is nothing more than
a foolish struggle, Son Gohan.
G-Gohan...
Gohan!
Gohan-chan! There's no helpin' Goku-sa!
Up until now, he's always just
disregarded me, and went off fightin'!
I've given up hope on him!
But as for Gohan-chan...!
And here, after all the times
I've warned him about this...!
Gohan! Don't you go
fightin' that monster-like guy!
Gohan! Gohan-chan!
Chichi, simmer down!
I-Is that child really planning to fight Cell?
The same Cell that we were no match for?
You brat!
The young boy who was
thought to be selling bento lunches
is fighting for some reason!
However, Cell has overwhelming superiority!
The young boy is just running away from him!
I-Is it okay for that child to be fighting?
It's crazy! It's outrageous!
Monarch, the military
preparations have been completed.
We'll get that guy for sure this time!
It's futile.
With that monster Cell's power, there's
nothing our military can do against him.
B-But...!
The young man who saved the
Earth before fought him and lost.
And now, the person who that young man
designated with full confidence is now fighting.
In that event, we too will entrust
everything to that young boy.
The fate of Earth rests in
the fight that boy puts up.
Up to now, Gohan hasn't...!
Gohan-san...!
Gohan!
Son Gohan, if you must blame someone,
blame your own father for roping
you into this ill-advised battle!
G-Gohan-san...
H-How horrible!
Maybe I overdid that a little.
That was a bit immature on my part.
Chichi! Chichi! Hold it together!
H-How could this be?
The bento salesboy recklessly challenged Cell,
a-and has lost his young life!
I-Is he dead?
Poor thing!
Goku! You're responsible for this!
You've completely underestimated the situation!
Everyone warned you about this!
Goku, you're the one who killed Gohan!!
Take it easy, Piccolo.
Gohan's ki ain't dropped in the least, has it?
It's true!
Now then, Son Goku, the absurd jokes are over.
Take one of those senzu, and fight me again!
You idiot!
Take a good look behind you!
What?
Gohan-san!
You're alive, Gohan?!
This is a surprise.
You're exceptionally tough, aren't you?
L-Let's stop this already.
This fight is meaningless.
Are you losing your nerve, kid?!
Of all the things you could have said,
you're telling me to put
a stop to the Cell Games
because they're meaningless?
Yeah.
There is meaning to them!
For me, this is a pastime.
I am going to defeat you,
and then little by little,
I will take my time to kill all of humanity.
If you wish to save the Earth...
I-I really don't want to fight you.
I don't want to kill you.
Even though you're as evil as you are...
W-What's Gohan saying?
He's speaking so softly, I can't pick it up.
W-What are you getting on the long-range mike?
I-I can't make anything out.
I don't like fighting and
stuff the way Father does.
I can understand well enough
why you don't like to fight.
But I can't understand
what you mean by saying
you wouldn't want to kill me.
You couldn't kill me in a hundred years!
How about it? Am I wrong?
I'm beginning to understand more
and more why it is that Father said
I'm the only one who could defeat you, Cell.
What is this?
You say you can defeat me?
Ever since I was little,
whenever I flew into a rage,
things have happened
that not even I understood.
The first time I realized it
was when the Saiyan Raditz
came from space to attack us.
Indeed! Fools such as
yourself are quite uncommon!
To think that you would
be so completely taken in!
Just as I thought, there's no
way that you could be a warrior!
Th-That was dirty!
But I'm not like you. I'm a first-rate warrior!
I have absolutely no
hesitations about killing you,
even if you are my brother!
Shall I provide you with a sample?
Father...
There you go, there you go!
Suffer even more! Your death is near!
B-Battle power...
O-One thousand... one thousand
three hundred seven...?!
Stop picking on...
...my father!!
And when I was trained by Piccolo-san...
Stop your bawling!
If you don't get quiet,
I'm going to snap your neck!
Apparently, you still haven't realized it yourself.
The power that you have
locked within you is something else.
That's why we're going to draw
out that power through training,
until you can use it effectively.
It can't be... I don't have any power like that.
You want to see some proof?
W-What are you doing?!
Stop it! That hurts! That hurts! That hurts!
Here you go!
Come on! Show me that
power you have locked away!
W-What the...?
W-What a surprise!
This is more than I imagined!
When I went to Planet Namek,
and fought with Freeza...
Kuririn-san!
You're thinking of saving him?
It's pointless, he'll die momentarily.
How about instead, you
worry about your own safety?
Out...
Out of my way!!
When I fly off the handle,
I seem to go beyond my own will,
and start fighting
hysterically with amazing power.
And now that I've trained in
the Room of Spirit and Time,
I've powered up.
Father took that into account...
But if it comes to that, I'm sure I will kill you.
That's an interesting story!
You blew it.
Did you think I would be
scared off by hearing that story?
You really are a brat.
On the contrary, now I want to
make you angry, no matter what.
I want to have a look at this
so-called hidden power you have!
Come on, come on, come on!
Come on, now...
G-Gohan-san!
Goku! Put a stop to this!
If you go in and fight in his
place, Cell will release Gohan!
Goku!
It's okay. Gohan can win.
Get angry, Gohan. Get angry.
Get angry! Get angry and
show me your true power!
Get angry!
Get angry! Get angry!
Get angry! Get angry! Get angry!
The bento salesboy is getting beaten up!
Cell's assault is all one-sided!
Can this boy escape the pinch he is in?
What do you say, Mister Satan?
Impossible. Not that bento salesboy.
If someone doesn't step
in and fight in place of him–
Oh! Then Mister Satan, you'll take his place?!
People of the world,
it appears that we will be able to see
the grandeur of Mister
Satan's fighting once again!
M-M-My stomach started hurting again!
Satan-sama...!
U-Unfortunately, it seems that
Mister Satan still has a stomachache.
A-Are we to just watch on as the
bento salesboy gets killed like this?!
Is there no one who can save him?!
Come on, get angry! Get angry,
and show me your true power!
C-Cell got knocked on his can!
Son Gohan, no matter what it takes,
I'm going to make you angry.
That's right, Cell. That will be fine.
Make Gohan angry.
When that happens, you will
experience some true terror.
The key to the fate of Earth lies
in Gohan's grasp as he fights...
Will Gohan's hidden
power be able to burst forth?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Watch out, everybody!
Cell is sending something after us,
in order to get Gohan angry!
Whoa, what are those things?!
Little monsters are coming out of Cell's back!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Teeny Menaces!!
Attack of the Cell Juniors."
Stop, Cell! Please stop!
I can't control my power yet!
"Next time"
"Teeny Menaces!!
Attack of the Cell Juniors"