Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Nine days from today,
on the morning of the 21st,
I have decided to hold a martial
arts tournament, called the Cell Games.
In the event that all representative
warriors are defeated by me,
I have decided to kill
every last person in the world.
What?!
S-Something astounding has happened!
"Goku and Gohan... The Hero
Father and Son's Ultimate Level-Up."
After Cell's television broadcast
the entire world went into disarray.
As such, people began their
futile efforts to hide themselves,
so as to avoid becoming
targets, no matter how small.
W-What are you doing?! Hurry it up!
That monster is going to be coming!
The hell with it!
You stupid punk!
It was indeed a panic.
I feel like running somewhere far away myself.
But no matter where
you run, it will be the same.
That's right.
Cell said if all the representative
warriors were beaten,
he would kill every human
throughout the world, after all.
I-I know! What if we were to use
the spaceship at Bulma's house
to escape to some faraway planet?
Oolong!
After all, Cell might not
come chasing after us into space.
You have no feelings for Yamucha-sama
or Kuririn-san, or the others, do you?
You lousy traitor.
T-This is all my fault! If only, at that time...
I had destroyed No. 18...
I'm going to go fight Cell!
What?!
It's my fault!
Kuririn!
You must not go!
He is not a foe you can fight and win.
As your master, I will not
allow you to throw your life away!
If you absolutely must do this,
then you can wait until
the Cell Games have begun.
Don't be so hard on yourself, Kuririn.
Put your money on Goku and the others.
How much can those Saiyans, with the
ridiculous power they keep under wraps,
power themselves up in
the Room of Spirit and Time?
How long will it be before
Goku-san and Gohan-san come out?
Still nearly three more hours before one full day.
Hmph! They won't necessarily
come out after one full day.
They could get greedy and
go considerably over their time.
There's no reason to be hasty.
There's still nine more
days until the day of the fight.
It hasn't even been one whole day
since you came out of the room, right?
You'd better get a little rest.
I will go in first.
That will be an outright waste of time.
What lies ahead is a domain
that only Saiyans can set foot into.
Fine, I'll let you do as you like,
but then I will take the remaining eight days.
It's too bad about that.
You can only go into the Room of Spirit and Time
for two days–48 hours–during your lifetime.
W-What?
What will happen... if you go over 48 hours?
Exit from room vanishes. Can never leave again.
Still, Dad, we can use it
for about 23 more hours.
Those are Goku and Gohan's ki.
Have they already come out of the room?
What? Why would they, as early as this?
Oh? Vegeta and Trunks are here too!
I feel Cell's ki too, so he's alive.
What in the world is going on?
Is that Gohan? I hardly recognized him!
Tell me what's going on.
Well, as it happens...
Say, before that, Mister Popo,
would you make us something to eat?
I'm unbelievably famished, and all!
That's just like you, Goku.
Yum, yum!
Indeed, this is sure delicious!
Goku, I'd like to
ask you something...
You guys... did supposedly eat food
while you were in there, didn't you?
Om cosh me ane!
Me nin ean, mun nee'eh me nonn No'an
can coom ennyninn neshenn, shee?
Sho ish minn a nonn naim shinsh
me man ennynin nish nummy!
Hey, don't talk until you've properly
swallowed what you have in your mouth.
Be sure you chew!
Of course we ate!
We did eat, but neither me nor
Gohan can cook anything decent, right?
So it's been a long time since
we had anything this yummy!
S-So that's it.
What is that? Is that Super Saiyan?
No... the air about them is a little different.
They're in that state as if
it were natural for them!
Thank you for providing this feast!
Ooh, I'm full, I'm full!
Sorry to keep you waiting, Trunks. Start talking.
R-Right! As it happens...
Hey! Hey!
You're sure caught up in that.
Do you see something?
Out of the way!
We can't go forward, you know!
That's right, that's right!
Weren't you coming this way?
If you're not coming, then I'll go to you.
You forgot something!
I don't get any of this...
This part here is strange too...
This is really no use trying to figure out...
What does all this mean?
I took a peek into No. 16's memory,
and it's all information about Son-kun.
What, now? What, now?
I see.
Yeah.
I'm sure No. 16 is an Artificial Human who
Doctor Gero built solely to defeat Son-kun.
But right now, he doesn't
show that manner at all, huh?
Either that, or I wonder if somewhere even now,
he's thinking that he'd like to beat Son-kun.
Nah...
He has a complex manner about
him that I don't completely understand,
but I can't bring myself to
think he's that bad a guy.
In any event, there's no doubt that he
possesses an unusual gentleness to him.
That's true, huh?
Maybe it's a result of history being changed,
but if you think about it,
this may turn out to be lucky.
After all, he's become a valuable
warrior, who will fight against Cell for us.
Strange things do happen, don't they?
So that's how it is, then?
A martial arts tournament, huh?
He sure has thought up something interesting.
I-Interesting, you say?
Mister Popo, my gi ain't been thrown out, right?
N-No, not thrown out.
I washed and left it.
Thank you, Mister Popo.
You don't have to wear that.
If you ask Mom, she'll give you a new one.
Naw. This is still best.
I want to fight as an Earthling, as well.
Piccolo-san, I want new clothes too.
Your clothes, Piccolo-san.
Understood. I'll present
you with something handsome.
Thank you, Piccolo-san!
So...
How about it?
Do you think you have
what it takes to defeat Cell?
I don't know!
I ain't seen him since he's
become that perfect form of his.
I think I'll go have a look at him right now.
Son Goku, huh?
Yeah. That's right.
What do you think?
This is the ring of the Cell Games,
which will determine the fate
of the world nine days from now.
Do you like it?
It's an awfully puny ring to determine any fate.
So, you've finally turned into it, huh?
That's your perfect form, then?
That is correct.
W-What's going on?
S-Such a ferocious ki! Is that Cell?
Yeah. But that's not all.
There's one other, mind-boggling ki there...
Goku!
It's Goku's ki!
You've finally come out, haven't you,
from the Room of Spirit and Time?
I will be sure to come for
the matches. So until then,
don't you kill even a single person! Got that?
It looks like it will be a good match.
Son Goku, huh?
It seems that this will be an even
more enjoyable event than I thought.
H-How was it, Goku-san?
To be honest, I didn't think
he had gotten that strong.
I couldn't guess how strong
he could become if he felt like it.
I won't know until I try,
but the way things are,
I probably can't win, I bet.
T-That can't be!
Is that so?
You'd better use the Room
of Spirit and Time again.
There is still time.
We just made up the order.
After this, I will go in,
and then I understand
Vegeta will be going in alone.
Hmph. But really, once I go in,
none of this will be necessary.
You'll excuse me, but I took a pass.
He's just not the kind of
opponent I can match up against.
And then, Trunks.
After that, Goku and Gohan,
you two will go in again.
–No, me and Gohan have had enough.
–What?!
We'll train in the outer world.
We have nine whole days,
so something will turn out.
W-What did you say?!
W-What's this? Goku says
they will train in the outer world?
Does Goku have some chance of winning?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Gohan, our next training is to go
home, take it easy, and rest up.
Ain't no sense in forcing
ourselves to train any further.
Gohan-chan! What's the matter with your hair?!
Have you gone and turned delinquent?!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Goku's Composure!?
Let's Rest and Wait for the Cell Games."
Are you sure we should be taking it so easily?
"Next time"
"Goku's Composure!?
Let's Rest and Wait for the Cell Games"