The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Boo's fury had given birth
to another, evil Majin Boo.
There were two Majin Boos–the battling,
evil Majin Boo and the original Boo!
I-I'll turn you into chocolate!
Boo transformed yet again, and a
purely evil Majin Boo had appeared!
Ah, hell!
This Majin Boo is able to seek out our ki!
Is there indeed anything that can be done?
"A No-Timeout Catastrophe!!
Earth's Humanity Exterminated."
W-Who the hell is that?!
This is the transformed Boo?
I knew it. Here you are.
W-We'll be killed!
W-What an incredible ki!
Gimme!
Gimme!!
Gimme? What the hell do
you want us to give you? Tell us!
Gimme the guy who will fight me.
He promised that guy would fight me.
I want to do it now and kill him.
He has to be here. I know
there's a great power here.
It's the only place he could be.
H-He's become able to seek
out ki after all. Th-This is bad!
What was that voice just now?!
W-Who's here makin' that loud-voiced ruckus?
What?! Who is that?!
Gimme the guy I'm going to fight.
That guy whose hair turns
golden made me a promise.
Those who you're looking for are
sure to appear in three–no, two days!
So until then, don't do anything, just wait!
Are those guys strong?
Stop killing people for no reason!
–Gimme.
–W-Wait!
To be sure, those two are here.
But right now, they are sleeping.
Wake them, we'll fight!
Th-They just barely went to sleep!
Let them sleep a little
while longer! I beg you!
They still aren't at their full power yet!
And as long as you're going to fight,
you'll want to go against
warriors at their full power, right?
It's just no good. I hate waiting!
Th-The promise was for two days
afterward. There's still another day!
I've changed my mind.
My mind changes fast. Gimme!
He's come to fight Trunks and Goten!
He's gotta be kiddin'! Who's
gonna let somethin' like that happen?!
I'm gonna go shoo that guy away!
W-Wait! Chichi, if you head on out there,
he ain't the kind of foe
you can do nothin' about!
Let me go! Let me go! Let me go, I tell you!
Let me go! Pa, let go of me! Let me go!
Chichi!
Gimme the strong guy!
If I let Goten and Trunks fight now, there's
absolutely no chance of them winning.
Somehow, I have to buy us some time.
Gimme the strong guy!
Please! Wait just a moment!
Just a little while more will be fine!
Th-That's right! You said you were
going to kill every Earthling, didn't you?
There's still a great deal
of people who are still alive!
You can fight after you're
done with that, can't you?
Piccolo-san!
S-Sorry, those of you people still remaining!
We'll be sure to bring you
back to life with the Dragon Balls!
W-What's this?
So that's it! He's looking over
the condition of the lower realm!
Is he thinking of taking off
to kill those remaining people?
Still, at least it will buy us some time!
What is he walking around for?!
He thinks he's so great!
Kuririn...
go wake up Trunks and Goten right now
and take them to the Room of Spirit and Time.
They'll train in there.
In that place, they can do a
lot of training in a short time.
Eh? Why don't you let them fight right away?
Because I wasn't aware of that guy's power.
In his state, there's no way that the little
squirts could beat him, even with Fusion.
Tell those half-pints that if they don't
want to die while they're still little scamps,
then to train for all they're worth in there.
Okay!
Now's my chance! I'm gonna
push him over the side!
See here, Chichi! Stop it!
–Y-You dummy!
–I am Chichi!
Chichi-san!
Hey, you! Wait there!
I'll kill you!
Chichi! Are you okay?
Goten-chan... Goten-chan must
not be allowed to fight him! Pa!
What's this? He sure is a strange one, huh?
I'm afraid!
Wake up! Wake up, I say! Wake up!
Hey! Wake up!
I can't eat any more...
This is no time for you to be talking
in your sleep! Wake up! Wake up!
G-Gone all the way around...
Why?
What is this?!
Wow, how pretty!
What is it?
What's the matter, Kaioshin-sama?
J-Just now, on Earth,
there's something happening.
What is this? What's going on?!
Ten-san!
Chaozu!
F-Forgive me, you people. I will surely
bring you back to life with the Dragon Balls!
I've killed all the Earthlings.
Now, I will fight. Gimme that guy!
Understood! But we have to prepare
for the fight. Give me some time!
Two hours–no, just one hour will be fine!
Please!
One hour? How long is that?
Once all the sand in this sandglass has fallen.
No!!
Why not?! Why can't
you wait for just an hour?!
Goten-kun and him aren't
going to run away or anything!
You're a smart-aleck!
Hold it! That girl is Mister Satan's child!
Mister Satan's child
says she wants you to wait!
It's true. Her smell is similar to Satan.
All right, I'll wait for you.
When time is up, I'll kill everyone!
I'll even kill Satan's child!
Th-That was close!
What is happening up in the heavenly realm?
It's strange. Fireworks at a time like this?
Y-You're awake?! Go to the Room
of Spirit and Time right now and train!
W-What's happened?
The people of Earth... have just
about all... been exterminated.
By Boo?! But there was still
a good deal remaining, right?
No... The Earth itself
remains largely unharmed.
I don't understand. Why is this happening?
Kaioshin-sama...
A-Aren't you done yet? It's well past
time we should be finished, isn't it?
Oh, is it that time already? Yes, it
is time we should be finished, huh?
Hoo! The fact that we aren't done yet
means that you must have
incredible dormant capacities!
Would you please cut this out?!
There's no way I'm going to be able
to beat Majin Boo with all
this... nonsense... of yours...
W-What was that? That power
that just seemed to boil up?
W-Was that me?
Hurry up and sit down!
If you keep fooling around,
we'll lose that much more time!
I-I'm sorry about that!
Really, I am...
A-Awesome! He really
ain't any ordinary old geezer!
Y-Yes! He's the Kaioshin from
15 generations before me, after all!
For what that's worth...
Dormant capacities are really one's
true power that's hidden away, right?
That's what I believe.
That couldn't be! Just how much
power does Gohan have hidden away?!
This is great! Gohan is one extraordinary guy!
Majin Boo has transformed
into the ultimate evil.
Goten and Trunks begin training anew.
And the elderly Kaioshin's training was for real.
Will Gohan's hidden power be fully realized?
The battle with Majin Boo draws closer.
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Oh? Is Piccolo planning
to have Goten and Trunks
fight inside the Room of Spirit and Time?
If they fight in there,
then even if they do get killed,
by destroying the entrance,
Majin Boo will never be able to come out again.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Special Training Is a Success!!
You're Finished Now, Majin Boo."
All right, the little guys are ready.
"Next time"
"The Special Training Is a Success!!
You're Finished Now, Majin Boo"
The battle is about to begin!