Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Goku and Gohan have gone
into training on the Earth's surface,
whereby they rest for
three days, train for three days,
and then rest for three days, as Super Saiyans.
I will take you on now!
And, in the Heavenly Realm, Piccolo,
having entered the Room of
Spirit and Time for the first time,
was engaged in rigorous training as well.
Be sure you defeat Cell for us!
You're entering, aren't you?
Into this Tenkaichi Tournament?
Eight days remain until the Cell Games,
which have plunged all of Earth
into the depths of terror, are held.
"Hidden Power!!
When Gohan Was a Baby."
I remember at the time, Yajirobe was like,
"Sorry 'bout that!
I-I got lotsa respect for ya!
Lemme be your friend!"
That's no good, Gohan.
You've got to control
your power just so, like me...
Whoops! I goofed,
I goofed! But not this time...!
Oh, man...
You gotta be kiddin' me!!
I don't care if it's because
you're goin' to fight Cell or not,
when you're eatin' at least,
stop bein' Super Saiyan!
At this rate, no matter
however many place settin's–
no, however many houses we
may have–it won't be enough!
This afternoon, I was meanin' to
have a birthday party for Gohan!
Why are you doin' this to me?!
Birthday party?
But Mother, today isn't my birthday...
I know that!
But even so, listen.
When you were in that
Room of Spirit and Time place,
Gohan-chan turned 11 years old!
Birthdays are important milestones and all.
I decided that we were
goin' to celebrate it today.
Now, Goku-sa, you go on out.
G-Go? Go where?
While I'm gettin' ready for the party,
I couldn't stand it if you
broke anythin' else on me.
Go catch us a huge fish
or somethin' for the party.
I get you.
If that's the case, I guess I'll be off.
I'll go too!
Father, me too.
Gohan-chan, you'll stay here studyin'.
Until the party begins,
you study good and hard!
After all, you've fallen
behind a whole year's worth!
Even though it's my birthday?
Your birthday's got nothin' to do with it!
B-But...
Gohan...
Your mother's right. You stay here and study.
W-What?
G-Goku!
Father!
Goku-sa!
You don't have a fever...
Great, great! It sounds like
he's studyin' nice and hard.
But still, what has come over Goku-sa?
He's never once before told him to study,
or anythin' else a father might say.
It's kind of spooky, huh?
I hope it doesn't start snowin' red snow next.
Yahoo!
Goku is romping around like a little kid!
Hey, Kuririn!
Here!
You know, Goku...
It would have been nice if
Gohan could have come too.
Chichi-san doesn't have anything
else in her mind except for studying.
On top of that, after having
even you tell him to study like that,
I feel sorry for Gohan.
It's all right.
In eight days, me and
Gohan have to go fight Cell.
Cell is ridiculously strong.
To be honest, it's a fight I ain't sure we can win.
So, during the time until then,
I want to allow Gohan
to be together with Chichi.
Goku...
Let's see...
I'm sure I put that tablecloth
away in here somewhere...
Where is it, where is it?
Yow!
What's this?
Wow! This sure takes me back!
He's gotten a lot bigger now,
but there was a time when he was like this, too.
He's so cute.
But ain't he awful tiny?
Babies are supposed to be tiny.
Um... w-we oughtta be givin'
him a name before too long, huh?
I've already thought up a name for him.
Y-You've already thought of one?
Einstein.
–Einstein?
That's a fantastic name for a scholar!
Huh?
There, there. That's better.
I'm sure he's not fond of that name.
Oh, no! Well, Archimedes is okay, too.
That's no good either.
Well then, what do you think is good, Pa?
I thought up a whole mess of them!
See?
Here goes! Ready?
Gyumataro... Gyumahiko...
Doctor Gyuma... Gyumanosuke...
Gyumashin... Gyumantohihi... Gyumasuki...!
Pa, yours aren't any good either.
No good, huh?
That's right...!
Me?
Goku-sa, haven't you thought of any names?
You've got some, right? At least one?
I...
I'm hungry!
Goku-sa!
What are you talkin' about,
here at an important time like this?!
We just ate asagohan a little while ago!
[asagohan: breakfast]
I mean really! You're not a child!
Can't you wait until hirugohan?!
[hirugohan: lunch]
Sorry, sorry...
Goku-sa, you're always like this!
Oh, Chichi!
What?!
Uh, listen to this for a sec!
Asagohan!
Hirugohan!
Gohan!
Gohan...?
That's it! This guy wants
to have Grandpa's name!
I'm sure that's gotta be it.
If you wanna give him
the name of my fellow pupil,
Son Gohan, I got no complaints.
All right! You're Gohan! Son Gohan!
So, you're happy about
that too, Gohan? Son Gohan!
Goku-sa...
Gohan!
You don't have to study any more today!
What are you doin'?!
Hurry up and go help Goku-sa!
Right!
Currently, I am extremely scared!
However, today I will gather my courage,
and literally put my life at risk,
in order to bring you this report.
Ladies and gentlemen, please watch.
That person over there is he
who is now the topic of conversation
throughout the world, Cell.
Why did I take this job, anyway?
When all of humanity could be
destroyed in eight days anyhow,
what will it gain me to go to my grave now?
However, I've realized this too late.
It's all hopeless. I can only keep going.
I'm scared, all right!
Ladies and gentlemen,
just in case something happens,
let me wish you my final farewells.
Hurry it up!
Right...
Cell-san, please excuse me a moment.
Uh, where is it that you come from?
Are the rumors that you came
here in a UFO from deep space true?
What is your true goal
in holding the Cell Games?
If all of the representatives lose to you,
which of Earth's districts
will you begin destroying first?
If humans were to escape into space in a rocket,
would you chase them down and kill them?
You are annoying scum.
And you're in my way.
I-It's huge!
I wonder if this will do.
Sorry, but would you share
some of your fruit with us?
Okay, that's enough, Goku!
Bravo, bravo!
Wow, how pretty!
Look there, Gohan-chan! There's some birds!
Parents and child, three of them. Just like us.
You're right.
There, did you see them, Gohan-chan?
Oh, no!
Wait up!
Gohan!
Gohan-chan!
G-Gohan-chan! Goku-sa,
don't dilly-dally, stop him!
Whoops...!
Gohan-chan!
You're not hurt anywhere?
Thank goodness!
Your father saved you!
That's your father for you!
No, it wasn't me...
It's great that you saved him, but Goku-sa,
it was wrong of you to be lettin'
go of the handrail in the first place!
If you hadn't been lucky,
he could have gotten killed!
If you aren't more careful,
there's gonna be trouble, you know!
S-Sorry.
Come on, Gohan-chan, let's
just ignore this awful father
and go home together with your mother, okay?
Ah, Chichi!
Sorry about that, making
a hole and everything...
Father, let's go home.
Yeah, right.
I'm sure there's an
incredible feast waiting for us!
I'm so hungry!
Gohan-chan, congratulations
on your 11th birthday.
"Happy Birthday"
Congratulations!
Thanks!
I brought you a heap of presents, Gohan!
Wow, incredible! Thanks, Grandpa Gyumao!
Now then, Gohan-chan,
first you have to blow out
the candles on your cake.
Great!
Be sure to make a wish!
Right.
Gohan, looks like you still
can't control your power, huh?
Gohan...!
Mother, I'm sorry.
What's the use?
You are Goku-sa's child, after all.
Goku and Chichi have warmly
watched over Gohan's development.
And Gohan has also felt the
deep affection held by both of them.
However, will Goku and Gohan be able
to preserve peaceful times such as these?
Seven days remain until
the Cell games are held.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
The army is launching an
all-out attack against Cell?
Stop! You'll just be killed for no reason!
Say, Goku-sa, is there no
way that you can bring back
Kami-sama and the Dragon Balls?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Seek Out Kami-sama!!
Goku's Great Instantaneous Movement."
Father, you can Instantaneously
Move through outer space?
"Next time"
"Seek Out Kami-sama!!
Goku's Great Instantaneous Movement"