Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
My power has shot up!
Bring Vegeta here at once.
You're still alive, huh?
As a result, I'm going to be spared.
Who is it that will be able
to put a stop to Freeza's ambitions?
"Back from the Brink of Death –
The Miracle Man, Vegeta."
This 50-times gravity
is as tough as you'd expect.
Yamucha and the others must be going at it.
I wonder if it's the same training that I did.
No, I can't afford to be doing that.
Damn...
Mock me, will you?
O-One more time!
And he was so close, too?
M-My body is so heavy...
You almost had him, huh?
All right, now me.
Here goes!
Ten-san, good luck!
Don't rush, now. Take your time.
What?
I have no intention of doing
the same training as those guys.
Teach me your techniques now.
I can't do that. There is an order
to these things, you know... huh?
Anyhow, when you try to jump straight
to the end, things are apt to turn out badly.
By the way, if you're not doing anything,
would you like to pull weeds with me?
Why are you in such a hurry to grow stronger?
You promised me that you had
given up on defeating Freeza, didn't you?
For shame. Liars have to swallow
a thousand needles, you know.
For that matter, you should be enjoying
your life here in the Next World more.
This can be quite fun to do.
Hmph! You're just playing the fool.
Huh? Are you leaving?
D-Damn...
Hey! Let's eat!
Son Goku was something else,
but you guys eat a lot too, huh?
We can't be outdone by Goku!
If he ate 10 bowls, then I'll eat 20!
Hey, come on now! If you don't
stop now, you'll eat my portion, too...
Besides,
it's pretty good.
Oh, it is, it is, huh?
I know I may not look it, but when I was
a youngster, I went to this cooking class,
and I was so good the teacher there told
me I would make a good husband someday,
so I'm somewhat confident of
my ability to– huh? Hey, you guys!
Ah, all full, all full...
Good grief. The dead these
days have no sense of moderation.
Okay, now that my belly is full, I'll be fine.
I'll catch you this time for sure.
You won't be able to do that to me any longer.
Got you!
He did it!
I did it!
I'm surprised you can get by on just water.
You did it, Tenshinhan!
Ten-san, incredible!
Those guys are something else.
Once they've gotten a handle on
this, they'll make rapid progress.
Don't you think so?
I have no interest in those small fry.
I will not allow the existence of anyone
stronger than me. That's all there is to it.
I did it! I did it!
I caught him! Look!
Oh? Oh, my! Even Chaozu
has mastered this, has he?
I see. All right, I'll give
you your next training lesson.
Hey, Gregory!
Hi! Hello, everybody! I am Gregory!
This guy is your next opponent.
Please knock me down as
hard as you can with this hammer.
You don't need to hold back.
However...
That assumes that you
can keep up with my speed.
All right, I'll do it.
Here.
W-What's with this weight?!
Ready? Here we go!
B-Bring it on!
Okay...
Too slow, too slow!
D-Damn!
Yamucha, hang in there!
Yamucha-san, fight!
Hey, Piccolo, aren't you going to do this?
It's a waste of time. I'll train by myself.
Piccolo...
Chaozu...
What's the matter? Are you giving up already?
D-Dammit!
Hey! We're going to take a nap now!
Piccolo is sleeping comfortably out back.
Don't push yourselves too hard.
I-I'm not about to be lumped
in with that guy! I'm up next!
My, my...
Oh, dear...
There's someone even stronger than that Saiyan.
How is he?
His condition is fairly serious.
His life signs are extremely faint.
Even if he does pull through, I'm not sure
whether or not he will regain consciousness.
Make sure he recovers, no matter what it takes!
Use whatever methods you have to, understand?!
Y-Yes, sir.
Otherwise, it will mean my life.
All right...
Hey, hey! You can do it, you can do it!
Chaozu, go easy on him! Easy!
–Okay, this is it, the bottom
of the 9th, 2 outs, bases loaded!
–All right, Chaozu, go!
–The count is 3-2. If he runs away,
the walk scores a run, and it's goodbye!
–Knock it out of here!
M-Me, run away?! You're
trying to make a fool of me!
V-Very well, I'll show you!
It's not going to be that easy!
Any time you're ready.
W-Why, you! Hit this one, if you can!
Not so fast! Forkball!
"Crack!"
W-W-What was that?!
When you go out, call out to
someone first, and lock everyone else out!
That was a come-from-behind,
bases-loaded, say-goodbye home run.
Oh my, Gregory, what are you doing?
With Chaozu's hit just now,
we've all cleared him.
That's right.
What's that? Is this true, Gregory?
T-These guys didn't hold back at all.
Wow, that was fast, huh?
Oh, my, just over an hour? Are
you sure you're not going too fast?
Okay, Kaio-sama, please
give us our next training.
Next, we will spar.
Nothing is better than
sparring to learn each other's
strengths and weaknesses, after all.
As a matter of fact,
we've been waiting for this.
Ready to go at it?
Oh, hold on, hold on,
I'll determine the match-ups.
Let's see, who should I put you with?
I'll do this!
Oh ho, you've woken up, have you?
All right then, Piccolo and–
–All the rest of them.
–Wha–?
What?!
You think I can fight decently against someone
who had trouble with a monkey, or some batter?
At your level, even if there were
ten of you, you'd still be a pushover.
You bastard, now you've said it!
My, my, what a humorless conversation
this is. Did you come here to fight?
Well, there is some truth to what Piccolo says.
Kaio-sama!
To be honest, at your current ability,
a one-on-one fight would be absurd.
But with all three of you, perhaps–
Don't be ridiculous!
They don't even have a
1 in 10,000 chance of winning.
What's the matter? You want to go at it?
All right!
Watch this. I'll put you away in five seconds.
Ready? Begin!
What?!
What the–?!
They're surprisingly tough, aren't they?
Whooee! That smarts!
W-Why, you!
Chaozu!
Are you okay, Chaozu?!
Hey, don't panic.
–You guys are already dead. You don't
need to worry yourself pointlessly.
–But...
The pain of the body is just a remnant of
when you were alive. It will soon be gone.
3... 2... 1... there.
Huh?
See?
How? Up until a little while ago,
their movements were so slow,
and suddenly, I barely recognize them.
Is this because of Kaio's
training? It couldn't be...
Resume sparring!
Piccolo...
Take off your weights.
Yeah, and then we'll fight you again.
That same trick isn't going to work anymore.
All right!
Okay, that's enough.
That's all for sparring. We're moving on
to the next training. Everyone come with me.
Oh, right...
A vegetable you eat in the morning that
makes you fart is called asa-para-gas...
[asa: morning]
...asa paragas...asa paragas!
That was a great one!
R-Right...
There's quite a bit of damage
here. There may be no hope.
I'm counting on you. If you
don't regain consciousness,
I'm the one who Freeza-sama
is going to take it out on, after all.
Then again, even if you
do come back to life here,
you'll be on your way to hell again by
Freeza-sama's hand soon enough anyhow.
That should do it.
Well, all there is to do now
is wait for you to wake up.
Don't give us any more trouble, okay?
Vegeta-chan?
How is Vegeta?
He should regain consciousness shortly.
That is good, huh?
Y-Yes, sir.
W-What was that explosion just now?!
It cannot be!
Looks like you've underestimated
my powers of recovery, huh?
Now, then...
Dammit, it's coming from
the treatment chamber, all right!
Zarbon-san, hurry!
Oh, no! He escaped outside!
He did what?!
Terrific, Freeza is with him!
Hurry! Hurry and go after him!
Why, you!
Hurry! You must find him at all costs!
He could not have gotten far yet!
Fools! You fell for it all too easily.
Dear Freeza-sama,
Allow me to take this current opportunity
to inform you that your era is at an end.
–Your loving Vegeta.
I have won!
Vegeta, the miracle man who
returned from the brink of death...
Will he be able to outwit
Freeza and collect the Dragon Balls?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Damn, I have to hurry, or Vegeta
will collect all the Dragon Balls!
Just how far is luck going to go my way?!
It serves you right, Freeza!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"An Enormous Battle Power!!
Freeza's Scheme is Shattered."
Father, I'm going to protect the last Ball!
"Next time"
"An Enormous Battle Power!!
Freeza's Scheme is Shattered"