The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
In order to block
Madoshi Babidi and Majin Boo
from heading to Metro West and
destroying it, Goku turned Super Saiyan 3.
Trunks' ki still hasn't moved!
What are you doing, Trunks?!
It's no use. I'll have to buy a little more time...
It's here! It's here!
My! That's terrific! Now,
won't you enjoy some snacks...?
There isn't time for that! I'm in a hurry, so...!
Trunks' ki has started moving!
He's safely found the Dragon Radar
and started moving away from Metro West!
All right! This is where my role ends!
See you later!
You let him get away, didn't you?!
It's your fault for
dilly-dallying around! You dimwit!
I've taken a lot from you.
Now I don't have any more to do with you.
I won't stand you any more!
Die! You fool!
"Absurdly Awful-Looking!?
The Special Training Transformation Pose."
Yahoo!
Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Yea! Yea! Yea! Go! Go! Go!
What's the matter, Father?
H-Hey, Goku... Goku...!
Boo has gone and done it!
He killed Babidi!
What did you say?!
N-Now that you mention it,
Babidi's ki has vanished.
I got the feeling he was
going to do so before too long.
He really has done it!
S-So that means that there's
no one left to order Boo around.
It could be that Majin Boo
will now stand down quietly...
Then, that means that peace
will return to Earth, right?!
I wonder...
It would be nice if that were so, but...
So, don't do anything, just wait!
Stop killing people for no reason!
Two days. Just two days! That's okay, ain't it?
Are those guys strong?
Of course they are!
Yea! Yea! Oh boy, oh boy!!
Yea! Yea! Where should
I start demolishing now?
Over there! Over there!
Over there! Over there! Oh boy, oh boy!
Isn't that...?!
Ready...
Go!!
S-Spare me!
Please! Don't kill me!
Do you think I look cool?
Y-You look cool! Really...!
Well then, let's smooch!
You lied to me, huh?!
"Popular Super-star, Barry Karn"
I get it. Earth women
like this kind of man. Okay!
How's this?
Let's smooch!
No!! I won't!! I won't!! Absolutely not!!
You're a selfish woman!
You turn into a caramel!
Now then, it will be boring
until those strong guys come, so...
I'll play around by eliminating all Earthlings!
H-How awful!
So, we were too optimistic in our thinking.
Now that he's all by himself,
Majin Boo is enjoying destroying cities.
He's pretty nasty about that.
Damn! If that rat felt like it,
he could wipe out the whole Earth in
an instant, everything here included!
It'll be all right!
He ain't going to destroy the
whole Earth at once, I don't think.
When I told Boo that in two days,
someone even stronger than me was
going to fight him, he seemed happy.
For the next two days,
at least, you'll be okay here.
I feel sorry for the Earthlings
down in the lower realm, though.
Well, in any case, we'll return everything
back to normal with the Dragon Balls,
so everything will be fine!
Which means that no matter what,
we have to get those two to
master Fusion in two day's time.
That's what it means.
I have to teach them quick,
or the time I have left will be...
I ain't got more than an hour!
O-One hour?!
That can't be right! You should
have more time than that!
Can we learn this Fusion
technique in just an hour?
That Super Saiyan 3 thing I did earlier?
It's a technique I can
only use in the Other World.
Here in this world, where you have time,
it uses up too much energy,
and all at once, it gets me tired out.
Is that it? So that's why
you're so short of breath, Goku.
In that case, ask Dende to
have him replenish your energy!
No. This is something I have to
go back to the Other World for.
Your remaining time...
...is down to 30 minutes.
You better start getting
ready to go back, Goku.
Uranai O-Baba! Only 30 minutes?
Is that all I have left?!
That's right, unfortunately enough...
Damn! Get back here fast, Trunks!
Are you all right, Gohan-san?
Yes!
It is utterly unbelievable!
For him to be able to swing
around the same Z-sword...
...that generations of Kaioshin found
unmanageable in this short a time...!
It is indeed as I anticipated.
Knowing Gohan-san, he is certain
to be able to defeat Majin Boo.
Gohan-san, why don't you take
a short break for the time being?
You are doing very well!
Better than I had imagined!
No, I still have much to do!
Father continued his training,
even in the Other World.
Even if just a little bit...
Even if just a little bit,
I have to become more like Father!
Majin Boo is still alive, after all!
Goku, there's something
I want to ask now, while I can.
What's that?
With that Super Saiyan 3–
If you had gone all-out,
you could have defeated
Boo, couldn't you have?
How about it? Am I wrong?
Eh. I don't know.
When it comes to Majin Boo's
strength, everything's so unreal.
I think that beating him would
have probably been impossible.
Probably?
Being that it was you, why didn't
you try holding out until the end?
Does it have something to
do with that energy thing?
No...
I'm a person who ain't particularly
even supposed to be here.
I shouldn't be the one to do it.
This is a thing that living people
ought to do something to solve.
Even if I were to defeat him,
someone else outrageous
will appear at some time, right?
It's a dangerous risk to take...
but looking at those
two ultra-prodigy squirts,
I decided to try taking that risk.
You're betting the future of
Earth on Goten and Trunks?
Yeah. Doing it this way is more promising.
You really are something!
It's too bad about Gohan.
Say, when you go back to the
Other Side, tell him I send my regards.
I think the most regrettable thing
about him dying is that he can't see you.
Gohan adored you, after all...
Hey! Trunks has come back!
Welcome back, Trunks! Well done!
I'm back!
I brought it with me!
This, right? The Dragon Radar?
All right!
This is it! This is it! As long as we have this,
we can return the cities
back the way they were,
and bring everyone who died back to life!
Uncle, you're incredibly strong!
You might even be stronger than Papa!
That ain't so!
Not your dad...
Father, you said you were unconscious,
so we thought maybe you were weak!
Goten! Trunks! The Fusion
training continues now!
Right!
I only have a little bit of time left now.
Unless you guys are all fired up,
it really is the end of the Earth.
Understood?
–Yes, Sensei!
What's this, you've gotten
considerably more submissive, huh?
Looks like Super Saiyan 3 has
served a purpose in this area, as well.
Okay, here goes!
Let's do over from where you
were matching your ki together.
–Right!
He's here, he's here!
I have spotted Majin Boo,
altitude 3000 meters, at point SX-39.
He is casually flying southwest.
He's coming this way!
Looks like fun! Let's play, you!
It's okay now. We've gotten clean away...
That's kinda itchy!
H-Help!!
That wasn't very fun.
I-Incredible!
To think those two half-pints could raise
their ki from within themselves to this extent...!
Hang in there, Trunks!
All right!
That's about the same.
This is what it feels
like to fit your ki together.
Practice it well afterwards.
Are you okay, Goku? It looks
like this is pretty hard on you.
I'm all right. I'm all right!
It's only for a little bit longer.
This ain't anything!
Does it use that much of his vitality to
become Super Saiyan 3 here in the lower realm?
N-Now listen.
In order for you to achieve Fusion,
the real hard part starts now.
–Right!
Once you've gotten your
ki to be exactly the same,
if the two of you can also perform the
Fusion Pose together exactly the same,
your Fusion will be complete!
I'm going to show you the Pose,
so you two learn it well! Got that?
–Yes!
First, you two will stand with a
certain degree of space between you.
Then, do this! Be careful
about the angle of your arms!
"Fu–" As you switch your arms,
you move towards each other.
At this time, you move
your feet three steps' worth.
"–sion!"
Carefully watch the angle of your legs!
"Ha!!"
Then you put your fingers together like this!
Again, carefully watch the angle of your legs!
What do we do?! That looks awful!
Oh boy, oh boy! Oh boy, oh boy!
Without anyone to control him,
he's become even more violent!
Boo goes on a rampage!
Okay, you guys try it now!
–Right!
Hurry, Goku! There isn't any time!
Initiate Trunks and Goten to the ways
of this new finishing technique, Fusion!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
I'm just about out of time.
Trunks, Goten, practice
that Fusion good and hard.
You're gonna be the
ones who defeat Majin Boo.
Say, they said they were training,
but is this dance training?
Are they really going to be
able to defeat Majin Boo like that?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"See You Later, Everybody!!
Goku Returns to the Other World."
We've got to work hard,
to make up for Father leaving.
"Next time"
"See You Later, Everybody!!
Goku Returns to the Other World"