Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Ginyu, Commander of the Ginyu Special Corps,
attacks with a frighteningly destructive power!
However, Goku did not fall behind.
In fact, Goku's true power
may be even greater than Ginyu's!
Kaio-ken!
90,000... 105,000... 110,000...
It's still going up!
"What of the Battle's Outcome!? Freeza's
Evil Hand Closes Around the Grand Elder."
1 17,000... Unbelievable!
Even Commander Ginyu's highest
battle rating only reached 120,000.
120,000... 130,000...
140,000!
In all the universe, I should be the one
whose strength is second only to Freeza's!
150,000! How can this be?!
Stop it!
Why you!
180,000?!
I-I can't believe it! This is your true power?!
N-No wonder we didn't
stand a chance against him!
How can a Saiyan be so strong?
And just so we're clear,
I can momentarily put out
much more power than even this!
What?!
You can't possibly...
You can't possibly be...
How awful! I want to get
away from this planet soon!
The Dragon Balls can grant any wish...
Grand Elder-sama, it's Nail-san!
I know.
Why have you returned?
Have I not charged you with the
task of assisting the people from Earth?
My sincerest apologies.
However, it is my duty, above all others,
to defend your life, Grand Elder-sama.
Even so...
If you die, Grand Elder-sama,
the Dragon Balls will also disappear.
If that happens, then the
Earthlings' wish cannot be granted.
Very well.
It's just over there, Kuririn-san.
Okay. Hurry!
Bulma-san!
We're here for the Dragon Radar!
Bulma-san! Please come out
from wherever you're hiding!
Good grief. And us without a moment to lose.
She's never around when
it's really important, huh?
Kuririn-san, look!
Jet-Bike tracks!
Where do you suppose Bulma-san
would have gone on a Jet-Bike?
You don't suppose
she's decided to go off touring
Namek or something at a time like this?
Touring?
We'll follow her!
We have to get the Radar from her and locate
the Dragon Balls before we run out of time!
Right!
There it is.
Sure enough, it appears that
he finally sniffed this place out.
He's almost here.
Dende, come here.
Right.
Go to them, Dende.
The Earthlings stand in need of you.
I've drawn out the power within you,
so you should be able to
arrive in a short amount of time.
B-But...
Go now.
Very well. Grand Elder-sama,
please don't die on us!
I wonder, will I be killed, or
will my time to pass on come first?
Y-You can't possibly be a...
...Super Saiyan, can you?!
You know, Vegeta said
the same kind of thing earlier.
But I have no idea what
you guys are talking about.
A Super Saiyan! A legendary
warrior stronger than any other!
How can this be?!
H-He's a... He's a...
...Super Saiyan, the only
thing Freeza-sama is afraid of?!
Sorry, but there ain't any
way that you can beat me.
I don't want to fight a meaningless battle.
You guys get off this planet.
W-What? Do you really mean that?
I really mean it. Especially you.
You're a much fairer warrior than I thought.
I don't want to kill you.
You don't want to kill me?
You don't want to fight meaningless battles?
Get off this planet?
A Super Saiyan is supposed to be
the strongest warrior in
the universe, who loves to fight.
S-So then,
you're not a Super Saiyan, are you?
You have not completely become a Super Saiyan.
I see... You are not a Super Saiyan after all.
Is that right?
I see. So that is where the Namekians are.
Oh, very well. I suppose I can
leave such a speck of dust alone.
He is here.
What do you want?
My name is Freeza,
and I have a wish that I would like
to have granted with the Dragon Balls.
I have managed to gather
all seven Dragon Balls together,
but for whatever reason,
I cannot seem to get my wish granted.
And so I was hoping you could tell me,
how does one get their wish granted?
I must ask you to leave.
I cannot tell that to anyone who is evil.
Well, well, you still have
some friends around, do you?
They must have fairly low battle powers.
My Scouter did not pick
them up until just now, after all.
Those guys!
Looks like we're in time.
Yeah.
S-Stop! Don't do it! You
don't have a chance against him!
Maybe we don't have a chance,
but we can still land a punch or two!
After all, we're warrior-types
too, just like you are.
Warrior-types?
Oh, all three of you have
battle powers of around 10,000.
I suppose I should expect as
much from warriors of this planet.
As far as I am concerned, however,
you are still like rubbish to me.
What did you call us?!
Stop it! Your deaths will be meaningless!
Nail, you take care of Grand Elder-sama.
My children...
Do you know the password for the Dragon Balls?
Well?
No, I suppose that rubbish
like you would not know.
It was silly of me to have even asked.
I think it would be best
for you to accommodate me.
There is no reason why I should not kill you.
There are two of you here, are there not?
Either one of you would be
acceptable in answering my request.
You can do as you wish. But
before we fight, I will say this much:
The other one, who resides within this house,
is the Grand Elder-sama of Planet Namek.
The Dragon Balls are the
creation of this Grand Elder-sama.
Listen well, and get this
through that head of yours!
If you kill Grand Elder-sama,
the Dragon Balls will also disappear!
Grand Elder?
Now I see. Apparently,
you are telling the truth.
He is certainly different
from the other Namekians.
Grand Elder-san, I do not suppose that you
would be of a mind to tell me, would you?
However,
you would not refuse to
tell me if this gentleman here
were about to be killed, would you?
Nail will not be as easy
to defeat as you may think.
He is the strongest of
the warrior-type Namekians.
You will not be able to do to him
as you have the other
Namekians you have killed up to now.
It appears you have no intention
of telling me, no matter what, do you?
I'm counting on you, Nail.
Buy us as much time as you can.
Understood.
Very well. If you are
going to be as stubborn as this,
then I will show you the terror of
the strongest being in the universe.
You are not a Super Saiyan.
But you are at least far stronger than I am.
Such incredible strength!
Freeza's evil grasp closes
around the Grand Elder and Nail.
Will they be able to keep the
secret of the Dragon Balls safe?
And what will be the outcome of
the fight between Goku and Ginyu?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
I-I can't move... W-What am I doing over there?!
I've made an exchange.
Your body, with its tremendous
hidden power, for my body.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Surprise!! Goku is Ginyu
and Ginyu is Goku."
Father, Mother is going to
cry when she sees your face.
"Next time"
"Surprise!! Goku is Ginyu
and Ginyu is Goku"