Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Freeza's fearsome, severely brutal
power assaults Goku again and again.
However, Goku is not giving in.
They're freaks! Both of them, dammit!
I think I'll put an end
to all this warming up,
and finally get serious about this.
Me too.
Is this where the real super battle begins?
"Freeza's Terrible Declaration!
I Will Defeat You Without Using My Hands."
W-What a ki!
Mid-air battle or ground
battle, which are you better at?
Which, you ask? I guess ground battle.
Where are they going?
They're just changing locations.
They're probably moving to someplace
where they can fight to their heart's content.
What incredible guys!
Father...
This means we're going to fight
on the ground, where I'm better at it?
I'm getting good service.
Or is it... you're that confident?
When you look at me this way, I'm very kind.
I know! How about I offer
you another great service?
Great service?
I will keep myself from using both my hands!
How's that?
Both hands?
How very generous of you.
So then, can I start us off?
Of course.
Whatever you like.
Ah, I've finally perfected it.
Well, she sure seems
to be in a hurry to depart.
Yes, indeed!
Why are you dawdlin' around?!
Tell me! When exactly can we leave?!
While we're all down here
like this, my Gohan-chan is...!
Gohan-chan is...!
S-See here, Chichi-san! Calm down!
Yes, indeed!
What are you doin' durin' all this commotion?!
Dirty old man!
Not at all, Chichi-san!
Yeah, converting this from a
single-seater to a five-seater is quite a chore.
Ah, that reminds me, I haven't decided
where to place the stereo speakers.
We don't need that stuff!
Hurry up and make this thing go!
The biggest issue there is the energy, you see.
The difficulty is, in order to fill
up this spaceship with energy,
it's going to take a little time.
So?
How long's it gonna take?
Well, I just started a
moment ago, so... I don't know.
What?!
You know, guys...
How come we have to
go to Planet Namek too?
That's the place where Piccolo was born.
On top of that, Vegeta and other
even more terrifying guys will be there!
Yamucha-sama!
I, Pu-erh, vow to go and strike
down Yamucha-sama's enemies!
"Certain Victory"
Please just sit tight, okay?
You're not gonna live too long, are you?
Come on! To think, me, goin' to Planet Namek?
Don't even kid 'bout that!
I'm gettin' out while I still...
Thinking of running away by
yourself, huh? Not going to be that easy!
Oh dear, what's the matter?
Have you finished attacking?
Your motions are too slow!
There, and now from the left.
Next, from the right!
Right! Left! Right!
And the final one, left!
He's strong! Got great
speed too, as big as his talk.
G-Goku...
Father!
It's strange. Here I am fighting
someone so incredibly strong,
and I'm giddy with excitement!
If you're not going to come at me,
then I'll bring it to you again!
You know something, I'm glad I met you!
I was getting so bored, and the creatures
on this planet are all so weird anyhow...
Ah, sorry, sorry! I've hurt your feelings!
You're an exception!
When I first saw all of you
clustered around, I was all freaked out,
but you alone were different!
That's enough!
Who would ever expect me to
die here among all these frogs?!
Ah, so gross!
You seemed to have a lot of
promise, so I'll let you be my friend!
Do you want to eat some too?
For a frog, you're really
eating this stuff, huh? Well then...
Would you eat some of this, too?
It's been a long time since I laughed so hard!
Overall, you really do seem
to understand what I'm saying.
Say! If we had a translator
device, I bet I could talk to you!
I'm so clever!
It's finished!
That was easier than I expected.
Indeed, the word "impossible" doesn't
exist for a genius like me, Bulma-sama!
Here goes!
Switch on!
Go on, try saying something!
Don't be shy!
Chaan-ge!!
W-What's this? What is it?
You're the first person I'd encountered
in some time, so I tagged along,
hoping some kind of
chance would come around...
...but to think that I'd be
able to Change so soon...
W-What am I doing over there?!
Just what is going on here?!
You have my gratitude, little miss.
It's enough that I want
to dance the Dance of Joy!
However, this is one unsightly form!
Well then, how about I set
out to find a stronger body?
Who would have thought he
could have possibly done this much?
Dammit... I can't get free...!
I thought you weren't
going to use your hands, right?
The service time has run out.
Well, let me offer my service,
if you want to call it that,
by giving you some advice.
Advice?
You put too much faith in your own strength.
As a result, you leave
yourself wide open to attack.
My thanks.
Incredible!
Goku's super power is such that
not even Freeza is able to appraise it.
With his pride injured,
will Freeza's anger explode?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
I'm so glad to be able
to fight against someone
with the awesome ability that Freeza has.
Goku says that he's fighting seriously,
but he's still keeping
back quite a bit of power.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"That Was No I dle Boast!!
Son Goku, an Audacious, Wonderful Guy."
F-Father, you can beat him, right?
"Next time"
"That Was No Idle Boast!!
Son Goku, an Audacious, Wonderful Guy"