The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Here, put one of these Potara on your left ear.
Having obtained the Potara earrings,
mysterious items used for
merging with someone else,
Son Goku at last returned to this world.
Everything...
...be gone!!
I-I'm sorry, Majin Boo!
W-Why, you...!
Gohan! Here!
Here it is!
D-Dammit, no!
However, Majin Boo absorbed Gohan!
This is great! I'm much
more powered-up than before!
"Merged!! Vegeta's Pride And Goku's Rage."
So, what will you do?!
I have taken the Son Gohan
you wanted to merge with first!
What should I do?
Damn, what should I do?
There is nobody anywhere
left for you to merge with!
Th-That was dirty, Boo, absorbing everyone!
Winning is everything,
just as it must be for you.
Damn you...!
Well now, it's nothing
to get so despondent over.
I'll put you out of your misery soon enough.
You will only suffer for a little bit!
H-Hey, why is Majin Boo still alive?
Th-This is bad. I don't have any bullets
left in my pistol. I can't finish him off!
Y-You don't say.
I am kind at heart, and will give
you a chance to merge with someone.
You have until I count to five to decide
which one of them you will merge with. Got it?
One!
Two!
D-Dende ain't a fighting type.
Even if I do merge with him,
it won't mean any more power.
Three!
I-It's no use!
With Satan, it would be like a power
of 1000 rising to a power of 1001,
and we couldn't beat him!
Or worse, if I'm unlucky, I could
even become weaker, couldn't I?
Four!
Damn! It's all or nothing!
Satan!
Catch...
...this!
That ki...!
I-It's a huge ki! It couldn't be...!
Th-This is as far as I bring you.
I'm sorry it's a bit distant, but I'm too scared!
Hmph. Don't worry about it.
It will just mean my getting killed
by Majin Boo will come a little later.
Five!
I-It's Vegeta!
What's the matter? Have you
given up on combining with someone?
In that case, die right now!!
Lucky!
Instantaneous Movement, huh?
–Okay then, be careful!
–Yeah.
Vegeta!
All right! It really is you!
K-Kakarrot!
G-Goku!
Hey!
W-Why are you here?!
You aren't supposed to return to
this world again! This can't be possible!
V-Vegeta-san!
Good timing! If he combines with that
man, something could just turn out!
W-Why is Vegeta-san there?
Everyone who goes to hell is
supposed to have their souls cleansed,
have their memories taken away,
and become a new life form.
This is Great King Yama's doing!
He might have a blank look about him,
but when he does something, he really does it!
Does he think he can escape me?
Be it under the ground, or another planet,
I will pursue you, no matter how far!
Until I have squeezed the life from you!
He's gone!
H-Hey, that man named Goku or whatever
looked like he was planning
on giving me something.
What could it have been?
I-It doesn't matter now!
Never mind that, I'm going to go
after them and see what happens!
W-Whoa, please, take
me too! I hate to be alone!
I won't let you go!
W-W-What does this mean?!
What's more, the ring over your
head is gone! You've come back to life!
Oh, this? There's this old guy,
the Grand Kaioshin-sama,
who exchanged his life so that I...
We'll talk later. Majin Boo is
coming this way at ultra-speed!
Ba-chan, hurry and run
away to the Other World!
Y-You're right! Good luck, the both of you!
I'll be pulling for you in the Other World!
I thought you'd already been wiped out in hell!
Yama-sama sure did something crafty,
to leave you the way you were, didn't he?
There ain't time! Vegeta, don't talk,
just put this on your right ear! Please!
Why?
If you put this on too, then
you and I can merge together!
Merge?
That's right! Our powers
will be multiplied together,
and a warrior with absurd power will be born!
Don't be ridiculous! How can I believe that?
V-Vegeta!
There's another person
there with a large power!
However, naturally, they're no match for me!
Even if they were to combine together!
Vegeta! There ain't nothing else we
can do, if we're going to beat Majin Boo!
Why should I have to unite with you?!
If I'm to become one with you,
I'd rather be wiped out!
I've found you!
H-He's here!
Stop it, Vegeta! You're simply no match for him!
Please! Put this on!
I refuse! It's the same, no
matter how many times you say it!
Move it!
All right, come on!
You, huh? We've fought before.
No matter what, you are no match for me!
Tenshinhan-san!
Tenshinhan-san...!
Dende? Thanks. Where's Goku?
Where's Majin Boo?
He's gone, with his Instantaneous Movement.
Boo then chased after him.
I see...
W-What's this? Another trick?
What's the matter? Have you chickened out?
Vegeta! This is insane!
Majin Boo is far, far more powered
up than when you fought him before!
Hmph! I know that he has tremendous strength!
Even so, is there any way I can give up?!
So long as there is an opponent
before my eyes, I will fight him!
I am the proud prince of the Saiyans!
The warrior race Saiyan prince!
Dammit!
Stop, Vegeta!
Ah, hell!
Damn it all!
Even the two of you
together cannot stand up to me!
D-Damn...
Stop it, Vegeta!
No matter how many times we
try this, we're no match for him!
There really ain't
anything to do but combine!
Vegeta! Please! Put this Potara on!
Vegeta!
No!
Vegeta-san! Goku-san!
There's no other way to defeat Majin
Boo except to quickly merge together!
What in the world are they doing?
Is it that they don't
get along with each other?
I suppose that under these rocks
would be a good place for them to die.
Please, Vegeta! This ain't
the time to be particular! Okay?
It will be the end for everything!
You irritate me!
Earlier, when you were fighting with me,
you hid the fact that you
had an even higher power!
I was watching from the Other World!
What is this Super Saiyan 3?!
You were toying with me!
You really grate on my nerves!
How am I supposed to
merge with someone like you?!
I'm sorry. The time I can transform
into Super Saiyan 3 is limited.
Your excuses don't matter!
It doesn't change the fact that when
you fought me, you were holding back!
I have been made a fool of!
This fighting between
yourselves is getting all too annoying!
If you're not going to
come at me, then I'll go at you!
Dammit!
All right! Now!
It's hopeless! No matter
what we do, we can't win!
The Earth and everything
else are going to be blown away!
It's the end of everything!
Hmph! Do I care?!
Vegeta, everyone was eaten by Boo!
Including Kuririn, and Chichi...
...and Bulma too!
Piccolo too, and Gohan, Goten, and
even Trunks were absorbed by that guy!
That's what Boo's sudden power-up is due to!
Everyone will have died for nothing like this!
We're going to be killed here,
without being able to offer any resistance!
Is that okay with you, Vegeta?!
Kakarrot!
If we merge, will we really
be able to win against Boo?
I don't know. All that's certain is
that we will become incredibly strong!
It's about time I put you out of your misery!
Give it to me! Quickly!
Stop dawdling! Hurry up!
Vegeta! Here!
I'm done playing with you!
Dammit! It was the right ear, right?
Vegeta! I'll tell you now,
once we merge together,
we can never return to being
two people again! Got that?
W-What was that?! Dammit,
tell me at the last second, will you?
This is the end!
This is okay then, right?
Thank you, Vegeta!
All right, then!
At last, Goku and Vegeta have merged!
And so, the ultimate clash of
the mightiest is about to begin!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
It looks like we managed to
successfully merge together.
What's more, our power
is beyond imagination.
Don't get too carried away with yourself.
You think that joining together
is all it will take to defeat me?!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Magnificent Power!!
Vegetto Surpasses the Ultimate."
No one is a match for Father and Vegeta now!
"Next time"
"Magnificent Power!!
Vegetto Surpasses the Ultimate"