The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Having taken Vegeta's ferocious assault,
Boo has at last let his anger explode!
Why, you...
Why, you...!
I hate you!!
Hmph! How can this be?!
You're strong, on top of which,
you're immortal... it's ridiculous!
Dirty bastard!
You're finished now. Bye-bye. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye. Bye-bye! Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
K-Keep it under control, Trunks!
Even if you were to go,
there's nothing you could do!
You'd just die for no reason!
You'd only be hurting
Vegeta all the more!
No way!!
"For Those Whom He Loves...
Vegeta Perishes!!"
Wait!! Trunks!
Trunks-kun! I'm going too!
Goten!
Stop! It'll be the same if you go!
Don't do anything futile!
But Uncle and Trunks-kun...!
If my Big Brother were here, he'd definitely go!
Goten!
Ah, dammit!
What?!
W-What was that just now?
–Uncle!
–Papa!
Papa!
Who are those pipsqueaks?
Did he still have some companions around?
Well, it's all the same, no matter
how many of those guys there are!
Papa!
Are you okay, Uncle?!
Shake it off, Papa!
Papa! Papa!
Papa! Papa! Papa!
–Is he dead?
–Don't say such a stupid thing!
There's no reason Papa would
die from just this, you know!
B-But, it's impossible for him to fight anymore!
Get this, Goten! Pick out
your ears and listen well!
I heard this from my Mama.
Papa is–get this–the proud Saiyan prince!
A prince?!
That's right! My Papa is incredible!
You think the Saiyan prince would
be beaten by the likes of that guy?!
Ah, Papa!
Uncle!
T-Trunks...
What happened to him?!
Still alive, are you?
It would have been so much easier for you
if you had just died and gotten it over with.
You're such a fool!
My Majin Boo is invincible!
You'll be killed together with those pipsqueaks!
Majin Boo is reprehensible enough...
...but you're the most
reprehensible one of all, Babidi!
Y-You...!
You're as pallid as ever,
aren't you? You're green!
Well, it's no wonder,
now that you've seen the strength
of my Majin Boo's with your own eyes!
It's normal that your complexion
should change, you know!
My face is naturally this color.
Don't get so full of yourself!
You're just a lowly Madoshi!
W-What did you say?!
You've got a lot of nerve,
don't you, angering me so?!
All right, I'll have Majin Boo kill
you in the most painful way there is!
That's kind of you, but I must decline.
You can no longer be allowed
to make use of Majin Boo.
What?! I want you to stop your nonsense!
Majin Boo may be too much,
but I'll bet I could kill you!
Barrier!
How about that?! I can
manage a little bit too, you know!
Papparapa!
Majin Boo! Boo! Majin Boo!
What are you doing?! This one! Kill this one!
Are you sure you're able to kill me?
F-Fool! If you kill me, Majin Boo
can never be sealed up again!
I-If that happens,
Majin Boo will destroy the whole
universe until there's nothing left!
Is that okay with you?!
The same holds true even if
you aren't dead! Am I wrong?!
Die!
This can't be! I was
going to be king of the world!
Who did it?!! Who made this happen to me?!
Trunks, take good care of Bulma–your Mama...
W-What do you mean by that, Papa?
"Take care of your Mama?"
You guys go take shelter somewhere, far away.
I fight alone against Majin Boo!
U-Uncle?
No way! We're going to fight too!
Papa, you'll be killed fighting alone!
If the three of us fight,
we're sure to defeat him!
–Right, Goten?!
–Yeah!
We're strong, you know!
No chance. No matter how
many of us were to attack him...
in the usual manner of fighting, anyhow...
Uncle! If the three of us fight, it'll be easy, easy!
This isn't like you, Papa! Getting all pessimistic!
Yeah! Right, right!
Uncle, you have to always act like a big shot!
Yeah!
Trunks, from the time you were a baby,
I've never once given you a hug, have I?
Let me hug you.
P-Papa...!
W-What is it, Papa?
C-Cut it out! You're embarrassing me!
Take care, Trunks...
P-Papa...!
Trunks-kun!
Uncle, how come?!
How come you hit Trunks-kun?!
How come?! How come you hit Trunks-kun?!
That's awful! That's awful, Uncle! Uncle!
How come?!
Who was it that hit me just now?
Take these two and get as
far away as possible. Hurry.
I'm counting on you, Piccolo.
You intend to die, don't you?
Just tell me one thing.
Once I die,
will I be able to meet Kakarrot
again in the Other World, or wherever?
At a time like this, it's not going to
help for me to speak in consolation,
so I'll tell you directly–
That's not possible.
You've killed too many sinless people.
When you die, your body will become nothing,
and your spirit will be carried
to a different world than Goku's.
There, your spirit will be cleansed,
your memory will be lost,
and you will be changed into a new life form.
Is that so? Too bad.
That's enough. Get going, and hurry!
Yeah.
Look here! I won't let you get away!
Hold it, Majin Boo!!
You take on them after you've defeated me!
Got that, you ugly balloon scum?!
You said something bad
about me again, didn't you?!
Even though you're a wimp!
You're a smart-aleck!
Hurry, Kuririn!
Hurry and get away from here!
R-Right!
You die, right now!
I'm really mad, you know!
I've figured out how to put you away, at last!
H-Hey!
What is Vegeta planning to do?
Like that, there's no
question he'll be killed, right?
For the first time, he's about to
fight for someone other than himself,
as he lays down his own life!
You're still so weak!
Should I turn you into choco and eat'cha?
Or maybe a cheese cracker?
In order to defeat you, I'm going to
make sure you can't restore yourself,
by blowing you to tiny bits!!
Farewell! Bulma... Trunks... and you, Kakarrot!
V-Vegeta!
Vegeta!!
A warrior vanishes in a
distant, astonishing light.
His name, Vegeta, the proud Saiyan prince.
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
After Vegeta went and gave his
life to blow Majin Boo to pieces,
it still doesn't look like it's over.
Just what is about to happen?
Impossible! The fragments of
Majin Boo have started moving!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Nightmare Revisited!!
Majin Boo Has Survived."
Guys, it's too dangerous on earth anymore!
"Next time"
"The Nightmare Revisited!!
Majin Boo Has Survived"