Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Freeza's overwhelming power was
far greater than anyone had expected.
And presently, following
Kuririn, came Gohan's turn.
"The Tide Suddenly Turned!!
Piccolo, the Warrior Who Came Late."
What's wrong?
Vegeta, aren't you coming to help him?
Looks as though your legs are
trembling, and you can't move.
Well, you just wait there
patiently a little while longer.
I'm about to smother the
breath of life from this one.
After which it will be your turn.
I-I don't care if the kid dies,
I'm just wondering what I'm supposed to do.
Freeza's power is beyond imagination!
Father... Pic... colo... -san...
Gohan's ki is disappearing quickly.
H-He's dying! Dammit!
I can't wait until I've completely
recovered from my injuries!
Gohan's ki has all but disappeared!
You're the only one that
ever freely associated with me.
Before I realized what had happened,
you found your way into my heart,
and made yourself a place there large
enough that I was unable to drive you out.
Stay alive, Gohan!
Is there nothing I can do?
If I don't act, I'll be next!
Gohan, just hang on. I'll be right there.
Now the big finish!
H-How can he be?!
He was supposed to have
been at least critically wounded!
W-Why?!
Kienzan!
Kuririn...
Kuririn's ki has been restored! What's going on?
If you don't like it, come on over here!
Come and paddle my bum!
Why you... How dare you make a fool of me!
Th-There's no way I can stand against him.
I'll just have to keep running away.
Somehow, I've got to keep him
a little bit further away from Gohan.
Oh no!
All right...
You will not die easily.
I'll take you apart with my own hands.
Damn.
Fool.
Now, come on out!
That was close!
I don't know how it is you recovered,
but you dared to clip the
tail of Freeza-sama, didn't you?
I'm going to knock you into so
many pieces, you'll never recover again!
Now I've done it!
Damn!
No matter how you struggle,
you will not escape my grasp.
Looks like you're about out of breath.
I'll tear you to bits with my bare hands!
Come on out!
Die!
Taiyo-ken!
M-My eyes!
Thank goodness! You're not dead!
I'll heal you right now!
R-Rotten Earthling!
Calling me out here for such a vain struggle...
Vegeta, now! Attack him!
S-So that's what's going on!
What are you doing, Vegeta?!
Great! Gohan's been healed!
Why did you guys keep silent about
the Namekian kid having that ability?!
We didn't keep silent!
We didn't know about it either!
If we had known, we would
have him heal Goku already!
It doesn't hurt at all any more!
You surprised me, Dende! Thanks.
Not at all. Good luck!
Shoot! Why you!
W-What's this?!
True to the Saiyan blood that
he carries, now that he's recovered,
his battle power has increased greatly!
Gohan...
All right!
Slight though it may be, fate
has somewhat turned to our favor.
With the three of us fighting
now, something may turn out.
Impossible! That runt has been revived!
And he should have been on the brink of death!
Now! Shoot him!
You guys just don't know when you're beaten.
How many times have I told you that neither
Earthlings or Saiyans are a match for me?
Dammit.
Have we had it?
I'm not giving up! How can I possibly give up?!
Whether we've had it or not,
there's nothing we can do but try!
Gohan!
You fool! Stop!
Piccolo-san!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Thank goodness! We've been
waiting for you, Piccolo-san!
So that's Freeza, is it?
Yes!
Indeed. He really is an incredible beast.
Well, if it isn't the guy we
slaughtered back on Earth.
So, I need not wonder what you
wished for with the Dragon Balls.
I see you brought this good-for-nothing
scum back to life with them.
That "scum" line was uncalled-for.
And I want you to remember something.
I want you to remember that after
I put Freeza away, your turn comes next.
After you put Freeza away,
you're coming for me?
I didn't think you Namekians
were capable of telling jokes.
It's no use!
No matter how much Piccolo may have
gained from training at Kaio-sama's place,
Freeza's on a completely different
dimension from the rest of us!
There's still a surviving Namekian, is there?
But there's something different
about you from the other Namekians.
There seems to be something special about you.
And even so, you are
still utterly no match for me.
Who is it? Who has arrived? I don't know.
I can't tell whose ki that is.
Piccolo? No, can't be. It couldn't be.
The ki's too great to be Piccolo's.
Gohan's ki has recovered as well.
I don't get anything that's going on!
Now, to clean up the dregs of the universe.
I'll do this by myself. You guys stay out of it.
That person they call Piccolo,
he looks just like Nail-san!
Take shelter somewhere, Dende!
You'll get caught in our crossfire.
Do it quickly!
How does he know my name?
Piccolo-san!
It's senseless! Not even Piccolo has
a chance of winning against that guy!
He may have a glib tongue,
but so long as he doesn't
realize his opponent's battle power,
I wouldn't count on him.
Everyone has stopped moving.
Now what's going on?!
Who is it that just showed
up with the enormous ki?
Piccolo finally arrives at the scene of battle.
His challenge to Freeza
may be thought of as reckless.
Does Piccolo indeed have a chance of winning?
And what about Goku?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Piccolo, hang in there.
Avenge the other Namekians.
Take care of things until I get there.
What's the matter, Freeza?
Even giant-sized, is this the best you've got?
Your moves are too slow!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Piccolo's Self-Confidence!
I Will Be the One to Defeat Freeza"
Piccolo-san will get him!
"Next time"
"Piccolo's Self-Confidence!
I Will Be the One to Defeat Freeza"