Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Son Goku's house is in a
mountain village in Sector 439 West.
To protect the ailing Goku from
the approaching Artificial Humans,
Kuririn and the others temporarily
shelter him at the Kame House.
Just then, some disturbing
facts make themselves known.
Tell me, how many time
machines did my future self make?
How many? It was all you
could do to build just one.
Yeah? This is really strange then.
This is definitely a time machine.
Trunks, here you go.
Another time machine.
Who could have been inside it?
"The Discovery of an Evil Egg!!
A Terrified Trunks."
There's no mistake.
This is the exact same
time machine I rode back in.
How can this possibly be?
Does she know the exact location
of where this photo was taken?
He asks if you know exactly
where this time machine is.
It doesn't say exactly,
but I think it has to be somewhere
around Sector 1050 West.
Are you going?
Yes. I'd like to see this with my own eyes.
Well, I'm going too. It's not too far from here.
U-Understood.
See you later.
You're sure there's only one time machine, then?
Yes, positive.
Um...
I'll go looking with you. Is it okay if I come?
Gohan-chan!
It's all right, Mother.
We aren't going anywhere
dangerous, so you needn't worry.
That ain't it!
You're right in the middle of studyin'.
I'll do it all when I get back.
Ah, here's some water for you!
Mama, I have to go out for
a bit, can you watch Trunks?
Goodness! Bulma-chan, where are you off to?
I have to go meet up with the big Trunks.
Um, Trunks-san, in the future,
you say your world was really devastated,
because of those two Artificial Humans?
Yes. The world's population has been
reduced to several tens of thousands.
Most of Metro West lies in a state of ruin.
Somehow, we manage to survive by
hiding in secret underground bases.
That bad?
I sure hope we can find some
weakness in the Artificial Humans.
Yeah.
There was that time...
The two Artificial Humans
went against Doctor Gero.
No. 17! What's this?!
We have no use for the likes of this.
But he was so far into the corner by then,
he had no choice but to use them.
Haven't you understood a single thing I've said?!
Don't push that switch!
In the end, he was killed by them.
However, Doctor Gero must have
determined how dangerous they were,
using progressively riskier tests.
I think he must have had some kind of device
to shut them down in an emergency.
If he hadn't, do you think he
would have reactivated them?
Of course, that must be it!
There's a slim possibility...
Section 1050 West should be under us now.
Let's start looking.
There it is! There it is!
Trunks-san, it's over here!
Way to find it, Gohan-san!
That must be Bulma-san.
I'll lead her down here.
Hi, Trunks!
It's your beautiful mother!
Indeed.
Well? Let me know what you think,
seeing your mom all young like this.
I-It's just... Mom, you
don't really change that much.
I don't change?
That means I'll keep my
beauty for decades to come!
I hope no one blames me for it.
More to the point, please look at this.
This is the time machine I came
in, and had reduced to a Capsule.
Gee, then there's no way
this older one could be yours.
Not exactly.
You only built one time machine in the future.
This is also the very same time
machine I used to come back in.
No way.
Look at this.
"Hope."Kibô?
[Kibô: hope]
Yeah. These are the letters
you wrote here when I took off.
Naturally, they appear on
the other time machine as well.
But how can that be?
It looks like this one has
been here for quite a while.
Hmm? This hole is strange.
It's like the glass melted from intense heat.
But this hole was made from the inside.
S-So, what? Was anyone inside this one?
In any event, let's open this up.
Excuse me.
There's one here, too.
What's that you've got?
It doesn't appear to be a coconut.
What? Say, give me a look.
Here.
No doubt about it.
This is some kind of eggshell.
Eggshell?
If that's an egg, I've never
seen another egg like it.
Do you suppose that whatever
made that hole hatched from the egg?
The energy reserves are almost on zero.
It came here from...
Age 788?
That's three years later than the time I left!
Three more years into the future!
It arrived in this era...
Nearly four years ago!
This arrived here fully a year
before I appeared the first time.
W-What could have come back
in here, and for what purpose?
Could this be the reason history
has changed so drastically?
...and that's how it went.
All of that happened, huh?
It'd be great if Goku were able to get
better before they come looking here.
All we can do now is pray that he does.
Just a minute!
If the Artificial Humans are after Goku,
won't this house be the very
next place they come looking?!
Yeah, probably so.
So, doesn't that make this the
next most dangerous place on Earth?!
I got no patience for being in harm's way.
Hey, I'm still here, you know.
I won't be defeated by
them so easily. Right, Kuririn?
And I'm just supposed to rely on you, then?
What did you dare say?
I'm still Muten Roshi, spoken
of as the god of martial arts!
I've even won the Tenkaichi
Tournament, you know!
That all happened a long time ago!
Now you're simply a lecherous old man!
You plan on defeating the
Artificial Humans with lechery?
Hey, No. 16. You really are
the silent type, aren't you?
Don't you find it dull to
keep all bottled up like that?
Come on, say something.
I mean, we're all taking special care
to enjoy ourselves like this, aren't we?
Give it up, No. 18.
He's got nothing on his
mind besides killing Son Goku.
Besides which, we're coming up on a town.
You're still looking to get
some new clothes, right?
You bet!
I can finally part ways with these torn-up rags.
Speed up, already!
You know, I really am a genius!
I build a time machine in the future, after all!
In any case, we can't just leave
these time machines sitting around.
For now, let's turn them back into Capsules.
I'll return this one to a Capsule.
Yes, please do.
I'll take this strange eggshell with me.
Yes, be my guest.
Bulma-san, the rest of us, we've gotten
together at Muten Roshi-sama's home.
The Kame House?
How come?
Long story short, three Artificial
Humans have been reactivated,
and are aiming to take my father's life.
But, since Father is down
with his illness, in his state,
they took him there to hide him from them.
Well, why don't the whole lot of you
just get together and put them all away?
You must be kidding!
Dad, myself, Piccolo-san and
Tenshinhan-san all took them on,
but we were powerless against them!
Wow, they really must be incredible.
How's Vegeta? Is he all right?
Did Vegeta go to the Kame House with you?
He survived with the help of a senzu bean.
But Dad didn't join up with us.
He went off somewhere else.
That's just like him.
What is it?
Nothing, I'm just wondering what that is...
Huh? What, where?
Please, come have a look at this!
What, what's wrong?
What is it, Gohan-san?
Over there.
What is that?
It's huge. What made this?
I-Is it dead?
It isn't dead, it's a shell that's been cast-off.
A shell?
You mean the cicadas
grow this big around here?
There are no cicadas like this.
Could it be...?
Probably,
this is from whatever came out of
the egg back in the time machine.
Yeah. It must have started
growing, and then shed its skin.
What does that mean?
What could have possibly
come out of a skin like this?
I don't know. I've never seen anything like this.
But how did it come to be here?
Who could have sent
this egg back through time?
For that matter, someone could
have come back with this egg as well.
I don't have any idea what's going on any more.
Whatever came out of here,
it must have just barely happened.
What do you think?
In all honesty, you've got
a bad feeling about this too?
Yes!
Well, I guess I should get out of here.
You guys will be at the Kame House, right?
If anything happens, I'll be in touch.
Right.
Trunks, if you get the time, come visit!
Grandma and Grandpa will love it!
What exactly is happening now?
I don't know!
I absolutely do not know!
Still peeping down on the lower realm?
Can't say I approve of your little pastime.
I guess that ability will likely
disappear once you become one with me.
Enjoy it now, while you still can.
So, the uneasiness I've felt in
my heart these last four years,
it was not a result of the
Artificial Humans after all.
I'm not sure what it is either.
What did come back in that time machine?
What?
All I know is that there is a life
form down on Earth somewhere,
one that possesses an even greater
power than even the Artificial Humans.
What are you talking about?!
Tell me what's going on!
To be sure, the day when I turn to
Piccolo and forsake my office as Kami,
and we stand together
as one has finally arrived.
Very soon now...
Very soon now, something
terrible will happen on Earth.
This is not the kind of crisis Earth
has faced so many times before.
I have a hopelessly dreadful feeling about this.
A being that comes from
a future even beyond Trunks.
Elsewhere, the Artificial Humans
continue to pursue Goku.
Danger swells up on all sides.
Goku, get better soon!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
All the people in Gingertown
have been wiped out?
Ain't no doubt, whoever came
in that time machine did this!
Piccolo, it looks like the time
for us to merge has finally come.
Hurry! Right now what the
earth needs is not a Kami...
but rather, the mighty!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"To Face an Unprecedented Foe...
Birth of a Super Namekian!!"
What is that monster?
"Next time"
"To Face an Unprecedented Foe...
Birth of a Super Namekian!!"