Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
As Cell mercilessly and indiscriminately attacks,
hunting down No. 18 in
order to achieve his perfect form,
Vegeta appears before
him right at the last moment!
Watch very carefully, Cell!
I'm going to erase that disagreeable
little smile of yours for you!
The intense power of a newly-born
Vegeta rises above that of the monster Cell!
Is this the power that surpasses Super Saiyan?
"On Your Knees, Cell!
I Am Super Vegeta!!"
What's the matter?!
Did you doze off or something?
You lousy Saiyan Monkey!
You're pretty spirited, aren't you?
However, at this level of battle power,
it's no more than a brave pretense!
Is that so?
This is the fruit of his training.
Cell is unable to see Dad's motions through.
I couldn't see... how Vegeta moved!
You've got to be more
serious about this, Cell.
It would seem you're
not too bad at this, huh?
So, this is the extent of the
results of training in that room?
Dad!!
Dad!
Do not bother me!
Worthless fool.
Dad!!
I will go beyond Super Saiyan!
I will reign over the universe!
D-Dad...
Is this the extent of the
results of training in that room?
What's the matter?! Is this over already?
That's right! It's over!
Your life, that is!
S-So that's it!
This incredible ki is Vegeta's!
It's even greater than
Cell's ridiculously huge Ki!
What's going on?
That's right! Goku was
talking about that place
where you could do a year's
training in one day... is that it?
Let's go see!
Come on, now! What are you
guys seeing all by yourselves?
How's Vegeta?! What's happening to Trunks?!
I-Incredible!
To think that he wouldn't be
having any problems with Cell!
H-He's winning! At this rate, he will defeat Cell!
Say, there! What's happening?
Is he winning? Is he losing?
It's okay!
He's overwhelmingly assaulting him!
Grrrrr...
Oh, dear, dear! Such a ferocious face...
How awesome, indeed!
Both your papa, and yourself!
There, there, there, there, there, there!
Just as you'd expect of battle maniacs, huh?
There, there, there, there!
So this is power that
exceeds Super Saiyan, is it?!
This is how much difference in
power there is between us now?
No, no! You're just making your ki larger.
Becoming Super Saiyan
gets its start from anger.
Get angry! Pop off, with a bang!
J-Just saying it like
that, I can't get angry.
I know! Either me,
or Piccolo, or even Kuririn–
try imagining that one of us
is about to be killed by Cell!
But, I've never seen Cell.
Good grief!
Ah, well, Freeza or anything else is okay!
Right!
I-It's no use...!
Starting right now, I'm
going to show you what hell is!
I shall enjoy it.
That was hell, then?
You do seem to want to
make me get serious about this.
I'd long thought you were already serious.
If that's the case, then
don't hold yourself back for me.
W-What's this?!
To think that he's been
concealing that much power...
That was quite a jump in your battle power.
Still, so what about it?
Dad has this won.
There's Vegeta... and that's Cell over there.
They're monsters, both of them!
So, this is your level after all?
Apparently, during my training,
I opened up too wide a
gap between our powers...
Impossible! You're...
Vegeta, aren't you? Am I wrong?
I... am Super Vegeta!
With self-assuredness and power,
labeling yourself "Super Vegeta,"
will you settle this battle
right here and now, Vegeta?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
What's wrong, Vegeta? As you are now,
you should be able to defeat
Cell. What are you doing?
Geez, here I wondered what
an exceptional guy you must be,
and that's all you've got? How disappointing!
Killing you has become a frivolous matter!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Dangerous Pride!!
A Challenge to Cell's Perfect Form."
Don't tell me Vegeta is
thinking of letting Cell get away!
"Next time"
"Dangerous Pride!!
A Challenge to Cell's Perfect Form"