Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Six days? I can get there in just six days?
Son Goku had finally blasted
off into space for Planet Namek.
However, at the same time, on Namek...
D-Dragon Balls!
Having at last found the
Namekians, as well as the Dragon Balls,
they had already fallen into enemy hands.
"Surprise Attack!!
The Elder's Target Was the Scouters."
Come on! Unless you want to die, get moving!
I told you to step forward further!
Hey, hey, snap to it!
What are they planning
to do with the Namekians?
K-Kuririn-san, are those all Saiyans?
No, they're not. They're wearing the
same battle dress, but they're not Saiyans.
Besides, Vegeta is supposed
to be the only remaining Saiyan.
Not including Goku or yourself.
T-Then...
Come to think of it, there was that
guy who said he was Goku's brother.
Our task is to go through space,
searching for planets with good environments,
and once we've exterminated
those who already live there,
we sell them for a high price to
aliens who are looking for a suitable planet.
It could be that these
guys are in league with them.
Though if so, I don't see Vegeta around.
Is he off somewhere else,
looking for Dragon Balls?
My name is Freeza, and as you can see,
I am gathering your so-called Dragon Balls.
Incidentally, where are the
others? According to our survey,
there are supposed to be ten of you here.
You intend not to say anything, do you?
I will kill you.
6,588...
6,590... Whew...
20-times gravity sure is tough...
But I have to thoroughly retrain
myself, starting from the fundamentals...
...or I won't be able to
bear multiple Kaio-ken levels...
Now, I shall have your answer, please.
Not in Namekian. Speak to us in a
language that we can all understand.
We know that you are able to speak it.
T-The others are out working the fields.
Only those of us who are
elderly or children remain here.
There you go. As long as you
answer me honestly like that,
I will not do anything to you.
Now then, I will continue
to have you answer me, please.
Where is your Dragon Ball?
I believe there is another one here.
I-I don't know.
We don't have anything like that.
Dodoria-san?
Sir?
As I recall, the second Namekian that we killed
said something quite interesting, yes?
Yes. "We can only turn over the Dragon Balls
to those who we judge to be men of valor."
Yes, yes. He was a very stubborn man, too.
I simply could not get
him to cooperate with me...
...but then I killed one of
them, to serve as a lesson to him.
What?!
Once I did, I got him
to say all sorts of things.
The seven Dragon Balls were
created by the Grand Elder of this world.
Each of them is in the
custody of one of seven Elders.
Each one is to engage in a
contest of wits, a contest of strength,
and to ask the reason for one's wish.
And once each Elder
judges you to be a man of valor,
you are at last able to obtain
their Dragon Ball, or so he told me.
Well, I attempted to do as I was instructed,
but he told me that he was
absolutely unwilling to turn his over to me.
I could not help but kill him.
H-How could you do that?!
And so, it took some
effort to find the first Ball.
The next three were easy.
Everyone was very accommodating.
I see. So that's it, huh?
A-Accommodating, you say?
You are lying!
T-That's right! There's no way
the other Elders would obligingly
hand over their Dragon Balls to you!
Oh, no, they became quite
accommodating once we did this.
Zarbon-san, please show them.
Yes, sir.
–Why, you!
–No, don't!
H-How could they do that?!
That was awful!
Gohan, control your ki, or they'll find us.
But I can't take this!
Still, you want to bring Piccolo
and everyone else back to life, right?
That's not the sort of opponent
that we can stand up against.
If we come forward now,
we'd just die for nothing.
Darn it!
And here, after we've come
all the way to Planet Namek...
How about it? Are you feeling
a little more accommodating?
What is your purpose in
gathering the Dragon Balls?
Oh, it is just a trivial little wish.
I would like to obtain eternal life.
What?! Then, he and Vegeta
are both after eternal life?
Maybe they aren't friends with Vegeta, then.
I don't know.
I would not turn over the Dragon Ball to the
likes of you, even if it meant my own death!
So you mean that you would
choose death over handing it over to me?
I see. The people of this planet
do seem to be quite stubborn.
However...
...will you still be so stubborn
after the deaths of those children?
W-What?!
You would even kill children?!
Oh, no! Hide!
There's a strong battle power...
Freeza-sama, over there.
Oh, you've come for us?
Namekians!
They've come to save them!
Damn! Then our bad
feeling turned out to be true!
This is trouble. Here I was, just about
to have the Dragon Ball brought out to me,
when you interrupt your work...
...just to come here to be killed.
I see now. So the rumors about
someone attacking the villages
and taking the Dragon Balls are true, are they?
You're going to pay for this!
Trample on the peace of Namek, will you?!
Be careful fighting them!
These guys are quite strong!
Good luck!
Oh, you plan to fight, do you?
I wonder how much battle power they have.
Dodoria-san?
Yes sir, I will check.
Please do not be discouraged, sir.
All three are around 1,000.
We will not even be needed to fight them.
So that's it. I get it.
So that's how they can
pinpoint the few small villages
that dot the vast surface of Namek.
It's because they can
search for us with those devices.
9,998...
9,999...
10,000...
I'm so hungry...
Vegeta, and someone even more
incredible than him, are up ahead...
All right!
This is laughable! You want to tangle
with us with a battle power of 1,000?!
Not true. Those three are just suppressing
their ki. Don't they even know that?
The Saiyans were surprised about that, too, huh?
Get them!
What is this? You call
that a battle power of 1,000?
What's going on here? All three
of them have increased to 3,000.
Way to go! Awesome!
Hang in there!
Oh, my, they fight pretty well, do they not?
I've got it. The Namekians are a
race that can control their battle powers.
That's not a type you see very often.
Way to go! Hang in there!
Go on! Go on! Let them have it!
All right, including his, there are only
three devices that have not been destroyed.
Children, stand back from me.
Quickly!
Dodoria-san...
Yes, sir.
Those guys are pathetic.
Now I have to be put out.
May I take care of all three of them?
Feel free.
Y-You bastard, you think you can
defeat me with such a puny technique?
Elder!
No! He was targeting the Scouters!
Scouters?
Those devices that can tell
your opponent's strength and location!
So that's it! Then they can't tell
precisely where the Dragon Balls are, after all!
Using those Scouter things, they just searched
out Namekians, then forced them out of them!
That old man knew that, so that's
why he destroyed all of their Scouters!
Why, you–!
I-I'll kill you all...
I'll kill you all!
I'll kill each and every one of you!
Elder! Look out!
The Elder had made a quick-witted attack.
However, it has set the enemy's fury ablaze.
Can Gohan and Kuririn do nothing but watch on?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Control yourself, Gohan!
You can't take those guys on!
I am going to take you down!
This runt is my quarry!
The rest of you, stay out of this!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Gohan in Peril!
A Pursuing Dodoria Summons Death."
Kuririn-san, let's fight him!
"Next time"
"Gohan in Peril!
A Pursuing Dodoria Summons Death"