The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Everybody on Earth! I beg you!
I beg you, share your Genki with me!
Hearing Goku's cry, his dear friends from
the past raised their hands one after another!
And then, as a result
of Mister Satan's actions,
the Genki of the whole
earth amazingly became as one!
All right! That's it! Go!
It's done!
At last, the Super Genki Dama was complete!
The long battle with Majin Boo
was at last facing its final phase!
Get back, Vegeta! Here it goes!!
"Son Goku is Strongest After All!!
Majin Boo is Eliminated."
Vegeta! Get out of the way, quickly!
Would you shut up?! I can't move my body!
Y-You what?!
You've got to give it your all, and
somehow get away from there, Vegeta!
You'll be caught in the blast!
S-Stupid bastard!
D-Don't worry about me!
Hurry up and get him, dammit!
D-Damn you!
V-Vegeta-san!
He can't throw the Genki Dama like this!
G-Goku-san!
It's that softness that will cost you your lives!
Boo! Give it to them, now!
K-Kakarrot! If you are one of the fighting
Saiyan people, then do not hesitate!
Yeah, but...!
K-Kakarrot!
Vegeta!
Dammit!
Boo...!
Boo!
Boo! Are you all right?!
Boo... What on earth...?
No!
Goku! If you get finished off,
then that Genki Dama you
worked so hard for means nothing!
Give it to him, Goku! Give it to him!
D-Damn it all!
It's no use!
Vegeta, I'm sorry!
Satan!
S-So that's it! All right!
I'm sorry, Boo!
Damn it, man, do it!! Put him away now!!
Nice work, Satan!
You really could be the world's...
...savior!!
Burn in hell!
Go!!
W-What?!
Dammit! Go, go!!
Do you hear me, Gohan?
Yes, Piccolo-san. Do you feel it?
There's an incredible collision of
ki happening! It's Boo and Father!
Yeah. Apparently, they're
fighting in the Kaioshin Realm.
In that holy region? So that's it.
If it's the Kaioshin Realm, then unless
Kibit-san were here, we can't go to their aid.
For the time being, let's
go to the Heavenly Realm.
We should be able to feel Goku
and the others' ki more strongly there!
Right!
Hey, squirts! You guys come too! Hurry!
D-Dammit!
Th-This ain't just my power here!
This is the genki of all Earthlings!
Th-That's why there ain't no way...
no way I can allow us to lose!!
Piccolo!
Gohan!
Gohan-kun...
You dummy, you dummy!
I was so worried about you!
U-Um, you don't need to cry so hard...
W-What's this?! Are you leavin' me,
your own Ma out?! You're my Gohan!
Now, now, it's all right, isn't it?
It'd look bad if he had a mother complex.
Trunks!
Goten!
This is strange... Goku's ki is
getting weaker than it was earlier.
W-What the hell is taking
you so long, Kakarrot?!
Damn! I can't muster enough power!
D-Dammit! Damn it all! We were so close!
S-So that's it. We miscalculated!
There's not enough strength left in Kakarrot,
which is so critical in
throwing the Genki Dama!
Dammit...!
Th-This is bad! I wonder if that Genki Dama
thing is still lacking a little bit of power.
Th-That can't be! W-We've
already used up all of our ki!
J-Just how tough is this guy–Boo?
H-Hang in there, Son Goku!
That Genki Dama has power from
the Other World in there too, you know!
Dende! Do something!
Raise Kakarrot's strength!
P-Please take me to where Goku-san is!
I-I'm sorry, I used up all my strength just now.
Until I recover it, I cannot
instantaneously move.
I-It can't be!
I-I'm sorry, Vegeta-san! Our power is
gone as well, and we cannot come there!
Then it's all or nothing!
Hey, Satan, gather the Genki from
those guys on Earth one more time!
Raise the power of the Genki Dama,
and squash that Boo bastard! Make it fast!
W-Wait, Vegeta! You can't do that!
Everyone has yet to recover their strength!
If you suck out their
Genki again, everyone will die!
Are you trying to take the Earthlings you
brought back to life and kill them all again?
You shut up, Kaio!
If we lose to Boo like this now,
they can't remain alive anyhow!
Now, do it! Power-up the Genki Dama!
Hurry it up! There's no time!
I-It's no use! I can't muster the power!
Understood. I will call out to everyone again.
Stop, Mister Satan!
Provided that this was all my...
...all in my dream...
What?
However, this is no dream!
I can't believe it, but this is reality!
I'm sorry, but I cannot do anything that
would allow the people of Earth to die!
Hey! Listen to me well!
We can just bring back to life those
who die again with the Dragon Balls!
Besides, we still have
our third wish left, and so...!
That's it!
Dende! The third wish!
Th-That's right!
Do you still not have a third wish?
In that case, if you would
allow me to disappear...
W-Wait! Polunga-san!
C-Can you raise the strength
of the person named Son Goku,
who is now fighting Majin Boo in
the Kaioshin Realm, back to normal?
If all I must do is return that person's level of
strength to its usual level, then it is possible.
Thank goodness!
D-Do that right away, if you please!
Okay!
I-I-It's no use!
Goku-san! With the third wish, Goku-san,
your strength should be returning to normal!
It's back! It's back!!
Thank you, Dragon Balls!
He did it!
Very, very nice!
Way to go!
Father's ki...!
It suddenly swelled up!
You are awesome!
You fought well, all by yourself!
You changed forms so many times...
...so much so that I was
finally getting tired of it.
This time, get reborn as a good guy!
I want to fight you,
one-on-one. I'll be waiting for you!
And I will have gotten much, much better!
See you later!
Goku-san!
Kakarrot!
Father!
Goku!
Go!!
It's over...
Took you long enough...
At last, Majin Boo has disappeared.
He has been completely vaporized,
with literally no cells remaining.
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
The battle is over, and
we're finally back on earth.
And so is the chubby Boo.
Hold on. Boo, why is it that
just by coming into the city,
there's a big prize-fighting,
robbery-foiling to-do about it?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Peace Returns!!
Majin Boo, Champion of Justice!?"
Nice going, Boo-san.
"Next time"
"Peace Returns!!
Majin Boo, Champion of Justice!?"