The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Ten years' time had passed
since Majin Boo was defeated
by the power of Goku, and of all mankind.
Grandpa, I flew around the Earth!
Goku, together with Goten, as well
as Gohan and Videl's daughter, Pan,
decided to enter the Tenkaichi
Tournament, after a long absence.
Why, all of a sudden, have you
decided to enter this time in particular?
Because there's going to be
somebody strong entering too.
What's this?
I can more or less tell.
This guy is definitely strong!
"I Am Oob!
Now 10 Years Old, the Former Majin!?"
Good luck!
A-Awesome... I've never seen so many people...
Hey!
What's with you?
S-Sorry!
Geez, you're nervous!
Still, a kid like you is lucky to
have gotten past the preliminaries.
I'm sure it was just luck.
Of course it was! Every year, there's
always one lucky guy that gets in.
Well, this year, there's another,
super-lucky one as well.
Yow-ow-ow...!
Hey!
That hurt, you know! You runt!
Have you got something against me?
Well? Why don't you say
something? You runt!
Grandpa!
There, there! Don't cry, don't cry, Pan.
Now then, sorry to keep you waiting!
We would now like to begin the drawings
to determine the matches
for the Tenkaichi Tournament!
Ladies and gentlemen,
as I believe you already know,
these matches are
carried out tournament-style,
with the contestants who
have passed the preliminaries!
The pairings for the tournament
are impartially decided by this lottery.
Further, the one contestant that
wins their way through the tournament...
...will compete for victory against
the Super Champion, Mister Satan!
Hey, is that incredible guy that Goku-san
was talking about really among us?
Beats me.
W-Well, there sure are
some weird bastards, anyhow.
Tell me, Kakarrot, which one is he?
You'll see.
So then, contestants, when I call
your name, please draw your number!
Let's see, first up is Son Goten-san!
Right!
This way, if you please!
Say, Boo...
Can you be sneaky and change
the numbers with your magic for me?
When Mister Satan was still drawing numbers,
he asked you to cheat for
him, right? Now I'm asking.
I get it. Fine.
What is it you're planning?
What are you thinking?
Sorry, but no matter what,
I want to fight with him.
Both him and me, in the first round,
while we're both at 100 percent strength.
Here.
Number 8! Son Goten-san is number 8!
Let's see, next comes Mo Kekko-san.
A pretty strong-looking
guy has come forward, huh?
That guy is all looks.
There's no substance to him.
That may be so from
where you're looking, I suppose.
Why didn't you enter?
You knew that there was going to be this
level of guys here from the start, didn't you?
If you had finished, we could have gotten
some prize money, you know, prize money.
Don't be crazy! Never mind the others,
with Goku and them as my opponents,
there's no way I could win, is there?
I won, ten years ago. I did let
Mister Satan have the victory, though.
But that was because of
the commotion around Boo,
when Goku and the others dropped out.
You really don't have any guts, huh?
Come on, would you...?
Mama, next is Pan-chan's turn!
Which one should I choose?
Hey, is it still okay not to use any magic?
Mm-hmm, it's still all right.
Let's see, this one!
Right! Number one!
Contestant Pan is number one!
Oh! Pan-chan is number one, huh?
Which means, her opponent is...
"Mo Kekko"
W-What's this?! Of all people,
it's that ferocious guy?!
Number one, number one, number one...
Okay, next is Son Goku-san! If you would...!
I've been waiting for this!
Which one is open...?
All right! Boo, number three, please!
Gotcha.
Yo!
It has been some time. Son-san,
we've missed you in the tournaments
that you haven't been here for.
Right, Son Goku-san is number three!
Let's see, next comes Kirano-san!
Right.
Give him... let's see... let him have number six.
Gotcha.
What? He's not the one?
Number six! Kirano-san is number six!
Okay, now then, Oob-kun!
R-Right!
Boo, number four! Give that boy number four!
After this, you don't need to cheat any more.
Okey-dokey.
W-What, now?
Don't tell me... it's that kid?!
Yeah, it's him.
While training alone,
I've been waiting a long time
for that boy to enter the tournament.
I'm not understanding
this at all. Talk to me, already!
Ten years ago, when that unbelievably
evil Boo died, I asked for a favor.
I asked that he be reincarnated
as a good guy this time,
so that we could go one-on-one.
Apparently, Old Man King Yama
heard me, and took it under consideration.
Y-You're telling me that
kid there is his reincarnation?!
Mm-hmm, no doubt about it.
For some reason, I can tell.
Even his name, see? It's "Oob," right?
If you read that backwards, it's "Boo," ain't it?
Right? That's a strange coincidence, huh?
C-Can it be?
H-He's what?!
M-Maybe Mom was right after all.
Even if I am the strongest in the
village, the world is a big place.
There's sure to be very strong people out
here, lots of people who are stronger than me.
W-What should I do?
I told her I would definitely win.
I promised everyone that I would use
the prize money to buy lots of things to eat,
and bring them back.
Son Goku-san, huh?
The pairings for the first
round have been decided!
In the first match, Contestant
Pan versus Contestant Mo Kekko.
In the second match, Contestant
Son Goku versus Contestant Oob.
In the third match, Contestant Captain
Chicken versus Contestant Kirano.
In the fourth match, Contestant Mister
Boo versus Contestant Son Goten.
In the fifth match, Contestant
Trunks versus Contestant Otokosuki.
And in the sixth match, Contestant
Knock versus Contestant Vegeta!
The matches will begin right away, so when
your names are called, please come to the ring.
Until then, you are free
to rest or begin warming up.
Very well then, we'll see you afterwards.
That's not fair, having to go
against Boo-san in the first round!
You're just lucky when it
comes to lotteries, huh Goten?
You're only in trouble because
you're always skipping your training.
I'm the one who should be upset!
I've got this kid for an opponent!
I didn't come here to play around in
some nursery school, you little turd!
How did someone like her
get through the preliminaries?
Go home and suck your mama's
milk now, while you still can!
Thank goodness! You're just
what I like in an opponent!
I'll be sure to let you
have it as hard as I can!
Trunks-kun, you're lucky when
it comes to lotteries too, huh?
Hey, pops. Hey, you! I'm talking to you!
What are you ignoring
me for, you old piece of crap!
I was just going to pay my respects
as your opponent in the match.
Die!
Someone tell them that
somebody has dropped out.
Geez, Vegeta, for the love of...!
Papa is strong!
We're terribly sorry for the delay!
We now at last begin the final
competition for the Tenkaichi Tournament!
Of the 114 participants in this tournament,
we have selected the finest
twelve to fight for the prize money,
and for the right to challenge the champion!
Once again, the prize money is
being sponsored by Mister Satan!
Satan! Satan! Satan! Satan!
Hang tough, okay?
Your Papa and Mama will be
cheering for you from the second floor.
Don't get nervous. Relax, relax.
Now then, right off,
let's begin the first match!
Okay, come back soon!
I'll be right back!
The first match is between
Contestant Pan and Contestant Mo Kekko!
Contestant Pan is–won't
you be surprised to hear this–
a gifted little girl, who is only four years old!
However, as if that weren't enough, amazingly...
...she is also Mister Satan's granddaughter!
She faces Contestant Mo Kekko, who
was unfortunate enough to be defeated...
...by Contestant Mister Boo in the
semifinals at the last tournament.
He is a powerful contender,
standing two meters, 30 centimeters!
How cute! Good luck!
Don't you pick on her, Mo!
She's Satan's granddaughter, then?
E-Even so, that doesn't change the fact
that this is making a laughingstock of me!
Damn it all!
Still, how did that little squirt
get through the preliminaries?
Even if she is Mister Satan's granddaughter...
Beats me. Well, she could have
cheated her way though, right?
I hope you're all right, Pan-chan.
Hang in there, Pan-chan!
Pan! Don't go too far out there!
Pan-chan, good luck!
Very well then, please begin!
What choice do I have? I'll toss her out.
What?!
She did it!
Well, he's all right!
Contestant Mo is still breathing!
He is not dead, so Contestant
Pan wins the first match!
You did it!
Way to go, Pan-chan!
A-Are you okay?!
Pan-chan!
You're not hurt?
Mm-mm, I'm all right!
There's no reason she shouldn't be, right?
That was really something to see, Pan.
We're next, huh?
Let's give it our best!
R-Right! Please accept my regards!
Now then, the second match will be
between Contestant Son
Goku and Contestant Oob!
Contestant Son Goku has previously
appeared in the tournament several times,
and incredibly, as a
martial artist of super ability,
he even has the experience
of being victorious once!
I personally expect his abilities to place him
among the top class of
contestants in this tournament!
I anticipate a white-hot match
between him and Mister Satan's
number-one pupil, Mister Boo!
Facing him is Contestant Oob,
a young boy who has come all the
way from his village on South Island!
The oldest of five, he is a hard worker,
who often looks after his
younger brothers and sisters!
He absolutely wants the prize money,
and has bravely gone
ahead to enter this time around.
Give him all you've got, kid!
Hang in there! Your big sister
will be cheering for you, here!
Oh, I feel so sorry for him.
For him to have come all this way,
just to have Son-kun be his opponent...
This will be the fight of
greatest notice this time around.
Indeed it will.
So then, please begin the match!
Don't be so nervous! You can't put
out what you're capable of like that!
R-Right!
This isn't going to work.
It's no use. All right, if it comes to that...
Hey there, you! Come at me! You little hick!
Earlier, you were pretending in
front of everyone to be a good little boy,
but you're really an
incredible brat, ain't you?
And I... let's see... I hate you!
I'm going to knock you flying!
Or would you rather, um, get killed,
and go back home as a pile of bones?!
Let's see, let's see...
Your mommy's belly-button sticks out!
M-My mommy's
belly-button does not stick out!
Well then, she's just a pile of poo!
Yeah! Yeah! She's a pile of poo!
What are they up to?
All they're doing is talking out there.
Search me.
All right, now for the final blow!
Your daddy...
...is a pile of poo, too!
Neither my father...
...nor my mother...
...are piles of poo!!
At last, Oob snaps. What is the
reincarnated Majin Boo capable of?
The second round that Goku
promised Majin Boo is about to begin!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Oob, you're as awesome as I thought, all right.
You wanna come train with me?
Son-kun, what are you thinking,
suddenly ditching the match and flying away?
Next time on the final episode of Dragon Ball Z,
"Even Stronger!!
Goku's Dream is Super-Huge."
Father sure does seem happy.
"Next time"
"Even Stronger!!
Goku's Dream is Super-Huge"