Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
The Artificial Humans No. 17 and
No. 18 prove to be extraordinarily strong.
Piccolo, Trunks, and Vegeta each
found there was nothing they could do,
and were defeated.
Goku was still down from his heart illness.
We were created to kill Son Goku.
This is just a game.
Son Goku is the strongest
one in the world, right?
Humans... It's a game to kill him.
See ya! Bye.
The puzzling nature of the
Artificial Humans–now what?
"Piccolo's Resolution!!
The Last Measure in His Reserve."
That's right, I have to help everyone!
Let's see...
There are six senzu left.
I just split them up between
myself, Tenshinhan and Piccolo.
Hey, Tenshinhan, stay with us!
Here, have a senzu.
I guess I should feed one to Vegeta too.
What? You mean they
even knew the word "senzu"?!
What does it mean?
If they knew so much, why didn't they kill us?
Good question.
Are they saying they don't need to kill us?
That we're no match for them?!
Of course they are.
Those guys are incredibly
strong. They're too strong!
How could anyone have
guessed they were as strong as that?
Vegeta!
Trunks! Don't go after him! Stop!
Leave him alone.
He had become a Super Saiyan,
and utterly regained all of
his pride and self-assuredness.
And yet, even though
they were Artificial Humans,
he was soundly beaten by a woman.
His shock must be pretty great.
As for the rest of us,
to think that we even teamed up
on them and couldn't beat them...
I'm sorry. My legs just cowered on me,
and I wasn't able to fight with you.
Don't worry about it.
Our opponents were such that
Trunks had even turned Super Saiyan...
...yet he was still all but defeated in one blow.
If you had joined in, there's
not a thing you could have done.
Dammit, if only Goku were healthy!
This guy easily took care of even Freeza.
And yet, he was powerless to do
anything against the Artificial Humans.
Let's be frank. No matter
how strong Goku may be,
he can't be that much
different from Vegeta or Trunks.
There's absoultely no one who
can beat them, Goku included!
They were also somewhat different
from the Artificial Humans I knew.
How do you mean?
The ones I know didn't have
this kind of unbelievable strength.
I was able to at least hold
my own against their strength.
At any rate, the path
ahead is in complete darkness.
What should we do now?
First, you guys go to Son Goku's house
and move him to a different location.
Whatever we do next, we can't
think of doing it until Goku recovers.
That's for sure.
So, Piccolo, what are you planning to do?
Good question.
W-What's up with that expression on your face?
You must have some kind of strategy, right?
Come on, tell us! We're all friends here!
Friends, you say?
Don't get carried away with yourself!
When did I ever become friends with any of you?!
I am a demon clansman! Don't you ever forget...
I'm just using you to
help me take over the world!
That's right, I'd completely forgotten.
He is, after all, the reincarnation...
of Piccolo Daimao, who Goku
and I fought against so long ago.
Damn, don't tell me Piccolo is
still bent on world domination.
All his talk about scheming
to take over the world?
I don't think he means it.
He's just like Goku or Vegeta.
I bet all he thinks about is
being stronger than anyone else.
Therefore, he's flown off to take the
very last measure left in his reserve.
Probably so, anyway.
What is this last measure you're talking about?
Piccolo flew off in that direction.
Do you know what's over there?
That direction?
Beats me. Nothing comes to mind.
Is it somewhere I know of?
Kami-sama's place.
Kami-sama's?!
I'm sure everyone already knew,
but Kami-sama and Piccolo
Daimao were once one Namekian.
Once they divided, they
went their separate ways.
And Piccolo's been reincarnated since then.
When I was on Namek, the
Grand Elder-san told me something.
He said if Kami-sama and Piccolo hadn't split up,
they could have stood up to even a Saiyan.
What I'm saying is,
I think Piccolo has gone to Kami-sama's
place in order to become his one,
original self again.
What?
If Kami-sama and Mao join bodies,
they'll return to a Namekian warrior.
However, since Piccolo is
so much more powerful now,
they'll become an exceptional warrior!
If Goku and company are Super Saiyans,
then Piccolo would be a Super Namekian!
Super Namekian? That's incredible!
But if so, and Kami-sama disappears,
won't the Dragon Balls also vanish?
Yeah, probably so.
But if Piccolo or Kami-sama were to get killed,
the Dragon Balls would vanish anyhow.
If Piccolo really is planning
on reuniting with Kami-sama...
If he really feels that boxed in
by the three Artificial Humans,
it should tell us how fierce an enemy they are.
Piccolo hates Kami-sama's guts.
What is my fath–I mean,
Vegeta-san planning to do?
Hey, there's no need to
hide it any more, Trunks.
We all know you're the grown-up
version of the baby Bulma-san was holding.
The only one who doesn't
know is your father, Vegeta.
Is that so? Please excuse me.
It's really nothing you need to apologize for.
Vegeta is definitely not the type to
run away just because he's lost a battle.
He's nearly the incarnation of pride itself.
I'm sure he'll come up with
some new finishing technique.
He'll be back to face the Artificial Humans again.
Yeah.
Damn those Artificial Human
bastards! Toy with me, will they?!
They're going to regret turning me,
Vegeta-sama, back without finishing the job!
Forget about me. I don't
know when I'll be back again.
Farewell.
I'll be waiting for you.
Until you come back to me...
No matter how long it takes, I'll wait for you!
Love is sure beautiful.
It's true. In the end, love will overcome.
Maron-chan!
Huh? Has Kuririn come back?
Maron, I've been looking for you!
Well, if it isn't Mark!
Hey, Maron!
Ah, Tommy!
Maron!
I love you!
I came flying back for you!
Oh, you've all come for me? Maron's so touched!
W-What's all this commotion?
Just a minute, guys!
Oh, Maron-chan, what is all this?
Things got dull, so I called my boyfriends.
Y-You mean these guys are
all your boyfriends, Maron-chan?
That's right!
Each of them has proposed to Maron,
but they're all so handsome, I can't decide!
Everyone else is waiting, so I'm leaving!
Give Kurin-chan my regards! See ya!
She really left.
This may be for the best.
She's not a bad girl, but
she just doesn't suit Kuririn.
Listen to me.
We're going to keep the fact that
Maron-chan came back for Kuririn a secret.
Right.
Still, even if it were just once...
I wanted to pafu-pafu with
Maron-chan's chest! What a pity!
Say, Trunks, how long will it take Goku...
...to get better with that
medicine you gave him?
Knowing Goku-san, I'd say
he'll be fine in ten days or so.
Ten days, huh? I think we can
manage to keep him hidden that long.
Yeah, one way or another.
Although, the idea of Goku getting better...
...and winning this fight seems
a little too good to be true now.
In any case, we're lucky those
three don't seem to have any kind of...
...radar device that can track our power.
Right.
Goku-sa, are you okay?!
Chichi, hurry, his medicine!
It's gone! The medicine's gone!
Gone, gone, gone...
Isn't that it over there?
Oh, is this where it was?
Goku-sa, I got your medicine. Take this.
Goku-sa, I'm beggin' you, get better quick!
Huh?
Oh my! Bulma! Gohan-chan! Trunks-chan!
Mama!
We're back!
My, welcome, all of you!
Gohan-chan, look how big you're getting!
You look so much more
brawny every time I see you!
Come, make a stay of it.
I'll prepare some cakes and tea right away.
There's no need to be so modest!
Actually...
I have to hurry back to my father.
I'm stayin' for the chow
'fore I leave. It's good manners.
Goodbye!
Dear me, has he left already?
I'm sure he must be busy.
I wonder what the matter is?
What's the matter indeed?
There's nothing like playing the wetnurse.
Now, I'd better hurry!
So, Piccolo, you've finally made your decision?
Long ago, myself and Piccolo
Daimao were one and the same.
We were a single, gifted martial artist.
The time came when I learned of
Kami's existence, and I came here.
Unfortunately, even a Kami dies.
I wanted to be Kami's newest successor.
However, no matter how much time passed,
Kami would not approve my request.
"There is an evil that dwells in
the deepest reaches of your heart. "
"As long as any amount of evil
dwells there, you cannot become Kami."
This was because in the depths of my heart,
there lurked the slightest amount of evil.
Kami was able to see through to it.
However, after rigorous training,
I was able to drive that evil out.
That became Piccolo Daimao.
I became Kami's successor...
...but Piccolo Daimao fled to the
ground, and seeking to rule the world,
became a cause of suffering to many.
But as he did, one young man
came and appeared before him.
It was Son Goku.
And so, what was reborn
is the Piccolo we know now.
It appears that the time
for that which was divided...
...to be brought back together has come.
Piccolo's final resolution:
Reuniting with Kami-sama.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
You're going to observe
for a short while longer?
What are you talking about, Kami-sama?
The future is in tatters because of them.
Please understand, if this
is the last decision I make,
then I would like a
conclusive reason to proceed.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Walking Weapons of Mass Destruction!!
The Artificial Humans Draw Near Goku."
Hurry and get Father someplace safe!
"Next time"
"Walking Weapons of Mass Destruction!!
The Artificial Humans Draw Near Goku"