Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
The monster Cell exhibited frightening power!
Piccolo had fallen, as had Tenshinhan.
However, at the last possible
moment, Goku appeared!
I'd like to settle everything right here,
but no matter how you shake it up,
there ain't no way I can win the way I am now.
However, just you wait one more day,
and I'll be sure to thoroughly
defeat you, you'll see!
Goku and the others escaped to the temple...
...using the Instantaneous Movement technique.
Right now, Son Goku does not matter!
I have to catch No. 18!
Burning with ambition, and
having already absorbed No. 17,
the evolved Cell took off after No. 18.
"I Will Dispose of Everything!!
A Reborn Vegeta, Father and Son, Sally Forth."
Please excuse us. We've kept you waiting.
We've really been waiting for this!
–Trunks-san!
–Trunks, you've really gotten all strong, huh?
You been in quite long time.
Popo not know anyone been in this long.
Once we entered, Dad appeared
to have already overcome the
Super Saiyan wall in two months.
But even then, he didn't appear to be satisfied,
and all the time up to now has been–
Trunks!
Don't say what you don't have to.
It went pretty well, huh Vegeta?
Hmph, I suppose.
But even if you were to go in
now and train, it won't do any good,
because I'm going to dispose of everything–
including Cell and the Artificial Humans.
What?!
Vegeta, I don't know how
strong you may have gotten,
but you're taking them too lightly.
While you were in that room,
Cell absorbed the Artificial Human
No. 17, and has gotten even stronger!
You'll be surprised at his strength.
Vegeta, I went and saw the
evolved Cell myself for just a moment.
He was one abominable monster!
This is no time to be playing around!
We have to hurry to Kami-sama's temple!
Trunks, we're speeding up!
That's it!
He looks like he's angry
about something. Oh well.
Damn that wretched No. 18!
Where did she vanish to?
She's together with that injured No. 16.
They couldn't have gotten too far.
That miserable Cell! Aren't you upset, No. 16?!
You really are a strange one!
I don't have any idea what it is you're thinking!
You tried to help us.
You, who were built solely for killing Son Goku.
So this is Kami-sama's temple, huh?
Hey there, everyone!
Where are you? If you're here, come on out!
That's Bulma-san's voice!
They're here, they're here!
Bulma, why are you here?
I asked Kuririn.
He said you were all here.
Good day!
Huh?
Say, say there, you're Trunks, aren't you?
–You are, right?
–Uh... Right...
Why has your hairstyle changed?
Is it a wig?
Whoa, and haven't you gotten taller?
T-There is a mysterious room
in Kami-sama's temple here,
where one year inside is
the same as one day outside.
Me and Dad trained together in that room...
Huh?
But hey, even taking that into account,
Vegeta's hair hasn't gotten any longer, has it?
The hair of a pure Saiyan does not
undergo any weird changes
from the time they're born.
–Yeah?
–Is that so?
So that's why I've always had–
Haven't you ever noticed up until now?
Yeah, I've always thought
it was a little strange, but still...
You amaze me.
This is no time for you to be
speaking about things of no importance!
Why the hell have you come here, Bulma?!
Right, right. I'd forgotten.
See, that battle suit that
Vegeta requested to be made?
It's got an incredible defensive capacity, right?
So, I had them made for everybody
and brought them here! See?
Wow, this takes me back!
These are the clothes I wore on Planet Namek!
This is unexpectedly light, huh?
So this is a Saiyan battle suit?
It took a lot of effort for me to make
them out of the same material, you know!
As I might have expected of Bulma-san!
No, no, you flatter me!
Huh? Aren't you guys going to wear them?
I have no inclination to wear the
same clothes as Freeza or the Saiyans.
Me either.
I'd die before wearing
the same clothes as Vegeta.
Don't be so particular!
It's pretty easy to move around in this!
Like I said before, Kakarrot,
there's no use in you wearing that outfit.
You will have no active part in this.
Because you're going to
defeat that monster Cell, right?
If so, that will be best!
So then, why don't I go beat Cell now?
Shall I take you to him with
my Instantaneous Movement?
Don't be absurd. I will not
be making use of your powers.
See you later.
My, my. He's as obstinate as ever.
Well then, I will be going too.
Yeah. Oh, just a second...
Vegeta's and your share of
the senzu. Take them with you.
I am most thankful for them.
Good luck. But don't overdo it.
If it gets dicey, get out
of there right away! Got it?
Yes. Thank you for everything.
Goku-san, good luck with your training as well.
Dying is definitely out of
the question, both of you!
You got that?
All right, Gohan!
Now it's our turn for
some father-and-son training!
Right!
Oh, just a moment! Before we do...
I'm hungry!
I've gotta eat something first!
At a time like this?
Dammit!
Given No. 18's speed, I should
have overtaken her now for sure!
Seeing as how she is not visible,
she would appear to have hidden herself
on one of the islands around here somewhere.
Fine.
Can you hear me?! No. 18!!
Show yourself!! If you don't show yourself,
I'm going to destroy these
islands one after another!!
You got that?!
You have to hear me! No. 18!
Come on out immediately!
W-What's that?
You idiot! Where the hell
were you looking?! Come on!
What was that loud voice just now?
I-It sounded like it came
from the sky, really far away!
Listen!! No. 18!! I am not bluffing!!
You must be thinking that if I destroy you,
then I will not be able to
achieve my perfect form,
so there's no way I would do so!!
W-What is this?
That's just too bad!!
It is certainly true that
I desire to become my perfect form,
but even as I am now,
there is already no one in
the world that can oppose me!!
Come on out!
No. 18!
Hurry up and come out!
Cell's voice, is it?
To think that he would be the
one to let me know where he is.
Just you wait, Cell.
You'll know right away who
the strongest in the universe is!
If you do not come out,
I will destroy all these islands!!
You got that?!
You despicable piece of crap!
It's all right, No. 18! Don't move.
He may say that, but he's
not about to destroy anything.
He is greatly devoted to
becoming his perfect form.
Lousy No. 18...
Not going to show yourself, huh?
Put me to all this trouble, will you? Idiot!
Well then, shall I drive
her from that island first?
Hey, isn't that whatever it
was that put out that loud voice?
Why is he floating in mid-air?
H-He's the devil! The devil has come!
It's the end of the world! It's all over!
It seems that No. 18 was not on that island.
Okay, on to the next island.
No. 18!! Do you still
intend not to show yourself?!
The island you are hiding on will
soon vanish, and you along with it!!
What do we do, No. 16?
He really has started destroying islands!
You need not worry.
Cell is attacking at a level
such that you will not die, No. 18.
No matter what happens,
he wants to assimilate you, No. 18.
Even if he does spare me, with
your injuries, you will not survive!
Why is it that Cell is as particular as
this about becoming his perfect form?
He already has enough
power to make himself invincible.
There is no one in the entire
universe that can stand up to him!
Is it just that he is genuinely
seeking the ultimate power?
Miserable Cell! It appears he's making
quite a show about going into action.
Mmm, nummy!
Ah! Here comes, here comes!
I'm full, I'm full!
Son Goku, that enough?
Yeah! I've had plenty to eat!
Gohan, about ready to go?
Yes!
Well then...
See there? Stick to it! Stick to it, Trunks!
Starting now, you've got a
great deal of working out to do!
Ah, here they come, here they come!
Indeed! You really are
happy-go-lucky about this!
Okay, just about time
you guys take turn entering.
Wonder how long you can stay in.
It's hot...
At last, Son Goku and Son Gohan
enter the Room of Spirit and Time.
Will they be able to surpass even Super Saiyan,
and gain enough power to
exceed the fearsome monster Cell?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
What do you think, Gohan? Pretty cool room, huh?
My training will be more rigorous
than Piccolo's, so brace yourself.
Standing before Cell,
Dad's ki is rising incredibly.
He's planning to surpass
Super Saiyan right away!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Suddenly Full-Throttle!!
The Super Power of a Radiant Vegeta."
Incredible! That's the result of his training?
"Next time"
"Suddenly Full-Throttle!!
The Super Power of a Radiant Vegeta"