Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
The death battle against
the evil Artificial Human Cell,
which involved Goku's noble sacrifice,
had finally come to a
conclusion at Gohan's hand.
Peace had returned to the Earth.
And, as for Goku...
He was happily living the free
and easy life in the Next World.
I don't have the heart to build it again.
"A Deep Impression!! There They Are!
The Next World's Awesome Dudes."
Just– Hey–Cut that out, will you, Goku?
Hey! This is dangerous! Stop it! Hey!
The Serpentine Road
is as long as ever, huh?
So, Kaio-sama, can't you run a little faster?
Goku, there's no reason to be in such a rush.
We are utterly dead, here.
We've got plenty of time.
But I want to hurry and meet
these masters of the Next World!
I want to fight them,
and see how strong they are!
That may be easy for you to say,
but if you take the masters
of the Next World too lightly,
you'll get yourself in a big mess.
Those dudes are really that strong?
These masters of the Next World?
Now look here!
I won't have you calling them "dudes"!
With all due respect to him,
the masters include the greatest
gentleman in the Next World!
The Grand Kaio-sama!
The Grand Kaio-sama...?
The Grand Kaio-sama, you see...
The Grand Kaio-sama
stands at the head of us Kaio,
who preside over the North,
South, East, and West Galaxies,
and is the most important, most
powerful person in the Next World.
On top of that, the Grand Kaio-sama
is a great fan of the martial arts.
On Grand Kaio's World, those
fighters who are champions of justice,
who, like yourself, have been given
special bodies, engage in daily training.
Now I want to meet this Grand
Kaio guy all that much sooner!
Oh yeah, I can fly!
Whoopsie, whoopsie!
I forgot to ask how to
get to Grand Kaio's World!
You get to Grand Kaio's
World by taking an airplane.
All right, an airplane, you say? Okay, then!
There's just no helping that guy.
I'll bet he comes back here again.
There, see! Here he comes!
So, where is this airplane?
It's at the airport next to
Great King Yama's castle,
for those that are going to heaven.
All right, got it! Later!
I wonder if he'll be coming back once more.
I sure hope he comes back.
Here he comes! Here he comes!
If we're going to Great King Yama's
place, it's faster to go this way!
Goku! See here!
Okay, now, don't push.
Please observe your place in line.
You go to heaven.
Yay! Yay! I made it to heaven!
Yay! Yay! All right! Yay!
All right...
Bring in the next one.
Heya!
Of all the people it could have
been, if it isn't you, Son Goku!
Have you died again?
And you're here too, Kaio-sama?
Well, a lot has happened
to bring us here, you see.
Well, Great King Yama, I need to hurry on ahead.
Whoa, won't you have some tea before you go?
Excuse me, there, we can't have you taking cuts.
You have to remain in line
and receive your judgment.
You've got a body...!
Y-You're one of those special
"free pass" people, aren't you?
You're the first one I've ever seen!
Frankly speaking, I am impressed!
Now, now, be my guest!
Th-Thank you...
Good grief, that guy just goes around
putting people out one after another.
Well, see you around, Yama!
Sure, take care.
So that's a body given
only to just martial artists,
that you can train with
even in the Next World?
Oh, Goku saved the Earth,
did he? That explains it...
Okay, those spirits in A Group
going to heaven, please follow me.
You there, don't get out of line.
Please be sure to follow right
behind the spirit in front of you,
so you don't get lost, okay?
Right!
How come our airplane is
the only one this run-down?
I wanted to ride on one
of those bigger airplanes.
Is that heaven? It sure is huge!
We're just about there, Goku.
Huh? Where, where? Where?
Look, look. Over there.
Huh? Where?
That is Grand Kaio's World.
Wow, it's a smaller planet than I imagined.
N-Now look here! How can you say that?!
Sorry, sorry. It's definitely much
bigger than your planet, Kaio-sama.
That's plenty rude in it's own right.
Awesome! These folks all
look pretty strong, all right.
Kaio-sama!
It's been so long!
Excuse us for not coming
to see you for so long.
Yeah, you're working hard, aren't you?
Yes.
Wow, Kaio-sama, you're pretty
famous here in the Next World.
They come from the North Galaxy, you see.
You mean, the same as me?
Yeah, which would make them
about 2,300 years your seniors.
2,300 years...?
Eh?! 2,300 years?!
They've been training
here for that long a time?!
45,303...
This is the Hall of the Grand Kaio,
where Grand Kaio-sama lives.
I'm about to meet the strongest
guy in the Next World, the Grand Kaio.
You'll call him Grand Kaio-sama!
If you conduct yourself disrespectfully,
you're going to wind up hurting later!
Is that how strong he is? This Grand Kaio?
Sama!!
Sama, I meant.
The truth is, not even I have
seen Grand Kaio-sama fight before.
However, his fighting is
widely said to be so wonderful,
yet so terrible, that it
cannot be described in words.
Yeah! Th-This is it! This is the car that I wanted!
Grand Kaio-sama, how nice,
how nice! I want one of these, too!
Oh, the hind end on this is so sexy!
Wow! It's the greatest! It's the greatest!
Kaio-sama, let's hurry up and go!
You!
W-What?!
Kaio of the West!
Huh?
What's going on? Eh? Eh?
What? What? What? What is this?
What are you doing here?!
What are you doing here yourself?!
Today, I'm here to see Paikuhan
here, after a long absence.
Paikuhan is the West Galaxy's
greatest martial artist, you know.
What?!
W-What?!
Wha–?!
Y-You've died, have you?!
Y-You mean this...?!
A Kaio that has died...!
This is much funnier
than any of your lousy jokes!
Lousy jokes? What do you mean, lousy jokes?!
There are a number of
circumstances that account for this.
I got Kaio-sama dragged into this.
Who is this kid?
Me? I'm Son Goku.
Goku is a just martial artist, who saved
a planet in the North Galaxy named Earth.
He's one exceptionally strong fellow.
What? You say he's exceptionally strong?
Ha! But he's not as
strong as Paikuhan here.
Nope. Goku is the stronger one.
Ridiculous! No, Paikuhan
is obviously the stronger one!
No, that would definitely be Goku!
It's definitely, definitely, Paikuhan!
You don't get it, do you?!
You're the one who doesn't get it!
In that case, how about
we let them fight?!
That's just what I wanted!
Okay, go get him, Goku!
Eh? Go get him? You mean, fight right here?
Paikuhan, put him away nice and easy!
Just a minute!
That voice!
It's the Grand Kaio-sama!
Huh? Where?
Come on, come on,
come on, Goku! Bow your head!
Hii!
Grand Kaio-sama!
That's the Grand Kaio-sama?
Forgive me for interrupting you
while you're busy, but Paikuhan-chan,
would you go to Ku-jigo for me for a little bit?
Yes, sir.
What's Ku-jigo?
He's talking about Jigoku.
[Jigoku: Hell]
You take the "ku" from Jigoku
and put it in front to get Ku-jigo.
Something troubling has cropped up in Ku-jigo.
Something troubling?
Recently, this guy named Cell was
sent to Ku-jigo by Ma-ya-chan, you see...
Cell?!
Cell, you go to hell!
This Cell, accompanied
by someone named Freeza,
is going around wreaking havoc.
–Cell?
–Together with Freeza and them?
So, I'd like for you to
go and take care of them.
As you wish.
You can't do it alone! I'm going with you!
G-Goku! You can't do this without permission!
Oh, it's okay.
Kaio-chan of the North, why
don't you let him do as he likes?
I don't remember anyone asking you to help.
You don't know Cell or Freeza,
which is why you can say that!
Those guys are awfully strong!
This is terrible.
Please oni!
I-If you would, let us go please oni!
Huh? If it ain't Gozu and Mezu!
You're the one who fell from the
Serpentine Road before! Son Goku!
Thank goodness we haven't
been found by Cell oni!
We've come to put down Cell.
–Eh? Really oni?
Well? You've learned well who it
is you should be following, right?
Who's the boss of this place?
I can't hear you!
C-Cell...!
You mean Cell-sama, don't you?
Oni!
You guys! You still plan on
misbehaving here in Hell?!
Son Goku!
You ain't repented one bit, have you?
This is terrific. It appears
that you have died, too.
I'm glad to see you again.
Men of the Special Corps...?
Yes, sir!
Paikuhan!
W-What?!
W-When did Goku get so–?!
Do not panic!
That was nothing. I did kill him, after all.
I-I should have known,
Cell-san. If you would be so kind...
What the...
What?!
Impossible!
Paikuhan...!
W-What speed!
D-Damn!
To just get trounced like
this, and not be able to die...
It's like being in Hell.
They shouldn't be causing
any more mischief now.
Yeah, I doubt it.
Awesome. To think that there'd
be someone as awesome as this...!
The Next World is going to be pretty exciting!
There were masters in the Next
World that were even better than Goku.
Goku's chest swelled greatly with anticipation.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Kaio-sama, if I win the Anoyoichi Tournament,
the Grand Kaio will train me, right?
Yeah. But Goku, everyone
who enters this tournament
is going to be like Paikuhan.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"I'm the Best in the Next World!!
Heroes of the Ages Assembled."
How nice. I wish I could enter, too.
"Next time"
"I'm the Best in the Next World!!
Heroes of the Ages Assembled"