Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
I would not be proud of myself if I defeated you
the pathetic way you are now.
Very well. You may become your perfect form.
What's this, has Vegeta let Cell go
in order to become his perfect form?
As well, Kuririn had by his own hand...
...destroyed the device that
would have shut down No. 18!
Get away safely!
No matter what, don't
get absorbed by Cell! Please!
No. 18! I found you!
They now face their greatest crisis!
"A Shock to the Entire Universe!! Cell's
Spectacular Evolution Toward His Perfect Form."
I-I've found you, No. 18!
You've been hiding over there!
Great! Now I can become my perfect form!
Power! Speed! Technique!
Brains! Mental Strength!
The time when I achieve a perfect
existence in all things has come!
Aren't those the Artificial
Humans? Kuririn-san is there too.
This is bad! They haven't
realized that they've been found!
Why?! This was your singular chance!
Just what is it you think you're doing?
I-It's just...
Stop staring me down like that, would you?
That doesn't matter!
In any case, just get away safely!
If you're too slow about it, you'll
be swallowed up by Cell, you know!
I beg you! The destiny
of the Earth rests with you!
Hey!!
You've been found by Cell!
Oh, no!
I will not allow you your perfect form!
So, then...
Luckily enough, the
Artificial Humans are here, huh?
Amazing! Is that how strong Trunks has become?
His ki has vanished.
Run! Cell has concealed his presence
and is sneaking around underground!
T-This is dangerous!
We have to hurry and scram!
R-Right! No. 16!
No. 16!
I'll be fine. You guys run away!
I cannot protect you any more. Go now!
No, dammit!
This is an extraordinary chance for me.
I won't let you interfere, Trunks!
It's been a while, hasn't it, No. 18?
Don't strain yourself, No. 16.
You're only moments from
shutting down, aren't you?
On top of which,
Vegeta seems to be cooperating in
allowing me to become my perfect form.
Damn it, Vegeta!
Now then, shall I have her?
My most first-class cuisine?
What are you loafing around for, Cell?
Hurry up and become
this perfect form of yours!
That fool!
That cursed Vegeta!
What? What's happened to Vegeta?
Hey, there!
What's happening with Vegeta?
And what about Trunks? Hey there, I said!
Still not yet? Hurry up, Son!
Thanks, Vegeta.
We had quite an intrusion there, didn't we?
You piece of crap!
Small fry!
For a mechanical doll
who has turned into junk,
this is what your power ought to be, I suppose.
It isn't hurting a bit.
You miserable monster!
Dad, you are mistaken!
We can't let him reach his perfect form!
What are you going to do if his
power becomes greater than ours?
You're so pathetic!
Don't you feel like seeing
how strong he will become?
I... I don't want to see it!
I've had enough hellish futures!
You'll see, I will prevent his perfect form!
Even if I have to defeat you, Dad!
Defeat me?
Impossible! I don't think you're
capable of attacking your father.
If you can shoot me, then shoot me!
I-I'm sorry, Father.
Since I'm making so little progress,
Father, your training hasn't advanced at all.
That's fine! You just worry
about becoming Super Saiyan!
R-Right!
Now, we're off to bed for the rest of the day.
We have more harsh training
waiting for us tomorrow.
Right!
Damn...
So, it's all over?
N-No. 18...
It's all hopeless!
Hurry! Get away from here as fast as you can!
Why, you...!
Don't worry about me! Get going, now!
I can't do that!
Y-You...
Damn that Trunks...
He really did shoot me!
That bratty piece of crap!
I won't let you get away!
I won't let you run anywhere, No. 18.
That brat...!
Taiyo-ken!!
No, dammit!
My eyes...!
Now, to savor you slowly, No. 18...!
Damn it all!
S-Stop it!
No. 18!
Damn...
Cell is changing!
Is this perfect form of
his finally coming around?
You're sure taking long enough.
Don't you disappoint me this time!
Damned if I'm going to let
you reach your perfect form!
What's going on here?
It's as if the whole Earth
is trembling, you know?
Cell's ki is continuing to swell up!
Grand Elder-sama!
Dende, huh?
You've felt it too, have you?
What is this evil ki?
What in the world is happening on Earth?
I don't know.
I don't know, but at
this rate, it's not just Earth,
but the whole universe that could be destroyed.
T-The whole universe?
I-I was wrong not to have shut down No. 18...
At last... At last, No. 18 having been absorbed,
Cell is becoming his perfect form.
Will his terrifying form lead
the universe to devastation?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Cell has finally achieved his perfect form.
Damn. We have to hurry up with our training.
Hmph, that's your perfect form?
Took you long enough.
Now let me see what you've got!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Battle Power Infinity!!
Birth of the God of Destruction Named Cell."
I have to become stronger, too, and fast!
"Next time"
"Battle Power Infinity!!
Birth of the God of Destruction Named Cell"