The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Gohan, concerned that his
identity would be revealed
when transformed into a Super Saiyan,
had Bulma make him a transformation device.
I am...
...he who loves justice...
...the Great Saiyaman!
That is so uncool.
"Gohan's Frantic First Date!?"
I am... the champion of
justice... Great Saiyaman!
It still doesn't have enough punch, huh?
Maybe the previous one was better...
Big Brother, hang in there.
All right... how about this one?
The heavens call...
the Earth calls... the people call...
they call for me to strike down evil!
Do you not see the helmet on my head?
You know I am invincible!
The ultimate hero!
The Great Saiyaman!
That settles it.
Big Brother, that's so cool!
Gohan, did you come up with a good one?
Uh-huh. Leave it to me, Mother.
Still, it's about time you were gettin' to bed.
You'll oversleep tomorrow,
and be late for school.
It's okay, it's okay.
Waugh! I overslept!
Uh-oh. I'm going to be late!
Th-That girl saw me transform.
She knows that I am the Great Saiyaman.
What are you looking so miserable about?
The teacher isn't even here yet.
"Richo of Rosai was a young, erudite
man with a profound love of knowledge,
whose name had come up for a promotion.
"But he was a very self-dependent man,
who considered himself above
being a low-ranking public servant."
Okay then, next, Son Gohan, let's have you read.
Son Gohan?
I'm screwed. There's absolutely
no doubt that girl saw me.
As long as she doesn't tell anyone else–
Son Gohan!
Son Gohan-kun, enough!
Go stand out in the hall.
Right.
I've had it.
"Even when the nearby mountains
and fields had been searched,
there was no sign of him.
"Afterward, there was not a single person
who knew what had happened to Richo."
Okay, next up, Angela-kun.
Angela-kun...!
Angela!
Angela-kun, you too?
Sensei, I'm so sorry!
U-Um... Angela-kun...
And so... I... I...
I'll go out and stand.
Um...
Huh? You're...
W-What's going on?
Um... Gohan-san?
U-Uh...
My name is Angela.
N-Nice to meet you.
I know this is sudden,
but do you have a girlfriend?
N-No, not exactly...
There is someone, isn't there?
It's true! I knew it, there is someone!
Uh, hold on a minute, there.
W-What to do?
I know your secret.
So you do, after all?
Would you take me on a date?
A date?
I knew it! You have a girlfriend!
And here I thought we could keep
your secret between just the two of us!
A-All right, understood.
Really?
Yay! Yay! Okay then, tomorrow,
Sunday, let's go right out and have a date!
I'll be waiting for you at
10 o'clock at Satan Station.
Sure enough, that girl
knows that I'm Great Saiyaman.
And to make sure she
doesn't reveal my identity,
I have to make sure that
I don't hurt her feelings.
But come to think of it,
I've never been on a date before.
What should I do?
I'm home!
Ah, welcome back.
Um, Mother, I need to ask
you about something awkward.
How did your first date with Father go?
Huh? Oh dear, my boy.
What a thing to be askin' me!
Let's see... as I recall...
Okay, Goku-sa, today we're
goin' to have a good solid date.
But Chichi, I ain't ever had a date
before, so I don't know much about them.
Oh my goodness, Goku-sa! A date has
always been the most enjoyable thing
that a boy and a girl can do together.
The most enjoyable thing, huh?
I know what you mean.
Yes, I mean...
Yeah, this is really fun!
Goku-sa's right jab from back then
is even now engraved upon my heart.
R-Really...?
Gohan-san!
Gohan-san, I'm impressed.
You really came, huh?
U-Um, so does this mean you
won't reveal my secret to anyone?
Huh?
I mean, it's not as though... ummm...
Huh? A m-m-movie?
I'm so happy!
Okay, let's go, let's go!
U-Uh... er...
All right, hurry up!
Ah! Gohan-san!
You're not interested in being with
me after all, are you? I'm going home!
I'm sorry! It's not like that!
It's not like that! It's not like that!
Excuse me...! Excuse me...! Please, excuse me...!
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry about that.
Let's go to a coffee shop!
At a time like this, you should ask
the girl how many sugars she wants.
Is that right?
How many?
Thirteen.
12... 13...
Ah! Thank you!
You know, Gohan-san,
you'd never think it, just by looking at you.
I was so surprised when I saw you.
She means the Great Saiyaman thing.
Um, what do you think about it?
I think it's very cute.
Cute?
Gohan-san, is that what you always wear?
Oh, it's just in case something happens.
It is cute, all right!
So, please make sure to keep
it a secret from everyone, okay?
Uh-huh, I know.
Say, let's go to Satan Tower now.
Okay?
Fire! Fire!
Gohan-san!
Hey, I heard there are some folks
who couldn't get out in time on the roof!
Are you serious?
Videl-san...
Can't you get any closer?
It's no use, Videl-san.
I can't do any better, because of
the upward currents from the fire!
At this rate, those people will be...!
Hey, I can see a large water tank over there!
Can we do anything with that?
What do you mean, "do anything"?
I mean, use that water to
put out the fire, or something!
Even if you open the valve, the water
will just drain through the plumbing,
and won't extinguish anything.
However, there is a
valve which isn't hooked up.
If I open it, the water will come out, right?
Yes, and it will flood the roof,
but I doubt it will put out
the fire within the building.
That should at least buy us a little time.
Videl-san, you can't mean it!
It's all or nothing!
Videl-san!
Here it is.
Hot!
Gohan-san, where are you going?
I have to save the people on the roof!
But Gohan-san, you going up
there won't help anything, will it?
Huh? What are you talking about?
It's times like this when a
champion of justice is needed!
Hey, you! Watch out!
Gohan-san...
It won't open...!
W-We're done for!
The Great Saiyaman appears!
Now then, make way.
All right...
W-We're saved!
And just then, he appeared.
Son Gohan-kun!
What are you doing here?
Er, nothing special.
Are you sure you're not hiding anything?
N-Not at all...!
Angela-san...
Gohan-san, how awful!
You do have a girlfriend after all, don't you?!
Videl-san is your girlfriend,
isn't she, Gohan-san?
That's why you paid no mind to
the danger and rushed into the fire!
Well, Videl-san, do you
know about that thing?
That thing?
Anything but that!
The truth about Gohan-san is...
...he wears teddy-bear underpants.
Teddy-bear?
Underpants?
That's right. I saw it myself the other day.
I saw it myself, just the other day.
How cute...!
It was a teddy-bear!
And that's my secret?
That's right.
Then, you didn't see anything
on the rooftop yesterday?
What do you mean? I didn't
have my contacts in then,
so I could only see things
close by. Did something happen?
Teddy-bear underpants?
So that's the kind of taste you have, is it?
Well... those are what my
mother bought me by mistake,
and as it happened, all my
others were in the laundry–
I won't have anything more
to do with you, Gohan-san!
I suppose I really ought
to apologize to Angela-san...
I've liked you for a very long time.
I'll be waiting for you next
Sunday in front of Satan City Station.
The Great Saiyaman's
identity had not been revealed.
However, has Videl become aware of something?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
You sure seem busy, Gohan.
Transforming, saving people,
running away from that girl Videl...
The Great Saiyaman is unbelievably uncool,
but I am interested in his uncommon strength.
I promise, I'll identify who he really is.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Gohan, Scramble! Save Videl!!"
To not be able to get out
of class now, of all times!
"Next time"
"Gohan, Scramble! Save Videl!!"