The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
At last, Majin Boo was
obliterated by the Super Genki Dama,
created by Goku from Genki collected
from throughout the entire universe.
And so, half a year later...
Using Shen Long's power, people
had their memories of Boo erased,
and peace returned to the streets.
That's dirty, using Fusion! All right, then...!
"You're Late, Goku! Everyone Party!!"
This one, maybe?
Nope, this one after all, I think...
I wonder what kind of clothes
they're wearin' in the city now.
That's perfect on you, Gohan!
Mother, do I really need to go in this outfit...?
What are you talkin' about?
We're goin' to the city!
Oh, well...
How many years has it been since
we've gone to the city? I'm so excited!
Say, Gohan, which one do
you think is better lookin'?
We may be going to the city, but
it's only to Bulma-san's house, right?
We're going to go eat barbecue!
Gohan!
Do you know where my lipstick is?
Mother, you have lipstick?
I got some before, from Bulma-san.
The same goes for some paint-like
stuff for spreadin' over your eyes.
I don't know anything about
them. Don't know, don't know...
I must have packed
them away somewhere...
By the way, has Goku-sa finished gettin' ready?
Huh? He was here until just a moment ago.
I wonder where he went.
You don't think...?
There's one missing!
Ah, is that where it is?
All right...
W-What's the matter?!
I was just trying to return
it to the nest, you know!
There!
But if the egg hatches in a place like this,
the child is going to fall off the cliff!
He went to see some eggs, you say?
Why does he have to go see those
dinosaur eggs again at a time like this?!
He said they looked like
they were going to hatch today,
so he was just going to
go see how they were doing.
Mother!
He's not in the vicinity.
Shall I go look over on the
other side of the mountain?
I've had it! We're goin' with just us!
Good grief, that Goku-sa is never
around at important times like this!
He's always gettin' himself left behind!
It's not my fault if he whines about it later!
Really, at times like this...!
I don't think that reinforcing
it that way is going to hold.
Okay! You're saying you want
to do this all yourself, right?
These are your first children, after all!
Now then, I'd better get back soon,
or Chichi is going to get angry at me.
You can't have these!
Sorry about this.
I can't leave them alone like this...
Kuririn-san!
Oh, Trunks! You've gotten
a little bigger, haven't you?
Aw, gee... Come on in!
Hey, Trunks! Thanks for stopping us!
I had a bit too much speed going.
Yamucha, is this yours?
Yeah, Kuririn!
This is the latest model
our company makes!
Actually, I asked Bulma to
have them make it cheaper for me.
How nice! Maybe I'll ask her too.
Hey, Chichi!
Good day!
Yeah, you're all looking well.
Huh? Where's Goku?
Uh, about that...
He said he couldn't come, because
there are cute babies of his to be born!
Hey, what does she mean, babies?
Don't tell me...!
I-I'll explain everything later.
Thanks!
Look at that, look at that...!
You're sure it's okay for
Kami-sama to go to parties?
It's fine, once in a while, isn't it?
Here.
Thanks.
Piccolo-san!
Is this where you've been? It's been too long.
Come to think of it, I was found by Gramps
over in a bamboo thicket on this mountain.
Around there, I think,
is where I was picked up...
Gramps sure was strict...
Even so, Gramps was also kind.
Gramps...
Hey, hey, hey!
Sorry, but if you're going to fight,
could you do it over there?
All right, fight!
Let's dance!
Gohan, dance your heart out!
What are you doin', Gohan?!
I'll show you the secret to how it's done!
Awesome, awesome!
Goten, your mom is incredibly cool, huh?
Big Brother, did you know?
Mm-hmm... I knew that mother was
a master of the Eternal Turtle style,
but this is the first time
I've ever seen her do it.
That's right! Gohan-kun, you and
the others hadn't been born yet, huh?
Chichi-san once even entered the
Tenkaichi Tournament, you know!
Are you okay, Mother?
Sure enough, you can't win out against age.
Incredible! Just what you'd
expect of Goku-san's wife!
Goku?
Goku sure is late.
I wonder if Son-kun
isn't going to come after all.
Are you that concerned about it?
Ah! So that's it, Bulma-san!
You like Goku-sa, don't you?
You'd best give up on him!
I'm far and away prettier, after all.
Indeed! You're very pretty today, Chichi-san!
That makes it sound like
I'm usually not pretty, doesn't it?
Somehow, I feel sorry for Chichi-san.
He'll come, that's for sure.
What, you guys were
worried and came to watch too?
I'd like to relocate that egg to a safer place,
but it's gotten so weak that if I move
it at all, it looks like it might break.
Damn...
Okay, wait here. I'll be right back!
Hang in there for bit until I'm
finished with that nest up there!
I'm going to reinforce
that with this right now!
Whew, that was close!
Your egg is all right!
Well, let's keep going!
Well now, the rain has stopped, and
it's about time we were going home.
Okay then, we'll see you later.
Mm-hmm. Be careful, okay?
Don't be a stranger.
Goku!
–Son-kun!
–Goku!
Father!
Goku!
Hey, sorry, sorry I'm here so late.
–Where's Chichi...?
–I'm right here!
What do you mean by moseyin' on in
here now? Everyone's gettin' ready to leave!
Yeah, I meant to come right
back, but you see... Forgive me!
Well, it's not like this is the first time, huh?
If I were to get upset over every little thing,
I could never be Goku-sa's wife, could I?
Have you eaten yet?
No, not yet.
For cryin' out loud! For a husband,
you sure need lookin' after!
I'll go fix you somethin'.
Bulma-san, would you help me?
Of course!
So? So? Were they born?
Yeah.
Tell us the story of these eggs!
Right. They were incredibly
cute babies, four of them!
They're born!
Tell me, tell me, compared to when I was
born, which one of us was more adorable?
Which, you ask? I was dead
when you were born, Goten, so...
Hey, Vegeta!
Don't just stand over there,
you come on over here too!
Just by him being there,
everything around Goku is livelier.
everyone has more fun.
Sure enough, you are Number One, Son Goku!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
It's been ten years, huh?
It looks like someone I'm interested in
will be entering the Tenkaichi Tournament,
so I've decided to enter too,
along with my granddaughter, Pan.
Huh?! Pan-chan is still
just a four-year-old girl!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Grandpa Goku! I Am Pan!!"
Who is it that Father could be interested in?
"Next time"
"Grandpa Goku! I Am Pan!!"