Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
P-Piccolo-san?
Piccolo is brought to the edge of
death by Freeza's demonic hand!
I'm not letting a single
one of you go home alive!
Goku!!
And then, Kuririn too...
Y-You're going to pay for that...
How dare you... How dare you...!
Gohan, take Piccolo with you
and get yourselves back to Earth.
He's still barely alive.
Go home now, while I still
have some sliver of reason left!
Right!
His fury toward Freeza has changed Son Goku!
At last, the legendary
Super Saiyan has appeared!
"An Explosion of Anger!!
Goku, Avenge Everyone's Deaths"
W-What's with his transformation?
Saiyans are only supposed
to turn into great apes.
W-What does this mean?
Quickly, Gohan. If Piccolo
dies, Kami-sama dies too.
You must know what that would mean.
Father!
Don't concern yourself about me!
I will be sure to return to Earth later!
B-But how will you?
If we take your spaceship back...
Don't argue! Do you want to annoy me?!
Father...
Thank you! Thank you, Father!
I'll be waiting.
I'll be waiting for you to
appear in good shape, Father!
There's no way I'm letting
you get away like that.
Enough is enough, you scumbag!
You've killed so many blameless
people, one after the other...
You even killed Kuririn...!
W-Why do you have this kind of power?
Don't tell me... don't tell me you're...!
Father, I understood!
What Vegeta was saying is true, isn't it?
Father, you've become one. A Super Saiyan!
That's strange...
There aren't any malfunctions anywhere.
Aren't you done fixin' it yet?!
While we're here doin' this,
Gohan-chan's growin'
more and more delinquent!
What's the matter, ol' timer?
You've got such a serious look on yer mug.
I want to go see Gohan now!
It's nothing.
I just had a strange, uneasy feeling is all.
'Bout what?
Goku. I'm worried that as a
result of his getting so strong,
he's become a double-edged sword.
What're you talkin' 'bout?
A double-edged sword can deliver
a powerful blow to an opponent,
but it can also deliver the
same kind of blow the other way.
Yeah, what about it?
What about it? Up until now, he's fought so
many powerful opponents, one after another.
As a result, he's gotten so strong.
But supposing this Freeza guy turns
out to have the ultimate in strength...
Supposin' he does?
As he fights against someone
his equal, Goku just might...
Ah, on the other hand,
maybe I'm worrying unnecessarily.
I...
I am furious with you, Freeza!
You talk like you're so self-important.
You say I've killed the blameless?
Are you trying to say that what you
Saiyans have done up until now was so right?
That's why we were destroyed.
I'm the one who destroyed you.
All of you monkeys got on my nerves.
And now I'm going to destroy you.
Me, Freeza-sama?
Don't let things go to your head.
There's no way you can win.
Even supposing you were a Super Saiyan.
Father...
I ain't forgiving you, even if you apologize.
Dammit!
Y-You dodged it!
T-There's no way you could have!
W-Why you...!
If only I could hit you, you'd be...!
Hit me and see.
W-What did you...?
Mock me, will you?!
You can destroy whole planets,
but it seems you can't even
destroy a single man, huh?
W-Wh-What the hell are you?!
As you are surely well aware...
I am the Saiyan who
came from Earth to defeat you.
Despite my calm, quiet heart,
I am the legendary warrior,
awakened by intense anger.
I am the Super Saiyan, Son Goku!!
The transcendent power of a Super Saiyan!
Goku, now is the time to avenge everyone!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
I'm going to beat Freeza! I'll beat
him, and avenge Kuririn's death!
If it is to come down to this,
I'll blow up the whole planet.
I can continue to live,
even in the vacuum of space.
I wonder though, how about you Saiyans?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Destruction of Planet Namek!?
A Demonic Flash Pierces the Ground."
Father, hurry up and escape in the spaceship!
"Next time"
"The Destruction of Planet Namek!?
A Demonic Flash Pierces the Ground"