The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Upon Trunks winning the Junior Division,
a pair of mysterious men
appear before the Z Warriors.
And so, the drawing for
the Tenkaichi Tournament began.
Vegeta, huh?
Mister Satan, number 10.
It's been too long!
So, shall we get slightly rowdy?
Right, ladies and gentlemen!
We are about to commence
the Tenkaichi Tournament!
"What's the Matter, Piccolo!?
An Unheard-of No-Fight-Forfeit."
Mister Satan, the board with the matches for
this Tenkaichi Tournament has been drawn up.
Can we have your impressions at this time?
Well, this time, from where I see it,
I would say that many high-level
contestants have come together.
I hope they will stick it out
well in the cause of advancing
and expanding the
techniques of hand-to-hand fighting,
as they take aim at such a large star as myself.
As might be expected of Mister Satan!
Always thinking about the
world of hand-to-hand, aren't you?
Of course, as Champion, it's only natural.
Champion, could you tell us your
aspirations for this Tournament?
Well, there can be only one aspiration
for someone aiming to be World Champion.
Can we take that to be a
declaration of victory, then?
Oh, no, you never know what
might happen during the matches.
Carelessness is forbidden.
Such modesty!
Moving along, does anyone
know who my opponent is?
She's a lady contestant, named No. 18.
Ho, a lady? No, this is too much!
He's known all along, and I told him.
Piccolo-san...
Say, Gohan-kun, that person has
been just like that for some time now.
He's unusually uptight, isn't he?
That's not it in the least.
He does that to heighten his ki is all.
Piccolo-san, why are you so uptight?
Is it your next opponent?
You're sure fired up, aren't you Goku?
I just can't seem to wait.
Considering your first match is against Vegeta,
it'll be like holding the final round right there.
I'm already excited!
Piccolo...
Yeah, he's pretty fired up too.
Indeed, looks like you'll be my
opponent in the second round, Piccolo.
Take it easy on me, okay?
Right, Goku?
And as for you, your opponent
is the World Champion for now.
Spare him enough face accordingly.
Leave it alone! I know, already.
Videl's in the third match?
For some reason, I'm starting to get excited too!
Not to worry.
Videl winning is about as sure
a thing as Mister Satan winning.
That's a good point.
Oh, The Great Saiyaman is here!
That means the second round will have
a match between the two friends of justice!
That'll be interesting, huh?
Hmph, I'm not even sure that yokel
boy will even get past the first round!
Listen up, raise your voices!
We, the Satan City Police will support
Videl-san with everything we've got!
Here!
What's up, Bulma? You're
having an unusually fun time of it.
After all, Trunks just won the Junior Division.
With that having sunk in, of course I'm happy.
Vegeta will win the Senior Division,
and father and son will have
won the Tenkaichi Tournament.
That'll be impossible!
His opponent is my Goku-sa.
Forget victory, Vegeta
will lose in the first round.
Oh, we don't know that.
After all, Trunks-kun beat out Goten-kun.
It's an absolute certainty
that Goku-sa will be the victor!
As sure as the sun comes up in
the west, Goku-sa does not lose!
I'm sorry, but you know, Vegeta has
been undergoing ferocious training...
...with my newly-modeled
hyper-gravity device for five years now.
This time Vegeta will win for sure!
Goku-sa knows our family's
livin' rests on him winnin'!
Not like some people I could mention
who are here to fight as their hobby!
Vegeta will win!
Goku-sa!
Vegeta!
H-Hey! Cut it out, you're
both acting like children!
You shut up!
Ooh, ow!
We apologize for the delay.
Who from among this group will
it be that stands at the pinnacle?
And so, we commence the matches!
First up is Contestant
Kuririn vs. Contestant Punter.
Good luck, Kuririn.
Well, guess I'll be back in a moment.
Whaddya think you're...
Oh, so that's where you were!
I thought maybe you'd run away again!
You've gotta have no luck
to be my opponent right away!
Well, don't worry yourself.
With any luck, you'll just
have to be taken to the hospital.
And so, the two contestants take the ring.
Contestant Kuririn placed very well in
this Tournament during his younger years,
and this will be his first
appearance in a long while.
He faces Contestant Punter,
known for his ferocity,
who last Tournament made
it all the way to the semifinals,
where he unfortunately
met with a loss by ringout.
This Tournament, he naturally
came with his eye on victory!
That man fighting with Father
looks big and strong. Is he okay?
Relax, relax. That guy is nothing at all.
Your father is the strongest man in the world!
Really?
Yeah, really.
Among earthlings, anyhow.
What's the deal with
that difference in body size?
This is no excuse for a match!
That poor Contestant Kuririn!
Oh, Contestant Punter!
Even with that much difference in their size,
he doesn't appear to be
going easy on him one bit!
Contestant Punter is here with a purpose!
So, how will Contestant
Kuririn face off against him?
It's obvious! I'll have to make him understand
that the Tenkaichi Tournament
is no place to play around.
It's no place for a pipsqueak
pappy like yourself to come to.
Man, this is no time to be wasting
my energy on a bonehead like him.
Once you set flame to Punter's
brutal way of fighting, he has no mercy.
And so, please begin the match immediately!
As you can see, I may be large,
but I'm also fast and nimble. Got that?!
You know that it's useless for
you to try to scamper away from me!
I got it, I got it. I won't run, I won't run.
It's too soon to lose heart yet!
I'll show you how tough I am next!
Go ahead and try punching me.
What's the matter? Don't be shy!
Well? Well? Well?
All right.
I accept your...
...gracious offer!
Right, Ringout!
Contestant Punter, Ringout!
Contestant Kuririn wins!
Awesome!
–He did it, he did it!
Father is strong!
Told ya.
Way to go! As good as ever!
I've been waiting for this!
The Tenkaichi Tournament
has got to be just like this!
Nice going, Kuririn.
No problem.
Piccolo, your turn is next. Good luck!
Hey, what are you so nervous about?
This isn't the kind of match you
should be getting nervous over!
What's up, you guys?
No fair, Trunks-kun.
Let me have some too!
No way, we'll be found out! After the match!
But it's hot in here, I can't stand it!
Ah, watch out! You can't
just let go! Here, have some.
Ah, that was good.
Continuing to the second match,
we will have Contestant
Shin vs. Contestant Ma Junior.
Both contestants, will enter the ring.
I see now. This would appear to
be quite an entertaining tournament.
And so, both contestants, if you would...
This is Contestant Shin's
first Tournament appearance.
He faces Contestant Ma Junior,
who showed us an extraordinary final
round battle in a Tournament long ago,
one that I remember quite well!
Uh, er, please don't
destroy the stadium this time.
Hey, isn't that one of the
guys that got in the way
when Mister Satan fought Cell?
You're right! Unmistakable, it was on the TV!
What's the matter?
Does he really bother you
that much? This Shin character?
Yeah, guess so.
I don't know... He doesn't look all that great.
Finally, we'll find out exactly the
extent of this guy's battle power,
which so far we can't even guess at.
And so, our second match! Please begin!
My power is failing me...
W-Why? For some reason,
it's difficult to fight him...
Yet I've just met him.
What's wrong?! Why aren't they fighting?!
What's happening?
What's the matter? Please begin!
Stop messing around and go, already!
We came here to watch a match!
We didn't come to see some staring contest!
Time is running out! Please, hurry and start!
U-Unbelievable!
What's the matter with you, Piccolo-san?
That rotten...
J-Just who is this guy? What is it about him?
You will know soon enough.
But now, let's just enjoy the game.
Piccolo!
What is the matter?
E-Excuse me.
I withdraw.
W-Withdraw?!
By withdraw, you mean you aren't fighting?
That's correct.
That's right, he used to be
the Kami over this planet.
Perhaps he has already
begun to sense who it is I am.
Since Contestant Ma Junior has withdrawn,
Contestant Shin wins without a fight!
What was that?
What's going on?! Doesn't he feel well?
You're right, he does seem awfully pale.
Piccolo-san!
Hey, Piccolo...
That bad, Piccolo?
Yeah. Our dimensions are too different.
You're kidding, right? Stop joking around!
I have to fight against him next!
Well, let's keep on going.
Next is the third match.
Contestant Videl vs. Contestant Spopovitch.
Videl! Videl! Videl! Videl!
You're incredibly popular, huh?
G-Good luck, Videl-san!
Hey, Spopovitch! It's your turn!
Hey, you hear me?
It's time.
Gohan-kun...
I'll be waiting for you in the second round.
Contestant Videl is, as everyone
knows, Mister Satan's daughter,
as well as a friend of justice,
who in cooperation with the police,
has helped punish many bad people.
At the Tournament seven
years ago, despite being a little girl,
she prides herself on
winning the Junior Division.
She faces Contestant Spopovitch,
who was eliminated in the
first round of the last Tournament,
but having undergone an Image
Change, is up to the challenge again.
Videl! Videl! Videl!
The Tenkaichi Tournament
reaches high tide with the appearance
of the ultra-popular Videl.
However, there is a mysterious contestant,
against whom even Piccolo is powerless.
What is the nature of this Shin?
And what is the meaning behind his gaze?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Hey, Gohan, there's something
weird about that Spopovitch guy.
You should get Videl to withdraw.
Eh?! His neck is broken,
but he acts like it's nothing!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Undyingly Unpleasant!?
The Mystery of Spopovitch."
I've got a bad feeling about this.
If this keeps up, Videl-san is in danger.
"Next time"
"Undyingly Unpleasant!?
The Mystery of Spopovitch"