Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
I do you a great service!
You will experience a terror
even greater than that of Hell's.
And so, gaze upon my true form!
Freeza, or anyone else, bring it on!
I have now become a Super Saiyan!
At last, Freeza shows his third transformation.
What is this unprecedented, ultimate power?
"The Death of Dende...
Come Forth! Intense, Wide-Open Power."
That's Freeza's true self?
He's smaller, more simple-looking,
and less formidable...
He's become an excellent example of why...
...you don't judge another's
ability by outward appearances!
Everything he's looked like up
until now has been cute by comparison!
D-Damn it to hell!
After all the trouble you went through
to revive me with the Dragon Balls!
I'm sorry...
There's simply no way I can
save the rest of you now. Damn...
Piccolo-san...
Freeza, you've finally
shown your true form, have you?
Even supposing Son Goku recovers,
Freeza now has the power to
destroy the universe as we know it.
This could be the point of no return!
How can this be?
Freeza's ki has risen once again!
Dammit...
"Bang."
What?
Dende!!
I didn't see it coming!
A-All I saw was some kind of flash!
T-That's not possible!
Now, there will be no more revivals.
Dende...
Someone just died. Who was it? Damn!
I can't tell what's going on any more!
Dende's been... k-killed...
H-He...
He saw that we were being
revived by that Namekian...
That's why he was first...
Damn you...
H-He vanished!
Y-You fool!
J-Just where...
Over here!
How did he?
I made you a promise, didn't I?
To show you a terror even greater than Hell's.
However, for that Namekian child
there to not be able to experience this...
it seems a shame, doesn't it?
I'll just have to let you guys take his share.
You bastard!
Take this!
You're not getting away!
Did you get him?
H-He's vanished again.
T-That's impossible!
You ignorant fools!
He's behind you!
What?!
As he said...
Get out of the way!
Worthless idiot!
O-Once again...
I couldn't see... him move... or attack...
But he... Vegeta saw it!
Why? Have his abilities gone up that much?!
Thanks!
You saved me.
You've got it all wrong.
I didn't do it to save you.
I thought I'd show you guys something good.
S-Something good?
Don't tell me you... you think you can beat him?
You might say that.
You can't possibly...
You guys are in our way.
Pull back and watch very closely!
Such confidence, Vegeta.
Or perhaps you're so frightened,
something has snapped?
You just keep on smirking
like that, while you still can.
What stands before you...
is that...
which you fear most!
A Super Saiyan!
Super... Saiy... an?
What's this "Super Saiyan"
business he's talking about?
As always, your jokes go too far.
In that case, I'll show
you the abilities I possess,
now that I have become a Super Saiyan!
Is this ki Vegeta's?
He's had an incredible power-up!
A-Awesome!
What's this?
Why is he so powered-up?
It's like he's a different person!
What the hell happened to him?
W-When a Saiyan recovers from near-death,
their power goes up several times over!
What?!
Gohan, let's put our money on
Vegeta, and take shelter for now.
Right!
You know, to think that suddenly,
someone could have
achieved this much of a power-up...
You can see it for yourself.
This is exactly why Vegeta
purposely came close to dying,
then got himself revived by Dende.
S-So that's what he was doing, huh?
He was right...
And now, Vegeta really is incredible!
With any luck, he might
actually take Freeza! Right, Gohan?!
W-What? What happened?
They're both the same
as they were before. What...
No, they aren't, Gohan. Try sensing Vegeta's ki.
It's calm now, but unbelievably huge!
Incredible! I can't believe his ki is so full!
Yeah. Vegeta really might be
able to beat Freeza at this point.
I'm supposed to think that
somehow you've powered up quite a bit.
You dare say! Just be grateful
you don't have a Scouter with you!
If your Scouter were to
read my battle rating now,
you would run away from here in tears!
The reason being, my power has
now become even greater than yours!
Brace yourself, Freeza.
This time, for sure, you
are going to meet your end!
What's the matter?
Are you too frightened to say anything?
Well, Freeza-san?
Okay, okay. I get you, I get you.
If you mean everything you said,
then I've decided to see for myself
the power of this so-called,
legendary Super Saiyan,
the strongest warrior in history.
Don't you mock me!
I see you!
Kakarrot won't even get a turn!
I-Incredible!
He's completely got Freeza on the run!
No!
V-Vegeta's... h-had it!
P-Piccolo-san...
What's the matter, Freeza?!
You can't defeat me by running away!
What? I-It can't be! Where is he?
There's no way I... a Super Saiyan
like me could have lost sight of him!
What?!
Im... possible...
I raise my speed in earnest for just a moment,
and you can't keep up, can you?
And you call yourself a Super Saiyan?
I-It can't be...
How can he toy with Vegeta,
with all his power and speed?
He really is an unthinkable beast after all!
F-Father!
A little longer... a little bit longer,
and I will have recovered!
Overwhelming speed and power–
and yet, it's still not enough to
match Freeza's ultimate power?
What will be the fate of Vegeta,
now that he has been shown his limits?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
I've gotten stronger! It's like
the power is welling up inside!
I'm coming now, everyone!
No matter which of you lower-life-form,
nothing-in-your-mind-but-fighting
Saiyans show up, it's all the same.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"How I've Waited for this Moment!!!
Son Goku Revived."
Father has finally arrived on the battlefield!
"Next time"
"How I've Waited for this Moment!!!
Son Goku Revived"
Father has finally arrived on the battlefield!