Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
I'm not going to put up with you anymore.
So you've finally shown
your true form, have you?
Now things are beginning to get interesting.
Give these to everyone.
Right.
Gohan showed his overwhelming strength
by defeating the Cell Juniors in an instant.
Is this the limit-transcending power
of Gohan that Goku was speaking of?
"Cell gets KO'ed!!
Just 2 Super Ironfisted Blows."
K-Kuririn-san? Kuririn-san?!
Thank goodness, he's still breathing.
Trunks...?
How's Gohan?
He's incredible.
I've never seen Gohan-san like this.
Th-That's Gohan?
I-Incredible! What happened to him?
That could be what Goku was talking about.
S-So it would seem...
Okay, everyone, hurry and
move away from here, please.
I'm going to go deliver these
senzu to Goku-san and Piccolo-san.
Quickly!
Come.
Too slow!
Toy with me, will you?!
C-Cell's attacks aren't connecting...!
So that's it, huh?
Son, I've figured out the
reason why you fought first.
You wanted to show Gohan
how Cell fights. Am I wrong?
Is that true?
It's Cell!
P-People of the world!
My camera may be broken,
but is my voice still getting through?
Right now, the death battle
between Cell and the bento salesboy
is unfolding right before my eyes!
Y-You're such a pro.
H-However, I will not move!
What a courageous announcer I must be!
U-Um, your mike...
"One moment please..."
What in the world is going on?
Isn't it obvious?
Is there anyone besides
Satan who can defeat Cell?!
Which must mean that Satan has lost...!
Is this the end of the Earth?
Is this the end? It surely is...
I-It can't be...!
"One moment please..."
Hey, Piroshiki! What are you doing?!
You'll be caught in the crossfire there!
I-I can't move!
I-Is he still there?! That idiot!
Doesn't he understand that
unless he's a pro at fighting,
like I am, that he can't stay here?!
Take this!!
W-When did you find time for them...?
I-Impossible...!
That's it, Gohan.
Thanks to you,
Gohan is completely reading
Cell's movements ahead of time.
That's got nothing to do with it.
Gohan has surpassed Cell in every way.
What?
G-Gohan's not bad, huh?
With Gohan like this,
he might be able to beat Cell.
Why, you...!
To think that there's another bastard out
there besides Kakarrot that has surpassed me...!
Dad...
Here's a senzu.
Sheesh, do I have to rely on one of these again?!
Damn...!
I-Impossible! How could
not even one punch land?!
If only I could hit him...!
W-Why, you...!
Don't get too full of yourself, kid.
You don't seriously think
that you can defeat me, do you?
I'll defeat you, all right.
That's pretty big talk, huh?
Well then, why don't I show you the true,
terrifying power of Cell?
What?!
Impossible!
You mean Cell hasn't been
taking this serious up to now?!
Th-That can't be...!
I-Is he saying he's going to
raise his power even higher?!
He's bluffing... He has to be bluffing...!
W-W-What kind of guy is this?!
It's a trick! It must be a trick!
He's swelling his ki up, augmenting it...
He wasn't... bluffing...!
That miserable freak!
Gohan...!
This is impossible...!
I-Is there no bottom to
the depths of his power?!
Th-The Earth is trembling!
W-What's this?
I-It's an earthquake!
I-It's finally here!
The end of the world!
The Earth–the Earth is lost!
"One moment please..."
So Cell's finally going
to fight at full power, huh?
What a ki!
It's like the whole universe is shaking!
I-Is this possible?
That's an outrageous amount of ki, isn't it?
G-Gohan-san...
How's that? This is me, when I mean business!
What of it?
H-He's fast!
His power isn't the only thing he raised!
His speed is also greater!
I-Impossible...!
W-Why, after only two punches...
...have I taken this much damage...?
A-Awesome... what power...!
Looks like there's still a
difference between their two forces!
H-He can win... Gohan-san can win!
After just two blows, the
full-power Cell is on the ropes!
Gohan, finish this once and for all!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Gohan, hurry up and finish Cell off!
If you press him any further,
there's no telling what he will do!
Ah, look! It's No. 18! Cell has spit out No. 18!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Something Amiss With Cell!!
His Perfect Form Crumbles."
It's too soon, Father! I've got to
make this guy suffer some more!
"Next time"
"Something Amiss With Cell!!
His Perfect Form Crumbles"