Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
This is a magnificent fight!
I would hate to let it end
due to an out-of-bounds defeat.
Let's remove the out-of-bounds
defeat from the rules.
It doesn't hold any meaning for us.
With the ring blown away,
the ferocious mortal combat
between Son Goku and Cell continued.
Ka... me...
You can't shoot a
Kamehame-Ha from that position!
If you did, it would be a disaster for the Earth!
ha... me...
H-Hey...!
Holy–!
Ha!!
At last, Goku's full power
Kamehame-Ha exploded forth!
"A Conclusion to the Deathmatch!!
Goku's Declaration of Surrender!?"
G-Goku...!
I-Incredible... What could have happened?
H-He got him! He got him! So that's it!
There was always his Instantaneous Movement!
Hey, he got him! Goku has finally won!
W-What's wrong, guys? Aren't you happy?
Mister Satan, it looks
like he has taken care of Cell.
Mister Satan!
W-Well, he did all right, huh?
S-Still, it's too bad.
I wanted to be the one who defeated him!
It really is too bad, Mister Satan, since
now you can't display your magnificent,
graceful, powerful moves to the whole world.
–Right?
–Yes!
P-People of the world!
It is truly disappointing
that before Mister Satan could
make his marvelous reappearance,
this unnamed young man has defeated Cell.
S-So is it over now?
That was kind of disappointing, huh?
Say, Mama, Mister Satan
isn't appearing any more?
It looks that way.
What does this mean?
Even in this condition, he still
has a good deal of ki remaining...
Be careful, Goku!
Cell will probably recover!
What?!
W-W-What?!
Cell's lower half has stood up!
He's come back to life!
Cell has come back to life!
Is this a trick as well, Mister Satan?
O-O-Of course it's a trick!
Come to think of it, you
can regenerate yourself, huh?
That's correct. Just like Piccolo.
That dirty bastard!
Sheesh, I thought I had won fairly easily.
But even you had to have lost
quite a bit of your ki over this.
That goes for both of us.
You're breathing quite a bit harder yourself.
Okay then, let's keep going.
I'll warn you now, though,
I won't fall for the same trick twice.
Make sure you don't waste
your strength on futile attacks
that would make this fight dull.
I know!
You don't say...
Once again, it has
become a ferocious battle!
Cell is attacking fiercely, and the
unnamed warrior is fighting back!
It's shaking! Even the place
where we're standing is shaking!
How is this going to unfold from here on?
Goku... why...?
Good afternoon!
Oh, Bulma?
Yeah. You've got it on, huh?
I thought that watching this with
an expert and having him explain it
would make it easier to
understand, so I came over.
Oh, there, there, there,
what's the matter, Trunks?
That Kamehame-Ha earlier must
have used up a considerable amount
of both of their powers.
And yet, to think that they
could still put up this kind of fight...!
What's the matter, Goku? Is that all you've got?
Damn...
Oh, he got him!
It's working! Way to go, Goku-san!
Way to go, Goku! One more step!
You're one step away from defeating Cell!
F-Father...
The unnamed young man
has started a ferocious attack!
Cell is in a huge pinch!
But then, inside that thick,
billowing cloud of explosions,
could anyone convey
what exactly is going on?!
We can't see! We can't see a thing!
What's going on?!
Like I said, it is not a malfunction!
Our man is risking his life
to relay this coverage! It's true!
Everyone, cut the phone lines!
He's winning! Goku is winning!
Goku-san!
He's done it!
Goku...!
A-Are you all right, Mister Satan?
Yeah! Hey, I'm jusd doing
some warm-ub egsercizes!
I should have known!
Never refusing to get ready
to fight, that's our Satan-sama,
the greatest combat sportsman in the world!
Y-You mighd say dhad...!
Y-Your announcer will not abandon
his microphone, even if I should die!
And so, what could this gigantic ball be?
Son Goku...
Your attack was good enough that it
caused me to have to raise a barrier.
I took on more damage than I expected.
That's awesome...
I'm not sure what it is, but it's still incredible.
Say, Mama, this isn't a movie, is it?
That man is Chichi-san's
husband after all, ain't he?
Remember, she was sayin'
recently that he was dyein' his hair.
Huh? Yeah, it does look like him.
Come to think of it, he's always
wearin' that garish outfit, huh?
Someone's gossipin' about us, I bet!
Goku-sa, hang in there!
Ah, he was so close!
He had just this much farther to go!
"This much farther" nothing!
Sure, it looks like he's putting up a good fight,
but unlike Goku, Cell still
has some breathing room.
Y-You're sure about that?
I'm sorry to say it, but Goku can't win.
What's more, it looked to me like
Goku knew that while he was fighting.
I-I don't know what he had in mind.
His ki has dropped!
So has Cell's, but Goku's is down severely!
Your strength seems to have
fallen off considerably, Son Goku.
You should swallow one
of those senzu things.
We could have an even
more spectacular battle!
Th-This is our chance!
Like he said, if we give
Goku-san a senzu,
and then everyone gangs up on him,
we could surely defeat Cell now!
You're right! That would work!
Kuririn-san!
Kuririn-san, hurry and give him a senzu!
Hold your tongue, Trunks!
You don't seem to have
any Saiyan pride, do you?
If he has to win that way,
he would probably prefer to die!
Right now, he's not fighting for Earth!
Remember that well!
B-But, at this rate...
He'll be done in, that's for certain.
A-As infuriating as it is,
I have to admit that even
as hard as I trained this time,
I couldn't top Kakarrot there.
That bastard has a gift.
However,
Cell has stayed one–sometimes
two steps ahead of even Kakarrot!
In that case, what are we supposed to do?!
Just watch on in silence?!
You said it yourself, didn't you?
That he surely has some kind of strategy?
We'll just count on that.
Goku-san...
Just what sort of strategy have you thought up?
What's the matter?
Is your pride getting in the way,
preventing you from taking a senzu?
Right now, I've lost a
considerable amount of strength.
If you reach your full power,
then the possibility of you winning,
slim though it may be, will increase.
I want to enjoy fighting
with you more and more!
I give up!
I surrender. Cell, I've learned
well how strong you are.
I'm giving up.
W-What?!
Surrender?!
H-He couldn't be...!
G-Goku surrendering?!
Has anything like this ever happened before?!
F-Father...?
What is he thinking?!
But why?! Why would Son-kun,
someone who would never say die...
...surrender now?!
Goku has lost.
What is the fate of the Earth now?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
The Cell Games will probably
end after the next person fights.
There ain't anyone else
around who can beat Cell.
Gohan, it's you're turn!
That's preposterous,
Goku! What are you thinking?!
Are you trying to get your own son killed?!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"He Who Takes Over as Strongest...
His Name is Gohan."
Am I really capable of defeating Cell?
"Next time"
"He Who Takes Over as Strongest...
His Name is Gohan"