Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Didn't I say so? If I use
only half of my max power,
I could turn you into space dust, as I recall.
Aren't you forgetting
about the Kaio-ken technique?
With Goku as he is now,
he should be able to withstand as
much as ten times his regular power!
Regrettably, what he's using right
now is that very times ten Kaio-ken...
Not even Goku's ten-fold
Kaio-ken is of any use against Freeza.
Freeza has terrifying,
transcendently evil power!
"Showdown!! The Embodiment of Flame
in a 20-Times Kaio-ken Kamehame-Ha."
That's our Freeza-sama!
He's just playing with Goku! Such composure!
W-Who the hell are you?!
W-Who, me?
He's a frog! A frog, I tell you!
Chaan-ge!!
T-Then, this frog is...
B-Bulma-san?
Haven't I been saying so all this time?!
I'll send you all to hell!
I'll never get anywhere like this.
Your body is mine!
Chan-ge!
What?!
Piccolo, watch out!
I... I can't... move...!
Piccolo-san!
P-Piccolo-san...
W-What happened?
My hands...
My feet...
My body...
Ow! My cheek...!
Yeah! Yeah, yeah!
I'm back in my original body!
Ow, ow! T-Thank goodness,
Bulma-san, but it's very dangerous here!
If you don't take cover soon–
Enough already!
Bulma-san!
Get over here and save me!
This is getting ridiculous.
You can entertain me a
little bit more, if you like.
What a technique!
As I told you,
If I had to, I could destroy this whole planet.
I am the one who destroyed Planet Vegeta.
I-I've had it.
I can't win.
W-What did he do?
H-He's cut the whole planet!
N-Never mind that, I have to
wonder if Goku is planning something.
It looks like he's starting
to take a one-sided beating!
He's got no plan!
The fact is, Freeza's power is impossibly
greater than Goku or us could have thought!
You don't have to worry.
I wouldn't kill you instantly
with something like that.
D-Dammit...
Otherwise, I wouldn't be
able to placate my anger.
So, how about Goku?
Even using his upper
limit of a times ten Kaio-ken,
is Son being defeated, Kaio-sama?
On top of that, Freeza seems to
only be using half of his power!
T-That can't be!
This is why I told him
that no matter what happens,
he must not set his hand to Freeza.
He has lost!
So, then...
What can I do to cause you the most pain?
Should I break your arm? Rip off your ears?
Or perhaps I'll slit your throat.
T-The only thing I can do is pull up
to a times twenty Kaio-ken somehow!
My body may not be
able to handle it, though.
But if, like he says, he really is only
using fifty percent of his power now,
there ain't nothing else I can do...
It's much too late for
you to start agonizing.
You're the one who started this, after all.
You will become my toy,
until I grow tired of you!
What's the matter?
If you don't resist a little for me,
I will find you unresponsive and get bored!
Hey, hey, the fun is just beginning!
It's much too soon for
you to be going to bed!
It's no use!
How does it feel to become a fish?
Kuririn!
Goku-sa!
G-Goku!
Goku!
Chichi! Where are you?!
Old Man Turtle Hermit! Oolong!
O-Old Timer!
Chichi!
Goku-sa! Goku-sa!
Father!
Gohan!
W-What?!
Father!
G-Goku!
For the future of Gohan,
Chichi, Earth, and Planet Namek...
I absolutely must not lose!!
Fifty percent power, he says...
Whether those words are a
bluff, or whether they ain't,
all I can do is stake everything
on a times twenty Kaio-ken!
Ka... me...
ha... me...
Ha!!
Damn it to hell...!
Now that even his twenty-fold
Kaio-ken was of no use,
is there any chance of victory left for Goku?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
This Genki Dama is the
last thing I wanted to use.
There'll probably be too much force to it!
It will be hard not to squash the planet itself!
You're still thinking of trying
some kind of nonsense, are you?
What can you hope to do,
as worn out as you are?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"A Super-Huge Genki Dama–
I'm Playing My Last Card!!"
Don't tell me that huge thing is a Genki Dama!
"Next time"
"A Super-Huge Genki Dama–
I'm Playing My Last Card!!"