Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
You guys are finished now!
I'm going to blow myself up momentarily.
I may die, but all the rest of you will die, too!
The whole Earth will be caught in the blast!
What?!
W-What? He's going to blow himself up?!
Goodbye, Gohan.
Father!
Goku sacrificed his own
life in order to save the Earth.
Father!!
W-What?!
W-What's this...?
Th-Th-That ki...!
I-It couldn't be...!
I-It can't be...!
Cell was not dead!
"A Nightmare in Broad Daylight!!
The Terror Becomes Even More Perfect."
O-Only Cell has returned!
What could have happened to the
young man who disappeared with him?
How terrible, how dreadful,
how far beyond the limits of our
imaginations these Cell Games are!
I'm talking again...
How? How come?!
Cell's still alive?!
What do you mean, Kaio-sama?!
He blew himself up for sure earlier!
I don't know how it can be, but
nevertheless, I'm certain that he's alive.
H-He couldn't be!
Are you saying that I did that for nothing?
That's what I'm saying.
And yet, you still got my planet destroyed!
Damn...
Kami-sama, something wrong?
Cell–Cell came back to life!
W-What?
What's more, he's far
more powered-up than before.
B-But, with Son Gohan there...
This time, even Gohan-san
might not be able to do anything.
You appear surprised.
Very well, I'll explain it to you.
This turned out to be a
fortunate miscalculation, even for me.
Inside my head, there is a small lump.
That is what serves as my nucleus.
As long as that is not destroyed,
this body can continue to regenerate itself.
Sorry about this, Kaio-sama!
This was the only place!
How can you say that...?!
When I blew up, as luck would have it,
my nucleus survived, uninjured.
To be honest, I did not figure on regenerating.
I just got lucky!
What was even more joyful to
me was that my body regenerated
in its perfect form, even without No. 18.
And it wasn't my ordinary
perfect form, like Son Gohan,
it had become greatly powered-up!
This is probably because,
as I was rescued from the brink of death,
my Saiyan cells allowed
my power to greatly increase.
Moreover, I was able to study
Son Goku's Instantaneous Movement.
In short, I was able to return here,
even more perfect than before.
It seems that Son Goku,
rather than defeating me,
has instead given me several presents.
G-Gohan!
What's so funny?
I'm happy.
Happy?!
Yeah. I'm happy that
I can now avenge my father,
who died because of my conceit.
I wanted so much to kill you with my own hands.
That's what I was thinking.
We'll see about that.
I doubt it's going to go
too well for you this time.
Trunks!
T-Trunks...!
Bye-bye, everyone.
Father!
K-Kakarrot...!
It seems that Son Goku,
rather than defeating me,
has instead given me several presents.
Happy?!
I'm happy that I can avenge my father.
G-Gohan...!
I wanted so much to
kill you with my own hands.
N-No...!
He–Cell is not going to be defeated by
that lower-class warrior Kakarrot, nor his son!
It's going...
It's going to be by me!
Dammit!
W-What exactly could be happening here?!
V-Vegeta!
V-Vegeta...
Cell! I, the Prince of
Planet Vegeta, will defeat you!
Prince of Planet Vegeta, huh?
Cell has won.
What the hell happened just now?
Away with you, Vegeta!
Well, well... This is an unexpected harvest.
G-Gohan!
Gohan!
Vegeta, you stupid bastard!
Trunks could have been brought
back to life with the Dragon Balls!
Ho... Apparently, you haven't
lost any of your heart, at least, huh?
But I'm not playing around any longer.
I'm going to put an end to this right away.
C-Cell's power has gone
up more than I thought...!
A-A senzu! Aren't there any more senzu?!
We've used them all up...!
Th-This time, we're finished for sure!
Now that Gohan, who we were
depending on, has wound up like that...
I... will no longer tolerate you!
Let you and the whole Earth cease to exist!
The reborn Cell is about to wipe
out the Earth and everything on it!
Isn't there anything the
injured Gohan can do now?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Gohan, don't you dare give up!
Believe in your own power!
Right now, you are the
strongest one in the universe!
Damn, Gohan's ki is weaker than Cell's.
The way things are going,
he's going to be done in.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"From Goku to Gohan...
The Spirit of the Father is Handed Down."
Here goes, Cell! I'll show you
the power my father and I create!
"Next time"
"From Goku to Gohan...
The Spirit of the Father is Handed Down"