Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
On his way to Planet Namek, Son Goku
had fallen into some unexpected trouble.
But the results of his gravity
training had already emerged,
and he was able to safely escape the danger.
At that same time, on Planet Namek,
Vegeta, who had just defeated Dodoria,
had done an end run around Freeza, setting
out to search for the Dragon Balls himself.
"Courage Times One Hundred!
The Warriors Gathered Under Kaio."
Oh, is that so? So that's what happened, huh?
Mm-hmm. I really thought we were done for.
You should eat something. It may not
be that good, but feel free to help yourself.
What was that?
You're complaining about the food
that I made, after all you've eaten?!
Eh?!
N-No, I-I would never–!
I meant that it may not be
that good, but it's still delicious.
I don't blame him. Just about everyone
from his village has been killed, right?
Oh, right. This isn't the
right time for a meal, huh?
We don't eat things like this.
We just need to drink water.
No way! There were fields at your village
where you were raising
vegetables or something, weren't there?
Those were Ajissa seedlings.
Ajissa seedlings?
Yes. Long ago, before the
abnormal weather occurred,
Namek was said to be a
beautiful world, rich with Ajissa trees.
However...
The Ajissa forests and
most of the Namekians died out.
So now, we're trying to make Namek
beautiful again by growing more Ajissa trees.
And after we'd finally
raised some Ajissa seedlings...
We got him!
Why, you–!
Say, what is your name?
Dende. Uh, who exactly are you people?
Kuririn-san, is that–?
What's gotten into you all of
a sudden? Is someone else coming?
N-No, it's not that.
The ki are dropping, one after another.
T-The Namekians are being killed once again.
T-The one killing them is
someone we know very well! It's Vegeta!
He's attacking a different village!
W-What a horrible bunch these guys are!
V-Vegeta has acquired the
technique for sensing ki, all right.
This is going to be trouble.
Now we'll have to be wary about
moving around until Goku gets here.
I'm not sure whether Vegeta and that
Freeza bastard are on the same side or not,
but if either one of them gains
eternal life with the Dragon Balls,
it will be the end of the world.
If we are able to find and
hide even one of the Dragon Balls,
they won't be able to get all seven together.
W-We can't! If we were to do that,
then they would keep searching
until they had killed all of the Namekians!
O-Oh, no...
It's appalling, no matter
which way it turns out.
A-And even once Goku gets here,
there's no guarantee that he can beat them.
Damn!
If only I had finished Vegeta off back then!
Please tell me about yourselves.
W-Where have you come from?
How do you know about the Dragon Balls?
P-Please save everyone else on the planet!
W-Why, you–! How could you do this?!
No matter what happens, you have no intention
of handing over the Dragon Ball, do you?
I-I'm not about to hand
it over to the likes of you!
You are one interminably stubborn old geezer.
Well, fine, suit yourself.
I'll look for it myself.
Wait!
You are getting on my nerves.
Here I thought it was going to be hidden,
but there it is, on regal display.
Now then, for this thing...
If I submerge the Dragon Ball here,
no one will be able to find it.
I'm the only one who knows about it.
Freeza and his men have
five of the Dragon Balls.
I guess I'll search for the last one.
Dodoria is taking far too much time, isn't he?
Could he still be chasing
after those odd pipsqueaks?
Never mind him. If that fool cannot
catch those kids, then let him be.
More importantly, go and search
for the remaining two Dragon Balls.
Yes, sir, understood.
If we search the remaining villages,
they are sure to have the Dragon Balls.
With the two of us searching, we
should be able to find a village, at least.
Well, I will take these five Dragon Balls
and wait for you at the spaceship.
I am counting on you.
With just two more of them, I will be
able to have my wish granted, after all.
Yes, sir.
You search over there. If you find
a village, do nothing, and come inform me.
If there are any strong Namekians there,
they would probably be too much for you.
Yes, sir.
For now, we will meet back
at the spaceship in three hours.
Yes, sir!
It is possible that Vegeta may have
already found the remaining pair.
And if he has, he ought to be
coming for our Dragon Balls.
As such, he may be saving me
the trouble of searching for them.
When Vegeta comes to get ours,
I will kill him, and take his two from him.
Then I will have all seven of them.
Is that how I am to be
endowed with eternal life?
Now then, to wait leisurely at the spaceship.
Right, this Kami-sama person was a
Namekian who had made his way to Earth.
We want to use the Dragon Balls
here to bring our dead friends back to life.
If things go right when our wish is granted,
the Dragon Balls on
Earth will be revived as well.
S-So that's why you're here, is it?
I've finally unraveled the mystery about you.
I'm begging you, please come with me!
I will show you where the Grand Elder is!
Grand Elder?
Who is this Grand Elder?
The one who gave birth
to all of us here on Namek.
The only one who survived
the abnormal weather long ago,
and once again brought life to Namek.
I am Grand Elder's 108th child.
The only one? How do you guys have children?
How, you ask? We spawn
eggs out though our mouths.
O-Oh, yeah? T-That's unusual, huh?
Then, this Grand Elder person is a woman, right?
Woman? What's a woman?
W-What's a woman? There are two
kinds of Namekians, right? Male and female.
Let's see... f-for example,
you have a father and a mother...
Huh? Two kinds? W-Well, um...
Did you hear that? They don't have
male and female. What a dull planet, huh?
Thank goodness I'm not a Namekian.
N-Never mind that, tell me why
we're going to this Grand Elder.
T-The ones who attacked our
village already had four Dragon Balls.
A-And you just said
there were a lot of people
being killed in that direction, right?
Y-Yeah, probably by someone named Vegeta.
T-There isn't a single ki left anymore.
They were probably all wiped out.
If that's the case, then there are
hardly any Namekians left on this world.
I see. Assuming that Vegeta found the
Dragon Ball from the village he attacked,
then there's only one left.
By any chance, does the Grand
Elder have that last Dragon Ball?
Y-Yes.
Oh, no!
Those Freeza guys may have lost their Scouters,
but Vegeta has gained the ability to sense ki.
If he searches for ki, he'll arrive at
the Grand Elder's place before long,
and he'll take the seventh Dragon Ball from him!
T-Then we have to hurry and
go tell the Grand Elder about this!
Please! Please!
Whether it's Freeza or Vegeta,
if either one of them is given
eternal life, it will be terrible!
A-All right, let's hurry. Show me the way.
Right.
I'll go with Dende to meet the Grand Elder.
Gohan and Bulma-san, you wait here for us.
It won't do any good
for all of us to go, right?
U-Understood. Be careful.
Remember, you be careful, too!
Right!
Vegeta seems to be even
stronger than he was before,
and I sensed an even more
incredible ki from that Freeza guy.
I don't know what kind
of training Goku is doing,
but this time, even he
might not be up to the task.
In any case, we'll get the one
Dragon Ball the Grand Elder has,
and then just hide for five
and a half days until Goku arrives.
After that, all we can do is wait
for Goku to perform a miracle.
Ah, if I'm starting to hope
for miracles, then we've had it.
Geez, I've never had a
single woman in my life, either.
All right... terrific... I'm pretty
used to this twenty-times gravity now...
Okay, maybe I should try thirty-times now.
Goku! Can you hear me? Goku! Huh?
Oh! That voice! Is that you, Kaio-sama?!
Oh, indeed it is Kaio.
By any chance, is that outer space
you're in now? What are you doing in space?
Oh, I get it. Planet Namek, right?
It would be nice if you could
find their Dragon Balls, huh?
What's with you, Kaio-sama?!
Don't you know anything?
There's something terrible
happening on Planet Namek.
Something terrible?
Well, I'll ask about that later.
As it happens, I've had
some visitors come by here.
Visitors? What about them?
It's amazing.
These visitors cleared the Serpentine Road
and arrived in far less time than you did.
What's more, there are four of them.
Huh?
Four of them?
That's right. You know these four quite well.
Y-You don't mean–?
They all want even tougher
training than what you went through.
T-That's awesome!
You mean that each of them has arrived
there together at your place, Kaio-sama?
Can I talk to Goku?
Place your hand on my shoulder and speak.
Yo, do you hear me, Goku?
Yamucha!
We met the dead Kami-sama
here on the Other Side,
and he told us about this place.
Hey, we hear that you're
going off to Piccolo's homeworld
in search of the Dragon Balls there for us.
In order to bring us back to life.
He said there were four of you,
right? Yamucha and Tenshinhan...
By any chance, is Piccolo there, too?
Yeah, Piccolo is here.
Hmph. My pride won't allow for
only you getting stronger, after all.
Is the last one Kami-sama?
No, it's not.
Kami-sama stayed in the Next World.
It's Chaozu, if you can believe that.
Chaozu?! Chaozu got blown
to pieces. Is he still okay?
Yeah, Kami-sama apparently
regenerated his body, especially for him.
Wow, that's amazing! Good for you, Chaozu!
Awesome!
That's awesome! With everyone alongside,
my courage is a hundred times greater!
What's this? Familiar faces
gathered together under Kaio-sama.
However, Goku is still unaware of the
atrocities taking place on Planet Namek.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Is Freeza really all that incredible?
I can't wait to meet him.
No! This time around, you are no match for him.
You must not make him angry.
This is an order from Kaio.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Listen to Me, Goku! Hands Off Freeza."
I wonder if Piccolo-san can
make a pun in front of Kaio-sama.
"Next time"
"Listen to Me, Goku!
Hands Off Freeza"