The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
The Tenkaichi Tournament
had reached its closing act,
and the only ones who remained
were No. 18 and Mister Satan.
It was thought to be
an easy victory for No. 18,
but with her eye on the prize money,
No. 18 negotiated a deal with Mister
Satan, and sold her victory to him.
I will admit that you have considerable skill.
However, your opponent is too much for you!
You've fought well, but
after all, I am the champion!
Take this! Satan Miracle Special
Ultra Super Megaton Punch!!
The curtain has dropped
on the Tenkaichi Tournament
with a repeat victory for Mister Satan.
Elsewhere, as Goku and the
others try to prevent Madoshi Babidi
from fulfilling his scheme,
Dabura, King of the Demon Realm
of Darkness, stands in their way.
Dabura has put up a good fight, and
Gohan at length opened up his full power.
"A Wicked Heart Discovered!!
Dabura's Great Idea."
So, Gohan, show us your power!
What?!
Aah, Dabura!
You get serious! At this degree,
we can't even call it a fight!
I-Incredible!
Very well...
The real me is over here!
Die!!
Ah, damn!
That's one down...
Oh, ow, ow! I dropped my guard!
He's lying in wait for me, huh?
There you are!
Gohan!
Even powered up, that's
still the best you've got, is it?
Just what you'd expect from the
King of the Demon Realm of Darkness.
He really is on a different
level from Puipui or Yakon.
Dammit! I got careless there,
but it won't happen this time!
No, no, Gohan! You can't keep
up that monotonous style of attack!
He'll read your next move!
It's no use. He's completely
forgotten his intuition for fighting.
We're not done yet!
Why, that rotten... Here I come!
Look out! You'll be turned to stone!
That was close, that was close!
Satan! Satan! Satan!
"Martial"
Goten!
Trunks!
Goten! Goten!
Ah, Mommy!
Have you been a good girl?
Yeah!
No. 18, what on Earth happened?
How could you lose to a guy like that?
Are you malfunctioning somewhere?
W-What's with that attitude?!
And here someone's going out
of their way to worry about her!
Hey, hey!
What is it, Goten?
What's a Majin?
Ah, come on!
You don't even know that, yet you're
in such a fuss over wanting to see one?
Yeah! So, you know then, Trunks-kun?
Well, I... of course! A Majin is...
Yeah? Yeah?
A Majin is...
It's... see...
What's a Majin?
Ah, well, that is... anyhow...
It's this utterly incredible guy!
You'll be so surprised when you see him, Goten!
Wow! I'm sure looking forward to that!
Probably...
Yeah, let's hurry, Goten!
Y-Yeah!
Dabura's a lot stronger
than we thought, ain't he?
Hmph! Even so, he's not an
opponent that can't be beaten!
He's pathetic! He was
stronger when he was just a kid!
What are we going to do with him?
Gohan really has been
skipping out on his training, huh?!
This is getting on my nerves.
Where are you looking?
–You're mine!
–What?!
Has he really done it this time?
Dammit, what are you doing, Dabura?
You've got to do more
and more, greater damage!
O-Once Majin Boo returns,
those guys won't matter!
Gohan...!
What?!
Dammit, this is irritating!
All right, I'm going to put an end to this!
No you don't, Vegeta! Let him do this!
It's not exactly like he's
completely losing there!
All this playing around isn't important!
I want to put and end to this so
I can hurry and settle my score with you!
That's the whole reason
I went to all the trouble
of going to that ridiculous tournament!
If it doesn't look like he's
going to make any more progress,
I'll end this in an instant!
Babidi-sama, please return us
to the spaceship immediately!
I have made quite a grand discovery!
Grand discovery?
It will mean the revival of Majin Boo...
W-What?! Is this true, Dabura?
Quite possibly.
Just bring you back, right?
Yes.
Papparapa!
W-What?!
Huh? We're back!
W-What's this?
H-Hey! Are you running away from me?
Run away? Indeed not. I do not
need to bother myself with fighting.
I've found just the right warrior for all of you.
Wait!
Just the right warrior? What does he mean?
What is the meaning of this, Dabura?
There really is a great discovery, isn't there?
Yes.
I trust you didn't just get frightened
by those humans and come
running back here, right?
Dabura, King of the Demon
Realm, is afraid of nothing.
Well then, that's fine. So then,
hurry and tell me this great discovery!
There is one among them that has a
very strong wickedness within his heart.
With that degree of evil in his heart,
we can sufficiently draw him over to our side.
I-I get it! We don't even have to fight them,
we can turn them on each
other and just take in their energy!
If we do that...
Majin Boo will be revived!
Bravo! Bravo, Dabura!
Dabura has discovered
the evil in Vegeta's heart.
A critical clash between Saiyans is approaching!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Damn that Babidi!
He's planning to make Vegeta fight us
at the Tenkaichi Tournament!
Just what has come over you, Vegeta?!
Blasting the stadium, with everyone in it–
this is some kind of mistake, right?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Vegeta, Prince of Destruction, Revived!!
Intrusion at the Tournament."
No, Vegeta-san! Don't let
those guys control you!
"Next time"
"Vegeta, Prince of Destruction, Revived!!
Intrusion at the Tournament"