The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Majin Boo absorbed Goten,
Trunks, Piccolo, and Gohan,
obtaining intellect and power.
In order to save the Earth from Majin
Boo, Goku and Vegeta merged together,
becoming the ultra-warrior Vegetto.
You and the Earth together can cease to exist!
The battle between Majin Boo and
Vegetto reached an extreme in intensity!
Offensive and defensive sides
continued to switch back and forth,
and just as their two powers
seemed evenly matched,
from within an aura of
light appeared Super Vegetto!
This is Super Vegetto!!
"A Fissure Between Dimensions!!
Has Boo Snapped!?"
Satan-san! Satan-san!
It's Satan-san's shoe...
D-Don't tell me he fell from here...!
Satan-san!
Satan-san! Satan-san!
S-Satan-san?
I thought I was going to die!
Thank goodness, Satan-san! You're all right!
It'll take more than this to make me,
the strongest martial artist in the world,
Mister Satan, kick the bucket!
By the way, what happened to Majin Boo?
W-What?!
Super Vegetto, you say?
You don't seem to understand yet, huh?
I have absorbed three Saiyans–
the two half-pints, as well as Gohan!
Now that you have combined
together and become a Super Saiyan,
what is that supposed to do for you?!
You're the one who doesn't understand.
Merging via the Potara
is not that simple a matter.
Hmph, of course, you probably wouldn't
understand if I explain it to you verbally.
I'll show you.
You're right! If you can't
understand something you're told,
all that's left is to make you
understand by force! You miserable fool!
The likes of you...!
What about "the likes of me"?
Your nose is bleeding.
It's disgraceful. Hurry and wipe it off.
The more you make me angry, the
more you're going to suffer and die!
Have you understood that?
Goku-san! Vegeta-san!
Hmph! Didn't feel that at all. I wish
you'd take this a little more seriously.
Inflicting damage is done like this...
Y-You're not...!
Big Bang...
...Attack!!
He did it!
Take that!
Satan-san...!
How was that? I bet you felt that!
That didn't hurt...
That did not hurt!
How about this? Can you see me, I wonder?
Nah, I can't see you. However...
W-What?
The important thing to grasp
is strength and movement of ki.
You follow me with your eyes, which is
why you can't keep up with my motions.
Y-You think you're so great!
He's so strong! To think
that Majin Boo is so helpless!
I never thought the Potara
union could be so incredible!
What are you so carried away for, you moron?
It's only because those
two did it that it's gone so far.
You've got two of the three greatest experts,
from This World and the Next World
combined, merged together, after all.
Moreover, you've got
two rivals teamed together.
That's obviously going to be what's strongest!
Under the circumstances, something
like that doesn't really matter, does it?
In any case, now the Earth–no,
the whole universe, will be saved!
How unsightly.
Awesome! This is really awesome!
Majin Boo there is no match for him at all!
Thinking ahead just in case, I requested
Yama-sama to leave you with your bodies,
but it seems you won't get your turns.
Get our turns nothing,
if our opponent is someone that
Goku and Vegeta couldn't handle,
there's no way we could win, is there?
That is true...
Hold on... if we don't get a turn... *ulp*!
Are we going to lose our bodies
and be turned into ordinary spirits?
You don't have to worry.
As with Goku, you are warriors who
saved Earth from crises countless times.
I will ask the Grand Kaio-sama to
allow you to train here like Goku does.
Thank you very much, Kaio-sama!
Yamucha, good news... huh?
Yamucha? Yamucha?!
W-What are you doing?
This place is incredible!
There are strong guys like
I've never seen before all over!
My blood, which has been inactive,
is boiling hot for the first time in years!
And here, when he was alive, he had given
it up completely, and hadn't even trained...
What's the matter? You've
gotten awfully quiet, haven't you?
You know something, this isn't any fun at all.
I wish you would take this more seriously.
Or perhaps you have been
serious, and this is how it turned out.
In that case, it was rude of me to say
that, and I was out of line. I apologize.
Why, you...!
Y-You laughed at me!
A mere man such as you...!
What's this?
How about that? I've entered
inside your own body!
No matter how powered-up you may become,
I doubt there's anything
you can do about this!
Prepare yourself! I'm going to
destroy your body from the inside!
You're the one who
should be preparing yourself.
What?!
W-Why?! Why can't I move like I want to?
It's only natural. I've bottled up
your movements with my ki, after all.
As long as you're inside my body,
you cannot move freely.
What are you going to do?
You want to continue?
You are one distasteful creep!
And yet, with all those
many guys you've merged with,
if that's all you've got, I'm fairly disappointed.
Disappointed, you say?
In me? In me, the strongest in the universe?!
That's enough of you making a fool out of me!
Make a fool out of me, will you?
Me...?! Me...?!
Incredible power! You can
manage it if you just try, can't you?
You'll pay for that!
You can't! You mustn't
anger Majin Boo any further!
What do you mean?
There was a time when Majin Boo was
sealed up in the Room of Spirit and Time.
I can't stand this!!
Mad with anger, Majin Boo used his power
to break through the wall between
dimensions, and then came out.
Look at this, if you would.
Having forgotten himself in anger, the
extreme power radiating from Majin Boo
is causing the space surrounding him to warp!
At this rate, the walls between
dimensions will break down,
and other dimensions will rush through!
That would be awful.
Make a fool out of me, will you?
Make a fool out of me, will you?!
This is bad! He's gotten completely fired up!
If I don't stop him, this universe will
be crushed by alternate dimensions!
What the hell happened to me...?
That was close, that was close!
You sure do have awesome power, huh?
In which case, use that power to come hit me!
You were going to defeat
me as proof to all, right?
That you are the strongest in the universe?
Why the hell is he taking so long?!
Hurry up and defeat Majin Boo!
Ultra powers clash
between Majin Boo and Vegetto.
Will the one who decides
this fierce battle be Vegetto?
Or will it be Majin Boo?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Hey, now, what's the matter, Majin Boo?
I could beat you with just my feet.
You fool!
Nothing good can come of you
holding your power back, Vegetto!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Ace Up Boo's Sleeve!!
'You Become a Hard Candy'!"
Father, you can't let Boo
sucker punch you like that!
"Next time"
"The Ace Up Boo's Sleeve!!
'You Become a Hard Candy'!"