Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
P-Please take me, too, by all means!
I want to go, no matter what.
I want to be the one who
brings Piccolo-san back to life myself.
Piccolo's got nothin' to do with anythin'!
You are a little child,
and you should act like a child!
Shut up!
G-Gohan-chan... you've
turned into a delinquent!
M-Mother... right now... right now
really isn't the time to be talking about that.
We all fought desperately to save the Earth,
and we have to bring
those who died back to life,
to fight against the Saiyan once again!
Seeking a new set of Dragon Balls,
the trio of Bulma, Kuririn, and Son Gohan
had departed for Planet Namek,
the native land of Kami-sama and Piccolo.
"Friends or Foes? Children of
the Mysterious Giant Spaceship."
I am bored to death.
I've had it. This is still
only the seventh day, too.
We've still got twenty-some days to go.
I should have installed hibernation devices.
Are you guys image training again?
Nice for you to be able to pass the time.
Wow, you're not bad! You sure are strong.
You've inherited Goku's blood, and
you've been trained by Piccolo, after all.
Still, I was surprised by how
many techniques you have, Kuririn.
Listen...
It's fine for you to train inside your heads,
but the room is starting to get
pretty messy, so would you tidy it up for us?
There's a lady present.
B-But Bulma-san, you're the
one who made it messy over there.
We've cleaned up our own messes.
I'm busy here! I've got
a lot of things to think about.
You guys are just passengers,
so that's fine for you.
I thought you just got
done saying that you were bored.
You hush! I wish you would show a little
more consideration toward a delicate lady.
So busy, so busy...
As a lady, I sure wish she
wouldn't stroll around in her underwear.
Oh, not again.
Four more.
Son-san, you mustn't do that!
Nurse, I'm all better now.
Goku is immortal, you see.
Did I just do something? Must be my age,
but lately, I don't even know what I'm doing.
Oh, for heaven's sake...
These sponge cakes are delicious.
Of all the...
Doctor!
How many times must I say
it before it gets through to you?
If you keep doing that,
you'll never get to go home.
As you can see, I'm all–
It should hurt. You were very
severely injured, after all. Get back to bed.
S-Sorry.
You there, Grandpa Glad-hands, give him a hand.
"G-Grandpa Glad-hands"?
My word, "Grandpa Glad-hands," huh? My, my...
"Grandpa Glad-hands"!
At your service.
Where is his wife, who is usually with him?
Oh, she probably went to the
roof to look up at the sky again.
Gohan-chan, are you doin' all right?
I told you over and over
to send me a letter every day,
but you haven't sent a single one...
Come back to me soon, safe and sound.
Say...
By the way, I've been
wondering about this for a long time,
but about that Saiyan, Vegeta, who
ran away–where did he run away to?
What do you mean, where?
Well, the Saiyans' planet
was lost a long time ago, right?
Oh, right. He had taken an awful lot of damage,
so I think it would have to
be a civilized planet somewhere.
Could there be such a place?
Earlier, Son-kun's brother
mentioned something, remember?
He said that, "We exterminate those
who live on planets with good environments,
and then sell them to aliens."
Do you think that maybe Vegeta went to
one of those aliens' planets to get treated?
If he did, then when he comes back to
Earth would depend on where that planet was.
If it was far away, then
it would buy us some time.
You know something, that's one
terrible fellow who has set his sights on Earth.
T-To think that it would come to this...
–What was that just now?
–Something flashed, huh?
It wouldn't be Planet Namek, right?
It's too early for that,
to say the least, isn't it?
Huh? Something is approaching.
But I don't see anything.
B-Bulma-san! Flying saucers!
B-Bulma-san!
Leave them to me!
Counterattack!
You got them! You got them!
It's too soon to celebrate. Look!
It's a spaceship.
It's coming closer and closer!
I can see that. It's coming straight toward us.
Is that...?!
We're going to hit!
Do something!
H-How could they turn in the same direction?!
W-We're done for!
Where could we be? It looks
like the inside of a spaceship,
but even so, there isn't a soul around.
I have no idea what's going on here.
There may be some weird aliens hiding from us.
You're right. They might suddenly–
...pop out, like this.
Gohan! Don't scare us like that!
I-It looks like it's safe to go
outside. Let's go have a look.
Here goes!
Maybe I should have stayed
on Earth after all, like Yajirobe.
Oh, no!
I forgot to put on some pants first.
Huh? But you are wearing them, aren't you?
These are my shorts. Ah, oh well.
Let's hope you don't embarrass mankind.
Kuririn-san...
All right, let's go.
Gohan! Don't push!
Gohan, watch yourself! It looks
like there are some booby traps in here.
Remember, you two! Men are to
protect ladies at all times! Don't forget that!
There should be a doorway
into the main room somewhere–
A wall like this will be easy to take care of.
Kame...
hame...
K-Kuririn!
Kame...
...hame-Ha!
Must be nice for you guys,
being able to perform Bukujutsu.
I get the feeling that they want to
eliminate any intruders, no matter what.
Is this a Saiyan spaceship?
Beats me.
Suppose Vegeta were to
suddenly appear from over there...
C-Cut that out! Look,
I'm starting to get goosebumps!
I wonder if that man Vegeta is recovering
from his injuries somewhere right now.
I'd appreciate it if he'd just die.
K-Kakarrot... remember this... I will
definitely go back there to settle the score!
Say, I get the feeling
that we've been walking around
the same place in circles for a while now.
There wasn't anything
that looked like a door, huh?
There's one!
It looks like the real door is down here.
Yay!
Damn... They sure built
this thing to be convoluted!
All right, let's try going in here.
Kuririn, be careful.
I know.
Outer space!
I thought we were dead!
I-I'm getting hungry...
My tummy is grumbling, too.
Something smells good.
Y-You're right.
Wow, that looks delicious.
It might be a trap!
It sure is a spread!
Be careful when touching anything.
You won't catch me falling for that!
Bulma-san!
Help me!
Bulma-san, your reflexes are so slow!
It's you guys who are the unusual ones!
We're coming to help you out now!
Please move away from the cage!
What is this?! Who set this childish trap?!
Don't move!
Bulma-san!
Why, you!
Stay back! I'll be shot!
Kuririn-san, they're all children!
D-Don't shoot! We're not your enemy!
Is there an adult here that I could speak to?
Never mind about me! Give
these kids a good hard spanking!
B-But...
Don't dawdle around! Hurry up!
Okay then...
Kuririn! Don't offer any more futile resistance!
Just hurry and surrender, already!
B-Bulma-san...
K-Kuririn-san?
W-What should we do?
Ominously, these children
have suddenly appeared.
What exactly is the true nature
of this mysterious spaceship?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Huh? Gohan and the others have
been caught by a strange alien ship?
What in the world happened?
H-Hey, there's nothing
sinister about us! Listen to me!
Huh? Invaders? Freeza?
What are these guys talking about?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Honest to Goodness?
There Lies Namek, Planet of Hope."
There's no choice but to act now!
"Next time"
"Honest to Goodness?
There Lies Namek, Planet of Hope"