Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Barely a year remained until the time of
the raid on Earth by the pair of Saiyans.
Son Goku, having gone
over to the Other World,
was eagerly proceeding
down the Serpentine Road
in order to be trained by
Kaio-sama, the mightiest of gods.
Elsewhere, his son Gohan had been
left to himself on a wide plain by Piccolo.
Dirty brat! Give me trouble, will you?
However, this is the
last time I lend you a hand!
From here on, if you are unable to survive,
then that's all you're worth as a kid!
"A Great Transformation on a Moonlit Night!
The Secret of Gohan's Power."
Mother...
I can't do anythin' at all with Goku-sa!
I'm sure that right now, he's
keepin' Gohan up, no doubt about it!
And right now is the most
important time for him, too!
With everyone gathered at the Kame House,
there's not a single person who
can serve as a good example for Gohan!
Goku-sa has to know that it's not good
for him from an educational standpoint!
I can see from this how
Gohan's future is goin' to be.
I've really had it this time.
There's no way that I can tell
them that Goku has died now...
I guess that for me to return to the
Kame House would be best for now.
Goku-sa...
Eat some more. We've got
barbecued elephant this time...
No need to be shy. You can
start by gnawin' on its head...
Goku...
Nobody would have
been able to tell them, right?
Wah! It's too bright!
I can't get down! And I'm hungry!
If you're hungry, you can just climb
down from there and find something to eat.
What? You couldn't tell them?
I'm very sorry.
Don't tell me you didn't say anything!
No...
What's the use?
Geez, you're so spineless!
T-That's easy for you to say,
but if any normal person saw Chichi-san's face,
they'd be unable to tell her!
Oh? So you're saying
that I'm no normal person?!
T-That's not what I meant...
Well, I suppose it's no surprise.
But we can't just keep quiet like this.
If we wrote her a letter
explaining what happened,
perhaps she would understand.
R-Right! That will work!
By the way, Kuririn,
what about the Dragon Balls?
There were two of them
at Son-kun's house, right?
I forgot.
You're good for nothing!
I wonder what happened to Kuririn.
Chichi, don't get so worked-up,
I tell ya. Kuririn was just–
Pa, would you shut up?!
He told me he'd be sure
to be back by nighttime!
Goku ain't been to the
Kame House in a long time.
He must've just accidentally lost
track of time talkin' about the old days!
That may be fine for Goku-sa,
but Gohan has his cram school!
D-Don't be silly!
Gohan is four years old!
It won't hurt for him to
skip just one day of cram school.
You're too soft, Pa!
In these coming times, it's
those who can study that will win out!
Chichi! Chichi! I ain't fastened in!
I wonder if this is it...
Hey there, it's finally finished!
How nice of you guys to be
napping around at a time like this!
Now then, you there,
Grandpa Turtle, stand on up.
G-Grandpa Turtle?
I changed the display numbers
to make it easier to understand.
Let's see, 139...
139? I'm not as young as that!
This is the number that represents
your strength, Muten Roshi-sama.
The number that represents my strength?
Whoa, that's an incredible device.
It can even tell that?
B-Bulma-san, what would my number be?
Amazing! It says 206!
Muten Roshi-sama,
I really have surpassed you, huh?
H-Hey, are you sure it's not malfunctioning?
Malfunctioning?
That could not be.
Just 0.001!
It's not malfunctioning, all right!
Yahoo!
Is that right?
I don't mean to brag,
but when it comes to my skills–
Hey! Hey!
Who could it be, this early?
Hey, I say, hey! Hey!
Hey! Hey!
Who's out here calling to us so unusually?
It's me!
Y-You're that guy who was at
Karin-sama's place, as I recall–Armadillo!
That's Yajirobe, ya dumb bastard!
I'll just betcha ya got
my name wrong on purpose!
What're ya doin' buildin'
a house way out here?
Makes it a real hassle to find.
I came here at Karin's
askin' to give ya a message.
A message from Karin-sama?
"I know the whole situation," he says.
So you, along with that Yamucha guy,
and that Ten-whatever-guy
and Chaozu are to come immediately.
Everyone is to go to Karin-to Tower?
What for?
Kami-sama, see, is gonna give us trainin',
he says. I'm in there with ya too.
R-Really?!
Yeah. For my part,
I told 'em that I don't wanna
fight no whatever-their-face-is aliens,
but they says I gotta do it no
matter what. I've had it with 'em.
U-Understood! I'll go find
everyone and head there right away!
Catch ya later. I told ya
everythin', that's for sure.
Oh yeah, right. I forgot.
Goku says not to bring him
back to life 'fore those enemies come.
W-Why not?
He says he's gonna train in the Other World.
If ya wanna know details,
some old hag named Uranai Baba's
supposed to be along pretty soon. Ask her.
W-What? When?
T-Training in the Other World?
O-Of all things!
Huh?
He turned around again.
It's a different kind of plane.
Ahoy! Muten Roshi-sama!
It's Chichi and Gyumao!
Muten Roshi-sama, what do we do?!
I still haven't written their letter!
Muten Roshi-sama,
it's been a terribly long time!
Have you been well?
I-I suppose so.
–Y-Yikes...
My Goku-sa and Gohan
are supposed to be here!
Where are they?
Are they inside the house?
U-Um, the f-fact of the matter is...
He was taken away by Piccolo Daimao?!
W-What happened to Goku?!
He d-died...
Chichi! Steady!
Hey! Hey!
Let me down!
Hey!
They're gone...
Mother... Father... I can't get down...
What have we here?
You don't have to run away.
I won't do anything mean to you.
Hold on...
Ah, so that's how you get down. But still...
I want to get down!
Urinating, huh?
Why is this happening to me?
Why is it this bright out?
It's the moon!
Wow! It's completely round!
This is the first time
I've ever seen a full moo–
What is it?
What?!
I-Impossible!
What's going on?! He's got
extraordinary destructive power!
A-At this rate, Earth will be annihilated
before the Saiyans even get here!
How can this be?
Don't play stupid! It is
when the moon is at its fullest
that we Saiyans are
at our best, you know!
That's it!
It's the full moon!
Get lost!
T-To think that he could transform!
It must be his Saiyan blood.
I get the feeling that I've discovered
the secret to him and Son Goku's strength.
Looks like blowing the moon
away was the right thing to do.
I shudder to think of those Saiyan
guys turning into monsters like that.
He said something
or other about their tails,
but it appears that both the tails
and a full moon are required to transform.
Maybe I'll pull out his tail, too.
There's no need to worry
about him transforming like this,
but Saiyan tails seem
to be their weak spots.
All right, then.
I think I'll provide him clothes
and a sword at no charge...
I'll let you have the
same design as your father's.
Although the character
may be a little different.
I have to go do my own
training. I'm leaving now.
If you can survive here without
anything happening to you for six months,
I, Piccolo-sama, will personally
put you through some hellish training!
So much so that you'll come to
believe you'd be better off dying!
Brace yourself!
I'll also turn you into an
outstanding Demon Clansman!
The goal is to bring down the Saiyans.
Separated by time and space,
the harsh trials that both the sleeping
father and son must face, continue on and on.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Hello, I'm Gohan.
Father, I met a robot in
the middle of the desert.
Oh, yeah? What kind of robot?
A crabby one. But he really is nice.
Lucky you, Gohan. I know it
may be rough, but hang in there.
Right!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Sorry, Robot-san –
The Desert of Vanishing Tears."
Still, I miss Mother.
"Next time"
"Sorry, Robot-san –
The Desert of Vanishing Tears"