Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Fifty percent power, he says...
Whether those words are
a bluff, or whether they ain't,
all I can do is stake everything
on a times twenty Kaio-ken!
Ka... me...
ha... me...
HA!!
Goku has risked it all on a
twenty-fold Kaio-ken! And yet...
"A Super-Huge Genki Dama–
I'm Playing My Last Card!!"
It's no good.
Not even with Goku's times twenty Kaio-ken.
How can it be?
That didn't have much effect on him at all!
He wasn't bluffing this time either!
H-He really hasn't been using
any more than half of his power!
Ow, ow ow! Where am I?
Let's see...
I was a frog, and the frog
was me, and Kuririn was there...
Um, and Son-kun might have been there...
Enough! What's taking Son-kun so long?
Just take care of those aliens, already!
This planet really is the worst!
I've found you! This is your fault!
You won't get away with it!
Unbelievable! Goku's Kamehame-Ha
just now had incredible power!
Y-Yeah...
Why, then?
Why is it that Freeza has
barely taken any damage, then?
Father's ki has dropped considerably!
To think that a guy like
that could exist in this world!
It's utterly lost.
It's just as Kaio said.
No matter what, we should
have kept our hands off of Freeza.
T-That was a close one!
How?!
How does that lower life form
Saiyan have such awesome power?
This is the first time anyone has
done this much harm to my body!
You damn Saiyan!
That one...
...hurt.
It hurt!!
Father!
Monkey!
What happened to all that
energy you had a moment ago?
K-Kaio-sama, what is happening?
He's being beaten! Goku is
taking a one-sided beating!
H-He's what?!
H-He can't be!
F-Freeza is frighteningly strong.
That twenty-power Kaio-ken
was beyond Goku's limits after all.
What's wrong?
Have you finally used
up the last of your power?
How dull.
And here I thought I'd found an opponent
I could get somewhat serious over.
I really have lost a great deal of power.
Looks as though that times twenty
Kaio-ken had its price, all right.
Indeed, the Saiyans are a lower life form,
whose only talent is in fighting.
Every last one of you are fools.
Killing you off was the right decision.
It's... all over...
Kakarrot, you disappoint me!
Is that the extent of your power?
Where has your Saiyan pride gone?
I ain't no Saiyan!
Are you still saying that?!
You're a Saiyan unlike any other!
Vegeta, none of that matters now.
Team up with me...
You are a Saiyan!
You have the fighting Saiyan
people's blood flowing through you!
Do you not feel the anguish?
The man who destroyed Planet Vegeta,
the world where you and
I were both born, is this same Freeza!
Does it not wound your pride as a
Saiyan to be battered about by him?!
Saiyan... pride?
Your father, Burdock...
As well as my father, King Vegeta...
Kakarrot, you are the last remaining Saiyan!
He wants to kill every last Saiyan.
This is because he fears the birth
of what is said to be the
strongest warrior in the universe,
the legendary Super Saiyan!
If I could have, I would have
killed him by my own hand.
And then I get killed like a rag doll!
If you understand my anguish,
then be sure to kill him by your hand!
I... don't understand
what it is you're thinking.
I hate that sort of thing!
But I won't let you die easily.
I still want to have some fun, you see.
Vegeta, I was raised on Earth,
so I don't know
anything about being Saiyan.
But I can at least understand your grief!
You're talking nonsense again.
I must not lose.
I must not lose, not to the likes of Freeza!
Stop messing with me!
What?!
Don't fool...
...with me!
Why, you!
That was kind of close just now!
Looks like you've got
a bit of fight back in you.
But you Saiyans are still lower life forms.
I can read what you're
going to do next as you attack.
You will forever be unable to beat me!
F-Father!
Looks like this is it.
You'll be wanting to die pretty soon, right?
I'll put you out of your misery right now!
What's that? What's the matter?
It's Bubbles-kun!
It sounds like it came from the house!
What's the matter, Bubbles?
Gregory!
It looks like there's someone in there!
–Ah, yum! Yum!
–Look at all this food!
Yummy, yummy!
Who are you guys?!
ReaCoom!
Butta!
Jheese!
Ghurd!
Together we are...
The Ginyu Special Corps!
It's missing something, huh?
Maybe because the Commander isn't here.
We haven't done this in a while, either.
No, it has to be the gravity!
Okay, let's try it again!
Together we are...
The Ginyu Special Corps!
All right! That one went well!
We nailed it!
Okay, from now on, that's how we'll do it.
W-What's the deal... with these guys?
I can't take it any more! I'm going!
W-Wait!
How come? Father will be killed!
Goku is about to do something!
But what?
What can he hope to do with
such little remaining power?
What's this? What are you trying to do?
Ah! A Genki Dama!
What? A Genki Dama?
T-That's right. The Genki Dama,
a last-ditch technique
he learned from Kaio-sama.
The foliage and animals on this planet,
as well as ourselves,
and even microorganisms...
He takes a fraction of the
Genki, the basic energy of life,
from every living thing,
and apportions it to himself.
And then... and then he creates a
ball of energy, and attacks with it!
What?!
Damn, Kaio.
You kept that back from us, didn't you?
B-But will it work against Freeza?
There's a far smaller number of
living things on this planet than on Earth!
What choice is there?!
Goku has to realize that too!
Are you saying there's another option left?!
All we can do is gamble that this works!
I can't beat Freeza with just
the energy from this planet.
Those planets in the vicinity of Namek,
I only need a little from each of you...
Share some of your Genki with me!
T-This Genki Dama is the
last thing I wanted to use.
There'll probably be too much force to it!
It will be hard not to squash the planet itself!
But if I don't wipe out Freeza here and now,
the universe itself could be torn apart!
I don't know if this is
going to go right or not,
but it's all I can do now!
What's this you're doing?
You're still thinking of trying
some kind of nonsense, are you?
What can you possibly do,
as worn out as you are?
G-Goku...
Can you really beat
Freeza with a Genki Dama?
W-What's this I'm sensing?
I-It's...
G-Genki Dama...
I-It can't be! It's so huge!
A Genki Dama, loaded
with the hopes of the universe.
Will this turn out to be Goku's very last card?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
The time it takes to gather the ki required
is the Genki Dama's greatest weak spot!
Don't let him find out about
this for a little while more, please!
Gohan, Kuririn, give over
what remaining ki you have to me!
I have an idea!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Keep the Chance Alive!!
Piccolo's Suicide Support Strike."
Everyone who lives in the universe,
share your Genki energy with Father!
"Next time"
"Keep the Chance Alive!!
Piccolo's Suicide Support Strike"