Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Facing the persistent attack of Vegeta,
who had transformed into a Great Ape,
Goku was near death.
However, he was unexpectedly saved by Yajirobe.
Still, the damage to his whole body was severe,
and he faced his greatest pinch.
The only means left to them was the Genki Dama.
Goku entrusted the ki he had
gathered from everyone on Earth to Kuririn.
"Shoot, Kuririn!
The Genki Dama, Packed with Hope."
Stay with it, Kuririn...
Gohan can't control this ki...
T-T-There it is! Is this–?
A Genki Dama... You did it...
Hit him... with that...
I can't make another Genki Dama...
Make sure you hit him... please!
Y-You got it! I'll try. Let me take care of it.
He's so strong! He should be fairly
worn out from fighting with Father, too...
You're a tough little runt, but
you appear to be nearing your limit.
Gohan-chan, fight!
Fight, Gohan-chan!
W-W-What are you sayin', Chichi?!
Gohan's no match for that guy!
Gohan, get out of there!
Gohan-chan...
Chichi, are you–?
Pa!
Chichi...
They've vanished!
Gohan-chan?
Uranai Baba, hurry up and show me Gohan-chan!
A-All right! All right! I'll try! Let me go!
You've got a ridiculous
amount of strength for a woman!
Kamehame-Ha!
Is that your last-ditch effort?!
Darn it!
One more!
Damn! With my skill, I can't hit
him when he's moving around like that!
You don't hit him with the
Genki Dama by using your eyes.
You sense out his evil ki and shoot at that.
W-Who's there?!
I am Kaio, the one who
taught Son Goku the Genki Dama.
K-Kaio-sama?
Everything will be decided by your one shot.
Know that the ball of that Genki Dama
is filled with the hopes of the whole earth.
The ball is filled with the
hopes of the whole earth?
No matter how many of you scum gang
up on me, you're still no match for an elite.
It looks like once you
realized that, it was already too late.
S-Sense out his evil ki
and shoot at that... So that's it...
Kuririn, we're counting on you!
You'll only get one chance.
I'm done playing around.
You think you can get away?!
F-Feel it! Feel his evil ki!
K-Kuririn!
H-He's fixin' to do somethin'.
That's a humungous amount of ki.
If you're gonna get him, then get him, already!
Watch closely, Kakarrot!
This is the end of your foolish son!
I've got him!
What're ya doin', ya dimwit?!
Hurry up and hit him with that!
W-What?
T-That idiot!
Damn it all!
W-What is that?!
Hit him!
It missed!
W-What happened?!
How could my crystal ball crack?!
G-Gohan-chan!
It's hopeless now!
Bounce it back, Gohan!
Gohan, that thing is on our side!
As long as you don't have any evil in you,
you should be able to bounce it back!
You did it!
Yahoo!
We did it! We did it!
We did it, Goku!
Turtle, do you have any quick-drying glue?
Glue? Hmm, I seem to remember
having some around here somewhere...
What about Gohan-chan?!
Uranai Baba, can't you do
something about the crystal ball?!
Chichi! Stop that!
Pa! Gohan-chan is still alive! So's Goku-sa!
Y-You're right. But how are we
goin' to get to where Goku and them are?
All right, Chichi-san, I'll take you there.
Really? But how?
In my airship.
Bulma-san, thank you!
If I were to ever have a husband
and son who were in trouble,
I would rush to their side, no
matter what. That's human nature.
All right, I'm going too.
I'm going, too.
K-Karin-sama!
Father...
You guys finally got him, huh?
Time and again, I thought we were done for.
You two sure are a mess.
We're not as bad off as you.
T-The Saiyan!
It's okay. He's dead.
We can relax, now.
Damn it all, he was one horrible
fellow, but we could at least dig a grave.
You mean, a grave for you guys?
T-T-That's impossible!
He took that Genki Dama dead-on!
You put me through quite
an awful experience, huh?
E-Even I thought I was
going to die from that one.
I may have taken quite a bit of damage,
but I still have enough
power left to take care of you trash.
After I've killed you,
I'll wait until I've recovered my strength,
and then thoroughly destroy this planet!
Just keep on going straight.
Bulma! For Karin-sama to
deign to give you directions...
...is an extremely
magnanimous thing for him to do!
It is? He looks like an ordinary cat to me.
Y-You guys dare to make me,
Vegeta-sama, use up nearly all of my power?
Never mind that you ganged up on me,
against trash like you, it wounds my pride...
Would you die already?!
D-Dammit... Dammit!
G-Goku!
Damn it! Coming from me,
that destructive force was pathetic!
All three of them are still barely alive!
I-I've taken more damage than I thought...
I-I have to put them all away quickly...
and then recuperate...
T-This brat has...
...re-grown his tail!
H-His tail? That's right... In the past,
Goku's tail suddenly grew back, too...
If he were to transform,
that would be a problem!
Gohan's tail has once again grown out.
Could this be a symbol
that the fate of the Earth–
that the fate of mankind–
is to be saved from extinction?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Gohan, look at the ball of light in the sky!
It's our last gamble!
Transform into a Great Ape!
T-That's right! If Gohan becomes a Great Ape,
he'll revert to being a ferocious Saiyan!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Cause a Miracle!
Son Gohan, the Super Saiyan."
Stop picking on my father!
"Next time"
"Cause a Miracle!
Son Gohan, the Super Saiyan"