Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Using the Aquamist, Garlic Jr. conspires to
rule the whole world by taking Kami's place,
and turning all living things
on Earth into Demons.
Furthermore, Piccolo also becomes
demonic, and has come under his rule.
Piccolo, squash him!
Let him know the power of the Demon Clan!
Piccolo-san...
"Retrieve Everyone's Minds!!
The Ultra Holy Water Resting in the Temple."
Stop, Piccolo-san...
Gohan!
Piccolo-san...
That sure looks like fun.
That contemptible Piccolo!
Is he trying to kill us too?
How truly delightful!
The pupil who he trained
as his own apprentice...
...is now being destroyed by his own hand!
This is so characteristic
of a Demon Clansman!
Kami, you should watch this too.
The moment your own alter ego
crosses over to the glorious Demon side!
Dammit!
That's enough. Leave the rest up to us.
This is for Tard and Zald!
Brace yourself, kid!
That creep! Is he planning
to keep us out of this?
From the start, Piccolo and
Son Goku were bitter adversaries.
Perhaps when he entered the Demon Clan,
some dormant hatred
within him was released.
Pic... colo-san...
Now!
You asinine fool!
Did you really think you could
take this away from me just like that?!
Can you take it now?
Come on, what's the matter?
Hurry up and take it!
Now go to hell!
Kuri... rin... -san...
Loathsome trash! Say your prayers.
Stop!
Die!
Piccolo-san...
Look out, Gohan!
Stop!
Please stop, Piccolo-san!
Kuririn-san...
Here you go.
I did it! That's 22 wins in a row.
Hey, you! You can read minds,
can'tcha? Why don'tcha use that?
You hush! I was reading
her mind and still lost.
What?
This girl doesn't think anything.
That'd explain it.
I'll take this, then.
So this bell is required to
get to the Heavenly Realm.
Okay then, what do you bet next?
This!
It is another instrument necessary
to get to the Heavenly Realm.
This is the Nyoi Bo, and
can also be used as a weapon.
Karin-sama! Ain't this somehow wrong?
You be quiet! How can you be
satisfied with her shutting us out?
Kurin-chan's friends are so
much fun, every single one of them!
Well, let's play! Let's play,
let's play! I won't lose this time!
Take your time, take your time!
Remember what's riding on this!
Kuririn-san!
Please, come out of it, Kuririn-san!
Kuririn-san...
Very well. You shall
become our newest member.
Piccolo-san...
You'll have to thank Piccolo.
You get to see the bottle of
Ultra Holy Water before you die.
That's it?
Whoa, the way ahead is a restricted area!
Kuririn-san!
Kuririn-san, don't tell me you too...
Didn't you know, kid?
If bitten by a member of the Demon Clan,
once their saliva flows through your body,
it's the same as if you had
breathed in the Aquamist...
...you become a Demon Clansman!
Give it up, kid. You're all by yourself!
Garlic Jr.-sama, we request that
we be allowed to finish this one off!
Of course, we will save the final
blow for yourself, Garlic Jr.-sama.
Fine.
How can you...?
Wait. Didn't I say I would
strike the finishing blow?
So you did.
Kuririn!
You–how?!
You really expected me to do as you wanted?
Yeah, but you could have
pulled your punches a little.
I mean, poor Gohan!
He's trained hard enough that our
level of attack wouldn't have worn him out.
Why, you!
How dare you deceive me so!
Piccolo and the others at last manage
to save Kami-sama and Mister Popo.
However, the time when the Ultra Holy Water...
...will lose its effect is
steadily drawing nearer!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
It's no use. There ain't enough time.
The only way to sprinkle the
Ultra Holy Water before sunrise
is to pass through a fearsome
place called the Shinsenkai.
Kami, hurry and get going.
And don't go dying before
I've defeated that Garlic punk!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Can't Wait Until Morning!! Kami-sama
Determines a Suicidal Course of Action."
Okay, come and get it, Garlic Jr.!
"Next time"
"Can't Wait Until Morning!! Kami-sama
Determines a Suicidal Course of Action"