The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Madoshi Babidi and Majin Boo, in
order to call out Trunks, Goten and Piccolo,
head toward Metro West to destroy it.
Son-kun, it really will be
bad if Metro West is destroyed!
The Dragon Radar will also be lost!
All right, Trunks...
You return home as fast as you can,
get the Radar, and bring it back for us!
I will delay Majin Boo
and Babidi for a little while.
W-Will you be all right?
Uncle, can you delay them?
Won't you get beaten right away?
Well, if it's just for a little while,
I can manage something.
Never mind me, hurry! Or else
they'll reach Metro West first, Trunks!
Yo!
Here I go!
And then, this is a Super Saiyan
that's gone even beyond Super Saiyan.
And then... this...!
In order to delay Majin Boo,
Goku went even farther than
going even beyond Super Saiyan,
to Super Saiyan 3, and then fought him!
"Bye Bye Babidi!! Majin Boo Rebels."
Boo! What's the matter! Boo!
They're over our city!
How dreadful! How dreadful!
Way to go, Goku!
Stay with it, Father!
Th-This is Son?!
Super Saiyan 3 is far more
ferocious than we can imagine.
Nice going! Nice going, Boo!
That's the way! Crush him!
Goku!
Father!
It's okay! Son won't be defeated that easily!
Nice going! Nice going, Boo! Nice going!
Nice going! Nice going, Boo!
Nice going! Nice going!
It's not here! The Dragon Radar isn't anywhere!
Hmm, now where was it...?
Shall we take a short
break and have some snacks?
We'll do a full-scale search afterward.
There's no time for that!
If we don't hurry, Metro West will be destroyed!
If we lose the Dragon Radar,
we won't be able to return all
the dead people back to normal!
My, that is a problem.
Go! Give it to him, Boo! Way to go! Way to go!
Ah, for crying out loud...!
Trunks' ki still hasn't moved!
What are you doing, Trunks?!
It's no use. I'll have to buy a little more time...
Hey, you! Where are you going?!
Are you trying to escape?! You coward!
Look! They're moving farther and farther away!
Hooray! We're saved!
Nice going, Majin Boo!
Father! Hang in there!
–Goku!
–Goku...
That has to be it!
What does?
Trunks doesn't know
where the Dragon Radar is.
Sorry! After all of us went
searching for the Dragon Balls earlier,
I left it inside the airplane!
D-Does Trunks know about that?
He couldn't!
Then he must be figuring to
look in all the wrong places, right?
Come to mention it, he is taking a while...
We have to get in touch with Trunks right away!
Kuririn, a telephone! A telephone!
Easy for you to say, but
there aren't any phones here!
Um, if it's a phone you need, I have one here.
Videl!
Since I work as a Friend of Justice,
I'm always carrying around a cellular
phone with me, in case of an emergency.
All right! With this, we can contact Trunks!
Oh, Videl, nicely done!
You go away!
You got him! You got him!
Goku! That's quite enough!
Hurry and stop the fight!
If you use any more energy than this,
the time you can be on Earth will be gone!
This guy is much stronger than I had thought!
Ah, Bulma? How are you?
Is everyone doing fine?
Fine! Fine! Can you put Trunks on?
Trunks? Just a moment. Trunks! Telephone!
This isn't the time for that right now!
He says this isn't the time for that right now.
I don't have time for this either!
Hurry and put Trunks on!
Inside the plane? Gotcha!
I'll go get it right away!
The plane! The plane!
Eh? Do we have any planes
in the house? Oh... Oh... Oh...
Oh, the plane?
The plane is right here.
Okay, here goes again!
W-Wha-What the...?!
Boo! Majin Boo!
Majin Boo! Banzai!
Don't tell me he's
doing a Kamehame-Ha!
Dammit!
A-All the way here, at this temple...!
Incredible... It's an incredible fight!
We're this far apart,
and yet I can tell what's
happening as if it were within my grasp!
Gohan-san, it would be difficult
for Goku-san to win this after all.
Majin Boo is just that strong.
The best way to defeat Majin Boo
is still for you to master using
that legendary blade, the Z-Sword.
Understood.
It's quite difficult!
Can we rely on this?
This is the legendary sword that
generations of Kaioshin were unable to wield!
B-Be more careful!
I was almost put in danger,
you know! You imbecile!
Even so, that just now destroyed
about one-tenth of the Earth, didn't it?
What a Friend to Justice you must be! Nyah!
Boo! You're better than
I expected! I'm surprised!
You don't have the face of
someone who knows much,
but you've got a real gift for battle!
To think that you can read
through an opponent's techniques
and instead make them your own!
The airplane is inside this Capsule.
There you go, Trunks.
It's here! It's here!
My! That's terrific! Now,
won't you enjoy some snacks...?
There isn't time for that! I'm in a hurry, so...!
Oh, my! He came all this way.
He could have eaten
some snacks before leaving...
Trunks' ki has started moving!
He's safely found the Dragon Radar and
started moving away from Metro West!
All right! This is where my role ends!
Hey, why'd you go back to normal?
It's fun fighting you! Let's do some more!
That's quite an honor.
But I ain't got any more time.
I can't play with just you forever.
Sorry, but I have to get back.
Idiot! Do you think you can escape now?!
Majin Boo! Make an
example of him! Kill this guy!
After you kill him,
we'll go immediately to Metro West
and destroy everything there!
We'll kill everyone!
By doing so, those three that
opposed us are sure to come forward!
Listen up, Babidi!
The three who you're looking
for–Piccolo, Trunks, and Goten–
are guaranteed to appear
in three–no, two days!
So until then, don't do anything, just wait!
Stop killing people for no reason!
Two days. Just two days! That's okay, ain't it?
Are those guys strong?
Of course they are!
Do you really think I will
lend an ear to those words?
We're going to kill even more now, you know!
Gee, that's too bad.
It sounds like it would be a
rare, fun battle for Majin Boo.
Hey, Babidi!
I'm going to ask Great King Yama
to see to it that once you get to Hell,
you get squeezed plenty hard!
Up yours!
So then, see you later!
H-He vanished!
W-What was that all about?
That guy, why the hell did he come here?
Hey, Majin Boo! You let
him get away, didn't you?!
It's your fault for
dilly-dallying around! You dimwit!
He's got to still be around here somewhere!
Hurry and find him! Hurry!
Hey! Didn't you hear me?!
You do it! Get going now! Tubby!
Babidi-sama?
W-What is it?
I had a good idea.
What?! A good idea? An idiot like you?
I doubt it's anything too great,
but go ahead and tell me!
You know what, Babidi-sama?
What?! Hurry it up! Tell me
quick, and then go after that guy!
You can't talk, right?
That means you can't say
the spell to seal me up again!
Father!
Son!
You were incredible, Father!
Are you okay, Son?
Yeah!
Trunks is apparently
heading back here and all.
For the moment, we're out of danger, huh?
For the moment.
Even if Metro West is destroyed,
as long as we have the Dragon Radar,
we can turn it back to the way it was.
The dead people, too.
I've taken a lot from you.
Now I don't have any more to do with you.
I won't stand you any more!
Die! You fool!
At last, Majin Boo has
turned against Madoshi Babidi!
What will Boo do?
Will he continue his destruction?
Is there no one now who can stop Boo?!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Goten, Trunks, not to mention Piccolo,
I'm going to show you the Fusion Pose now,
so watch and learn closely, okay?
What do we do? That looks awful!
I don't want to have to do that!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Absurdly Awful-Looking!?
The Special Training Transformation Pose."
Once those two undergo Fusion,
I wonder what they'll look like.
"Next time"
"Absurdly Awful-Looking!?
The Special Training Transformation Pose"