Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
The recently revived Garlic Jr. turns every
living thing on Earth into Demon Clansmen,
by releasing the power of the
Aquamist, the fog of the devil.
And, to further secure revenge against
Son Goku, he had his demonic henchmen,
the Four Monarchs, launch an
attack on Gohan. But just then...
What have we here? If it isn't Piccolo-san.
Garlic Jr.-sama is waiting for you.
He has much he wishes to say to you.
Garlic Jr., you say?
"The Heavenly Realm is the Battlefield!!
Piccolo Becomes Devilish Again..."
Garlic Jr., huh?
There was once someone so foolish...
...he fell into a Dead Zone of his
own making and couldn't get out.
Wasn't that his name?
What?!
Garlic Jr....
What's happening?
Kurin-chan, do you hang
around with monsters like this?
–I'm shocked! I'm shocked! I'm shocked!
–M-M-Maron-chan!
How did he escape from the Dead Zone?
I doubt you guys had
the power to do it alone.
That's enough out of you!
I'll tell you how.
It's thanks to the Makyo World.
The Makyo World?
That's right.
The homeworld of our Demon Clan.
It approaches Earth every 5000 years.
You once numbered
yourself among the Demons,
you must have known this.
As the Makyo World approaches,
our dormant powers awaken,
and we grow several dozen times stronger.
Garlic Jr.-sama raised his increased
dormant powers as high as they would go,
and freed himself under his own power.
And now that he's defeated
Kami in the Heavenly Realm,
and gained immortality
with the Dragon Balls,
Garlic Jr.-sama has
become Kami for all eternity!
K-Kami-sama?
All that remains is to wait for the Aquamist...
...to change all living things
on Earth into Demon Clansmen.
That will only take a few hours more!
The effects of the Aquamist will
become permanent after 24 hours.
That means that 24 hours after breathing it,
not even the Ultra Holy Water
will return you to normal!
H-How awful!
By sunrise tomorrow,
every living thing on Earth will
bow down before Garlic Jr.-sama.
Piccolo, our Garlic Jr.
is a magnanimous being.
If you would go along, he said he
would be willing to forget about the past.
How about it?
Don't you want to once again live
as they do, as a Demon Clansman?
Don't you want to join us...
...in seeing that the world is again
filled with terror and hopelessness?
This is the desire of Garlic Jr.-sama.
Why you!
Is that your answer?
In that case, we'll have
to persuade you by force!
Go ahead and try.
What's the matter, Piccolo-san?
Stop this, Yamucha-san!
Move it!
Piccolo-san! Stop it!
What are you doing, Kurin-chan?
Your opponent is an old man, isn't he?
Why don't you clock him one?
Clock him one good!
H-How can you ask me to do that?
Kurin-chan!
Maron-chan!
Everyone is ganging up on me!
Help me!
Kurin-chan!
Maron-chan!
Haiya Dragon!
Take care of Maron-chan!
Kurin-chan!
Watching these friends kill each
other is really something to see.
Please stop!
Look out!
Piccolo-san!
Piccolo-san, are you all right?
I can handle this by myself!
You guys go to the Heavenly Realm!
Get the Ultra Holy Water away from Garlic!
B-But...
Gohan, let's leave this to Piccolo!
There's no time to spare!
If we don't hurry, they're
going to have their way!
Go!
Right! Okay, then!
This is unfortunate for all of
you, but I need for you to die.
Piccolo-san!
Stay away!
Hurry! Hurry up!
P-Piccolo-san!
I said go!
The kid, he's getting away!
Let him go.
He's headed to the Temple
of the Heavenly Realm anyway.
It saves us the bother.
I-I'm counting on you, Gohan!
Go-Gohan...
Gohan!
Kuririn-san...
Well, let's go!
Right!
Kurin-chan!
Kurin-chan! Just a minute!
No way, Maron-chan, you and Haiya
Dragon have to find somewhere safe to hide!
You have to be kidding! I'm going with you!
It sounds like fun. And I love adventures!
Maron-chan. Where we're going
isn't going to be all that easygoing.
It's all right.
If it gets really dangerous,
you're going to save me, Kurin-chan.
Unbelievable!
I get it now.
Go ahead and toss me aside, and
take off to wherever you feel like going!
Kuririn-san, we have to hurry!
Uh, yeah...
Oh, all right.
Haiya Dragon, fly as fast as you can!
This is why I like you so much, Kurin-chan!
This guy sure has a big mouth!
Don't.
If we kill him, then Kami dies,
and we won't be able to use the Dragon Balls.
Oh, that's right.
Besides...
Being bitten by one of these guys...
...puts you in the same condition
as if you had inhaled the Aquamist.
Rise then, our newfound ally.
D-Damn. Even with all of us
Litts against just one monkey...
For us to be wiped out...
Hey, I have something to ask you.
There should have been...
...a Saiyan calling himself Kakarrot
or Son Goku on this planet recently.
S-Saiyan, you say?
That's right. Where did he go?
You mean there are
more of them than just you?
Filthy Saiyan monkeys!
So then, you don't know?
If you see Freeza in the
Other World, tell him this for me–
"I'm going to beat the same
Kakarrot that killed you."
"You should feel grateful."
Freeza-sama killed by a
Saiyan?! That's impossible!
Naive, to the very end.
Kakarrot, I know you're
around here somewhere.
I can feel your unique Saiyan ki.
Wherever you are, whatever
you're doing, I'll be sure to find you!
Kuririn-san, this is strange!
Where could Karin-sama have gone?
You don't suppose that strange smoke...
Hey! What's the matter?!
All right, let's go in.
Keep your eyes peeled, Gohan.
Right!
Kurin-chan! I'm getting cold!
Is there anything I can wear?
Hey, is this the Heavenly Realm then?
Sure is a gloomy place.
Kuririn-san!
What noisy folk you are!
Oh, it's you guys?
Karin-sama!
You're all right then?
Indeed! And I was sleeping so happily, too.
What a cute kitty-chan!
Hey, now!
W-Who is the young lady?
M-Maron-chan.
What kind of fool comes to a holy
place such as this wearing a swimsuit?!
No, um, you see...
She is Kuririn-san's girlfriend.
What did you say?
Nice to meet you!
Who're you foolin'?!
Ain't no way a pachinko-head
like you could get yerself a girl!
It's nothing for you to get upset over, is it?
Well, in that case, it's okay.
So then, what can I do for you?
That's right! Karin-sama, right
now the world is in a terrible mess!
Hold on. Rather than having you go
spelling it all out, I'll read your mind.
What's this?! Aquamist?! I see.
That's why you're headed
to the Heavenly Plane?
R-Right!
That will be perilous!
The Ultra Holy Water is
surely up in the Heavenly Realm.
However, it is in a container deep
within the temple, next to the Aquamist.
It's pretty likely that
Garlic Jr. has it well protected.
Karin-sama! Thank you very much!
Take good care of Maron-chan!
Now hold on there!
Kurin-chan, take me with you!
How do you expect me to
look after this loud young lady?!
Now cut that out!
This is terrible!
Where are Kami-sama and Mister Popo?
Welcome to my temple!
I've been waiting for the both of you.
The Ultra Holy Water is in here.
Come and take it!
Gohan!
Right!
Piccolo-san!
Wait! There's something strange about him!
Piccolo, don't tell me, you...
We meet again, kid.
You're faster than we thought,
I'll give you credit for that.
Damn.
They got Piccolo-san too.
W-What's this?!
Piccolo has joined forces with Garlic Jr.?!
How will Gohan and Kuririn
overcome this development?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
If even Piccolo has turned demonic,
who's gonna protect Gohan?
What exactly is going on, Kurin-chan?
All your friends are turning
demonic, one after the next.
Are you really sure they're such prizewinners?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Direct Confrontation with Piccolo!!
An Angry Masenko in the Heavenly Realm."
Father! Come back soon!
"Next time"
"Direct Confrontation with Piccolo!!
An Angry Masenko in the Heavenly Realm"