Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Owing to Goku's strong will,
everyone besides him and
Freeza were transported to Earth,
by the power of Planet Namek's Shen Long.
But I've been waiting for this moment–
the moment when I could
fight you as hard as I want to!
And so, under two minutes remain
until the explosion of Planet Namek!
"Let's Get It On!!
Two Remain on a Vanishing Planet."
Either way, you will likely
be dead in two minutes.
You're quite the pitiable one.
You're the one who's pitiable.
After all, you're the one who's going to be
beaten by detestable Saiyan monkey scum.
Talk as big as you want,
the only one of us who can
escape the explosion of this planet
is me!!
Goku, there's no more time!
K-Kaio-sama, once Planet Namek explodes,
even supposing Goku defeats Freeza...
No matter that Goku
has become a Super Saiyan,
it's unlikely he can
survive in the vacuum of space.
Kaio-sama, is there no way to save Goku?
This is the path Goku chose for himself.
Y-You don't mean...
Yamucha!
Goku!
S-Son...
S-So what about Kuririn-san?
With the Earth's Dragon Balls,
one who has already been resurrected
once cannot be returned to life a second time.
Y-You mean...?
But Son-kun has only died once!
That man desired that everyone except
himself and Freeza be relocated to Earth.
T-Then Father is still on
Planet Namek with Freeza?
I-It can't be!
The planet is about to explode!
Planet Namek?! Grand Elder-sama...
G-Grand Elder-sama...
Unfortunately so.
I-It can't be...
That's ridiculous!
Not even Son could
survive the planet exploding,
even having defeated Freeza, right?!
S-Son...
If he wanted to, he could
have left Freeza behind
and returned to Earth together with us.
Son, you're really something...
Piccolo-san...
Son, why did you have
me return to Earth as well?
I wanted to fight together with you!
Sorry I took so long.
Thanks to you guys, I've recovered.
I'll manage this from here on.
Much as I hate it, Son,
your power has now far exceeded my own.
In exchange for your own life...
You've always been like that.
That's so true.
Father!
I know just how Kakarrot feels.
Vegeta!
All Kakarrot wanted to do
was fight someone strong.
What's this?!
Have you come back to life as well?!
It would have been fine
if you'd stayed dead on us!
Too bad.
Yow!
You're here too?
I've had enough!
Get lost!!
Of all the–what is it with that frog?! Indeed!
Kakarrot and I both
have valiant blood of the
Saiyan Warrior Race flowing within us.
To say nothing of Kakarrot having
become a legendary Super Saiyan,
that's all the more reason he
won't rest until he has defeated Freeza.
However, the book is closed
on both Kakarrot and Freeza,
together with the planet Namek.
Stop laughing!!
Now that I've died and returned to life,
I should be that much stronger.
Once Kakarrot and
Freeza die fighting each other,
I automatically become the
strongest man in the universe!
Why, you...!
This is quite the unexpected turn of luck.
Fortune just keeps favoring me!
You and I are the only ones who
still possess the glory of Saiyan blood.
How about it? Why don't
you come along with me?
I will rule the universe in place of Freeza!
W-Who would ever team
up with the likes of you?!
I-I am an Earthling, the son of Son Goku!
T-That's right!
How can you be doing this while Son-kun
is risking his life to fight against Freeza?!
Kakarrot chose his own path by himself.
From now on, I am going
to have you obey my orders.
What?!
There's still a little time left
before the planet explodes.
You'll have to entertain me a little longer!
For Goku to have remained behind...
Kami-sama...
There's no time, Goku!
That's right!
There are Dragon Balls here
on Earth as well, aren't there?
If I call on Shen Long to have
me made undyingly youthful,
I can reign over the universe forever!
That won't be possible.
I hear the Dragon Balls were already
used in order to bring you all back to life.
They have now turned to ordinary
stone for a year's time. Tough luck!
I'm glad to be able to settle this with you.
I'm sure to win this fight!
Such insolence!
You've touched that which
must not be touched. Son Goku!
Goku!
Grand Elder-sama, do you know
what is happening on Planet Namek?
Son-kun is okay, right?
He's a Super Saiyan, isn't he?
Unfortunately, I can no longer ascertain
what is happening on Planet Namek.
O-Oh no...
Son is all right!
Piccolo-san...
He's sure to be all right!
P-Piccolo-san!
Just what I'd expect of a Super Saiyan!
Very well. Let me explain to you clearly
why I will be the one who survives this!
Father...
Son-kun, don't die on me!
Son...!
Father!!
One more minute to your destruction!!
The super battle to determine
who is the strongest in the universe,
as well as the time to
Planet Namek's explosion,
has fallen below one minute.
Which way will the outcome turn?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
That this should be your final technique!
You disappoint me, Freeza!
I am not losing to the
likes of a lowlife Saiyan!
You're an impossible fool!
I had given you one last chance!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Pathos of Freeza! Once He
Starts Shaking, He's Unstoppable!!"
Father wins!
"Next time"
"Pathos of Freeza! Once He
Starts Shaking, He's Unstoppable!!"