Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Ghurd, of the Ginyu Special Corps,
the evil emperor Freeza's secret weapon,
was fighting Gohan and Kuririn.
However, at the last critical moment,
Vegeta jumped in and saved them.
Do you think I deliberately rescued you?
Don't get me wrong.
I just had the perfect chance to kill
that grubby bastard Ghurd, that's all.
ReaCoom!
Butta!
Jheese!
The real hell starts now.
"The Savage ReaCoom!!
He's Bad, He's Strong, He's Outrageous."
Okay, Vegeta-chan, now it's our turn.
You two little pipsqueaks
there, give Vegeta-chan a hand.
Use as many dirty tricks as you need to.
Hey, ReaCoom! Don't kill the little ones!
We're going to kill them, after all!
Leave a little treat for us, too!
Dammit!
Why, that jerk!
Ginyu...
...Special Corps...
ReaCoom!!
Hey, what's going on here? Vegeta-chan's
power level just rose to upwards of 30,000!
Get down!
More! More! More!
H-He got him.
Incredible... He ended it all in one instant.
Vegeta has ridiculous strength, all right.
Hey, it couldn't be, right?
A-A ki! H-He's alive! That guy is alive!
H-He couldn't be... N-No way...
Hi!
H-He's taken hardly any damage at all!
That's enough for the warm-up exercises.
ReaCoom is trying to look cool,
and we're getting all dusty over here!
Our cleaning bill is going to be outrageous.
W-What kind of monster is he?
How is it that we have to get the
Dragon Balls back from someone like this?
Whoops!
That was close, that was close.
I almost screwed up.
I have to make sure to
deliver these to Freeza-sama.
Planet Namek.
Environment: moderate; culture level: low;
practical resources: none;
scouting industrial space,
commercial space, and residential space.
Such a worthless planet, huh?
Perhaps I will make it a planet for exiles.
There are any number of
planets like this one in the universe.
I doubt there would be any value in
going to the trouble of developing it.
I will be acquiring the Dragon Balls shortly,
so I will have no further business here.
I know. As we are leaving,
I will turn this planet into fireworks.
F-Fireworks?
Yes. To celebrate my eternal life.
A big, flashy "boom."
Are there any other planets we can
sell for development at a high price?
Y-Yes, sir, I will investigate at once.
Dragon Balls... how delightful...
Well, should we get started?
ReaCoom Kick!!
V-Vegeta-san!
Good! That's pretty good, Vegeta-chan!
You're better than I thought, huh?
ReaCoom Elbow!!
He got him!
Speed Up!!
Yoo-hoo!
Way to go, ReaCoom!
Whoo! Whoo!
Thanks, guys!
V-Vegeta-san...
What's the matter, Vegeta-chan?
You can't possibly be
finished after that, right?
You're still pretty spirited, huh? Good for you!
Hey, now, are you okay?
Don't tell me you've kicked
the bucket already, have you?
D-Did he get him?
Okay...
Nice, nice, that's more like it.
There's the reason why Freeza-sama
adored you so much, long ago, huh?
But why would you turn
your back on him, Vegeta-chan?
ReaCoom is the same as ever, huh?
He's got a nasty personality.
What a freak!
Don't you have any techniques
with more panache than that?
If not, then it's about
time I killed you. Is that okay?
Y-You monster! Damn it...
To think he'd be this strong...
It's almost as though he's
treating me like a toddler...
If it keeps going like this,
I'm going to get killed by him...
G-Gohan...
Yes?
I-If Vegeta gets done in, then it
will be our turn to get killed next.
M-Make no mistake,
there's no way we can beat him.
I'm sure that not even Goku could.
At this point, it's all or
nothing. Let's charge him!
Right!
All righty...
Your life is mine!
There it is! ReaCoom's 18th final pose.
Poor Vegeta-chan. The life
of a flower is so short, huh?
Okay, I'll finish you with this.
All right... let's go, Gohan!
Vegeta doesn't have the strength
left to avoid ReaCoom's quick attacks.
Right!
ReaCoom...
...Eraser Gun!!
Vegeta-san!
Move! You're in my way!
W-Who asked you to do that?!
Y-You idiot! If you had time to rescue me,
why didn't you attack ReaCoom?!
For crying out loud, your
softness makes me want to vomit!
The ground's surface has been blown away,
and the planet's shape has changed...
What a terrifying beast!
That sneak attack just
now was a pretty good one.
Coming down from
directly above shut my mouth.
As a result, my teeth are messed up.
I think I might be a little bit mad.
Hey, Butta, Jheese!
Let me take out these two little squirts, too!
Do you mind? Okay? Do you mind?
What choice do we have?
Okay, fine! Do as you please.
In exchange, you're going to
treat us to chocolate parfaits later!
Okay! You heard him, maggot-kun.
Big Fire Toe Attack!!
Kuririn-san!
Kuririn-san! Kuririn-san!
M-My bones... How can this be?
With just one hit...
this is what happens to me...
He's too much...
I-Is this allowed?
And after having Grand
Elder-san raise my power, too...
I-I'm no use at all...
S-Shake it off, Kuririn-san! Kuririn-san!
F-Frankly, we're finished...
We're powerless against them, and
if we run, they'll catch us right away...
And the Dragon Balls have been taken from us...
There's nothing good about this...
Tch! Aw, man... I couldn't
help myself, and hit him too hard.
I was planning to play around
with him a little more, but too bad.
Now then, for the next
little pipsqueak's turn...
Darn it!
G-Gohan...
I-I'll do as much as I can! Just you watch me!
This should be interesting.
Darn it...
ReaCoom is an incredible foe.
Will Gohan be able to get
through this greatest of pinches?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
That's enough. Don't get up anymore, Gohan.
I-I am Son Goku's son! You won't...
Oho, aren't you spirited? I don't
know what planet you're from, kid,
but this is surprising.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Don't Die, Gohan! Goku Finally
Touches Down on the Battlefield."
Father is here!
"Next time"
"Don't Die, Gohan! Goku Finally
Touches Down on the Battlefield"