Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Ka...
me...
ha...
H-How can it be?!
Ha!!
It's the real thing!
Before I am to be absorbed by you,
you have to tell me something!
What in the hell are you?!
I am Cell, an Artificial Human
born of Doctor Gero's computer!
If I merge with Artificial
Humans No. 17 and No. 18,
I will become my perfect form,
with power beyond imagination.
That is the reason I have come to this era.
The surprising identity of
the monster Cell is revealed.
He must be prevented from
his perfect form at any cost!
My gratitude.
Thanks to you, all of the
mysteries have now been solved.
You've been quite informative!
Why you...
"Piccolo's Grievous Mistake!
Cell Turned Loose on the City!"
What the hell is happening?!
What is it?!
Cell, even figuring in the arm's
worth of energy you drew from me,
my power is still much greater than yours!
Get ready!
You sure thought that through.
To think you would pretend
you'd lost one of your arms
just to get me to talk...
You're quite the clever one, aren't you?
That was the wisdom of the one
who used to be Kami, not my own.
What?
S-So that's it!
You're the result of Piccolo
and Kami merging together!
That's right.
Heh, you just now figured it out?
Which means the Dragon
Balls have also disappeared.
Once dead, no one can be returned to life.
That's rather convenient!
Then it's no wonder you're so strong,
even though you still look
as if you were Piccolo Daimao.
Hmph. You still do not know my true power.
I'll show you now exhaustively
what that true power is!
There's no doubt about it,
he's merged with Kami-sama!
Who's that guy over there?
That's probably him!
The monster that came out of that shell!
Trunks! What's he doing here?!
I get it. So then he also came
to this era in the time machine?
What a fool!
That he should be killed by me in the future,
only to be killed in this era as well...!
H-He's a freak!
I-Is he the one that killed
the people of Gingertown?
That's right. Watch out for his tail.
The people here were all killed by it.
Why is it we feel Goku, Tenshinhan
and the other's ki from that guy?
I'll tell you all about it later.
Putting him away comes first!
Put me away, you say?
You think it will be that easy?
It s-spoke!
Under the circumstances,
I don't think you have much chance of winning.
I certainly have no choice but
to withdraw from this situation.
I'm not letting you get away!
You can't escape by using the
sort of Kamehame-Ha you did before!
Kamehame-Ha?!
How can this guy use Goku's Kamehame-Ha?!
Not just the Kamehame-Ha, Kuririn!
If I wanted to, I could probably
even form a Genki Dama!
I'm stunned!
He even knows my name! How?!
When I tell Goku, I'm sure he'll be surprised too!
Oh? Son Goku is still alive, is he?
Of course he is!
So, he's still alive...
It appears things are turning out slightly
different from the history I know.
I will acquire No. 17 and No. 18 no matter what!
No matter how you may try to prevent
me from becoming my perfect form,
it will come to nothing!
Not as long as the only one that
can hope to fight against No. 17
and the others is Piccolo!
What?!
T-That's...!
Taiyo-ken!
Ah, dammit!
Damn!
He's gotten away!
That bastard!
Kuririn! Wasn't the Taiyo-ken
Tenshinhan's technique?!
The Taiyo-ken isn't all that
difficult a technique! Goku–
and I can do it too!
Why, you...!
He's suppressing his ki dissipation!
He can even do that!
That was easy!
I'll never be caught again!
So long as I act while controlling my ki like this,
there's no way they can find me!
You guys! This is dreadful!
M-Muten Roshi-sama, Goku-sa is...
What? What's happened?!
Calm down, Mother!
Everyone, just come up here!
What is it, what is it?
Just what is the matter up here?!
Shh! Be quiet!
See that?! Goku-sa just smiled!
Oh, he certainly did!
It's true! He smiled!
Hey, that means he's all
but recovered, doesn't it?
It's really great!
Have you guys noticed it yet?
His smile is different
from any ordinary smile.
It's the same as the excited one Goku
gets before he fights someone strong!
Oh! Now that you mention it!
Looks like we can count on Goku after all!
He must be anticipating
fighting the Artificial Humans,
and he's starting to get excited!
That's just like him!
Once he starts to get a little strength back,
he starts thinking of fighting
again, even in his sleep!
We can relax now!
H-Hey, Yamucha?
Right? Isn't that so, Roshi-sama?
Absolutely! What a guy!
Y-Yamucha!
Huh? What's wrong?
U-Uh, Chichi-san, I didn't mean anything by that.
I am utterly against havin' Goku-sa
fightin' so soon after his illness!
Mother, Yamucha-san didn't necessarily intend...
You hush!
There's nothin' I hate
more than the barbaric idea
of you makin' him fight right away!
S-Sure.
Yeah? I'm talkin' to each one of you here!
You got that?!
Y-Yes!
In that case,
Keep it quiet!!
"Gingertown, 50 km"
As I evade their view, I'll absorb
more and more humans' life energy,
and increase my power more and more!
And then, once my power
exceeds No. 17 and the others,
I'll force them to merge with me!
"Welcome! Nickytown, 30 km"
My next catch is in Nickytown, is it?
Senseless idiot! You got a death wish?!
What concerns me most is whether
or not there exists a Controller that
can shut down No. 17 and the others.
Hey! Don't just stand there
like a moron, get out of the way!
Once incapacitated, even if we
are talking about No. 17 and No. 18,
destroying them will be easy.
But it's all right.
Such a Controller no longer exists.
–What's the matter?
–What's going on out there?
Who do you think you are,
wearing that strange costume?
Leave him to us!
I was just getting the
urge for a little light exercise!
Hey, you deranged punk,
move it before you get hurt!
I can't count on much,
but even these guys will
contribute some life energy.
And if Piccolo and company discover me,
I'll just move on to another place!
Damn you!
Battle Formation!
W-What?!
Vegeta?!
Then he hasn't been killed
by No. 17 and the others either?
Still, even he has a much
greater power than expected.
I'll probably have to hurry this up.
Of those two guys with the mysterious,
incredibly large battle powers,
one of them has disappeared!
H-However, one of them is still there!
It isn't that Artificial Human No. 17 or whoever,
those guys don't dissipate the slightest ki.
So who the hell is it then?
Dammit, I got careless!
I should have beaten him easily!
Incredible!
You lousy scum!
I will absolutely not let
you become your perfect form!
P-Piccolo! It can't be!
Vegeta!
D-Dad!
Talk! What happened here?!
Tenshinhan appears to be headed here as well.
Once he arrives, I'll tell everyone all at once.
Well then, beforehand,
I want you to answer me this.
Are you really Piccolo?!
How did you come to
have all that battle power?
Why, you!
P-Piccolo-san has...
Piccolo-san has once
again merged with Kami-sama.
W-What's this? You merged?!
J-Just from that?
I'm sure the battle power I felt before
was even higher than mine as a Super Saiyan!
Impossible!
He's just a mere Namekian!
He's here! It's Tenshinhan!
What do we do?
With No. 17 and No. 18, as well as No. 16...
Even with all the super power I've obtained,
I probably can't handle them.
Indeed, all we can do is defeat Cell himself.
Um, Piccolo... or rather,
Kami-sama... or rather, um...
What should we call you now?
Tenshinhan is here!
All right. I'll tell you everything.
Vegeta and Tenshinhan didn't see him,
but that monster that was just
here was an Artificial Human,
independently created
by Doctor Gero's computer.
What?!
Say, just so you know,
I don't like these clothes, okay?
If we come across a good city
somewhere, you've got to take us there!
I know, already.
Sure enough,
I'll just have to go to the city
and take its citizens one by one.
I-It can't be!
Me and Kakarrot's cells?!
That's how it is.
In order to prevent Cell
from becoming his perfect form,
we have to either
seek him out and kill him,
or seek out either No. 17 or
No. 18 and kill them, either way.
As far as I'm concerned, I think all
we can do is beat Cell while he still
doesn't have all that much power.
They dare to make a fool of me?!
Everyone is easily outpacing the
Super Saiyan, greatest in the universe!
It's pissing me off! What about you, Kakarrot?
Here, here the humans are!
You just sit tight, No. 17 and No. 18!
In just a few days, my
power will far surpass yours,
and I will absorb you!
It's a bad situation, ringing of ill fortune!
Who can save the world from this despair?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Say, Trunks, I guess it won't
help to go back to Gero's lab,
and bust up the computer
that gives birth to Cell, huh?
No, let's destroy it anyway.
We must not allow Cell to be
born into this dimension's future.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Secret of Cell's Birth!
What Lies Below the Laboratory!?"
How exactly was Cell born?
"Next time"
"The Secret of Cell's Birth!
What Lies Below the Laboratory!?"