The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
The instruments of evil, Yamu
and Spopovitch, make their move,
and throw the Tenkaichi
Tournament into great confusion!
That was easier than I thought!
So, you have come after all.
This will be most helpful.
If I cannot borrow your
powers, we will not likely win...
Not win? You mean against those two?
No. Those two are merely
being used by the Madoshi.
The situation grows more and more tense.
Who is this Madoshi
that Kaioshin is afraid of?
What is he like? And what is to
become of the Tenkaichi Tournament?
"The Man Behind the Curtains Appears!!
The Evil Madoshi Babidi."
That went well!
When we bring him this much energy,
Babidi-sama will be most pleased!
We are sure to get a fine reward! Let's hurry!
Yeah!
In other words, in the distant
past, this incredibly terrible monster,
Majin Boo, conjured up by Madoshi Bibidi,
was sealed up somewhere
here on Earth, is that right?
Yes. The only one able to
break that seal was Madoshi Bibidi,
and so we were relieved.
However, as we recently learned,
Madoshi Bibidi had a child.
That child has now come to Earth.
And he's the one who's
manipulating Yamu and Spopovitch?
Yes. Madoshi Babidi has the same
heart of evil as his father Bibidi.
Majin and Madoshi and such.
Nothing but bizarre guys popping up, huh?
So, in short, we have to see to it
that this Majin Boo ain't revived, right?
That is correct. That means
we must defeat Madoshi Babidi.
Babidi is the only one who can
break the seal on Majin Boo now.
So is he strong, this Babidi?
He uses formidable magic, but he
doesn't have any great power himself.
His father Bibidi was the same way.
However, a Madoshi can
seize upon the hearts of evil men
such as Yamu and Spopovitch,
and manipulate them.
It'd be nice if he didn't keep
such tough people at his side.
So what did Spopovitch and Yamu
come to the Tenkaichi Tournament for?
What is it they did to me?
In order to revive Majin Boo, who has
been sealed up for such a long time,
it seems they need a great
deal of unpolluted energy.
Unpolluted energy?
Babidi sent those two to
the Tenkaichi Tournament,
with the aim of collecting
such energy quickly.
Once you turned Super Saiyan, your
energy became their greatest target.
Both myself and Kaioshin-sama
knew that Babidi would probably do so,
so we slipped in as well.
We wanted to know where Babidi was.
Once we had come to Earth,
we searched around some,
but the ball that Majin Boo had been sealed
in was no longer where it was in the past.
It had been moved somewhere else.
That's why we wanted to follow those two,
so we could learn where Babidi is.
V-Videl-san...
You okay?
Y-Yeah...
If this Majin was so terrible,
why did you leave him alone when
you killed Babidi's dad way back then?
It could not be helped.
If we had damaged
him in the wrong place,
we might have
accidentally broken the seal.
Besides, we were at ease.
The ball Majin Boo was sealed in
was in a place where mankind on Earth,
who had just barely started walking upright,
would find it impossible to go to.
What happened to the matches?!
Start them up now!
Don't you try making fools of us!
Please, wait a moment!
We are currently in conference!
Please wait a moment longer!
What's going on?!
Both Videl and Son Gohan
just took off flying somewhere.
It's been a strange day, huh?
Videl got beaten senseless,
then suddenly she's okay again,
and even flying around...
You don't suppose it's all some kind of trick?
The way Mister Satan said before?
I-It has to be. This has got to be a trick!
Never mind Son Gohan, it's unthinkable
that Videl could fly through the air.
Oh, so that's what this is?!
Everyone's joined together
to play a trick on us!
When you take a good
look at it, this is such a waste!
I'm going to give them a piece of
my mind when I see them at school.
Hurry it up! We came to see a match!
Please do not throw things!
Please don't throw things!
Goten, what's going on?
I dunno...
At this speed we will not be
able to catch up to Kaioshin-sama.
We're going to raise our speed a bit more.
R-Right!
Uh, just a second...
Videl-san, I don't think
you should overexert yourself.
I hate it...
...but I can't do any more.
We're already going so fast
I can't keep my eyes open.
Videl-san, you've just
barely started flying is all.
You really should go back.
We don't know what's
going to happen from here on.
It looks like it's going to be
far worse than we can imagine.
I guess that's all I can do.
Any way I think it through,
I'd just be in the way.
Regrettable thought it may be...
Thanks. Go back to
the tournament grounds.
If you find Goten or Mother there,
explain to them what's happening here.
Understood.
But Gohan-kun, you were the
Golden Warrior after all, weren't you?
Y-Yeah. I'm sorry I had to lie to you.
I didn't want anyone to know.
Seven years ago, during the fight with Cell,
those strange people there
at the ring were you guys, huh?
That child who was there together
with them was you, Gohan-kun, right?
Yeah.
And it was probably you
guys that beat Cell, not my Papa.
Well, that is...
I knew it!
It's okay. You don't have to worry over it.
I'd always thought it was a little
strange that Papa defeated him.
It's a load off clearing that up.
Hang in there, Gohan-kun. Beat
this Madoshi Babidi and save us all!
Mm-hmm.
Gohan-kun! I'll be waiting for
you at the tournament grounds!
Right!
Is it all right now?
Yes, please excuse us!
Well then, let's raise our speed.
We must catch up to Kaioshin-sama.
Right!
Wh-What speed they have!
Don't die, Gohan-kun.
If you come back safely,
I want to date you and stuff...
Ah, we've caught up!
Father!
Oh, it's Gohan!
Hurry on up here!
Gohan, we've been waiting for you.
Right.
Have you heard?
Our enemy this time seems to
be some incredibly terrible guy!
Yes.
Well, it's been some time.
Should we get rowdy?
I'm sure of it.
Goku is all eager, but are we all right?
It sounds like it's
going to be pretty bad.
They're here...
There it is.
They've started to descend.
Around here?
Odd. I thought we'd
investigated this area once.
Gentlemen, please hold your ki. Is that clear?
There's someone there.
Is that Babidi?
No, it isn't. He must be
one of Babidi's henchmen.
Say, there's something strange
about the ground, but just in that area.
It's like it's been dug up.
That's it! Babidi must have buried
his spaceship in the ground to hide it.
That's why we searched all
over and still didn't notice it.
Which probably means that
Babidi knows we've come to Earth.
Otherwise he wouldn't have
taken the trouble to hide his ship.
Shouldn't we attack now?
Before they can revive Majin Boo
with the energy stolen from Gohan?
It's all right.
Majin Boo's revival should be
conducted outside the spaceship,
in order not to damage it.
Let's watch and wait a little
longer, until that time comes.
Someone's coming out.
Dabura!!
It couldn't be... Dabura?!
Babidi has placed the King of the
Demon Realm within the palm of his hand?
Dabura? Which one, the big one?
Yes.
Is he pretty awesome?
Of course.
He is the King of the Demon
Realm of Darkness, after all.
Wh-What's the Demon Realm of Darkness?
There's another world on
the opposite side of this world.
In this world, one of you
guys is probably Number One,
but Dabura is absolutely Tops
in this other, Demonic world.
King of the Demon Realm, you say?!
Such a world really exists?
This guy must be incredibly
dangerous! All this can't be real!
Which means that little one
must be Madoshi Babidi, right?
Yes.
That guy? That's the guy?
Of his own power, he's certainly helpless,
but he uses fearsome magic, so
you must not underestimate him.
It's strong enough that he
made Dabura one of his henchmen.
Then Babidi's magic is strong enough
to make even the kingpin of the
Demon Realm surrender to him?
No. We believe he probably takes a hold of
the evil and greed in his victim's hearts,
and uses it to steer them as he pleases.
In that sense, Dabura is the
most suitable henchman there is.
Truth is, that's the most
horrifying magic Babidi possesses.
Yamu, Spopovitch and all his other
henchmen are governed by that magic.
That's why those of us like
yourselves without evil in their hearts
are the only ones who
can fight against him.
Those without evil in their hearts, eh?
But doesn't that rule Piccolo out?
He was born a Demon clansman and all...
That was a long time ago!
You have a full tank of energy here?
Y-Yes!
You know, having Dabura
here was a great miscalculation.
To think of having
Babidi and Dabura together...
Are you trying to say our chances
of winning have all but disappeared?
Hmph, if Majin Boo is revived,
it's the end of the world, huh?
I won't have it! I won't be beat by them!
Th-This is going to be
pretty dangerous, all right.
Kuririn, you'd better go back.
This is a lot more tough
than we thought it would be.
I-I think I might just do that.
This doesn't appear to be
the level where I can help out.
That and not many days have
passed since you got married and all...
Y-Yeah, I've got a wife
and cute little daughter too...
Well, I hate to do so, but...
You've done well.
This brings us considerably
closer to Majin Boo's revival!
Hey, with our powers, it was an
easy job, not even worth mentioning!
Your use to me has now passed.
"Boom!" Every time I hear
it, it sounds good, huh?!
Yes. I think so as well.
Well then, I will do him...
Puipui, I bet you'd like a try, right?
Yes!
Nice shot!
Th-They did in their own...
What kind of guys are these?
At last, the ringleader of evil,
Madoshi Babidi shows himself!
The King of the Demon Realm
of Darkness is together with him!
There's a vile sense that extraordinary
events are about to occur!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Kaioshin-sama, if we defeat
Dabura, Piccolo and Kuririn,
who have been turned to stone,
will return to normal, right?
Just a moment! This is a trap!
Once we enter the enemy ship,
we play right into Babidi's hands!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Awaiting Trap!!
A Challenge from the Demon Realm."
Piccolo-san... Kuririn-san...
We'll make sure to save
you, just sit tight, okay?
"Next time"
"The Awaiting Trap!!
A Challenge from the Demon Realm"