Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
At last, the ferocious battle between
Goku and Freeza has reached a conclusion.
Don't stand up! Get down!
Get down!
P-Please...!
Save me...!
You dare ask anything for yourself?!
How many people have you killed
as they begged for their lives like that?!
Please...!
Freeza!
I've shared a little bit of my ki with you.
Knowing you, you should be
able to move, even in your shape.
The rest is up to you!
"Freeza Defeated!! A Single
Blast Packed with a Totality of Rage."
This is quite unexpected.
T-That you should share your
energy with me, you monkey scumbag!
You can survive in the
vacuum of space, right?
So hurry up and leave this planet!
Survive, and come to
understand the blessing that life is!
T-Thank you.
Hey! Wait up!
–You think you can touch me?
–You can't reach!
Come down from there!
It seems the end of my life has nearly arrived.
G-Grand Elder-sama!
Grand Elder-sama! Grand Elder-sama!
B-Bring... bring everyone together.
R-Right!
Grand Elder-sama!
It would appear the time for me
to take my leave of you has come.
I am pleased to be able
to fulfill my life's span.
Muri-sama!
Oh, how did it go?
Yes! As feared, we were unable to
locate those from Elder Tsuno's village.
What in the world could
have happened to them?
Those guys are probably the ones
from the village that I wiped out.
The wish to the Dragon Balls
was to bring back to life everyone
killed by Freeza and his men, right?
I'm neither Freeza nor one of
his men. Quite the blunder, huh?
Apparently the Dragon Balls
followed after, and have reached us.
G-Grand Elder-sama!
As I said earlier, virtually
none of my life's measure remains.
M-Muri...
Y-Yes?
H-Hold out your hand.
Right!
F-From now on, you are to be the Grand Elder.
In due time, the Dragon Balls will
regain their brilliance once again.
U-Use the Dragon Balls well.
Y-Yes, we will.
I-I'm counting on you...
Grand Elder-sama!
Let there be eternal
peace among the Namekians.
–Grand Elder-sama!
Grand Elder-sama!
Grand Elder-sama...!
G-Grand Elder-sama...
This is amazing...
You possess such incredible latent ability!
Are you really an Earthling?
Excuse me! Can I please have you hurry?
Grand Elder-sama, may you rest in peace.
N-Now I understand clearly!
Piccolo-san, you have
merged with Nail-san, right?
Everybody!
The Grand Elder-sama is no longer here.
Let the rest of us put our
remaining energies together,
and find ourselves eternal peace!
Grand Elder-san is dead and all,
and Kuririn cannot come back.
Yeah.
Since people who have been resurrected
once by the Dragon Balls cannot return again.
It's all right!
The Dragon Balls of Namek can
resurrect people any number of times!
It's likely, so long as it isn't a natural
death, it can be done infinitely many times.
Then... then...!
When the day comes that your
Dragon Balls can again grant wishes, Dende,
Kuririn-san and Chaozu-san
and everyone can come back to life!
Father! Be sure to come back!
Let's call Kuririn-san and the others
back together with the Namek Dragon Balls!
Planet Namek here is just
moments away from exploding.
Where are you thinking of going?
No matter how you may struggle, you
can't survive in the emptiness of space!
Death is all that is waiting for you!
There's no time before the explosion!
You cannot get to your spaceship in time!
And Vegeta has wrecked
the spaceship I came in!
Saiyans really are monkey scum after all!
You cannot depart this planet!
You will perish, together with this planet!
Isn't it ironic?
You, who won in battle,
will die, while I will be spared!
T-That's because you do such impudent things
as share your energy with me, Freeza-sama!
I will live too. You'll see.
I'm stopping.
W-What was that?!
What do you mean, you're stopping?!
There ain't any reason to kill you,
now that you've started trembling.
You should go on living with the shock
you have undergone here, in tranquility.
M-Monkey scumbag!
So you're Freeza?
You're much more of a runt than I'd imagined.
So there's still another one of you scum left?
Fifty percent power, he says...
Whether those words are a
bluff, or whether they ain't,
all I can do is stake everything
on a times twenty Kaio-ken!
T-That was a close one! H-How?!
How does that lower life form
Saiyan have such awesome power?
This is the first time anyone has
done this much harm to my body!
You damn Saiyan!
That one...
...hurt.
It hurt!!
I-I'll just take this and...
H-He took that huge Genki Dama
head-on, and yet he's still alive!
I-It can't be!
Goku!!
Y-You're going to pay for that...
How dare you... How dare you?!
How dare you...?!
What?!
Dammit!
I'm stopping.
W-What was that?!
What do you mean, you're stopping?!
In reaction to your using
your 100 percent power,
you've passed your peak,
and your ki is falling rapidly.
I've begun to think that it's
useless to fight you any further.
I'm already feeling satisfied,
and your sense of pride is in tatters!
After all, someone has come
forward and surpassed you,
when no one in this world was
supposed to have been able to.
And what's more, that someone...
...was a mere Saiyan!
There ain't any reason to kill you,
now that you've started trembling.
You should go on living with the shock
you have undergone here, in tranquility.
I-I'm the greatest in the universe!
I am Freeza, Emperor of the Universe!
And so, you...
...you monkey scum...
You must die at my hand!!
You...
must be...
killed by me!!
You stupid bastard!!
Goku was completely
victorious in his battle with Freeza.
However, Planet Namek is
already moments from exploding!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
I-It's going to explode...
Planet Namek is going to explode...!
I ain't gonna be able to
get back to Earth! Damn it!
Freeza's spaceship, the last
thing we were depending on,
cannot fly at all now.
Son Goku is going to die!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Planet Namek's Great Explosion!!
Goku Disappears into Space."
F-Father!!
"Next time"
"Planet Namek's Great Explosion!!
Goku Disappears into Space"