Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
It's over... It's all over...
The Earth will be wiped out...!
Don't talk such foolishness, Gohan!
It's not like a Saiyan to give up, Gohan!
Father! W-Where are you?
The Next World.
B-But right now, I can only use one arm,
and I've got less than half of my ki left...
That's all right, you can win!
Believe in your own power, Gohan!
Right now, you're the
strongest one in the universe!
U-Understood, Father!
I'll do everything that I can!
If that's what you think, then avenge me.
Right!
Ka...
me...
ha...
"The Battle is Over...
Thank You, Son Goku."
Burn in hell!!
Th-This is going to be a problem! Get back!
Gohan...
The shape of the Earth is going to change!
Damn...
It's no use trying to run any more,
no matter where we go! Huh?
Once again, the ground is being torn apart!
This is the end! We're finished!
Everyone, farewell! Farewell!
I-It's a trick!
I'm going to expose this trick
at some point, you just watch!
Are you still asserting that?!
Cell has started his extermination!
This is the end of everything!
Cell... Cell is completely overpowering him!
How could it be that not even Gohan-san
can stand up against Cell's power?
The Earth really is going to be blown away!
G-Gohan-chan!
Gohan, stand up to him!
To think that you could hold out
this long in your shape–I'm amazed!
Sure enough, it's no use!
He's completely overwhelmed!
Now, this is the end.
I'm putting an end to this!
Your son can handle this, huh?
What's the matter?
You still haven't summoned
up your dormant power!
I-It's too much. I'm at my limit.
It turns out I am just the weakling,
crybaby, spoiled little Son Gohan after all.
I haven't changed at all
from the way I was so long ago.
You're wrong, Gohan!
Maybe you ain't aware of it, but up to now,
you've helped me many times!
If you get serious, and release your full power,
like you did those other times,
you can beat Cell for sure!
What are you mumbling there?!
Have you given up, and
are now saying your prayers?
Stick with it, Gohan!
Incredible!
Gohan's power...!
Gohan...
Miserable fool! I have attained
this ultimate, super-perfect form!
I will not be beaten by this level of power!
What?
It can't be...!
Th-This shouldn't be...!
I've got it!
Gohan, somewhere in your mind,
you're worried over how
much the Earth is being damaged!
Don't concern yourself with that!
You can use the Dragon Balls to put
any damage done back the way it was!
Go all-out on him!
B-But...!
Down! Down! Down to Hell with you!
Gohan...
Hold on, Gohan!
Piccolo!
He's gone to assist Gohan!
Cell! Take this!
You're a nuisance! Get lost!
Piccolo...!
Piccolo-san!
Damn...!
G–
Gohan...!
Piccolo...
No matter how you slice it, that was reckless!
There isn't anything we can do!
Piccolo knows that well enough.
T-Tenshinhan...?
Hold on!
Tenshinhan, don't tell me
you're thinking about doing it, too!
It's not in my nature to just sit
around like this doing nothing,
waiting for death to come.
What you're trying to say is
that you've got too much pride
as a martial artist, right?
That's right.
Even when it's hopeless,
I'd still rather face forward.
Kuririn, look after Trunks for us.
N-Not you too, Yamucha-san!
Let's go!
For the love of...!
They're all a bunch of daredevils.
No. 18, I'm glad I got to see
you one more time, before the end.
Bye, now.
Them, too?
What are those good-for-nothings trying to do?
Raise your ki higher, Gohan!
Your struggling is useless.
I'm going to finish this once and for all!
Kiko-ho!!
Yamucha-san! Tenshinhan-san! Kuririn-san!
Gohan! Raise your ki even higher!
You can beat him!
Father!
You pesky flies!
Th-They're all going to...
Is this how badly you
want to rush to your deaths?
In that case, I'll give you your wish!
Piccolo-san!
Dammit!
Gohan... I'm not going to let you die alone!
You're the first one who
ever spoke to me decently.
Why am I even getting up again?
When I could just find peace by dying here?
In the past, I would have
already long-since given up!
It must have been Goku and
Gohan that made me act this way.
Yep, I've got you to blame
for this, both father and son.
I've come to use Goku as a target for myself
as I've walked the path of the martial artist.
The reason I am who
I am now is because of Goku.
Now that I've let Goku die like he has,
I cannot allow his son Gohan
to die right before my eyes as well!
Goku, Gohan is incredible.
He's just what we would
expect of any son of yours.
And I love the both of you.
Dammit...! I'm not afraid of him!
Do not interfere, small fry!
Gohan! Raise your ki higher!
You're going to win this!
You're all so impudent, one right after the next!
No matter how much trash like
you comes together, it's no use!
Away with you!
It's no use!
The Earth will be blown away!
Damn...
G-Gohan... Is this where it ends?
Sorry, Goku. We can't do
anything more at our power.
W-We're sorry.
Gohan-san!
There's no way Gohan-chan can lose!
There ain't no way my Gohan-chan can lose!
That's right!
Gohan is the son of Son Goku!
There's no way he's losin'!
Withstand him. Withstand him, Gohan!
Father...!
You still aren't using all of your power!
Let your power erupt!
Farewell!
Vegeta?!
Now!!
What?!
Th-This can't be–!
I-It's vanished...!
Cell's ki has completely vanished...!
H-He's finally been defeated, right?
Somehow or other, that's the way it looks...
He did it... Gohan finally
beat that Cell bastard...!
He did it! He did it! Gohan-chan did it!
It's finally come to a conclusion, huh?
Yeah.
Well done, Gohan!
At last... at long last, Cell is defeated.
The battle is over, and the
Earth has been narrowly saved.
Thank you, Son Goku. And... farewell.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Cell has been beaten. Now we
have to hurry and bring Trunks,
and everybody else killed by Cell, back to life.
How can you be so casual about that, Goku?
As it stands, you can't come back to life!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"I'm Going to Train In the Next World!!
A Smile at Parting."
Oh, no... Father, what am
I supposed to tell Mother?
"Next time"
"I'm Going to Train In the Next World!!
A Smile at Parting"