Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
The power of the Saiyans who had
arrived on Earth was overwhelming.
Yamucha...
Chaozu...
and Tenshinhan had
been defeated in succession.
However, Son Goku, upon whom
everyone was hoping, had not yet arrived.
Moment by moment, Piccolo and
the others' deaths were drawing nearer.
However, just then...
Wait!
Very well. We will wait
until Kakarrot gets here.
However, only for three hours.
We won't wait any longer than that.
"An Intense Three-Hour Delay!
The Kinto Un Bullet-Express."
W-Why do we have to wait for Kakarrot?!
Because he is a traitor to us Saiyans.
We have to punish traitors.
We're going to kill his son and his friends...
...right before his eyes.
After that, we're going to
deal with him, nice and slow.
We're going to make him aware of just
how powerless he is, as he writhes in agony.
And today, after another three or four hours...
...we should be able to put on
a magnificent, hellish show for him.
I get it! So that's why! That sounds great!
That's all assuming that he
gets here in the next three hours.
I'll leave Kakarrot to you,
but please let me take those other three!
Do as you like. However,
do it after we get the Namekian
to tell us about the Dragon Balls.
I sure hope that Kakarrot does come!
Kuririn-san...
Dammit, what are you doing, Goku?
Has he really come back to life?
Say, at this point, what if we ran away?
There's no way we can win.
This is no time to be stubborn!
Fool! They plan on wiping
out all of humanity in any case.
Even if you run away
now, you'll end up the same.
D-Dammit! Please, Goku, get here!
Show us how much
stronger than them you've become!
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
Not yet?
Guys! Hang in there a little longer!
Piccolo, Goku is sure to be
here in the next three hours, right?
Who knows?
Think of some way to
inflict some damage on them,
however little, before Son Goku gets here.
Regardless of how much power
Goku may have gained at Kaio's place,
his chances of fighting both of
them and winning are next to impossible.
We've made some tremendous enemies here.
If only I... I had been more
reliable earlier, Tenshinhan-san...
...might not have had to die...
That's right!
Who knew you were such a coward?!
Piccolo, be reasonable.
Gohan is still only five years old.
Ordinarily, he'd be in kindergarten right now.
It's miraculous that he's even here, isn't it?
Kuririn-san...
Gohan, I thought I had
raised you up to be a man.
Piccolo-san!
P-Please re-train me for the next three hours!
Don't act like a spoiled child!
I've got no time for cowards!
Get out of here, now!
P-Piccolo-san!
P-Piccolo!
Gohan, I've taught you everything I know.
Gohan, come back! You've got to show
Goku how big and strong you've grown!
Gohan!
Kid!
You trying to run away?!
Well, that would be the smart thing to do.
W-Who's running away?!
I just have to go pee!
And if you guys are going
to go home, now is your chance.
What was that? I didn't hear you.
Your momma's belly-button sticks out!
That brat! H-How...
How did you know my
mommy's belly-button sticks out?!
The mysterious energy that had
enveloped the battleground has disappeared,
as though it were never there,
which has allowed us to get closer,
so we are going to try to get
in as close to the scene as we can.
What in the world could be
happening? I am unaware of the details,
but could it be that
they have called a time-out?
I-In any event, it's certain
that the intense fighting
that was going on earlier is not occurring now.
Could they be taking a break?
What could this be?
I don't care what it is.
If they can buy even one minute–
one second of time to let Goku come back,
nothing could work to our advantage better.
I guess so. I wonder if
Son-kun will get back during this time.
On the other hand,
if Piccolo gets killed,
Kami-sama dies too, right?
What happens to our world if that happens?!
Isn't it obvious?
Either way, if Son-kun and the
others don't defeat those Saiyans...
...all of us are going to be killed.
Goku! Get here quick and defeat them!
If I have to die anyway,
I wish I could have collected
more gals' panties before I went.
Frankly, that's not possible.
Then there's no way they can win?!
I'm saying that there aren't
any gals that are stupid enough
to let their panties be stolen by you.
–Why, you jerk...
–Gohan!
Chichi, have you come around? Are you okay?
Pa!
W-Where's Gohan-chan?
Relax.
He's still all right.
Gohan-chan!
He's doin' fine.
We have to hurry and save him!
We can't! That's nowhere
that we can get close to!
All we can do is wait here.
Gohan-chan...
I'm going to go have a little fun.
I can't just sit still here
for three hours, after all.
Suit yourself. But Nappa,
don't go overdoing it, now.
Why not?
For the sake of the hellish show
we're going to have in three hours.
That's Vegeta for you!
It'll be fine, don't worry about it!
One of the Saiyans has
taken to the skies by himself!
Where exactly is he planning to go?
I-It appears that he is
coming toward our direction!
He is rapidly approaching us!
G-Get us out of here!
H-He's chasing after us!
H-Here he comes!
Run!
You guys are a blight! Away with you!
G-Gohan-chan...
Ch-Chichi!
So this planet has this
sort of military, does it?
This should be a good time killer.
I thought these guys would be a little
more effective, but they're all worthless.
Beat it!
You guys were a waste of my time.
By the way, hasn't Goku come by the way yet?
No matter how funny my
jokes are, this is no time for laughs.
The fate of the Earth is at stake!
Hurry, Son Goku!
I see it!
Just a little farther!
Goku's presence?!
Yeah! He is getting close!
He just might be in time!
Another two hours, huh?
You know, this planet Earth here
is a more wondrous
world than any I've seen before.
We'll be able to sell this one for a lot!
So this is the level of people it has, huh?
One more hour.
Kakarrot hasn't just lost
his nerve and run away, right?
Go for broke....
Looks like that's all we can do.
He's arrived! Son Goku has arrived!
Oh, Kami-sama! Hurry!
The Serpentine Road has ended!
That was fast! That was wonderfully fast!
Now then, there are only ten minutes left.
Shall I finish up with a little more fun?
Scream! Suffer! Writhe in agony!
You'd only live until tonight anyhow.
We're going to turn all of
you on Earth into space dust.
And the most hellish show still awaits.
There are two powerful ki,
separated from each other.
What's going on?
And so, with Goku still absent,
the three hours had passed.
Time.
Damn!
Looks like waiting for him didn't do any good.
He's still not here?
That coward Kakarrot did not come.
F-Father is not a coward!
Dammit! Why isn't he here?!
Son Goku...
Now then, to take my time in making you hurt...
It's too bad I couldn't
show this to Kakarrot, though.
It's almost time when I could die, too...
Dammit, I feel like a suicide trooper!
There's only one possibility for us to beat him.
Of course, that's only if
everything goes well. Listen up.
First, Kuririn, you go
all-out to draw his attention.
And then I will find an opening
to grab his tail, a Saiyan's weak point.
R-Right...
Once his power fails him, and he can't move,
Gohan, you'll call up all of
your power and rush him. Got that?
Yes. It'll be okay. I won't run away this time.
Of course you won't. Remember that
the fate of the Earth rests in your hands!
All right!
Awesome! That's Piccolo for you!
I'm starting to see a little light here.
We just might win!
Gohan, believe in yourself!
When you set your mind to it,
your power is even greater than mine.
All right!
Goku!
Kami-sama!
Hurry and grab hold!
You're on!
T-That kid! He really did
come back from Kaio-sama's place!
Okay, I'm off!
My training went great!
–We're counting on you!
–Good luck, Son Goku!
Guys!
Gohan!
Please be alive!
Here he comes! Son Goku is quite tired.
Hey!
Karin-sama!
Here are the last two senzu beans!
Thank you!
These will be a great help!
We're all counting on you!
I'll eat one of them right now...
All right, I'm at full health!
Kinto Un!
It's been a long time, huh?!
I could sure use your help!
There are some incredible ki
gathered all together! That way!
Hurry, Goku!
We're counting on you, Goku!
As fast as you can!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Way to go, Piccolo! Pull out that Saiyan's tail!
Hell of a miscalculation, huh?
Did you think we would leave
our weak spot untrained forever?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Leave it to Me!
Gohan's Great Burst of Anger."
Piccolo-san, run!
I'll stop him one way or
another until Father gets here!
"Next time"
"Leave it to Me!
Gohan's Great Burst of Anger"