Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Cell, an extraordinary monster
who has come from the future,
continues his growth!
Cell is an Artificial Human,
created by Doctor Gero's computer,
from the assembled cells of
Goku, Vegeta, Freeza, and others.
When I merge with No. 17 and No. 18,
I will become my perfect form,
with power to defy the imagination!
For that reason, I came from the future!
I will acquire No. 18 and No. 17 no matter what!
No matter how you may try to prevent
me from becoming my perfect form,
it will come to nothing!
Not as long as the only
one that can hope to fight
against No. 17 and No. 18 is Piccolo!
Taiyo-ken!
Ah, dammit!
Damn!
Will it indeed be possible
to frustrate Cell's scheme?
"The Secret of Cell's Birth!
What Lies Below the Laboratory?"
...and that's how it stands.
In order to merge with No. 17 and No. 18
and become his perfect form,
he's come from the future.
What a fix.
So we have to find that Cell guy from
earlier somehow and take him down.
But can we seek him out?
Now that he knows of Piccolo-san's
unexpectedly great strength,
won't he just assault other people
while keeping his ki suppressed?
If we don't prevent Cell,
No. 17 and No. 18 from merging,
no matter the cost, things will get unbearable!
And not just for Earth.
It will be terrible for all
the worlds in the universe!
Don't forget that he has
Freeza and his father's blood
running through him as well!
My blood too!
You've got nothing but clumsy strategies!
If he wants to merge
with them, then let him!
It'll reduce the number of opponents
we have to beat and save us some trouble.
I don't care what becomes of my enemy!
I'll just kill them anyhow!
Don't take it so lightly, Vegeta!
If they merge,
then as utterly unmanageable
as No. 17 and the others were,
he'll far surpass even them!
Don't you use that big-shot tone with me!
Do you want to be wiped out
before the Artificial Humans are?!
Hmph! I will go beyond, count on it!
Beyond even Super Saiyan!
Go beyond even Super Saiyan?!
Kakarrot will likely try to do the same.
That's for sure!
I am going to do this my own way!
You all do whatever you wish among yourselves!
Go beyond Super Saiyan, he said...
Beyond the terrifying
strength of a Super Saiyan...
Was he serious? Is such a thing possible?
Hey, Trunks...
It would be meaningless to take your
time machine back a little into the past
and destroy No. 17 and such, right?
Yes. It would probably be fine
for the future of that dimension,
but it wouldn't relate to this dimension.
Well, that means it wouldn't do any
good to go to Doctor Gero's laboratory now
and destroy that unfinished Cell, huh?
No, let's destroy him.
At the very least, Cell won't be able to
be born in the future of this dimension.
All right, you guys go to the laboratory.
I'm going to look around
the area here some more.
Right.
I'll remain here too.
Well, if it doesn't look
like you're going to find Cell,
come to the Kame House.
By watching the TV news, we might
be able to get a hold of his location.
Okay, got it.
Well then...
Go beyond even Super Saiyan?
I've never even thought of such a thing!
Certainly not.
But it could be possible, right?
Knowing Vegeta and Goku...
Gohan-chan!
Gohan-chan, it's your mother!
Ah? Gohan-chan!
So you're out here studyin', are you?
Commendable, commendable!
Here, have a snack.
Your studies are makin' progress here!
I really must have you become
a great scholar, Gohan-chan.
That's what I've been dreamin' of.
Well, keep studyin' hard!
Right!
Forgive me, Mother.
What I really want to do
is grow strong like Father,
and be of service to everyone!
Hmm, "the son of a frog is a frog," indeed.
So cold!
Is there really anything
under this laboratory anyhow?
How should we search for it?
Kuririn-san, please stand back a moment.
Kuririn-san!
Eh? What is it?
Kuririn-san, this is probably it!
–You're right.
–Well, let's go see!
Okay!
Be careful.
Right.
Rotten piece of crap!
This is that computer, huh?!
Kuririn-san, please look at this!
This is surely what will become Cell!
Dammit, this is what has all the cells
of the martial arts masters gathered within it?
Me and Goku must be included in there!
Just looking at it disgusts me!
I-In time, this will become a larva...
...shed its skin, and become Cell!
And then after that, he will
suck out the life energy of others
as he approaches his perfect form!
All of it under instruction from this computer.
Trunks, let's destroy this whole
underground laboratory right now!
W-Wait, just a minute!
They're plans!
What are they plans for? That Cell guy?
No, it has "No. 17" written here.
No. 17?
His, huh?
I-If I have Mom look at these, she just might
be able to catch on to a
weakness in No. 17, Kuririn-san!
Yeah! That's a good idea!
Say, are there any more?
Maybe the ones for Cell, or...
The rest of this...
...doesn't look like it would be of any use.
All right, then let's bring
down this underground laboratory!
Right!
Because of you, we in the future have suffered!
Take this!
Kuririn-san, let's get out of here, quick!
Okay!
Now to finish you off, you bastard!
We did it, Trunks!
Finding No. 17's plans in there
was an unexpected harvest, wasn't it?
Yes!
Um, Kuririn-san, would you take
these plans to where my mom is for me?
Huh? You're not coming with me?
I want to go try training together with my dad.
If he really can go beyond
being a Super Saiyan, then I...
That's fine, but...
well, he's your father, so I don't
want to say anything bad, but...
I don't think Vegeta will
let you do anything with him.
For my part, I don't really want to do this either.
However, even Dad has to know
that by training while
sparring against each other,
we'll grow a lot faster
than we will by ourselves.
All right, I get you.
You train real hard, now!
Please see this through.
Hang in there!
Right!
This is unmistakably the work of Cell.
So then his plan is to attack
people for their life energy,
and store it up for himself!
Not much time has passed since
this happened, he must still be nearby.
Why don't we go check?
Do you sense anything?
N-No...
Damn...
Over there!
It's slight, but there's a disturbance
in ki coming from over there!
You're right!
That city!
Damn, we're too late! He's a quick one!
T-There's nothing we can do like this!
Cell feels our ki, and quickly runs away.
And if we hold our ki, we can't go very fast!
Useless, useless!
While they're prowling around down there,
I think I'll go get my next meal!
So you're saying you
want us to find a weakness
in No. 17 and the others with these plans,
in order to prevent Cell
from merging with them.
These are incredible.
There's quite a few things
here not even I understand.
What a shame. If only Doctor Gero
had applied his genius a better way,
the world could be at peace.
From a human base,
he's been almost entirely remodeled
with just organic components.
In which case, at a cellular level,
uniting the two is a definite possibility!
I won't know until I look over these thoroughly,
but these sparsely-used, small devices
here may be an unexpected weakness.
We'll start investigating
these right away, Kuririn-kun.
Right! If you would be so kind!
Are we there yet, No. 16?
Is it still a long way to Son Goku's house?
Almost there.
Seeking his perfect form,
the monster Cell attacks
one person after another!
Can his merging with No. 17
and No. 18 really be prevented?
And what of Goku?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
I know I've worried you all,
but I'm all right now.
Now we have to do something about Cell, quick!
Goku-sa! You've just recovered,
and you want to fight already?!
You've gotta be kiddin' me!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Goku Awakens to Battle!
Go Beyond Super Saiyan!!"
Hooray! Father is all better!
"Next time"
"Goku Awakens to Battle!
Go Beyond Super Saiyan!!"