The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Vegeta's life was shattered in vain as he
put his life on the line challenging Majin Boo.
And Babidi, who had
been cut in half by Piccolo,
was revived by Boo, and his anger set ablaze.
That green guy and those two runts!
You're absolutely going to pay for this!
Will the Earth be turned to hell by Majin Boo?
"The Struggle of Videl and the Others!
Find the Dragon Balls."
Where could Gohan and Goten have gone off to?
Auntie, rather than these Dragon Ball things,
we should first be searching for
Gohan and the others, shouldn't we?
Hmm, Bulma-san?
We checked there,
but no one was around, right?
There's no way for us to look for them past that.
For my part, I'm not unconcerned
about Vegeta and Trunks myself.
Especially since Vegeta was acting so strangely.
Goku is together with them,
so I think they're okay.
We've already gathered six of the Dragon Balls.
Once we get the last one...
Bulma-san, don't tell me
you're thinkin' that Gohan
and the others are already dead, are you?
That we can have the Dragon
Balls bring them back to life?
No, that's not what I'm thinking...
As long as we don't know where everyone is,
I think that first we should bring
back to life all those spectators...
...that were killed as a result of Vegeta.
I... feel so sorry for them...
Let's hurry up findin' the Dragon Balls then.
Where's the last one at?
Let's see...
Can we really bring everyone
back to life with these balls?
If we appeal to Shen Long,
he will grant us any three wishes.
Yamucha, just keep going
straight for the last Dragon Ball!
Roger.
Yamucha, it's around here! What's beneath us?
Looks like it's the island in
the very middle of this lake.
It's there, no doubt about it. Land there!
Okay!
Yamucha! Can't you land
any better than that?!
Sorry, sorry! This wasn't
a very good place for it!
Old man! What are you doing?!
This wasn't my fault!
I just automatically slanted this way!
If you want to complain, talk to Yamucha!
Pafu-pafu-pafu!
Just like a real human!
Ah! My neck!
Why, you dirty old man!
Oh, please, no...!
I'm gonna be crushed!
But that was the tops! The tops!
Things're gettin' terrible again, huh?
Yeah. Aren't there any more senzu?
We gave the last three
of 'em to Goku, y'know!
You guys're gettin' too greedy!
Just like always, you
know the wrong thing to say.
Kuririn, hang in there tough!
I'm gonna hold off here
an' see how things go.
You shut up! You're no use to anyone,
so just be quiet! Let's go, Piccolo.
We've been expecting you.
Are those two all right?
Are injuries severe?
They're not injured. Vegeta only
did enough to knock them out,
so it shouldn't be too serious.
Let them sleep for a bit inside.
That's easy enough. Popo?
Got it.
Majin Boo... A fearsome
devil has come back to life.
Mm. At this point now, those
two are our only slim hope.
Dende! Do you know
what's happened to Goku?
You needn't worry about
the late Goku-san dying again.
I guess that's right, huh?
However, Goku-san seems
to have taken great damage.
What about Majin Boo and Madoshi Babidi?
Their ki, filled with evil,
grows greater and greater.
And Gohan?
Unfortunately, I cannot feel him.
I see.
Dende, can you feel Kaioshin-sama's ki?
Piccolo-san, you must be
able to feel it too, right?
Yeah. It's become weak,
but I can definitely feel Kaioshin-sama's ki.
Yes. Piccolo-san, what's going
to happen to the Earth now?
If you, the Kami over the Earth can't tell,
there's no reason I should be able to!
Sorry...
Even Kaioshin-sama had this
much difficulty against this enemy.
You have to know that our chances
of winning against them are very slim.
I wonder what's going to happen now.
Laid the two down to sleep. They fine soon.
Can't fight if hungry. Meal is ready. Quickly!
Be my guest.
Kaioshin-sama,
is there nothing more I can do but
stake everything on those two little ones?
Gohan-san... Please be alive...
We will need your power...
to defeat Majin Boo...
Stop!
Why didn't you avoid that?!
Here it is!
Bulma! Hang in there!
Isn't anyone going to help her?
Auntie! Hang in there!
Who is she calling Auntie? How rude!
What are you doing?!
Bulma!
You dummy! You can't eat that! You dummy!
Ah! Thief! Thief! Thief!!
Take this!
Gotcha!
Yamucha, you have to
take responsibility for this!
Dive in after and chase it down!
Right, right!
Dive from up here?!
This suit was kind of expensive, you know!
You can always take it off!
The trunks I'm wearing
today are awful flashy though...
Come on! It's getting away, you know!
I think I've come down with a cold today...!
No. 18?
I don't handle water very well.
You know that, don't you?
This is no time to be saying that,
already! Chichi-san, please?
All right!
Videl-san! You're gonna be
Gohan's bride! Don't go gettin' hurt!
We're counting on this, Four-Star-Ball!
Me too!
Flashy trunks be damned!
If I don't go now, I'm not a man!
See here, Videl-san's gonna be
Gohan's bride! Keep your paws off!
Cut it out! Don't embarrass me any further!
I've got a cold! A cold!
Here you go!
Good luck, there!
Ah! Muten Roshi-sama!
Pee-yew!
Let's get over our colds quickly!
Turtle Hermit, thanks.
That's our Muten Roshi!
He's not just a dirty old man!
Boo! Boo! Turn to the left!
O-Or you can go right, too, just turn!
Damn... Vegeta took the last remaining senzu.
He knocked me out and went off
alone to where Majin Boo is, didn't he?
I can feel Majin Boo's ki,
but Vegeta's ki ain't there!
Did he get beaten?
I can't feel Gohan's ki either.
Piccolo and Kuririn are alive.
They must have been returned
from stone back to normal.
Those two might know what's been going on!
How long do you suppose
until the two pee-wees wake up?
Let's see, probably another hour or so.
I can't stand this. Both
Vegeta and Gohan are dead.
I weep for them!
This is the worst!
We don't know what happened to Goku, at all.
Say, Dende–or rather,
Kami-sama, would it be okay
if I brought everyone in my family here?
I guess that would be wrong, huh?
Us only choosing to save our own folks.
–What about that?
–You're Kami. Use your own judgement.
I don't think I would mind.
After all, it's because of everyone
that we have the Earth here now.
It's the least I can do.
Thank you! I'll go and call them now!
Th-That ki! It's...!
Yo!
Goku! Then you survived?!
You might say I survived,
but I'm still dead, you know!
I guess so! You still have the halo and all!
Kuririn, I came to hear what happened.
What happened yourself?!
You're pretty banged up!
I will heal you, Goku-san!
Yeah, Dende, if you would!
Piccolo, now that Goku has come,
our hopes for fighting Majin Boo
have just gotten greater, haven't they?
Goku's heavily damaged body is
healed through Dende's mysterious power.
Are there any means left for Goku
and the others to defeat Majin Boo?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
If we're gonna defeat Majin Boo,
we'll have to use Fusion.
It's a move where two similar folks
become one, with awesome power!
Goten and Trunks,
power and size about identical.
Can they do Fusion?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Enormous Hope!! A New Finishing
Technique for the Little Squirts."
Terrific! Knowing those two,
I'm sure they can do it!
"Next time"
"Enormous Hope!! A New Finishing
Technique for the Little Squirts"