The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Having been spat upon by Dabura,
King of the World of Darkness,
Kuririn and Piccolo have
utterly turned to stone!
In order to return them to normal,
Goku and the others
enter into the spaceship.
They're here! They're here!
They really are simple fools, aren't they?!
They have entered our trap.
Madoshi Babidi's plan is to gather
the greatest energy in the world,
in order to revive Majin Boo, who
was sealed up in the distant past.
Babidi-sama is on the very bottom floor.
Unless you pass through the various Stages,
and defeat each of the
warriors that come out,
you cannot proceed downward.
Goku and the others have made their
way inside Babidi's mysterious spaceship.
Will they be able to defeat
the warriors who will appear
and reach Babidi's command center?
The first Stage has begun!
"Don't Toy With Me!!
Vegeta's Breakthrough First Strike of Fury."
Die!
You're better than I thought!
But that's as far as this goes!
See? Just as I said.
Vegeta alone will be plenty for this.
Over here, fool.
Incredible...
Just what we expect of Vegeta-san.
He's a lot more intense than before.
Vegeta has kept up his training as well, huh?
What is that Puipui doing?
Doesn't he know that unless
he inflicts damage on those men,
we can't gather the energy
we need to revive Majin Boo?
Oh, this is where it begins.
It appears that Puipui had
left his guard down somewhat.
What's the matter? Is that all?
What?
Damn you!
Hey! Where is it that Puipui is accustomed to?
The heavy gravity planet Zun.
Hmm, Planet Zun, eh? Okay!
Papparapa!
Wh-What? What's happened? Where are we?
This is the work of Babidi.
He has changed the room with his magic...
probably to a place that benefits his fighter.
That's really something.
But Goku-san, now Vegeta-san is...
Well, let's just watch.
You fool! This is as far as you go!
This is Planet Zun!
I was raised on this planet!
The gravity here is ten times that of Earth!
You guys can't endure this!
What about it? In only ten times
normal gravity, I don't feel a thing.
Wha–
You lie! I know you're bluffing!
You'll know whether
I'm bluffing or not soon enough.
Impossible! Die!
I told you I wasn't bluffing, didn't I?
Dammit!
He did it!
Hmph, that Babidi creep
sent me a worthless opponent!
Look! There's a hole
opening up to let us go down.
It's like an elevator, isn't it?
This is like a video game!
An insignificant game!
Hey! Let's go, Kaioshin-sama!
I-It can't be...! To think that they're so...!
Hey, this is the same kind of
room as the last one, ain't it?
Yeah, but the room will change
with magic, like it did before, won't it?
What are guys with that
kind of power doing on Earth?
Indeed. 300 years ago,
when we investigated here,
there weren't any guys such as these.
Dammit...
However, at that level,
there is no cause for worry.
There are still many Stages left,
And if the worst comes to pass,
I am still here for you, am I not?
Recess, huh? I wonder what's goin' on.
Wh-What is it?
Wh-What's the matter, Chichi?
Where's Goten-chan?
What's happened to Goten-chan?!
Goten-chan's gone off somewhere!
Huh? Now that you mention it,
we haven't seen him in a while, huh?
Hmm, and Trunks as well.
Once the Junior Division was over,
we'd agreed to watch the matches together.
You don't think the shock of
Trunks winnin' the final round
made him run off somewhere?
You thinkin' maybe he's gone home?
Say, Trunks-kun...
I'm getting thirsty, let's take a break!
Yeah, okay.
This is pretty tiring business, huh?
The two of us posing as one person.
That way! That way!
This way! This way!
Ah, right. I have to tell Contestant
Mighty Mask about this as well.
This way! This way!
In here, in here!
All right, no one else is in here!
There he is.
Trunks-kun, hurry and get down!
Just a second!
Don't rush me!
Hm? Children's voices?
Right, right, pardon me!
Indeed, how bothersome...
Ah, I'm so busy, so busy!
Unbelievable, how everyone
litters like this! I declare!
Er, I'm in a bit of a hurry myself...
Yea! Juice, juice! Juice...
Um... this one!
Of all the...
Contestant Mighty Mask!
Huh? You two... Trunks-kun
and Goten-kun, isn't it?
Y-Yes!
Only participating contestants are
supposed to come in here, you know.
Ah, um, we were hoping to
get Mister Satan's autograph.
That's right! And juice.
Hmm, well, okay.
You two had such high marks
in the Junior Division, after all.
So, where's Contestant Mighty Mask?
I'm sure he came into this room.
Isn't this Contestant Mighty Mask's?
Where could he have gone?
No, uh, I mean...
Mighty Mask-san?! Where are you?
Oh, he's in the shower?
Well then, Mighty Mask-san!
No! No, no!
He'll be very angry with
you if you peep in on him!
Mm? Ah, right!
Masked contestants hate having people
see their real face more than anything.
Gotcha, gotcha.
Well, Mighty Mask-san!
Mighty-san!
Wh-What is it?
At last. We don't know for sure
when the Tournament will begin again,
so please don't go outside, okay?
Yeah, got it.
That'll do it.
Now then, don't you two wander
around here too much, okay?
Now it's my turn to fight.
So, I wonder what kind
of guy will be coming out.
I sure hope he's impossibly strong!
Babidi-sama, which
warrior shall we send to Stage 2?
I'll make it Yakon.
Yakon! You're going to
use up Yakon on Stage 2?!
We must not take these
earthlings too lightly, I think.
See how Puipui inflicted
absolutely no damage at all on them?
I see. However, with Yakon as their opponent,
they will all be defeated at once,
and there will be
nothing left for me to enjoy.
Shouldn't your first priority right
now be that of awakening Majin Boo
from his long sleep,
rather than enjoying yourself?
Y-Yes! My humble apologies!
Stage 2 is Yakon! Relay that!
Yakon-sama!
Yakon!
Sorry to keep you waiting
so long! It's your turn now.
Fight to your heart's content!
Yes, Babidi-sama...
Hey! Ready yet? Hurry up and come on out!
This is senseless!
Why don't we knock our way through
the floor and head down there all at once?
You must not!
As I said before, if we
provide any strong shock,
then even if he's not at
full power, Majin Boo might...
Hmph, at this rate, how do we know
that Majin Boo isn't all that great either?
The same way that Dabura scum isn't.
Dabura isn't all that great?
How do you mean?
I'm saying that Dabura doesn't
seem to be the fearsome scumbag
you guys make him out to be.
Based on what we saw of
his attacks outside earlier,
as long as we're careful of his
saliva, we could have taken him.
There's no way to explain Kibit being
beaten, except that he bungled it.
I-Is this true, Goku-san?
Mm-hmm. Well, even supposing
that wasn't his full power,
a little while ago, we would
have thought him a terrifying foe.
Seven years ago, there
was this guy named Cell.
He probably has the same strength as him.
I-I can't believe it. Is this Super
Saiyan thing really that strong?
Come to think of it,
it was considerably difficult to
contain Gohan-san's movement
when he had turned Super Saiyan...
Was even that still not their full power?
Hey! Hurry it up, already!
This time it's my turn, you know!
What do we have here?
Yakon! Be sure to put away all
three of them this time for me!
Th-This is...!
The demonic beast, Yakon,
appears at the second Stage.
So, we will now able to see
Son Goku fight after such a long time!
Stay sharp, Goku!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Heh-heh, I ain't fought in the
Lower Realm in a long time, huh?
Hu-uh? I went from
Super Saiyan back to normal!
The demonic beast Yakon
devoured your light energy!
However strong you may be,
Goku-san, you can't take him alone!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Goku's Power Wide Open!!
Blow Away Yakon."
Incredible! Father's ki just surged!
"Next time"
"Goku's Power Wide Open!!
Blow Away Yakon"