The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
With only a day's training, Gohan
had become able to wield the Z-Sword.
In order to ascertain its sharpness,
he tried testing the blade. However...
I-Impossibly, rather than cutting through,
the Z-Sword itself was instead broken!
A Kaioshin from fifteen generations past
appeared before a
crestfallen Gohan and the others.
He, who had been sealed within the Z-Sword,
said he was able to draw out a
person's power beyond their limits.
Elsewhere, having mastered the Fusion Pose,
Goten and Trunks have finally
decided to test out their Fusion.
"Birth of a Superhuman Warrior!!
His Name is Gotenks."
Fusion! Fusion!
Hey!
Hey everyone, I heard the pee-wees
are about to try out their Fusion!
Then the special training is finally over?
Let's go see!
You're going?
Upon merging, they're supposed to
have an enormous ki, and there'd be trouble
if the palace were damaged,
so they said they're doing it out front.
Once they successfully merge, they're
supposed to become some wildly strong warrior,
but how do you suppose they'll look?
Hmm, well, those two little guys
resemble each other quite a bit,
so I don't guess they'll
change all that much.
Just think if they became
some predisposed macho man!
Their name... What'll happen to
their name, once they're done mergin'?
They're Goten and Trunks, so...
Gotenks? Or will it be Trunten?
Naw, either way, it's a deranged name, huh?
What are you saying?
They'll only be merged for around thirty
minutes, so a name doesn't matter, does it?
But, won't we have trouble tryin' to call him?
They're doing it, they're doing it!
Trunks, hold your ki down just a bit more.
This is tough. Like this?
All right! Your two ki
have become utterly identical!
Now then, start the Fusion!
Here it comes!
Fusion–
Ha!!
You're kidding!
Incredible!
–Hey...
–Is that... right?
Th-They can, in fact,
return back to normal, right?
I-I can't love that!
Is that really the guy Goku said
might be able to overcome Majin Boo?
He doesn't look like it,
but that must be it, huh?
S-So that's it! Oh, Goku!
An eye for an eye, and a
fatso for a fatso, is that it?
Looks like he's about
to start doing something.
He's started running!
That is one complete
and utter failed product.
Hey!
I-I knew it.
During the "–sion" pose just now,
Trunks had his fingers sticking out!
During this point, your hands must be in fists.
Okay? You got that?
All right, let's do it over once again!
What are you doing?!
Hurry up and return to normal, would you?!
How do I return to normal?
There's no use. Shall we wait
for thirty minutes to go by, then?
How strange! You're neither
Trunks nor Goten, are you?
Why did your clothes come out that way?
Say, what happened to Goten-kun?
Do you have a name?
Gotenks.
See? It's Gotenks after all!
It's almost thirty mintues.
–Trunks!
–Goten!
D-Did we do it?
I don't know.
Hey, what did that feel like, merging?
Don't you remember much about it?
Mm-mm.
Still, you really were able to merge!
Now we see light of hope!
Sorry, but I'd like to have you save your
talk until after they've defeated Majin Boo.
Right now, we don't have
even a moment to spare!
All right, one more time.
Okay, begin.
Fusion Ha!!
Surely a mistake, huh?
You can tell by one look.
He hasn't done anything yet,
and already he's exhausted.
This time, during the "Ha,"
your fingers were a bit off.
Let's do it again...
...in another thirty minutes...
All right, begin.
Fusion Ha!!
That was perfect! He's being born!
The warrior who will defeat Majin Boo!
W-What?!
W-What a storm of a ki!
Th-They've done it! They've succeeded!
Incredible, incredible!
I can't really tell, but
they must be extraordinary.
Lookin' at them, they
do seem pretty awesome.
What are you saying?
Even I can tell at least that much!
Incredible! He really has an incredible ki!
Okay, this finally turned out right.
Now, in another thirty minutes,
we'll finally have you
achieve this as Super Saiyans.
Aren't you underrating me?
What?
I'm enough to defeat Majin Boo just as I am!
Y-You moron! What are you talking about?!
You don't know anything
about how frightful Majin Boo is!
No matter how incredible you may say
you are, at your level, it's still impossible!
There is absolutely no way
you can prevail against Majin Boo!
Don't think that lightly of me! Okay, fine!
I'll show you right now!
Majin Boo's body, that is!
W-Wait! Trunten!
Er, Gotenks.
This way, huh? Fairly close-by.
In that case, give me thirty
minutes and I'll defeat him
and return in time to
give back plenty of change!
What speed!
Y-You miserable fool!
If you get killed now, everything
will have been wiped out!
H-He was sure an overbearing fellow,
but you never know, he may
just be able to defeat Majin Boo!
Yeah! He really did
seem sure of himself, huh?
Are you awakening, Goku-san?
Kaioshin-sama...
How's Gohan? Has his
power-up been finished yet?
Good grief!
It has only been two hours.
This ceremony takes five hours,
so there should be another three hours left.
Hey, Gohan, hang in there!
Come on, Father!
Thinking you don't have
anything to do with this...
You're not getting away!
Majin Boo!
Gotcha, gotcha! Yea! Yea! Yea!! Yea!
Help me!
H-Help me!
What's this?
I-I'm gonna drown!
Thank you so much!
–M-M-M-Majin Boo!
–I hate you.
You're quite the tough punk!
That was simply my way of saying hello.
I didn't think it would
have any effect myself.
Who are you?!
Hmph! Since you're going
to be dying here anyway,
there's no point in me
introducing myself, is there?
Die?
Sorry, but I don't have time
to waste chit-chatting with you.
I'm going to have to
put you away lickety-split!
Why, you...
Here goes!
Take this!
Hmph! Fatty! Call yourself a
Majin and that's all you've got?
Oh, no! I said I was going to
show them his body before I left,
and now I've vaporized it!
Well, nothing I can do about that now, huh?
What?!
You called me a fatty, huh? Now I'm mad!
In that case, what are
you going to do about it?
Gonna kill you!
Sheesh.
Too slow!
I-Impossible! I should have dodged him!
You mean that in that instant,
he was able to read my movement?
Now die!
Majin Boo! So long as we of
the defense forces are here,
we will not allow you to have your way!
All right, open fire!
I-It's no use! He's not an
opponent you can handle!
Get out of here, quick!
What?!
Everybody, everybody...
Stop!!
Now die!!
Th-This can't be!
Gonna kill more and more!
He's come back!
G-Goten!
Trunks!
I got beaten up all over!
Didn't I tell you?!
Listen up, your fight with Majin Boo
comes one more day from now!
Until then, you'll train as hard as you can!
Once you've gotten even a little bit
stronger, your Fusion will be more effective!
Okay?! You got that, Trunten?!
Er, Gotenks.
You got that, Gotenks?!
Fusion was a success.
However, its power is still
far from matching Majin Boo.
Can Gohan really achieve a power-up?
The only ones who can stop
the destruction of the Earth now
are Gohan and Trunten–I mean, Gotenks.
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Now, the moment you've been waiting for,
the appearance of the
savior of the earth, Satan!
What is he going to do
against Majin Boo with those?
He's giving him candy and games?
Those cheap tricks aren't going to work on him.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Final Weapon is Engaged!?
Satan Will Save the Earth."
If he's that scared of Majin Boo,
he didn't need to go there.
"Next time"
"The Final Weapon is Engaged!?
Satan Will Save the Earth"