Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
At length, Freeza completes
his colossal transformation.
I've decided!
S-So fast!
Kuririn-san!
Before such incredible power and speed,
Kuririn was powerless to do anything,
and found himself suddenly
run through the pit of his stomach!
"Is This the End!? A Brutally
Transcendent Power Attacks Gohan."
Bungling jackass!
That's what you get for being
distracted by that Namekian kid!
K-Kakarrot, that smooth-headed one,
and so on, all those guys
from Earth take things too easily!
Oh, my fault, my fault.
It seems I have too much power,
and can't control myself all that well.
Kuririn-san!
Who would have thought
you could still be this spirited?
Gohan...
How does that feel?
Not yet? Not yet?
Dammit, not yet? Then how long?
Calm down, Yamucha!
It's not good to get so carried away!
How am I supposed to be calm about this?
Right now, Goku and Kuririn and the others
are off fighting for their
lives against someone so awful,
they don't know if they can beat him or not!
And yet, here I am, so far away...
I want to go and fight as well.
However, getting worked up won't help.
Goku and Piccolo are sure to do well!
You must realize the only thing we
can do is to continue our training now,
so that if we do get to Namek, we'll
be able to fight as hard as we'd like to.
Goku, after how I warned you
against getting near Freeza...
He wields enough terrifying
power to destroy the entire universe!
Kaio-sama?
What is it, you guys? Why aren't you training?
What is the matter?
You are so absorbed in thought.
Your face is so pallid. Are you all right?
M-My face has been this color since birth!
I-I trust nothing bad has
happened on Planet Namek?
Is it Goku?
Or maybe Piccolo?
I'm finished!
I've had it! I want a bed! I want a shower!
I want cake with strawberries,
and lots of strawberry cake!
I want to be a cloud, too.
Oh dear, that looks just like Kuririn!
Speaking of which, what could he possibly
be dilly-dallying around about right now?
I mean, really!
I don't suppose they could've left me
behind and gone back to Earth, could they?
Or maybe they've been wiped
out by Vegeta, or that Freeza guy!
No, that couldn't be! I mean,
Son-kun is here, after all!
They're okay, for sure!
They're okay...
So, this is the end for me? What a shame!
I wanted to get married, even just once...
Kuririn's ki is dropping rapidly.
Hold on just a while longer, everyone.
Just until I've fully recovered. Please!
So, you've finally snuffed it, then?
Kuririn...
Kuririn-san!
So fast!
You're thinking of saving him?
It's pointless, he'll die momentarily.
How about instead,
you worry about your own safety?
Then again, you can worry all you like,
it doesn't matter if you're a Namekian...
...or an Earthling...
...or a Saiyan...
...it won't, of course, change
the fact that you're going to die.
Out...
Out of my way!!
What?!
That kid's power is rising so fast!
How can this be? Such incredible energy!
I can't believe it!
When that kid loses his
senses and flies off the handle,
he can call up that much power?!
U-Unbelievable!
H-He may be closer to becoming
a Super Saiyan than anyone else!
K-Kuririn-san!
Kuririn-san...
Kuririn-san!
It's okay! He's managed to hang on!
Don't die, Kuririn-san!
We don't have time to be worrying about him!
Do you think Freeza would die from just that?
You aren't any ordinary runt, are you?
Even I found that to be a little bit painful!
You did that to the wrong person.
Of course, like I said before, the
fact that you're going to die remains.
For all your effort, you've
only managed to incur my wrath.
O-Oh, hell.
It looks like we were
hoping for too much after all.
Now we're a laughingstock!
Impossible! His ki just keeps
growing stronger and stronger!
Who could have known he
can control his battle power?!
I will take the pain I have felt,
and return it to you many times over!
Freeza's power just billowed up suddenly!
At this rate, everyone will be...
You idiot! Get out of there!
Oh no, don't you suffer any damage just yet.
The fun is just beginning, after all.
You're just a kid after all, aren't you?
Is that the extent of your power?
Fool! You got full of yourself
and dropped your guard, didn't you?
You caught all of that blast!
All right!
Once again! I'll pound you
with yet another intensive shot!
Take this!
And you said I wasn't
going to be a match for you!
You look awfully stupid now, Freeza-san.
Don't be in such a hurry, Vegeta.
Once I finish with the runt, I'll
have plenty of time to play with you.
Our fates are sealed...
So then, how would you
like me to deal with you, hmm?
He's gone!
Here I am!
What's wrong? Can't you move?
This is where it ends, isn't it?
Die!
Gohan's ki is falling rapidly!
I'm coming! Wait there, Gohan!
Gohan...
Gohan's death draws near.
But what of Piccolo? What of Goku?
Can those that love him do anything to save him?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Who is it? That gigantic ki– who has arrived?
You're the only one that ever
freely associated with me, Gohan.
You stay alive until I get there!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Tide Suddenly Turned!!
Piccolo, the Warrior Who Came Late."
You sure are sure of yourself, Piccolo-san.
"Next time"
"The Tide Suddenly Turned!!
Piccolo, the Warrior Who Came Late"