Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
R-Remember this well, you trash...
There won't be any
miracles for you next time...
Be sure to enjoy yourselves
to the fullest until then...
Earth had been saved. But already,
a new drama was about to begin.
"We're Off Into Space! The Star
of Hope is Piccolo's Homeland."
Are you okay?
You can rest easy now.
Aw, did he leave?
Never mind that guy, what kinda idiot
are you? How come ya didn't finish him off?
Sorry about that, Kuririn...
Don't worry about it. I did feel
bad for everyone who died, though.
But even so, we might still be
able to bring them back to life.
H-He couldn't be!
Gohan-chan!
Ch-Chichi?
Gohan-chan! Gohan-chan!
Gohan-chan!
Ch-Chichi!
Gohan-chan! Gohan-chan!
Are you okay?! Wake up! Ma is here!
Gohan-chan... What an
awful thing to go through...
G-Gohan is fine.
Goku is in far worse shape than him.
See? You see? Over here. See?
You poor thing! Bein' forced
to go through somethin' like this!
You're never goin' to leave your
Ma's side again! You poor thing!
That's just not right. Goku had it hard, too.
S-Son-kun...
Goku...
Son-kun...
Are you okay, Son-kun?
T-This is awful.
S-Sorry... I let the Saiyan get away...
Not at all. Just driving
him away was quite a feat.
Ah, Karin-sama...
Saying he was strong doesn't begin to cover it.
B-Bulma-san, Yamucha was... Except for
the four of us, everyone else was done in...
Uh-huh, we saw it on TV.
But Piccolo died, which
means that so has Kami-sama...
He's right. And that means the Dragon Balls...
I know what that means!
Y-You knew, didn't you?
Y-Yeah.
If only Piccolo had been one of the survivors...
Well 'scuse me for livin'.
That's right! All you did was
run away! You didn't fight one bit!
What did you say?!
A good-for-nothing like you should
have died right off, instead of Piccolo!
You idiot!
If I hadn'a been there,
these guys wouldn'a survived!
This is pissin' me off! I'm sick of bein' good!
All right, all right.
More importantly, we should
hurry and get the injured to a hospital.
There aren't any more Senzu.
Easy, easy! Easy now...
Everyone's bodies are around here, right?
Um... a little more that way.
Bulma-san, don't cry. There's only
a very slim chance that this is possible,
and maybe it's even a little crazy,
so listen to me, but don't get your hopes up.
I-It's possible that we can bring everyone
who was killed by the Saiyans back to life.
What do you mean?
Really?
This is going to sound
like grasping at clouds...
K-Kuririn... you said
something about that to me, too...
What do you mean? Tell us...
A-As it happens...
Just a minute. I'll tell you later.
Muten Roshi-sama, land here. We
have to load up everyone else's bodies.
Chaozu's body is the
only one left. Let's see now...
There isn't one.
He blew himself to pieces.
I really would like to
bring them all back to life.
As it stands, their sacrifice was all too great.
Karin-sama, all I feel is anger...
at my own helplessness...
Now then...
That's okay. I'll pilot us.
I've calmed down a little.
O-Okay...
Gohan-chan! Are you wakin' up?
Relax! It's Ma! It's your Ma!
M-Mother?
You poor thing! It must have
been so scary! But you're okay now!
Yeah, you did great! You're really something!
We got through it!
H-How? Where is the Saiyan?
He got away... He got away from us.
B-But still, we all hurt
him something terrible, right?
He might never come back.
Where's Father?!
I'm in the back, Gohan...
Thanks to you guys,
I managed to survive somehow...
Hey, this is fine an' all,
but yer Goku's wife, right?
Stop worryin' about just the kid,
and look after yer husband, would ya?
How rude! Nothin' doin'.
It's because of Goku-sa that
Gohan-chan went through all that nastiness!
He didn't have to drag my boy into that!
That's not true, Mother! Father was–
I'm far more worried about your future,
Gohan, than I am about the Earth!
Goku, can I slug her?
Kuririn...
Would you tell us about
what you were saying earlier?
O-Oh, right.
The Saiyans probably learned about
there being Dragon Balls here on Earth,
via Goku's brother's radio, or whatever.
The part about having wishes granted, too.
So, as long as they were here, they
were trying to get the Dragon Balls, too.
Really?
Yeah.
But when they saw Piccolo's face,
they called him something weird.
A "Namekian."
Piccolo–and Kami-sama,
too–appear to have been aliens.
That's no wonder, what with his face.
The important part is what they said next.
Nappa! Kill them!
But what about the Dragon Balls?
I don't care! I have an idea.
If we go to Planet Namek,
the home world of that Namekian,
I'm sure that there will be Dragon
Balls that are even more powerful.
Is that all they said? That's nonsense.
I heard him, too.
He said that Namekians have
the power to create mysterious balls.
If–and that's a really big if–we were
able to go to this Planet Namek place,
we might be able to obtain their Dragon Balls.
I-I get it.
If you did that, you would be able
to bring those who had died back to life.
Piccolo-san could come back to life!
G-Gohan-chan, how can you say that?!
That's right! If Piccolo came
back to life, so would Kami-sama!
And that means we could
restore the Dragon Balls here, too!
–Banzai! Banzai!
–T-That's incredible!
Then there's a chance...
There really is a chance!
Isn't there? Isn't there? Isn't there?
You amateurs make it
sound so nice and simple.
There's no way we could pull off that
kind of dream. I hate to burst your bubble.
N-Not even you can do it, Bulma-san?
In the first place, Kuririn,
how are we supposed to know where
this whatever-it's-called planet even is?
L-Let me take care of that...
Kaio-sama, you're listening, right?
Do you know where this Planet Namek is?
Planet Namek? Of course I know.
Whatever else you may say,
I am a Kaio, after all.
T-This is amazing. We can hear him, too.
This gentleman is Kaio-sama, is he?
Kaio-sama, it looks like everyone
else can hear you, too, so tell us.
Before I do, allow me to say
one thing. You all did really well.
Once Son Goku had been done in,
I honestly thought it was hopeless.
That was really something.
Still, I got a pretty big shock.
Not even Kaio-ken worked against him...
Yeah, even I greatly miscalculated
that Saiyan Vegeta's strength.
Who knew he'd be that strong?
M-Maybe I really was
wrong to let him get away...
Maybe so.
H-Hey, what does he mean?
Don't tell me Goku intentionally...
I-I'll tell you all the details later.
Now then, Planet Namek's location...
To put it in the terms
you'd use on Earth... let's see...
Bearing SW66 by...
no, no, let's see here...
Bearing SU83 by... 9045XY, is it?
9045XY, did you say?!
B-Bulma-san, do you know where that is?
H-Hey, Turtle-chan, take
over piloting. I've got to calculate this.
T-Turtle-chan?
I've got a bad feeling about this...
Planet Namek used to be a
very beautiful planet, as I recall,
but some time ago, they went through
a terrible bout of abnormal weather.
I thought that all of the
Namekians died out at that time.
The planet itself is currently in
the process of returning to normal,
but as for whether
or not anyone survived...
O-Oh, no...
This is hopeless. Ain't no way
there're still Dragon Balls there.
H-Hey, you!
Don't panic. Once I check
up on Planet Namek, I'll know.
Now, where was it? Let's see...
This way, huh?
So that's it!
That's the reason why Kami– or rather,
the Namekian who became Kami–fled to Earth.
Kami himself may have forgotten
that because he lost his memory,
or maybe he was just too young a child.
Either way, it's a sad past.
Yeah, but Dragon Balls
can grant any wish, right?
If they're the guys
that could make them things,
they coulda just wished to have
the abnormal weather stopped, right?
That probably wouldn't have worked.
Shen Long said that he couldn't grant a wish
that exceeded the power
of the Dragon Balls' creator.
That means he couldn't rein in
that incredible amount of power.
That's why Shen Long couldn't
do anything against the Saiyans.
What're ya talkin' about? I guess
the Dragon Balls ain't so great after all.
You're a sassy fellow!
What's this? There are some! There are some!
There are some Namekians!
There's just under a hundred of them,
but they survived, and are thriving again!
T-There're a hundred guys like that?!
Not to worry. Namekians are a
very mild-mannered race by nature.
Like that guy who was Kami on your Earth.
Piccolo Daimao was
probably someone who was born
of the evil influence of earthlings
that he encountered before becoming Kami.
That explains it.
There are some nasty types
out there in the world, after all.
Look who's talking.
But now there's a possibility that Kami,
not to mention Yamucha and
Tenshinhan, can come back to life!
You're naïve! You're absolutely naïve!
Indeed, I figured out where Planet Namek is.
But how are you planning to go there?
H-How? Well, in a spaceship, of course.
That's where you're being
completely naïve, I tell you!
If you used a spaceship
with the world's most powerful engine,
an experimental model my dad made,
I calculated how much time it
would take you to reach Planet Namek.
Exactly how long do you think it would take?
I came up with a positively enormous figure.
Look here. It would take
4,339 years and three months.
You'd have to live to a ripe old age, huh?
K-Kaio-sama, what should we do?
Y-Y-You're asking me?
If that's the problem,
I think we'll be all right.
I'm thinking of using the spaceship
that that Saiyan came here in.
The Saiyan's? But the Saiyan took
that one and ran away, didn't he?
We saw the spaceship
belonging to that Vegeta guy,
but it was very small, and anyhow
you look at it, it had to be a one-seater.
Which means that the spaceship
belonging to that other one who died
has to be out there somewhere.
T-That's right! And there's the one
that my brother Raditz came in, too!
Come to think of it, that
one got destroyed by Gohan...
But anyhow, there's still one of them, right?
If I can find that one and analyze it,
I just might come up with something.
It's probably in Metro East.
That's the first place the Saiyans destroyed.
We'll have to go look for it later.
I was thinking that, and
picked up a nice little something.
This. I'm sure that Vegeta guy
beeped this thing to call his spaceship.
It has to be a remote control!
We can do this! We can definitely do this!
Yay! Yay! Hope is in sight!
Planet Namek or bust!
A destination planet had been settled on.
However, there were still some
difficult problems to solve beforehand.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Aw, man, they said it would be
four months until my injuries heal.
Hey, in one more month, some
new senzu beans will be ready.
More importantly, Mister Popo has taken Bulma
and gone out looking for a spaceship.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Mysterious Yunzabit!
The Search for Kami-sama's Spaceship."
This is a secret, but
Father is afraid of needles.
"Next time"
"Mysterious Yunzabit!
The Search for Kami-sama's Spaceship"