Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
There ain't any reason to kill you,
now that you've started trembling.
You should go on living with the shock
you have undergone here in tranquility.
Nevertheless.
Am I to have lost?!
You're an impossible fool!
I had given you one last chance!
Mere moments remain
before Planet Namek's explosion.
"Goku's Declaration of Victory!!
As Freeza Destroys Himself..."
Monkey scumbag!
You're going to evade right in
front of me and have it hit me, right?
I won't fall for such an old trick!
Got you!
Over here, Freeza!
That was an after image, huh?
The monkey's not too bad, is he?
I just can't bring myself
to fight with you any more.
Not if you're pinning all your
hopes on such a petty technique.
If you absolutely have to settle this with me,
then regain your strength
and brush up on your skills.
Petty technique, you say?
Kaio-sama, what has happened?
F-Freeza there is trembling...
Then, that means Goku has won!
Goku is fighting with
composure to spare. But... but...
There's no time!
Only moments remain
until Planet Namek explodes!
M-My technique... is a
petty technique, you say?!
In that case, how about two of them?!
You ignorant fool!
Someone who uses the
same pattern lacks innovation!
Kakarrot and Freeza will both be
destroyed along with Planet Namek!
There's no longer anyone in my way!
I, Vegeta-sama, am the
greatest in the universe!
I've been waiting for this day.
Having endured the
humiliation, being at Freeza's side...
We did it!
This battle has left me worn ragged!
I'd like to hurry up and
get to a recuperation capsule!
With just the three of us,
we subjugated Planet Shatts!
Quite a feat!
I wonder what Freeza-sama will give us.
Freeza-sama, we have just
returned from Planet Shatts.
They gave us a little trouble,
but we were able to conquer
them in three days' time.
Hmm, is that so?
Three days for such a planet...
I see. Please stand aside.
J-Just a minute! Is that all?!
We ran ourselves ragged, you know!
What about that?!
Zarbon-san, how long would it
take you to subjugate that planet?
Sir. If I were to have one day's time,
I am sure it would be enough.
I would think so.
It is such a tiny planet, after all.
Is there anything else?
I am quite busy.
If not, you may stand aside.
You filthy rat!
Stop, Nappa!
Freeza-sama, if you will excuse us...
You monkey scum.
Vegeta, doesn't it upset you?
I heard something–our world, Planet Vegeta,
was not destroyed in a collision
with another planet–or so they say!
What's that?
It was all Freeza's doing!
I-It was what?!
Vegeta, your father,
King Vegeta, being killed...
...as well as the destruction
of our homeland, Planet Vegeta,
it was all done under the
direction of Freeza there!
I'm aware of it!
Y-You knew?!
In that case, why the hell
are we working for that guy?!
Whoever may have killed my old man,
whoever may have destroyed my home,
that sort of thing doesn't matter to me.
In this world, strength is everything!
The strong stand at the top,
and subdue everyone else.
I know of Freeza's boundless strength.
There's no way I can stand against him now.
But just you watch!
We Saiyans have the blood of a
warrior race running though us!
And so, the more we fight,
the stronger we get!
Just watch me get stronger and stronger!
And then, one day,
I will take the place of Freeza,
and rule the entire universe!
I have the power within me.
At last, that time has come.
Kakarrot and Freeza are going down together!
Father will not die!
He is certain to come home alive!
You keep on spouting that nonsense.
Father will defeat Freeza,
and will surely return to Earth!
Lousy monkey!
These will follow you wherever you may go!
You think you can get away?!
You're going to be sliced to pieces!
He'll never learn.
Hmph! Someone who uses the
same pattern lacks innovation!
Dammit! You expect me to
fall for such a childish trick?!
Where is that monkey scum?!
You're no longer a match for me!
Get him! Attaboy! Nice going, Goku!
Right there! Give it to him! Goku!
I will not be beaten by that monkey scum!
Don't stand up! Get down!
Get down!
I-It can't be...!
K-Kaio-sama, what is it?!
D-Don't tell us Goku has lost!
Freeza's been...
cut clean in two!
Even though you may reap
what you sow, this ain't like you.
What a miserable end!
Somehow or other, I'm going back to Earth.
Now share the same
fate as this Planet Namek,
which you yourself have destroyed.
Help...
H-Help...
Help... me...
G-Goku! What are you dawdling around for?!
Hurry and take off!
P-Please... s... s...
Save me!
Save...
You dare ask anything for yourself?!
You... you...
How many people have you killed as
they begged for their lives like that?!
Please... save... me!
Please!
Freeza...
I've shared a little bit of my ki with you.
Knowing you, you should be
able to move, even in your shape.
The rest is up to you!
Goku and Freeza's ceaseless conflict
has come to a conclusion. However...
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Freeza, survive, and come to
understand the blessing that life is.
You're still soft to have
given your energy to me.
I will pay you back in full! Die!!
You stupid bastard!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Freeza Defeated!! A Single
Blast Packed with a Totality of Rage."
Father, make sure you come back!
"Next time"
"Freeza Defeated!! A Single
Blast Packed with a Totality of Rage"