Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Jheese! How high is my battle power?
23,000.
What?!
Having stolen Goku's body, Ginyu is
unable to use its power as he would like to.
Ginyu's Body Change finishing
move proved to be inopportune for him.
However, just then...
Die!!
Change!!
The Body Change burst forth
again, this time against Vegeta!
What will you do, Goku?
"Whoops!! Ginyu Has Turned Into a Frog."
I-It can't be!
Change!!
This is it! I can get my own body back!
Let me get there in time!
What?
O-Out of the way!
You bastard... How dare you... interfere?!
Ow-ow-ow-ow...
Looks like I'm back to normal.
W-What happened? What the
hell did Kakarrot do just now?
What was that light?
Did Goku jump between them
in order to stop Vegeta's attack?
I can sense Father!
Father is... Father is back in his own body!
What?
Are you sure, Gohan?
S-So then, that Ginyu bastard is now over there?
Damn!
I'll Change with you for sure this time, Vegeta!
I ain't going to let you!
What?!
Ka...
me...
That rotten Kakarrot...
ha...
me...
Ha!!
Damn, I've taken terrible
damage... I can't control my ki...
Father!
G-Goku!
That was pretty stupid of you.
You won't get in my way any longer.
T-This is bad! If we allow him to take
over Vegeta's body now... it's all over...
I'll take that body of yours!
Chan–
What?!
Impressive, Vegeta.
He's getting himself busted up,
just like he did against me.
He's planning on trading places with Vegeta!
What's the matter? Finished already?
That's right! You...
...are finished!
Stop, Vegeta!
You fell for it, Vegeta!
T-This is it.
Change!!
N-Now what happened?
Ribbit... ribbit...
Ribbit... ribbitribbitribbit...
I-I did it!
G-Goku! Are you okay?
Father! Hang on!
Y-You really did quite a number...
on my body, didn't you, Vegeta?
Never mind that, explain to
me what happened to Ginyu.
That guy that ran away is a frog.
And that frog-looking
thing over there is now Ginyu.
What?
Ribbit... ribbit...
I don't know how you did it, but
I'm still going to mash you underfoot.
Leave him alone, Vegeta.
Now that Ginyu is like that,
he can't do anything.
Oh, all right, you can go.
I pity you when I think
of the life ahead of you.
Goku!
Father!
Hey, Goku, don't you have a single senzu left?
N-Nope, I've really had it.
There's no reason why I couldn't
vaporize you bothersome guys right now.
What?
Vegeta, you dirty, lowdown...
I-It's all right. He can't kill us just yet.
You're right. There's still
the matter of the Dragon Balls,
as well as the fight against Freeza,
and I'm going to need everyone's
power, especially yours, Kakarrot.
–Come on.
–W-Where to?
Inside the spaceship. Bring Kakarrot with you.
W-What are you going to do to Goku?!
I'm offering to heal him.
Why should we believe you?!
Fine, suit yourselves. You can
croak right alongside Kakarrot.
Damn it...
K-Kuririn-san...
K-Kuririn, it's all right.
It's all right?
Vegeta's enemy right now is Freeza, not us.
B-But...
Let's go, Kuririn-san.
Hurry it up. We don't know
when Freeza will be coming back.
In here.
You go first.
This will treat Kakarrot's
injuries and restore him to full power.
W-With all this?
A needle!
N-No way!
I hate needles! Let go of me, Kuririn!
I don't need any medical attention!
You think I would treat you with something
as uncivilized as a needle, you idiot?!
R-Really?
Oh, Father, how pathetic!
Vegeta, what is this, anyhow?
It's called a Medical Machine.
In short, it's like a healing capsule.
By immersing oneself in this special solution,
one's energy is restored to
them in a short amount of time.
So that's how...
After I've defeated Freeza,
I'll kill you guys nice and slow.
By that time, make no mistake,
I will be a Super Saiyan!
How about you speak to me, already?
Just telling me one simple thing is enough.
How do I get the Dragon Balls to grant my wish?
All you have to do is tell me that.
Y-You expect me... to tell you?
You do not need to say anything else.
Well? Do you still want me to continue this?
Up yours!
My apologies, Nail.
Bear it just a little while longer.
Very soon, Dende will
arrive at the Earthlings' location.
Please, allow my life to last
for at least that much longer.
J-Just a little farther. Grand Elder-sama
said they were in the Maima region.
The Medical Machine in
this room is the older model,
but knowing Kakarrot, he should
be fully rejuvenated before too long.
The older model?
I destroyed the newer model.
H-He's not going to drown
or anything in there, right?
T-This sure feels good.
Now then, let's get you two some battle wear.
You'll do better by them,
as far as protection goes.
Battle wear? You mean like yours?
That's not how I want to picture us.
Boy, their civilization
sure is ahead of Earth's.
It sure seems like it.
Take off your clothes
and put on that undershirt.
Hurry it up. Freeza is coming.
Say, Gohan, if Vegeta
feels he needs even our help,
it must mean that Freeza is awfully strong, huh?
It scares me.
Now for your battle jackets.
Luckily enough, there
are some smaller sizes here,
for use by those from Planet Litt.
How do we put these on?
I can get my head
through, but my arms won't fit.
Just force them on.
Those are soft enough that if
you pull on them, they'll stretch.
Back on Earth, even when
I turned into a Great Ape,
my armor didn't break, remember?
Yet they can still stand
up to a shock pretty well.
Wow, you're right!
Are the gloves and boots
made of the same material?
I suppose.
This is incredibly light!
I barely feel any weight at all!
It's awful slimy of you guys
to be wearing stuff this nice.
What do you say, Vegeta?
Is something the matter?
I-It's nothing.
I wish I had armor more like Vegeta's style.
The shoulder area seems a
lot easier to move around in.
This is an older type. There weren't
any that fit me in the regular sizes.
However, these don't seem to be in the
way at all, Kuririn-san. I can move freely!
Are you sure you're all right?
You don't need to
concern yourself about me.
Well, if you say so.
So, what about Goku? How
long will it take him to heal?
Good question.
Knowing him, he should be fully
healed in around 40 or 50 minutes.
Gohan, I'm going to go see Grand Elder-sama.
I know that Freeza is probably there too,
but if we can't get the
password to summon Shen Long,
there's nothing we can do anyhow.
I-I'll go too!
No. I can handle this myself. You wait here.
Goku and the others regroup,
preparing themselves for
the coming conflict with Freeza.
Who is it that will be able to summon
Shen Long from the still silent Dragon Balls?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
There he is! The original is
far bigger than Earth's dragon!
So that's Super Shen Long, is it?
It will be to me, Freeza-sama,
that the wish is granted.
It will not be to you lower life forms.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Thou Who Hast Gathered the Seven Balls...
Now Speak Forth the Password."
Takaraputo Poppolunga Pupirito Paro!
That's the password!
"Next time"
"Thou Who Hast Gathered the Seven Balls...
Now Speak Forth the Password"