Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Less than five months
remained until the mighty Saiyans,
bent on attacking Earth, were to arrive.
Son Goku had at last
arrived at Kaio-sama's home,
which was a planet that had
ten times the gravity of Earth!
First off, you have to
conquer the harsh gravity here.
Catch Bubbles-kun here, if you can.
The chase went on for three weeks.
I finally did it!
I caught him!
He's as amazing as I thought.
He's already overcome the gravity here, has he?
"The Saiyan Legend Reborn!
Goku's Roots."
I did it!
I did it! I did it! I did it! I did it!
Kaio-sama, what should I do next?
What should you do? Let's see...
You'll polish off whatever I give you, right?
Uh-huh.
Even apple-polishing?
Kaio-sama, I have to train fast,
before the Saiyans arrive...
Take it easy.
There are still 135 days left.
That ain't hardly time
enough to catch my breath.
W-What are you doing?
It's about time for it to come back.
Come back?
Here it comes.
It takes quite a while
to catch one's breath, huh?
That's great, that's great!
Are you sure you're all that strong?
How rude!
W-What was that?
It looks like a cricket.
C-Cricket?
That's "crickediculous!"
–Oh, nice one!
–You are so disrespectful!
I am Gregory, the one
who looks after Kaio-sama.
You dare face the man
who stands at the head of all
the gods throughout
the universe, Kaio-sama...
"That's crickediculous!"
Ahem... You dare face
Kaio-sama, and ask him,
"Are you sure you're all that strong?"
I can only put up with so much
shamelessness from such a whippersnapper!
But I ain't even carrying a whip.
Son Goku, you got off a pretty good one, there!
Kaio-sama, this is no
time for you to be laughing.
This works out perfectly, Son Goku.
After Bubbles-kun, your
next opponent will be Gregory.
This guy?
What is that look on
your face supposed to mean?
But I wanted to get my training
directly from you, Kaio-sama.
Kaio-sama, I am absolutely infuriated!
If it's okay with you,
I would like to take this
disparager down a peg. What do you say?
Very well.
What's that?
K-Kaio-sama, isn't that a little big?
Son Goku, here...
What do you think? Heavy, right?
Your next training exercise will be to
take that hammer and swat Gregory with it.
With this?
Once you manage to do that,
I will begin training you personally.
All right, I'll give it a try!
Hmph! You think a pipsqueak like
you is going to be able to catch me?
He's fast!
Dammit!
Looks like this is going to take a while.
Yow-ow-ow-ow... All right,
I'll get you this time for sure!
That jerk!
Wait up!
He didn't!
It's a good thing I'm so cheerful...
Get up, now!
Don't get too full of yourself,
just because you managed
to dodge me once or twice.
You're still too soft!
Help me!
Come back up here on your own!
Squirrel! Watermelon!
Sea gull! Killifish! Monster!
Cow! White shark!
Quince! Apple! Gorilla! Lion!
You say the next one!
Both Ten-san and Yamucha-san
have gotten even better!
Yajirobe! Take this seriously!
Eeyow-ow-ow-ow-ow!
T-Time out!
K-Kaio-sama?
It's time for supper!
Yahoo!
You're really something!
Goku, how are you coming along?
Whew! He's so fast! I've never
seen anyone like this dude before!
"T-This dude"?
You may have conquered the gravity on this
planet, but now the problem is your speed.
The Saiyans that you have
to fight are unbelievably strong.
Kaio-sama!
Do you know about the Saiyans?!
L-Listen, you! Kaio-sama
stands at the head of all
the gods throughout the universe–
Gregory, it's all right.
Son Goku, as I recall, you said something
about yourself being a Saiyan too, right?
Yeah. But I don't know
anything about Saiyans.
Apparently, I came to Earth when I was a baby.
So that's how it is, huh?
In that case, let me tell you
about the history of the Saiyans.
Really?
Oh, my, thank you.
I'll just plop down here...
Once upon a time...
There were two races of people who
lived on a world named Planet Vegeta.
The Saiyans, who are your
forebears, and the Tsufruians.
Saiyans and Tsufruians?
Planet Vegeta, like my own planet here,
had an extremely strong gravity.
As a result, the Tsufruians,
who controlled the
larger half of Planet Vegeta,
were a race whose bodies were
only about half the size of the Saiyans.
However, they had a remarkable,
comparatively advanced level of civilization.
On the other hand, the Saiyans
were a race that was very few in numbers,
but their bodies were bigger,
not to mention stronger,
and they were an aggressive, primitive race.
The tails the Saiyans had were their
greatest distinguishing characteristic.
They were all warrior-like people, as it were.
At one point, these warriors bared their fangs,
and started to overrun the Tsufruians.
The Tsufruians greeted them with
advanced weaponry of their own making.
The Saiyans, who should have been
utterly outnumbered, were incredibly strong,
and gradually, they brought
the Tsufruians under their control.
The decisive factor was the full moon,
which only appeared on Planet
Vegeta once every eight years.
That's because when Saiyans see
the full moon, they transform into monsters.
For the Tsufruians,
this was their greatest threat,
and they suffered the most damage this way.
And so, little by little, as the
Tsufruian civilization pulled back,
the Saiyans quickly increased their numbers.
In time, they completely
took over Planet Vegeta.
Then, the Saiyans took off into space,
seeking to fight even more.
However, since the
Tsufruians had been exterminated,
further development of their
civilization was slow to occur.
They realized that even
though they wanted to fight,
they could not go out any farther into space.
So the Saiyans joined forces with rich,
advanced alien civilizations,
and in exchange for
furnishing planets to these aliens
for use in developing vacation estates,
they were able to obtain technology and money.
For the battle-hungry Saiyans,
this was killing two birds with one stone.
The Saiyans' activities escalated swiftly,
and they even started sending babies
to many other worlds, as was your case.
They had come up with long-term plans,
whereby once the baby grew up,
it would exterminate the planet's population.
That's awfully overbearing!
But Planet Vegeta had its own Kami.
He could not bear the Saiyans' evil deeds,
and using his own powers,
he pulled close some giant meteors,
which then collided with Planet
Vegeta, causing it to explode.
Including yourself, there were
only four Saiyans that survived.
No!
I ain't the same as those guys!
Yes, well...
One has died, and the other two mightiest,
most wicked Saiyans now
heading to Earth are the only survivors.
I'm going to protect the Earth!
Gregory! We've got
training! Help me out, please!
My, my, these are the first
respectful words I've heard out of you.
All right, I'll get you this time!
We'll see about that.
I won't let the Saiyans have their way!
Damn!
You have all far surpassed me.
There is no longer anything that
either I or Mister Popo can teach you.
From now until the time of battle arrives,
you should go down to the
surface and polish your techniques.
I leave the future to you.
Right!
So, can I take off this heavy shirt, now?
Do as you wish.
Guys, let's go down to
the surface and get to work!
We should still be able
to power ourselves up, after all.
Everyone, get better!
Goku, I can't wait to see you again!
Hammer in hand, two weeks went by...
Almost there!
He's persistent!
All right!
Oh, no!
Brace yourself, Gregory!
I did it!
It'd hurt if I hit you
as hard as I could, after all.
You sure are benign.
My body is harder than a rock.
You won't be able to
beat the Saiyans like that.
Is that right? Maybe so, but
you've still got a bump growing there.
There are still 1 18 days remaining.
He just might be able to master it!
The Kaio-ken technique!
Kaio-ken, the technique
that I could picture in my dreams,
but was ultimately
unable to perform myself...
As well as that finishing move...
Kaio-sama, like you promised–
I know you're ready for this, but my
training is harder than you can imagine!
Can you handle it?!
Mm-hmm, I'll give it a try!
You will be striving to be the best in
the universe, the greatest in all the world,
both physically and mentally. Got that?!
I got it!
All right, before we start...
um, care to have some tea?
Sis, I'd like you to tell the Earth's future.
W-What? The Earth's future?
I want to know what's
going to happen next year.
All right, I'll try to read it.
It's no use! Not even I
can tell the future this time!
All right, that's it!
You're starting to control your ki!
Weak!
What kind of technique is this Kaio-ken?
And what is this finishing move?
The time of battle pitilessly drew ever nearer.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Huh? You got the wrong day?
Then I won't make it on the
day the Saiyans arrive! Kaio-sama!
Hmm? What's that ki? Have they finally come?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Come Forth, Shen Long!
The Saiyans Finally Arrive on Earth."
Father, come quickly.
"Next time"
"Come Forth, Shen Long!
The Saiyans Finally Arrive on Earth"