The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Having infiltrated their
way inside Majin Boo's body,
Goku and Vegeta returned
to their original forms,
and began searching
for Gohan and the others.
Fighting against these
two opponents is truly hard!
And at a critical time like this,
Kakarrot is not around!
Even as they were baffled
by the sudden appearance of
false versions of Gohan and company,
they finally found the real ones!
Hey, Kakarrot!
This way! They're here!
"A Majin's Secret!!
Two More Boos Inside Of Boo."
The pipsqueaks' union has been separated,
like ours was, so there's two of them.
No, they separated because their
Fusion had lasted for thirty minutes.
When Gotenks was absorbed, Boo
certainly displayed the traits of Fusion.
Which means performing
Fusion is okay, even in here.
Just how many times does he have to
go around this city before he's satisfied?
This makes the 25th cake store he's been to.
Now then, my belly is full...
Now where does he plan on going?
W-What are you doing?
We're going to lose sight of him!
Please, allow me to rest for a little bit.
You can't trust anyone
that can fly through the air!
In recognition of my becoming
invincible, I'll eradicate this planet!
What in the world is going on inside here?
You're in the way. Move!
We're going to tear them out from there!
W-What's this?!
Come on...!
W-What?
What the hell does this mean? I-It can't be...!
Yahoo! Boo is returning
to the way he was! All right!
Way to go! Way to go! Way to go! Way to go!
Way to–!
He's gone back! He's gone back!
They did it! They did it!
Way to go! Way to go!
Boo's power must have
dropped considerably after that.
Just a little bit farther now.
There, see? The size of his ki is
completely different than it was before.
All right. Now we blow
this place away and get out.
Yeah.
B-But hold on a second. No matter how
much Boo may have returned to normal,
even at that, he still has more
strength than we can stand up to.
If we go outside like this,
we'll be beaten for sure!
In that case, what else
would you have us do? Huh?
This is because you're the
one who broke your Potara!
In that case, you can live
out your life inside Boo's head.
I'm not about to.
Even so, there's still one
method by which we can win!
No way.
I still ain't said a thing!
You want to suggest Fusion, right?
I know about it–what it is.
You already know?
I saw it from the Other World.
You've got to be joking!
How could I go through
an inelegant pose like that?!
I-Is it all that inelegant?
I don't think it's so bad...
And besides, I told you already that
I'm not about to merge with you again!
Hey! What does this mean?!
Majin Boo...
It's the one from the very beginning.
Inside of Boo, there's yet another Boo, huh?
Does this mean he was
absorbed too? By himself?
Huh?
Huh? Huh? What's this? Suddenly,
the inside of Boo isn't being displayed!
Th-That can't be! It was just
getting to something important!
Hey, should we try tearing him out too?
That skinny Majin Boo
was born of this Majin Boo,
then he turned this fat
one into choco and ate him.
I'll turn you into choco!
Then maybe everyone else who
was turned into choco and eaten
could be around somewhere, huh?
They aren't! He's the only
one to get special treatment.
Here I thought things were strange,
and sure enough, it's your doing...
What's going on?!
W-Why is Majin Boo showing up inside himself?!
I don't know how this happened,
but it seems you weren't absorbed!
How dare you remove the others
I took so much trouble to absorb?!
Damn, th-this could be bad!
This is why I told you to
keep the Potara on, you know!
Once we're outside, if we could only
merge, this guy would be easy to beat!
Is that so? You guys
cannot merge any more, then?
You idiot! If you'd kept quiet,
he wouldn't have known that!
You don't say. You don't say, then!
All right, if you're coming, then come on!
I'll open up a giant
hole here inside your body!
What are you laughing about?
You don't think I can open one?
It's impossible!
Don't you belittle me.
Th-That's ridiculous!
Th-There's no effect?
All I felt was a little twinge in this area here.
Have you forgotten? Right now,
you're much, much smaller than even fleas!
In other words, after we defeat you,
we'll have to find ourselves an exit?
That will be impossible as well,
for you two as you are now.
Shall we put it to the test?
Of course we will!
We've completely lost sight of Majin Boo!
No, we've gotten quite close to him.
I'm sure he should be around here.
H-How can you tell that?
From his ki. I can feel Majin Boo's ki nearby.
W-What? What was that? Majin Boo's "ki"...?
[ki: tree]
Tree!!
He's here!
S-See? On top of that rock!
What's the matter? He's not moving.
H-His form has gone back to how
it was before! W-What in the world?
W-What exactly could be going on?
I don't know either! I'm getting annoyed!
Annoyed, annoyed, annoyed, annoyed!
Don't you look down on us!
What?!
Y-You rock-head...!
That was a moronic attack, but
it looks like it had quite an effect.
No way it could have!
Let's go, Vegeta!
Don't you give me orders!
How long are you going to stick on me?!
Hurry up and get away from me!
Take care of the fragments from Majin Boo!
R-Right!
That bastard... If I'd known this,
I'd have rather merged with him!
Yo, Vegeta! Are you done there, too?
Stay back, Kakarrot!
What?!
Have you forgotten what place this is?
Where are you, Boo?!
Bastard!
This is the inside of my body!
Inside here, I am immortal!
Don't you understand?!
Why, you...!
Blow me to pieces, and I still
won't die! The reason being, I am Boo!
S-Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!!
Shut up!!
Vegeta, take it easy!
Don't fall for Boo's taunting!
Huh? Are you trying to kill your
friends who you worked so hard to rescue?
That was dirty, Boo!
Where's Boo?
Like I told you!
It's impossible for you to beat me!
I'm getting tired of this. I'm done playing!
This is a desperate pinch!
Even though they have managed
to rescue Gohan and the others,
can it be impossible for them to
escape from before the immortal Boo?
Vegeta!!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Hey, Vegeta, after you
ripped that chubby Boo out,
Boo's body started acting funny.
He's probably just going to transform again.
But never mind him, we've
got to get out of here first.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Where Is the Exit!?
Escape from a Collapsing Boo."
Boo is changing into a
form we've never seen before.
"Next time"
"Where Is the Exit!?
Escape from a Collapsing Boo"