The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Under manipulation by Madoshi Babidi's
magic, Vegeta returns as an evil warrior.
This fight is between me and Kakarrot!
It does not matter to me what
happens with Majin Boo or anything else!
Babidi! Change us to a place
where no one else is around!
I have decided to fight Vegeta!
Papparapa!
At last, Goku and Vegeta's
unprecedented, fierce battle had begun!
Elsewhere, Kaioshin and Gohan
have arrived in front of Majin Boo's ball.
Incredible. This is an enormous, evil ki,
the likes of which I've never felt until now.
I welcome you here.
"The Seal is Broken!
Out Comes the Vicious Majin Boo!!"
Gohan-san, no matter what,
we have to put them away
before the energy
accumulates in Majin Boo's ball.
If Majin Boo is revived, this
Earth will be destroyed in a flash!
Right.
Kaioshin!
Shall we go up to the surface?
Majin Boo is just about to emerge from
this sphere, having reached full power.
When he does, it will
be with devastating force,
and it won't do for me to
have my spaceship destroyed.
Fine. But no matter what may
come, we are going to beat you,
and stop Majin Boo's revival!
You think it will be that easy?
Papparapa!
Well, Dabura?
Just to be sure, let me ask you if you're
certain you can beat that Earthling.
Of course! I fought him
for a bit earlier, after all.
That scum! I can
undoubtedly take care of him.
Do whatever you like with him!
You may turn him to stone like those others,
or mess him up even worse if you like!
Right!
You've gotten strong, Kakarrot!
This is the result of your
training in the Other World?
You too, Vegeta! You're much
stronger than I'd thought!
Kaioshin, I'm so happy you came!
Now I can finally take revenge, you see!
Long ago, you killed my papa.
Surely, he must have been careless.
But I'm not going to be killed by
the likes of you, the way Papa was.
I have entirely greater
magical power than Papa did.
Dabura is here too, after all.
He's got it all covered.
If I'm not careful as I attack,
I'll be done in by his magic!
Damn! To think I had a
hard time with this guy...
While we're here like this, Majin
Boo is rapidly collecting energy!
Get angry! Get angry, Gohan!
F-Father!
Get angry, remember what
happened when you fought Cell,
and call up all the power you possess!
If you do, you can't lose to any
kind of guy in the whole world!
Any kind of guy, you hear?
I am angry! I am angry, but I can't
bring myself to the way it was then...
the way it was when I fought Cell...
Ka... me... ha... me...
Ha!!
Dammit!
I'll just have to do it now!
I-It can't be...!
It can't be! Not this soon!
What is it?
What is the matter, Babidi-sama?
F-Full... Full power! He's at full power!
Majin Boo is at full power!!
He's at full power! He's at full power!
Majin Boo is finally revived!
I-Impossible! Why has
Goku-san's damage energy
collected as suddenly as this?
Th-That's why!
Father is fighting at a level
even beyond Super Saiyan!
Perhaps, as his and Vegeta-san's
two incredible powers collide,
the damage done is also extraordinary!
Ah, dammit!
We did it, Dabura!
Yes, Babidi-sama.
H-How can this be? How can this
come out in the worst possible way?!
I've completely misjudged things!
Die!
What's the matter, Kakarrot?
There you are!
Die, Kakarrot!
Not bad, Vegeta!
I'm starting to burn now, too!
Mister Satan, congratulations on your victory!
This time there were a number of
accidents, and it must have been tough.
Well, it's always difficult
to win through to the end.
It's he who can overcome and be
victorious that is the true world champion!
That's true, isn't it? It looked
as if you had an especially
difficult battle in the
final match against No. 18.
That's why amateurs are so troubling.
Actually, if I'd wanted to defeat her,
five seconds would have been plenty.
My opponent being a girl, and all...
But it would have been
inexcusable to my many fans,
who came to see my strength,
if I'd ended it so readily.
That's why I intentionally drew things out.
Wow! You think that much about the fans?
This is precisely why you're
the true champion, isn't it?
That's right, that's right.
You're pretty sharp, aren't you?
You'll be a fine reporter!
Er, could you once again tell us the
technique that clinched the final match?
Eh, um, Satan Miracle Very Wonderful...
...Special Strong Bari-bari...
...Punch, I believe it was!
Ah, I have a feeling that is
a little bit different from before...
R-Really?
I-I don't even remember it myself!
Moving along, what can you tell us about
that group that attacked the grounds?
I'm sure they must have come thinking
to challenge me, the World Champion.
There's a lot of those kind, who come to
challenge me using their bluffs and tricks.
However, once they saw my no-nonsense
attitude, they became afraid and ran off.
So that's it!
Let me take this occasion to say to all
the martial arts combatants in the world,
Mister Satan will accept
any challenge from anyone!
Bring it on, fair and square!
Way to go, Mister Satan!
Mister Satan, you're so cool!
Satan...! Satan...! Satan...!
S-She doesn't have to look at me
with that frightening look in her eye!
I'm going to promptly
pay her the money, after all!
There's been this wild,
incredible ki for a little while now.
Who is it? Our Papas?
I don't know. I felt it a little while back
from the direction of the tournament!
Why is it we're feeling such an
incredible ki going back and forth?
Could it be that fights are
occurring all over the world?
I have utterly no idea what's going on.
Should we give up going, and head back?
No, no way! I want to see Majin Boo!
I absolutely want to see him!
All right, Goten! Okay! Let's go
look toward where the biggest ki is!
Yeah!
It's been a long time since I've gotten this wild!
Vegeta, no matter what
happens, I ain't losing to you!
Back at you!
You evaded that well, huh Kakarrot?
All that valuable power, and you still missed!
Hey, I'm just starting!
I-I can't believe it! I thought I had
trained considerably on the Other Side.
And here we are, utterly even!
You must have trained even harder than I did!
That's not it! Though I suspect
I have trained harder than you did,
you have a talent for
going even higher than I do.
No matter how much time has passed,
that difference has not changed.
I knew it.
When you fought that
monster Babidi sent you...
It was a shock, Kakarrot!
How could I, the prodigal prince of bloodshed,
forever be outdistanced
by you, a lower-class warrior?!
A-And so, I secretly made my resolution.
So that's it! Babidi!
That's why you intentionally
fell under Babidi's spell!
Yeah! That's when I remembered about those
two men of Babidi's, back at the tournament.
He's completely different from before!
It's like he's a different person, he's so strong!
Those who had known the men from before
spoke of how much stronger they had gotten.
I remembered it and began to think.
If I were to be controlled by him... Kakarrot,
the gap between us might be closed...
The result was just as I thought.
It wasn't a very favorable mode, however.
Vegeta, with your great pride,
you allowed yourself to be controlled
by that guy just because you
wanted to become stronger?
I... I...
I... wanted to return to the way I was long ago!
I wanted to return to the brutal,
cold-blooded Saiyan that I was,
so I could fight all-out with
you and not worry about anything!
I hated it!
I hated how, before I had realized it,
I had been influenced by
you guys and become so gentle!
I, of all people, had a family.
It wasn't an unpleasant feeling...
I came to like this comfortable Earth as well!
That's why it was necessary for me
to be controlled by Babidi
and return to my evil self!
And thanks to that, I feel great now!
Is that really so, Vegeta?
It is just about time, Babidi-sama.
Majin Boo's seal will be broken!
He's emerging! Majin Boo is emerging!
The seal is at last broken!
Majin Boo is appearing!
And what about the conclusion
to Goku and Vegeta's fight?
Hurry, Goku! Something
terrible is happening to Earth!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Empty?! Hey, did you say
Majin Boo's egg was empty?
Too bad for you, Babidi.
Gohan-san's attack just now
appears to have obliterated Majin Boo.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"I Won't Allow the Revival!!
A Kamehame-Ha of Resistance."
Ah! The smoke that came out
of the egg is taking human form!
"Next time"
"I Won't Allow the Revival!!
A Kamehame-Ha of Resistance"