Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Six months remained until the Saiyans arrive.
In the Next World, Son Goku was
running down the Serpentine Road
in order to receive training from Kaio-sama.
Tenshinhan and the others
had also gathered at Karin Tower
to begin their special training.
Elsewhere, Piccolo once
again appeared before Gohan,
who had given up his
wishes to see his mother.
What is your mission?!
To defeat the Saiyans, and to save the Earth!
"City of No Tomorrow!
The Long Road to Victory."
It's been six months since we parted company.
It looks like you've gotten a little better.
Now then, how about
I start training you properly?
Come at me!
One more time!
Over here!
Do not lose sight of your opponent!
I can't see anything that fast.
You don't see it. You feel it.
That's easy for you to say...
If you've got enough time to whine,
think about what you should do instead.
Then move.
We've only got six more months!
When you're not eating
or sleeping, you will fight me!
Set your mind straight!
You can't mean it. I'll die.
Then get stronger! Even stronger than me! And...
...stronger than the Saiyans
who will be coming in six months!
Now, come on!
The end still ain't in sight?
Pretty fired up.
Kami-sama,
Just how long will it be until you train us?
Yeah...
We've already been here for two months,
and yet you haven't taught us anything.
We want to get stronger, like Goku.
Please give us the same
special training that you gave Goku!
Goku's special training, huh?
I...
...taught Goku...
...absolutely nothing!
What does he mean?!
If that's the case, there's no reason
for us to've come all the way here at all.
It's 'zactly the same as
training down on the surface.
Tell us, just what kind
of training did Goku do here?
Okay?
We just want to get stronger.
Getting stronger... is
knowing enemy, and knowing self.
Do that, and what you
should do come naturally.
Knowing the enemy, and knowing oneself?
Enough of your smart-aleck talk!
I know better than anyone what
my strength is! I don't need to be told!
Sure about that? You not
know self. You not know weaknesses.
What? Are you calling me weak?
You want to try me?!
Everyone, come.
W-What kind of room is this?
Past. Present. Future. All intersect here.
You go on time journey now.
Goku trained here too.
What? Goku did?
Intriguing. Let's go, then.
Let's go!
I ain't going.
I'll wait for ya's here.
Those want to go, enter circle.
Close eyes slowly.
Where are we?
A tail?
It's a Saiyan.
What?
What happened here?
These happened during some kind of battle.
The people on this planet
appear to like fighting something fierce.
I'm raring to take them on.
I'm ready to have a go at them.
I'd like to try out my strength.
Come on, let's go.
All four of them together
have a battle power of 1,507.
None of them appear
to be all that strong, huh?
It'll kill some time. What do
you say we rough them up?
There's not a single person around, is there?
Maybe they're scared of us.
If this really is the Saiyan's planet,
we definitely should not take them lightly.
Chaozu, let's go.
Right...
Ten-san!
Chaozu!
Ten-san, help!
–Chaozu!
Why, you–!
Okay, who's going to face us next?
I will!
Tenshinhan, be careful!
Okay, now it's your turn.
Hold on, Tenshinhan!
Sokidan!
Get out of there, Tenshinhan!
I got them!
That didn't hurt one bit.
This time, all three of us will go at them!
It looks like we took care of them.
Those guys were incredible.
Chaozu, I have avenged you.
He vanished!
–Kuririn!
These guys are invulnerable!
Where did they disappear to?!
Kuririn!
–Kuririn!
Let's go save him!
Dammit!
At this point, I'll let them
have it, even if it costs my own life!
That's it. That's more
like it. Otherwise, it's no fun.
We've laid two of you to rest.
Who's going to be third?
What?!
Before you do that,
let me show you to your graves!
This is our last chance!
An extra-large Sokidan!
Those guys were awful! It's
almost like they were undying monsters!
We beat them...
I-I'm alive...
Where are we?
We're alive! We're saved!
'Course ya are! You've just
been standing there the whole while.
Your minds went on journey.
Kami-sama let you have
valuable experience in minds.
How'd it go with the Saiyans?
What's wrong?
What're ya keeping quiet for?
The Saiyans that you saw were still
only half as strong as full-fledged ones.
They don't even compare to the strength
that Saiyans who are
now heading for Earth possess.
You mean, they're even stronger?
How about it? Do you
feel like running away now?
All right!
I'm keeping at it!
Ten-san!
I'm going at it, too!
I'm going to train here for the
next six months to defeat the Saiyans!
Me too!
What's that?! Is that your defense?!
Concentrate harder!
I'm just itching to kill you!
The Saiyans' power is terrifying.
The fated time is drawing ever nearer.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
I made it! The tail of the Serpentine Road!
This is where Kaio-sama is! Yahoo!
What's wrong with the ground here?
What are you doing?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Last Stop on the Serpentine Road!
Are You Kaio-sama?"
Stop picking on my father!
"Next time"
"Last Stop on the Serpentine Road!
Are You Kaio-sama?"