Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Gohan and Cell; a battle with
everything at stake was underway.
Vegeta?!
Now!!
At last... at long last, Cell was defeated.
Now, peace would return
once again to the Earth.
However, to achieve that purpose,
the casualties have been much too great...
"I'm Going to Train In the Next World!!
A Smile at Parting."
Y-You did it! Y-You really defeated Cell!
That was awesome!
Hey, Gohan! You were
really incredible! You did it!
I still can't believe it!
We've all been spared, huh?
Yeah.
We'll take you to where Dende is
in the Heavenly Realm right away.
Even without senzu beans,
once we have him touch you,
you'll be back in business!
All right, let's go.
Th-Thanks...
G-Gohan!
It's all right. He's just passed out.
Never mind him, are you okay, Yamucha?
Are you sure you can fly all the way to
the Heavenly Realm in the shape you're in?
Hey, compared to what Gohan
has done, it'll be a piece of cake.
You don't say.
Well, I guess I'll take Trunks.
Yeah, okay then, I'll take No. 18.
A-After all, she was one of Cell's victims, too.
H-Hey...
Piccolo, we're going!
Yeah, you guys go on ahead!
Okay.
Let me give you a hand, Vegeta.
You mind your own business.
Go on, anytime you want.
I don't need any of your help.
Is that right?
I've been completely outdone by
them, both the father and the son.
D-Damn you, Kakarrot!
Dying the way you did...!
I won't ever fight again.
W-What was all that with those guys?
I-It's gotten quiet...
M-Mister Satan! What in the world happened?
Eh? W-Well...
I saw the bento salesboy and Cell ramming
that strange light against each other,
but after that incredible
explosion, I couldn't see anything.
Oh, no, I suppose not, I suppose not.
Where's Cell? What happened to Cell?
Huh? C-Cell, um...
I-I defeated him!
I wish...?
It's the broadcast van we drove in on!
Just what you'd expect of Mister Satan!
In the end, he settled things for us!
Hiding your true ability like that–
what a marvelous performance, Satan-sama!
I-Is that really so?
O-Of course it is.
H-How in the world did you do it?
Hey, they kept dragging out
that senseless light-ball trick,
so I became impatient, and
sent Cell flying good and hard,
telling him to cut it out already!
Good and hard!
How captivating!
S-So then, what about the
bento salesboy, and those others?
Good and hard! Huh?
Ah, they thanked me, and then went home.
Hey! The radio in the
broadcast van is working!
A-All right. Mister Satan, what
you've just told me is the truth, right?
Who do you take me for?
I am the World Combat Sports
Champion, Mister Satan-sama!
That's right!
The Earth has been saved
from the demonic clutches of Cell!
Give him your thanks!
People of the world, thank you for waiting!
We now resume our broadcast!
Rejoice, people of the world!
The Earth–the Earth has been saved!
Thanks to Mister Satan!
That's our Mister Satan!
He did it!
Yeah!
Satan! Satan! Satan!
A savior appeared for us.
Perhaps all of our prayers to God reached him.
We must be grateful.
Pa!
Th-There, now...
Well, that settles that, huh?
Yeah, all because of you, Kaio-sama. Thank you.
Now that the pressure's off, I'm hungry!
Kaio-sama, do you have anything to eat?
What are you talking about?!
You blew my planet away,
so now there's nothing!
Is that right?
Oh, I'm so hungry, I could die!
You're already dead.
What choice do I have? I guess I'll eat this.
This ain't filling me up at all.
Good grief, what a lively dead person.
Are they coming?
Hey! You guys all did purty good!
Yajirobe!
Y'know, I was gonna go help out too,
but my aircraft was all on the fritz.
You don't say.
You never really meant to come.
A-Are you Dende?
Yes. Let me see Gohan-san, quickly.
Gohan-san!
Dende...
Thank goodness!
I'm so sorry about Goku-san.
It's not like that.
I was able to hear my father's voice.
I felt Father's ki, and could even smell him.
I was together with Father the
whole time I was fighting with Cell.
It was because I was with
Father that I was able to beat Cell.
Well...
In any event, you've done well, Gohan.
Piccolo-san...
You really have grown strong, huh Gohan?
You've come to, have you?
Dende!
You'd better get away
from her, fast! You'll be killed!
That's not going to happen!
Th-This is Kami-sama's Temple. You're all right.
Cell has been defeated by Gohan.
Gohan?
That's right!
He's ridiculously strong!
It won't do you any good to start rampaging!
Hey, you! Come a little closer.
You can thank Kuririn.
He did all he could to stand up
for you after Cell spat you out.
Y-Yeah, well, I mean, we
couldn't just leave you there.
I get it!
Kuririn-san, you're fond of No. 18!
Don't just come right out and say it!
Eh?! Are you serious?!
You're kidding, right?!
S-She's an Artificial Human!
Who were you expecting to be grateful?
Did you think you would get me
to clasp my hands together and say thank you?
Eh, mister?
Don't kid yourself.
Why, that jerk!
What kind of attitude was that?!
I'm going to send her sailing!
I doubt you could, though.
Never mind her, shouldn't
our first order of business
be to hurry up and use the Dragon Balls...
...to bring Trunks and the other
people who were killed back to life?
Yes, yes.
I-It's all right, Kuririn-san.
As far as friends go, you've got us, don't you?
J-Just shut up...!
Come forth, Dragon, and grant us our wish.
W-What is that?
No matter how many times I see him,
Shen Long is always incredible.
Y-Yeah...
Kami-sama, nice work.
Shen Long perfectly restored.
T-Thanks.
Now, speak forth thy wishes.
I shall grant thee any two wishes.
Two? That's right, thanks to Dende,
the number of wishes has increased to two.
Shen Long!
Please bring those people who
were killed by Cell back to life!
That is a simple matter.
Satan! Satan! Satan!
W-What?!
Everyone, please listen!
The military that was annihilated,
as well as the people
from the city who were lost,
are reportedly coming
back to life one after another!
It's a miracle!
This is also thanks to Satan defeating Cell!
That's right!
Sure enough, it didn't work.
The Dragon Balls and Shen Long
that Dende reconstructed...
Just in case, I sought him out,
but sure enough, I can't sense Son's ki.
He hasn't come back to life.
Is that so?
I can grant thee one more wish.
Speak thy second wish.
Isn't there any way you can
bring Goku... Son Goku back to life?
We absolutely want him brought back to life.
Son Goku has already
been brought back to life once.
It is not possible. Speak thee another wish.
He says he can't do it.
No, I'm sure there's a good
way to go about this. Think!
What about this?
What if we have time turned
back to before Goku died?
Oh! Let's go with that!
If we do that,
then Cell will also be resurrected,
before he blew himself up.
We'd be right back where we started.
That's right...
I know!
We could just ask Polunga on Planet Namek!
I get you.
Polunga, the original Shen Long,
can bring people back to
life any number of times.
That's right.
Both Chaozu and Kuririn were
brought back to life that way.
In that case, if one of us goes to Planet Namek...
Well, should we make that our second wish?
Guys, hold on a second!
It's me! It's Goku!
Goku?
F-Father?
I'm speaking to you from the Next World.
Listen to me, would you?
There was something that
Bulma mentioned a long time ago.
She said it was like I drew bad guys towards me.
When you think about it,
she's certainly right, ain't she?
Mm-hmm, that could be so, all right.
That Bulma is always saying too much.
And so, I have a hunch that the Earth
will be more peaceful without me around.
Kaio-sama admits to that, too.
Well, I suppose...
It ain't as though I'm
saying I'm some kind of victim.
Since I've saved the Earth and stuff,
Kaio-sama says they're
going to treat me special.
Ordinary folks, and bad guys
like Cell become just spirits,
but they're going to let me keep my body.
What's more, I won't get any older like this.
There's also fighting experts
from the past in the Next World here,
and it sounds like it's going to be lots of fun.
Experts from the past, huh?
Kaio-sama could have been brought
back to life by Shen Long's power just now,
but he passed, saying he
would stick with me instead.
And so, maybe it ain't fair to Chichi and Gohan,
but you don't need to bring me back to life.
Gohan's already a lot more reliable than I am.
Th-That's not true, Father!
There you have it. Bye, now.
Once you all die, I'll see you again!
Bye-bye!
Goku...
You know, for a dead guy,
he sure seemed cheerful,
so I guess he's not too upset about this.
Yeah. He's been like that ever since he was a kid.
"Oh, well," huh?
Absolutely.
He is always leaving us behind.
That's the kind of guy he was.
He fed me a senzu after I tried to kill him,
and then turned down becoming Kami.
Father was always kind...
And he always gave me courage.
Father, thank you.
Um...
Goku remains in the Next World.
Gohan and the others move on,
with memories of Goku in their hearts.
Um, I am awaiting thy second wish...
...all this time...
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
I'm going to train in the Next World,
but I'll come visit once in a while,
so keep your chin up, Gohan.
Hey, you don't have to
worry about what's to come.
I mean, he is your son, after all.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"New Days...
Father! I'm Hanging In There."
Let's take off for a new tomorrow!
"Next time"
"New Days...
Father! I'm Hanging In There"