Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
At length, the seven Dragon Balls
had fallen into the hands
of the Ginyu Special Corps.
I'll take the Dragon Balls to Freeza-sama.
You guys take care of the rest on your own.
Yeah, you're the best!
Gohan, Kuririn and Vegeta had teamed up
in order to defeat the evil emperor Freeza...
Okay, Ghurd, go ahead and
take care of those two runts first.
All right...
"Super-Magic or Just a Trick!?
Mr. Ghurd is Angry!"
A leadoff attack, huh? Ha!
Well, I doubt it will do any good.
Gohan!
Right!
Fools!
Stop!!
You brats!
T-They're not there!
W-Where are they?!
There they are! All the way over there!
Did they move in that one instant?
Dammit, I can't hold my breath any longer...
Those tiny bugs are
better than we thought, huh?
Their rating on my Scouter...
It's a rare species that is able to change
their battle power without transforming.
You've got some nice friends there, Vegeta-chan!
Those guys' speed and
power is incomparably better
than the last time we fought. But still...
Incredible!
You've increased your destructive power
several steps over what it was before, Gohan!
That's all thanks to having
Grand Elder-sama unleash my power!
But that guy fled all the way over there.
I'm sure he must have
stopped time again. Let's go, Gohan!
Right!
Oh! They vanished!
Stop!!
They're already here?!
W-Wait, there's no need to run away.
All right, I'll start with
that pipsqueak over there.
Oh, crap!
Over there!
Kamehame-Ha!!
Oh, man, we almost had him!
What are we going to do with Ghurd?
He's having trouble with them.
At this rate, we're going
to have to redo our bet.
All right, I'll bet this bar of chocolate
that he finishes it in the next minute.
Okay, I'm in.
Damn it! Attacking while keeping time
stopped consumes energy too briskly!
I don't know what's going on!
Kuririn and Gohan took the
Dragon Ball they worked so hard to get,
and flew away with it!
And Vegeta was with them!
What? Vegeta was with them, you say?
What on earth does that mean?
If I knew that, I wouldn't be
letting it get to me, would I?
I can't stand anything
that's been happening lately.
So you say, but didn't your space
capsule get all busted up? Whoops...
There's no way you can come home, is there?
But then, it's been six days
since Goku took off from here,
so he should be arriving pretty soon.
Huh? I can't hear you very well!
I know!
Really! What is everyone thinking,
tossing a lady aside like this?!
Son-kun, hurry and get here.
Look, Gohan! Every time he
stops time, he gets more worn out!
All right, let's keep attacking him like this!
Right!
S-Stop!!
I-It's no use! I don't have enough energy!
All right...
I think I'll go hide
somewhere and rest for a bit.
Let's see, let's see...
Behind that rock!
He's gone!
Over there!
How did they know I was here?!
S-S-Stop–
Hey, Ghurd!
This is disgraceful! You're going to
bring shame upon the Ginyu Special Corps!
Ghurd, you dummy!
If you get yourself beaten by those pipsqueaks,
I'm not going to play with you anymore!
You'll have to take your
3 o'clock snack separately, too!
I-I just got a little bit careless!
I'm going to put these maggots away right now!
All right, now's our chance!
Let's charge him, Gohan!
Right!
T-They're coming again!
All right, if that's how they
want it, I'll use my trump card!
What is this?
My body won't move!
It's my paralysis technique!
No matter how hard you
struggle, you can't move!
Dammit!
I can't move!
What happened to all
that energy you had earlier?
Looks like Ghurd is getting pretty anxious.
He's using his paralysis technique,
which he doesn't show off that often.
And against those two
sawed-off little bugs, too.
Hey, ReaCoom, the chocolate.
That bet you just made.
One minute has long passed.
All right. Ghurd, you piece of crap!
T-Those idiots! After I told them
to watch out for his supernatural powers,
they go launching a frontal assault.
I'm going to get you good for all
the embarrassment you've caused me.
Way to go, hand power!
Get them! Get them!
No need to hold back!
Your flesh is so soft, huh?
All right, now it's time
for the 100-blow punishment.
I'm going to hit you a hundred times!
1... 2... 3... 4...
5... 6... 7... 8... 9...
15... 16... 17... 18...
G-Gohan!
I'll do it to you, too, just to be fair.
Yow-ow-ow-ow-ow!
You give me my due!
Hey, Ghurd, how long are
you going to keep this up?
You're holding up the next fight!
Hurry up and finish them off!
Okay... let's see...
All right...
This tree will do.
Hey, you guys! I'm going to skewer you!
You might be good if
I cooked you up and ate you!
Yeah, I bet you'd like to escape, huh?
What's the matter? If you don't run away soon,
this huge skewer is going to run you through!
F-Father! Uncle Piccolo!
Gohan!
G-Gohan is in danger!
Piccolo, are you sensing
the ki on faraway Planet Namek?
Still, there's nothing that you
can do with your power as it is now,
Piccolo!
I can't eat with this knife!
[can't eat: taberarenai-fu; knife: naifu]
Yeah!
Can't you move? You poor things.
All right, I'll take care of the kid in
the yellow outfit first with this thing,
and then I'll use a different
supernatural power on the other one!
G-Gohan, can you do anything?
I-It's no use! My nerves are all paralyzed!
Here goes!
Our constraints have been released!
Kuririn-san!
Gohan!
T-That was dirty, Vegeta!
T-This was supposed to be a
fight between me and those kids...
That's something that you
guys decided for yourselves.
You think there's such a
thing as fighting dirty in a war?
T-To think that I would be done in by a
lowbrow monkey bastard Saiyan like you...
It's infuriating...
Hmph. You're the last
person I want to hear that from.
Who would have thought
we'd ever be saved by you?
Thanks.
Don't get me wrong.
Do you think I deliberately rescued you?
I just had the perfect chance to kill
that grubby bastard Ghurd, that's all.
This is no time to be feeling relieved.
Brace yourselves. We won't get lucky this time.
Hey, hey, hey! Ghurd got himself wasted!
T-That is a problem...
Our Ginyu Special Corps fighting pose
won't be as beautiful with one of us missing!
ReaCoom!
Butta!
Jheese!
Ginyu Special Corps!
S-Sure enough, it's not beautiful.
We'll have to have Commander Ginyu
think up a new pose for the four of us.
Putting that aside, we have to decide
who is going to take out
those two runts in Ghurd's place.
I still get Vegeta, you know.
All right, Jheese, rock-paper-scissors with me.
Okay!
First time is rock!
Rock-scissors-paper!
Tie, go again! Tie, go again! Tie, go again!
W-What could those people be thinking?
Yeah... I can't figure
out their character one bit.
Tie, go again! Tie, go again! Tie, go again!
The real hell starts now.
Goku was moments away
from landing on Planet Namek.
However, the greatest,
most evil emperor in the universe,
Freeza, was waiting there.
Further, Kuririn and the others were
squaring off against the Ginyu Special Corps.
Could they defeat ReaCoom, Butta, and Jheese?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Damn, these guys are strong!
They're tossing Vegeta around like a child!
At this rate, they'll die before I get there!
Hi! What's the matter,
are you finished attacking?
Well then, it's about time
that I killed you. Are you ready?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Savage ReaCoom!!
He's Bad, He's Strong, He's Outrageous."
Kuririn-san, Father is almost here!
"Next time"
"The Savage ReaCoom!!
He's Bad, He's Strong, He's Outrageous"