Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Bulma was all alone, guarding the Si Xing
Qiu Ball that had been taken from Vegeta.
However, the Dragon Ball
rolled down into the sea.
And then, after going to
great lengths to retrieve it...
Where are the other Dragon Balls?
Where is Vegeta?
No matter. Once you go before Freeza-sama,
you'll talk, whether you want to or not.
F-Freeza?
Come on!
"Charge!! The Kaio-ken and
Kamehame-Ha of an Indomitable Spirit."
Let me go! Please, let me go!
I don't even know Vegeta!
Even if you take me to Freeza,
there's nothing I can tell him!
Which would mean...
I'm done for.
Thinking back, my life has
been a series of hardships...
No! No, no, no!
I don't want to die here! Let me go!
Hey, calm down!
For crying out loud, what a handful she is.
There are still some things we have
to ask you. We can't let you die so easily.
How many times do I have
to tell you before you get it?!
I don't have anything besides that Dragon Ball!
We'll see.
I wonder how well you'll be able to feign
ignorance like this in front of Freeza-sama.
So, why is it that Freeza-sama
started collecting these Balls, anyhow?
Beats me. It's probably something
lower-rank soldiers like us don't need to know.
Don't you guys have the slightest
idea what the Dragon Balls are?
Let's go.
Y-You dummies.
When you get the Dragon Balls
together, something fantastic happens.
You don't say.
It's true! The Dragon Balls are
amazing things that can grant any wish!
Stop talking nonsense!
It isn't nonsense!
If you bring the seven Dragon Balls together,
you could have power beyond even Freeza's!
What?
I-It's true. That's why everyone
is so desperate for them, you know.
Hey, Buleberry, we don't have
time to listen to her hogwash.
So, wouldn't it be better
if you guys left me alone,
and went off to gather the Dragon Balls?
H-Hey!
I-If you make a wish about
wanting to make the universe your own,
it could come true!
Let's go, Buleberry!
Sounds interesting.
Hey!
Now, hold on.
Freeza-sama would be thrilled if we
brought all seven Dragon Balls to him. Besides,
if what she says is true, then we
could become rulers of the universe!
T-That's right! That would
be the best thing to do.
Come on, let's go where
the other Dragon Balls are.
I-I don't know where they are!
Y-You guys go look for them on your own!
I see. You're saying you want to
meet a painful fate here, do you?
No! Help!
Now, where are they?
T-The sea! They're submerged beneath the sea!
Is that right? That's where they are, huh?
Let's go, Raasberry.
What choice do I have?
Kaio-ken!!
All right!
Here goes!
Ka...
me...
...hame-Ha!!
Yikes!
Whoo, that was close, that was close!
But it looks like my body is
pretty much able to take it now.
Yow!
Hey...
J-Just a minute, here!
Hey, what are you planning to do?!
We're going to have you lead
us to where the Dragon Balls are.
Y-You've got to be kidding me!
I can't accompany you guys into that sea!
Just come along.
Listen, I won't run away!
I can't breathe underwater! Honest!
You knew?
Once they realize there
aren't any Dragon Balls anywhere,
they'll kill me for sure.
Get going!
I know–!
I'm going! I'm going, okay?!
I don't have anything like a weapon installed.
The most that I have are flares.
Where are the Balls?!
At this point, it's time to get desperate.
I remember! It's a little bit farther that way.
Is this where?
That's it. If I can lure those guys in there...
In there! In there!
Go on in there!
In there, okay?
J-Just a minute! What are you doing?!
This is certain to be the place where I die.
J-Just... just a minute! See? Over there!
See? They're over there! Over there!
Are those?
That's them! That's them!
They're over there, aren't they?
You should hurry along, too.
He's going to have them all to himself. Go on!
The more the better, you know!
Hurry up and take them.
Nice!
I'm blinded!
You take it from here,
if you please, Monster-san.
What kind of guys are these?! I'm done for now!
I've had it!
Good grief, you've got to be
kidding me, making me work this hard!
No way!
Wah! Kuririn! Hurry up and come back!
It's been nearly four days. Is it still far?
Yeah, a little farther. Dammit,
Grand Elder-san is going to be dead.
All right...
How about we try drastically raising our pace?
As far away as we've come,
there's no way Vegeta will know.
Y-You're right. Besides,
Father will be here really soon.
That settles it, that settles it.
Let's fly at full speed!
Right.
Go!
If we fly at this speed,
we'll arrive in an hour.
Right!
I've found you at last!
There are two presences– Kakarrot's son,
and the runt who was with him.
Though I thought they would be
coming here, after my Dragon Balls,
but they're somewhere pretty far away.
I don't know what they're planning,
but if I let this opportunity pass,
I probably won't have another
chance to force the location...
...of the last remaining Dragon
Ball that they have out of them.
If I take this one with me,
then even if that woman does seek this place out
with her unusual little device,
she won't be able to get all seven.
All right!
You're going to pay this
time for sure! Brace yourselves!
Freeza-sama!
We just received a message
from the Ginyu Special Corps.
They said that they are currently
passing through the area near 9035-XY,
and that they would be arriving shortly.
Very well.
They are finally arriving, are they?
Seeing as how, fortunately,
nothing has happened,
it would appear that Vegeta has been
unable to get all seven Dragon Balls together.
Remember this well: Once I get the Scouters
the Ginyu Special Corps will be bringing,
I will be able to find you,
no matter where you are.
Exactly what sort of men are in this Ginyu
Special Corps, who would be arriving shortly?
And with Vegeta having finally
discovered Kuririn and Gohan,
is there any way for
them to get out of this crisis?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
A giant, mysterious force is
approaching Planet Namek!
Hurry up and give me the Dragon Balls!
The Ginyu Special Corps that
Freeza has called are as strong as me–
no, maybe even stronger!
And there are five of them!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Great Battle Approaches!
The Ginyu Special Corps Now Takes the Stage!!"
Father! Hurry! Hurry!
"Next time"
"The Great Battle Approaches!
The Ginyu Special Corps Now Takes the Stage!!"