The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Inside of Boo, there's yet another Boo, huh?
Does this mean he was
absorbed too? By himself?
Having intentionally infiltrated
the inside of Boo's body,
Goku and Vegeta had at last
discovered Gohan and the others.
Inside here, I am immortal!
Suddenly, Boo appeared within his own body!
Faced with his invulnerable attacks,
Goku and Vegeta found
themselves in a desperate pinch!
Vegeta!!
"Where Is the Exit!?
Escape from a Collapsing Boo."
I'm going to absorb you!
Vegeta!
Do not interfere!
I'm going to absorb you first!
Dammit...!
Behind you!
Great, great, do that some more!
All I have to do is wait, after all.
Wait for you to use up your
power on worthless attacks like that.
Why, you...!
What's the matter?
All that's left for you is to be
absorbed, once you stop moving!
I want to see inside! I want to see!
I want to see!! I want to see!!
What in the world is
going on inside Boo's body?
It's useless for you to hide!
Indeed, you really are something else.
Typically, you should have already
used up your power a long time ago.
I-I still have enough power left to kill you!
What are you aiming at?!
Apparently, that wasn't
enough power to kill me, huh?
You're the one who's going to die!
I'm not so sure about that.
It's not the only thing that might happen.
What would happen if I rip this guy out?
I wonder if it might be
somewhat advantageous to us.
I can't wait to see!
Will you turn back into this fatso?
Will you instead turn
back into that skinny guy?
D-Don't! Stop!
Either way, it would seem unmistakable that
your power would drop from where it is now.
Stop! Don't touch that! Take your hands off!
It seemed odd that you
would protect this fatso,
so I thought there might be something to him,
and saw about forcing you into giving it up!
Take your hands off of him!
This upsets you more than I thought!
You appear to be considerably bothered!
P-Please! You must not rip that guy
out by force! I won't be me any more!
I won't be me any more?
That sounds interesting! Did you
think I would listen to what you say?!
Don't let your guard down, Vegeta.
He might appear again from somewhere else.
Look at that, Kakarrot.
This time, it looks like it's different.
H-Hey... There's something
strange going on with Boo.
Yes. What could be the matter?
What are you doing, Kakarrot?!
Now, while we can, let's
take everyone and get outside!
Y-Yeah.
W-Which way are we supposed to go?!
How do I know?
Hey, for some reason, that area
there is starting to wriggle around!
He must be transforming again!
Either into the fatso or the skinny guy!
F-For some reason, it's getting incredibly hot!
W-What's this?
The temperature of Boo's
cells is increasing sharply!
A-At this rate, both of us
will be boiled octopuses!
Kakarrot!
Are you okay?!
Damn it all! Ain't there an exit anywhere?
That was incredibly hot!
Not even magma is like that!
If we had been touched by that,
not even our bones would be left!
Vegeta, look!
It's a little bit bright over there.
Ain't that light from outside?
All right!
We did it! That is outside!
Ah! It's closing!
Hurry!
Stop kidding around!
Dammit! Open up again!
Come on! Hurry and open!
What, what? Is that stuff
from before coming again?
What was that, anyway?
I know, Vegeta!
You see? The very first Boo, right?
When he got angry, that steam came "pweet"
whistling out of the top of his head, right?
That's what that stuff from before was!
Which means...
In any case, move back until
you're right against the wall.
It's here!
Still not yet?
It's opening!
We made it!
They've come out!
The rescue was a success!
They've done it, Grand Kaioshin-sama!
We did it! Everyone is back to normal!
I-Incredible!
Goku-san and company have rescued everyone
that was absorbed by
Boo from inside his body!
Hide these guys for the time being!
Boo hasn't noticed yet!
Yeah.
It couldn't be...!
Hey, Vegeta...!
It couldn't be that his ki is growing, could it?
I-Impossible!
What's this?
What is it?
I-It's...!
H-Hey... he's turning into
something awfully tough, ain't he?
No... hold on!
Look! He's intent on transforming again!
I wish he'd cut that out already.
Th-This can't be...!
H-He's turning back...!
Turning back, you say?
H-Huh...?
Don't scare us like that!
I-It's true, all right...
What do you mean, he's turned back?!
Come on! Explain this all to me, would you?!
At last, Goku and Vegeta had
safely escaped from inside Boo's body,
together with Gohan and the others.
However, at the same time,
Majin Boo transformed once again.
Look! He's shrunk down quite a bit!
We did it, huh Vegeta? We may be
able to manage something like this!
And yet, there's something unusual
about the way Kaioshin is terrified!
Stay sharp, Goku, Vegeta!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
He's back? Kaioshin-sama,
what do you mean, he's back?
That's–That form is the
same one the evil Majin Boo had
before he absorbed the two other Kaioshin!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Earth Disappears!!
Boo's Reverse-Transformation of Evil."
Ah! The earth is suddenly gone!
"Next time"
"Earth Disappears!!
Boo's Reverse-Transformation of Evil"