Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Goku has finally won against Freeza.
However, the time of Planet
Namek's explosion has come!
I will live too. You'll see.
I'm the greatest in the universe!
I am Freeza, Emperor of the Universe!
You must be killed by me!!
You stupid bastard!!
"Planet Namek's Great Explosion!!
Goku Disappears into Space."
Kaio-sama!
What in the world has happened?
What about Goku?
What about Freeza?
Freeza has died.
Goku shared some of his own ki
with Freeza as he pleaded for his life.
He gave him a chance to live!
Freeza made use of it to attack Goku.
That rotten Freeza!
At that point, Goku had no
choice but to finish him off.
Then Goku has completely won!
Mm hmm. After becoming a Super
Saiyan, Freeza was no match for Goku.
He did it!
So a Super Saiyan is as incredible as all that?
Now Goku's strength is
the greatest in the universe!
Somehow, it seems like he's become
a person from some distant world.
However... however...
His being the greatest in the
universe may last for only a moment.
Which means...?
The explosion of Planet Namek is closing in!
He doesn't likely have enough time
to reach the spaceship he came in.
He's headed toward
Freeza's nearby spaceship,
but it appears to be broken down.
H-Hey! This is Goku we're talking about!
He'll get through this somehow!
I mean, up until now, he's
gotten out of so many pinches!
On top of that, Goku is
now a Super Saiyan! Right?
Y-Yeah...
Goku, hurry! In any case, hurry!
All right...
Please, let me be in time!
This ain't it!
Where is the control room?!
All right, this is good!
It's just about the same as
the spaceship I came here in!
Where's the startup switch?!
It's this one!
Start!
Please, start for me!
Start! Damn this thing! Start!
Start! Start! Start!!
H-How can this be?! How can it...?!
What is the matter, Kaio-sama?!
Freeza's spaceship, the last
thing we were depending on...!
It cannot fly at all now!
In that case, what about Goku?!
He cannot return!
He can only share in the
same fate as Planet Namek!
It's going to explode...
Planet Namek is going to explode...
Damn it to hell!!
I-I can't watch!
Goku!
Goku... Don't you die!
Don't you die!!
Damn it all to hell!
Kaio-sama...
Is Goku really...?
As I feared, it was no use.
Damn it, man...
Goku!
Then he's died after all?
What a pity.
We'll have to inform Goku's son
on Earth that his father has died.
It's going to be hard.
If we could have Bulma-san tell him...
I suppose so.
Please, let me be the one to tell her.
Okay, Yamucha.
And so, if you would.
Right.
Bulma!
Bulma... Bulma, can you hear me?
Can you hear me, Bulma?
It's me, Yamucha!
Yamucha? Huh?
That's right, it's Yamucha.
Through Kaio-sama, I'm
speaking directly into your mind.
Into my mind?
Really?
What is it, Bulma-san?
By any chance, is it from Kaio-sama?
That's what he said.
You sure knew what it was, huh?
Yamucha's the one talking right now.
So how are you doing, Yamucha?
Mm hmm. I am dead, but if
you can say I'm fine, then I'm fine.
Never mind that, I want you
to settle down and listen to me.
It's about Goku.
Goku defeated Freeza. A-And then...
Say, say, listen everyone, listen!
Goku put Freeza down, he says!
Really, Bulma-san?! He did it!
So he did, huh? Son finally did it!
Father won!
He won! He won!
Kakarrot beat Freeza?
Just listen quietly for me! That's not all!
After he defeated Freeza, Goku...
...tried desperately to take off,
but he didn't make it before
Planet Namek exploded and died.
Say, hold on, everyone!
Son-kun died when Planet
Namek exploded, he says.
Quite a shock, huh?
You stupid twit!
How can you say it like that?!
Think for a moment about Gohan's feelings!
Goku cannot return again!
You don't know anything!
We have the Dragon Balls here,
the ones from Planet Namek!
Planet Namek's Dragon Balls came
to Earth together with its people, see?
You'll be so surprised!
They say the Dragon Balls from Planet Namek
can bring people back to
life any number of times!
In other words, Son-kun, Kuririn-kun,
and Chaozu-kun can be brought back to life!
R-Really?!
What's the matter, Yamucha?
Everyone can return to life! Chaozu, you too!
Really?
It is the folks on Earth
that don't know anything.
Certainly Chaozu can be brought
back to life with the Namek Dragon Balls.
But as for Goku and Kuririn...
What about Goku and Kuririn, Kaio-sama?!
The Dragon Balls return people
to life at their point of origin!
Which means...?
Goku and Kuririn will
return to life on Planet Namek.
However, Planet Namek is no longer there!
There's just the vacuum of space.
The moment they return to life,
death awaits them again.
Kaio, with your power, isn't there anything...
isn't there anything that can be done?
There is nothing that can be done.
That isn't my area.
What's the matter, Bulma-san?
S-Son-kun... can't come back, they said.
Even if they did return to life,
they'd die immediately,
since Planet Namek isn't there.
T-That can't be!
This is great! It's turning
out just as I was hoping!
Freeza is gone. Kakarrot is gone.
I'm the one who is greatest in the universe!
I will rule over the entire universe!
Father is sure to... sure to return to Earth!
Are you still saying that, kid?
Your pop has died!
Bow your head to me now.
You are a child of the warrior Saiyan race.
You're supposed to have
unfeeling blood flowing through you.
You can be my underling if you like.
Father is sure to come back!
Just keep on spouting that forever!
C-Cut that out!
Are we going to go at it, kid?
Father will surely... surely be coming back!
I thought of you as a kid,
so I took it easy on you,
but you had to raise it to this!
You're sure you're ready for this?
Whoa, it's too early to die just yet!
Gohan-kun will be killed!
Gohan-san!
You wretched kid!
Stop, Vegeta!
F-Father... Father is
absolutely coming back...!
Absolutely!
Your optimism makes me sick!
Gohan-san! Shake it off!
Father...
Son-kun...
Son-kun!!
Goku has disappeared, together
with the destruction of Planet Namek.
What will the world be like without Goku?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Polunga, thanks and all,
but I don't need your help.
I'll be coming home on my own soon.
Son-kun, cut it out already!
Kuririn, Yamucha and the others
have been brought back to life
by Super Shen Long,
and they're waiting for you!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Son Goku Survived –
The Z Warriors All Resurrected!!"
Father is training on his way home!
"Next time"
"Son Goku Survived–
The Z Warriors All Resurrected!!"