The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Majin Boo, having absorbed
Gotenks and Piccolo, and then Gohan,
had transformed into the
mightiest and most evil of Majin,
with both ultra power and ultra intelligence.
D-Dammit, no!
It couldn't be...!
All right! It really is you!
K-Kakarrot!
It's about time I put you out of your misery!
Give it to me! Quickly!
Vegeta!
This is the end!
This is okay then, right?
Thank you, Vegeta!
All right!
"Magnificent Power!!
Vegetto Surpasses the Ultimate."
This is awesome! Better than I imagined!
You seem nervous, huh?
What's the matter?!
There's nothing to be particularly
surprised about, is there?
Kakarrot and Vegeta have been united,
so I guess that makes me Vegetto.
I wondered what was going to happen,
but it appears as if they
successfully combined together.
Now then, let's continue!
So that's it? Still, do you think that
just by combining you two together,
that you are a match for me?
Don't you toy with me!
I felt that a bit just now.
Is that so? I was still
trying to hold back on you.
What's the matter? You aren't about
to cash it in from just that, are you?
All right... I've finally gotten warmed up.
My apologies! I'm still not used to this body!
But I'm okay now!
This time, we'll get started for sure!
Let's do that! If you were
to have died on me like this,
I would have been greatly disappointed!
The fun is just beginning!
N-Now you've done it...!
The Grand Kaioshin-sama was right.
The power of these Potara is incredible!
That's more like it.
Hey, aren't we there yet?
W-What are all these tremors?!
It's likely that it is the
sound of Goku-san fighting.
W-We can hear it all the way over here?
I see. You do seem stronger than
you were when it was the two of you.
Indeed I have gotten stronger!
Enough to be able to kill you!
Enough of you being
carried away with yourself!
I was planning on playing
around with you a bit more,
but I'm not going to hold back any longer!
I'm sending you to the Next World right now!
If you can do it, go ahead and try!
I-Incredible! It's incredible!
To think that he can fight toe-to-toe with
Majin Boo after he powered up that much!
Toe-to-toe, you say?
Look, you, where in the world
are you directing your eyes?
Open up your eyes and watch closely!
Boo is... The Majin is being overcome!
He can win! At this pace,
he can win against Majin Boo!
Right, Grand Kaioshin-sama?
No! We cannot tell.
The fight's outcome,
you see, is a matter of fortune.
However, see, if he doesn't win, you see,
then there's probably nobody
else that can win against him, see?
We're counting on you! Goku-san! Vegeta-san!
N-Not bad... How do you like this?
How about it? Did you find him?
Mm-mm. It's no use, we didn't find him.
What about you, Videl-san?
It's no good. I didn't find him anywhere.
I, too, have searched all over...
I see... Just where in the
world has that Gohan gone?
Say, there's no supposin'
he's gone to Hell, right?
Gohan-kun would be the
absolute last person to do that!
She's right!
There is no way a magnificent
gentleman like that could go to Hell.
Huh?
Y-You know something,
you've changed quite a bit, huh?
You were the king of the
Demon Realm of Darkness,
and Babidi's right-hand man, right?
Y-Yes... However, here in Heaven,
I have learned the importance of mind and life!
As well, thanks to everyone's encouragement,
I have been able to be
born again as superbly as this.
Y-You don't say...
Well, that being so, Chichi-san,
it would indeed be ridiculous!
From what I hear, never mind Earth,
the dead spirits from the whole universe
are beginning to gather here in Heaven.
And within those billions, those trillions...
mm-mm, even greater numbers of spirits,
it doesn't seem likely to
find just one Gohan-kun.
I hear that Heaven here is
comparable to the universe in size.
Even so... even so...
I'm so sorry for you, Chichi-san!
Please, find it in yourself to take heart!
I, Dabura, will be certain to find Gohan-san.
Leave that to me, if you please!
What?
Is that... don't tell me...!
Yes, that's right!
There's enough energy gathered in
here to smash the planet to smithereens!
Will you indeed be able to stop this?
If you fear for your life, you can also dodge it!
However, once it falls to the ground,
it's all over–the Earth will be blown away!
Without a trace, in an instant!
Now what will you do?!
Hide yourself around here, if you would.
Huh?! You don't mean...?
Please, be quiet, Satan-san!
We'll be detected by Majin Boo!
Is that...?
Who is that guy? He looks
a little like that Goku guy.
That is Goku-san. So that's it!
Here I thought I could feel Vegeta-san's ki too!
So that's what's going on!
W-What's going on?
Satan-san, it's just possible
the Earth will be saved!
R-Really?
That's great!
H-Hey, hey...!
You can't go off so far on your own!
You shouldn't do that, you know!
Be happy! The Earth is...
What is he going to do with
all that enormous energy?
Don't tell me Majin Boo is
going to destroy the Earth!
So, then, are you prepared?
Prepared? You don't get it, huh?
Do you seriously think that all
that bluster is going to work on me?
What did you say?!
Well, fine. I'll give it a try.
Whenever you like! I promise you,
I won't run even one step.
You carry your boasting too far!
In that case, you and the
Earth together can cease to exist!
It's over!
G-Goku-san!
Here, I'm returning this to you!
Y-Yeow!
Satan-san!
What's that smug look for?
Are you proud of yourself for
bouncing that back just now?
You certainly have become stronger.
However, you still cannot
say you have surpassed me!
Is that so? In that case, how about I show you?
What is he planning to do now?
This is Super Vegetto!!
At last, the ultra-warrior
emerges–Super Vegetto!
The end of time for Majin Boo is approaching.
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
What's the matter, Majin Boo?
It looks like you're powerless now.
Talk about your disappointments!
You idiot! Hurry up and finish him off!
Don't back Boo any further into a corner!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"A Fissure Between Dimensions!!
Has Boo Snapped!?"
This is bad. Boo is really steamed now.
"Next time"
"A Fissure Between Dimensions!!
Has Boo Snapped!?"