Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
As the destruction of Namek continues,
Kaio has called upon Earth's Shen Long,
in order to grant a wish to
return to life everyone who had been
killed by Freeza and his men.
At the same time...
The two unimaginable super-powers
held by Goku and Freeza at last collide!
"I Am Son Goku's Son!!
Gohan Returns to the Battlefield."
Kaio-sama!
Are you all right?
Such tremendous power! Still not yet?
Hasn't Shen Long granted the wish yet?
We're counting on you, Shen Long!
Once those who were killed by
Freeza and his ring are resurrected,
the Grand Elder should return to life, and
Planet Namek's Shen Long should appear.
This is the only means by which
Goku and the others can be saved now.
Shen Long...
Father, hang in there!
This is terrible!
In three minutes, this planet
will undergo a giant explosion!
Full power!!
What?!
I-It can't be!
Is something the matter?
Father–Father's ki has disappeared!
What did you say?!
How could Father lose?
Then Son-kun is...?
Did you see that? My 100 percent power?!
How about that?! That's what you get!
There was no way someone
like you could have beaten Freeza!
There's nothing else we can do!
You realize that, don't you Gohan-kun?
If we don't escape from here right now...
Gohan-kun!
Bulma-san,
take Piccolo-san and
return to Earth ahead of us.
What are you saying, Gohan-kun?!
Freeza intends to wipe out all Saiyans.
That means if I return to Earth,
then Freeza will go to Earth next!
You're not, by any chance...
H-Hold on!
Wait!
Gohan-kun!
I am my father's–Son Goku's son!
And now I... I will take on Freeza!
You can't!
There's no way you can win!
I'm sure Piccolo-san
would say the same thing.
Bulma-san, take care!
Gohan-kun!
Gohan-chan! Gohan-chan!
Chichi-san, our Goku
can't possibly be beaten!
He must surely be winning against Freeza!
He's right, he's right!
On the other hand, don't matter how bad
Goku may be thrashin' on what's-his-mug,
once the whole planet
blows up, he ain't–
Enough of that!
I'll thank you not to be
sayin' such ill-fated things!
My Goku-sa won't be dyin' so easily!
I'm sure he's comin' home in good shape!
I'm sure... I'm sure he's comin' home!
Oh? Sorry about that.
What is the meaning of this?
Have we returned to life?
There's something strange about this!
What's with the ground shaking?
Not to mention the sky being dark.
What in the world is going on?
W-Where am I? Am I alive again?
Hurry, Shen Long! There's no time!
The sky! What's this?
Is this an indication that the
planet is just about to explode?
It looks as though it would be best
for me to get away from this planet.
If I get caught in the blast,
I'll lose even more power sharply.
T-This can't be!
Now, you'll have to face me!
You surprise me!
To think you still had the power to fly so fast.
Just what you'd expect of a Saiyan brat!
You... I'm going to defeat you!
You're going to defeat me, you say?
Are you thinking of fighting me,
Freeza, in your exhausted condition?
You for one are aware of my
overwhelming power, aren't you?
You're so miserable, you Saiyans.
Even when outclassed, you still
can't keep yourselves from fighting.
It's fine with me. This saves
me the trouble of going to Earth.
So then, last of the Saiyans, come at me!
What do you think you're doing?
Weren't you going to defeat me?
Or is it that before my overwhelming power,
the only thing you could do was run?
Why, you...!
Now then, what manner
of death do you desire?
J-Just a little longer.
If I can detain Freeza for two minutes,
he'll be gone, together with the planet...
I have succeeded.
Whosoever was killed by Freeza and his ring
on Planet Namek have been returned to life.
Thank you for service.
So then, farewell.
He did it!
He did it! Everyone has been restored to life!
What about the all-important Grand Elder?
How is Planet Namek's Super Shen Long?
They're all right. They should
be all right. The sky is dark.
That's proof that Super Shen Long
and the Grand Elder are back alive.
I'll verify it now.
How is this so?
Why–why am I in the mortal world?
Great! It's just as I figured!
All right!
Kaio-sama, hurry! You have to hurry
and tell him your intentions, or he'll...!
That's right! The Grand Elder's
measure of life will once again...!
I know!
Grand Elder of Planet Namek!
I am the Kaio over the Northern Galaxy.
Kaio-sama...
I want you to listen closely
to what I'm about to say.
Just a little bit more time...
Where did all that spirit
you had a moment ago go?
I know! I just thought of something nice!
I think I'll put you into
the same grave as your father.
What do you think?
That must make you happy!
You should be grateful for my kindness.
Okay, that put a little
bit more fight into him.
That kid! What is he thinking?!
So that's it!
I've figured out what you were after!
You're stalling for time, aren't you?
That must be it!
You've realized that this planet
only has a few more moments
of its life span left, haven't you?
Y-You...
You, who killed Father and Kuririn-san...
I can't allow someone
like you to go on living!
Masenko!
Hmph. It has to be like this,
or it wouldn't be enjoyable.
Just like a Saiyan.
However, I'm done playing around.
You've gone to such
trouble, so let me show you...
my 100 percent power,
which is what killed your father!
Father... Piccolo-san...
You're finished!
What?!
F-Father!
Why haven't you escaped?
I thought I told you to get away!
B-But...
Go!!
Right!
Father...
You undying freak!
Goku rises again from the brink of death!
Can Kaio's wish reach the
Super Shen Long Polunga
before the destruction of Planet Namek?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Kaio-sama, change that
wish to Super Shen Long!
Change it so that everyone besides
Freeza and me go back to Earth!
Goku, I know how you must feel,
but for now, go back to Earth!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"I'm Staying on This Planet!!
A Final Wish Towards Victory."
Father is about to unleash his full power!
"Next time"
"I'm Staying on This Planet!!
A Final Wish Towards Victory"