The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
The ultra-power of Super Vegetto
overwhelmed even Majin Boo,
who had achieved the ultimate power-up.
Forgetting himself in his anger, Majin Boo
destroyed the wall between dimensions,
attempting to crush the universe.
However, at the last moment, Boo reclaimed
his sanity as a result of Vegetto's blow.
That was close, that was close!
You sure do have awesome power, huh?
In which case, use that power to come hit me!
You were going to defeat
me as proof to all, right?
That you are the strongest in the universe?
"The Ace Up Boo's Sleeve!!
'You Become a Hard Candy'!"
Wow, this is unbelievable!
To think that Majin Boo's
attacks are of absolutely no use!
Well, it's only natural, in a sense.
It's all because Goku and Vegeta
there have merged together, after all.
It wouldn't be going like
this if Goku was by himself.
Still, you did really well to
have left Vegeta with a body, huh?
It's not surprising! I foresaw that this situation
could occur, so of course I left him his body!
Just who do you think I am, anyhow?
I am the guardian of the World
of the Afterlife, Great King Yama!
Indeed! And here I thought you
were always just acting important,
and absent-mindedly
stamping your seals on everything!
What's the matter? Come at me!
Try hitting me with that
power you just displayed!
Did you think I would
be beaten from just that?
You're a pesky bastard.
Shortly, I'm going to let
your central body have that.
If you were to just be wiped clean out,
then not even you could
return to normal again.
D-Damn it all...!
S-Shortly? Why doesn't he
just defeat him all at once?
If he lets him alone,
he could release that power
that can even break down
the walls between dimensions!
He must be playing around. Hmph!
This is not a game! Now!
Wipe out Majin Boo now!
Unless, maybe he has thought of something...
Damn it all...! Damn it all! Th-This...!
This wasn't supposed to be like this?
Look, don't get so depressed.
I'm surprised at this myself.
To think that I would be able
to make this big a fool out of you!
Y-You piece of crap! In that case...!
Ta-daa!
Super Ghost Kamikaze Attack!!
So that's it. This is the technique
of Gotenks, who you've absorbed.
You knew that, huh? Then you must
also know how terrifying they are.
Touch them in the slightest,
and they'll explode!
They sure are some creepy guys!
Go!!
Let me give you something good!
Did you think that
technique would work on me?
It's a technique thought up by a child!
You're awfully harried, aren't you?
I didn't think it would work either.
It's a technique I'm not accustomed to yet.
That was just some light warming up.
What you say is certainly true.
That was an infantile technique
thought up by a child. However...
...you can also use them this way.
We begin immediately!
Even increasing their number,
it will be the same thing.
Now, go, my ghosts!
Super Ghost Kamikaze Attack!!
To the right!
What?
Kame...
It couldn't be...!
...hame...
...Ha!!
What?
Kame...
It couldn't be...!
...hame...
...Ha!!
They can control them too, huh?
He fell for it!
Masenko!!
That's what you get for looking down on
them as child's techniques, you wretched fool!
You're the one who's the fool.
You should have realized it sooner!
Instantaneous Movement, huh?
It was a well thought-out technique, for you.
Not even I could have escaped the damage
of a Kamehame-Ha/Masenko double-attack.
Still, a child's technique is,
after all, a child's technique.
It will not work against me.
I thought you were a bit stronger than this.
Could you make me get serious
about this before too much longer?
See here! Finish him off right now!
Are you planning on amusing yourself
some more by getting Boo angry?
Just what might his intentions be?
Damn, it looks like he's
gotten too strong! That idiot!
If you get too confident of your power,
things aren't going to go well!
I told you, the important thing
to grasp is the movement of ki!
Didn't you listen to what I said?
S-Shut up!
That was dirty of you–merging
yourselves together!
That's a fine thing for you to say,
when you're the one who kept
merging together with all those others!
Come on, come on, what's the matter?
Just my legs are enough
against the likes of you!
Why, you...!
Gohan-san!
Gohan-kun!
Hey, Gohan! Come on out!
Gohan-kun! Where are you?!
Where in the world could
that Gohan have gone to?
Please, do not lose heart, Chichi-san.
I, Dabura, will be certain to locate
Gohan-san, even if it costs me my life!
Now, look here. You're already dead.
There's no way you can die any further, so
there's no way it could cost you your life, right?
A-Ahem...
Gohan-kun could be
alive after all, couldn't he?
Of course, I don't want to
believe that Gohan-kun has died,
and I'm not saying it has
to follow, but far away, I...
Yes, far, far away, I can feel Gohan-kun.
It's not by the ki that Goku-san
talks about, but I feel Gohan-kun.
Videl-san...
I'm sorry, I can't express it well...
Sure, right? I believe you too!
Gohan-kun is still alive!
If you believe in your wishes...
if you keep believing in them,
they will surely come true some time!
And as for me, I want Gohan-kun to be alive!
Bulma-san...
A young maiden in love is strong, you know!
Why, I...!
Is this true?
I believe as well, Videl-san!
Surely, surely Gohan-san is alive! Indeed he is!
Ah, this must be what is called affection!
How beautiful it is! How marvelous it is!
You still don't seem to fully understand,
so under the circumstances,
I'll explain it to you bluntly.
It is useless for you!
Useless to try to win against me!
How about finally giving up?
It would be useless for
you to work at it any longer.
Damn... To think that I would have
a hard time fighting against this guy!
However, at this rate...
What are you going to do?
Do you plan on continuing still?
Of course I do! There's no way I can lose!
I am the strongest in the universe!
Come and get it! I'll utterly pound you!
What's the matter? Are you afraid of me?
Come on, now! Come here!
A little farther... A little bit farther...
You talk like you're so big!
You're just a wimp who's all talk!
Now, come on, come on!
Hmph! You're one punk that never learns!
All right!
Hey, do you like coffee candy?
What?!
G-Goku-san! Vegeta-san!
Yahoo!! Hey, hey, hey! Worthless fool! Take that!
That's what you get for
coming near me carelessly!
You piece of crap!
I-It can't be...!
Y-You imbecile! This is why I told you
to wipe him out quickly, you little turd!
I just knew he was too confident in his power!
Now everything has come to naught!
Shall I chew you up all at once?
Or should I suck on you, little by
little dissolving you away instead?
W-What is this?! Vegetto has
been turned into a coffee candy!
There are no longer any warriors
left on Earth that can defeat Boo!
And so, the greatest crisis
to face the Earth has arrived!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
What's the matter, Majin Boo? At this point,
there ain't but a single thing
left that you can do, is there?
Then, Vegetto-san did have an idea
in mind when he was pressing Boo.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"A Hero Lost!? Vegetto is Absorbed."
Now that even Father and
Vegeta have been absorbed,
what will become of the earth?
"Next time"
"A Hero Lost!? Vegetto is Absorbed"