Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Piccolo continues his
fierce battle to the death...
...with Artificial Human No. 17.
Until Goku, Vegeta and the
others return from their training...
...in the Room of Spirit and Time,
he must hold out, no matter what!
Elsewhere, Bulma had
finally completed a controller...
...that can shut down the actions
of Artificial Humans No. 17 and No. 18.
However...
Already out of time, Cell reveals
himself to absorb No. 17 and No. 18!
"The Suicide Counterattack Proves Ineffective!
Piccolo's Flame Burns Out!!"
C-Cell!
Hell, I was preoccupied with
the fight, and didn't notice him!
What's with that strange guy?
What? Doesn't he know?
No. 17 and the others don't know about Cell!
At last, the day of commemoration has arrived!
The day when I merge with No. 17...
...and No. 18 and become my perfect form!
No. 17!
No. 18!
Who is this one?
Judging by his Red Ribbon marking,
I have to think he is one of
Doctor Gero's Artificial Humans.
Well, in any case, he is an older model.
It will be okay to ignore him.
What are you going to do about it, Piccolo?
If you wish to interfere, come right ahead.
For you to have powered up to that extent–
Just how many people have you sacrificed?!
Sacrifice? Hmph, rubbish!
On the contrary, it is an honor
to become a fraction of my power.
What?!
H-How can it be?!
Cell's ki has gone up unbelievably!
It's all over now! We're powerless!
There's nothing we can do!
For Bulma to bring that controller
to stop No. 17 and the others,
it'll take her 20 minutes,
however fast she may be!
In that case, you could go and
get this controller thing from her.
Doin' that would get it to you
faster than just waitin' around here.
T-That's it!
You guys are all soft in the head!
That's how you get from
doin' nothin' but fightin'.
I'm going to go fly there and pick it up!
If I fly all-out, I'm a lot
faster than Bulma-san's plane!
Kuririn...
I'm going to go help Piccolo!
Even if I can't do anything for him,
it's better than just waiting here!
S-Stop!
Tenshinhan, get back here!
Do you want to throw your life away?!
Damn, there's not a thing I can do now.
I yearn for the days when
I was acclaimed as Muten Roshi,
the greatest in the world.
Goku, hurry and finish your
training, and come back to us!
You may get a year's
worth of training in one day,
but right now, that one day is too long!
Goku-sa! Gohan-chan!
Still not yet, Vegeta?!
I don't know what you are,
but you're in the way!
Get lost at once!
I'm playing with him right now.
No. 17!! He plans to kill you
and absorb you into himself!!
–Run!!
–What?
Sneak attack? Toy with me, will you?
What is this?
This monster is going to absorb me?
In short, his name is Cell,
and he's a beast that's been
created up by Doctor Gero's computer!
He's still incomplete, but
once he absorbs you and No. 18,
it seems he will finally
become his perfect form.
What did he say?
Rejoice, my siblings!
When you become a part of my body,
it will mean the birth of
the perfect super-being,
with power greater than any other!
We will be the very ultimate warrior that
Doctor Gero was pursuing all those years!
That's enough of your nonsense!
You expect me to let myself
be absorbed by the likes of you?!
And as for ultimate warriors,
there's already one here!
Your will is of no matter.
That you will be absorbed is already certain!
I'm going to silence that
troublesome mouth of yours for you!
Get out of there, No. 17!
The enemy's battle power is far too great!
He must not be allowed his perfect form!
His aim is no longer the death of Son Goku...
...he intends to destroy the whole universe!
My, my.
Here I'm thinking you finally
have something decent to say,
and you tell me to run away?
Don't you make me the fool!!
Die!!
Dammit!
Are both No. 17 and that guy
like Piccolo just being sloppy?
That isn't it.
This Cell guy is just too strong for them.
You at least should run away, No. 18.
No. 17 will not listen to my warning.
If No. 17 is absorbed, he will
be beyond anyone's control.
It will be the end of the world.
What are you going to do, No. 16?
You go to hell!
Yikes!
Piccolo got him!
He did not get him.
On the contrary, he has not even taken damage.
H-How can this be?!
There's nothing that can be done!
Our worlds are too different!
Get out of here, No. 17!!
His neck is broken! This is bad!
It appears I've gotten
too strong for you, haven't I?
It's because I got overly enthusiastic...
...and killed more humans for
their energy than was necessary.
See you around.
H-He did him in!
His ki has vanished. Then we weren't in time?
Kami-sama!
Gohan!
Wait, Gohan!
Piccolo-sama!! Piccolo-sama!!
Gohan! If you go now, you can't beat him!
Wait!
In any case, all we can do is wait!
Still not yet, Vegeta? What are you doing?!
Piccolo at length has fallen before
the terrifying Artificial Human Cell.
At this rate, he will absorb No. 17 and No. 18...
...and become his perfect form.
Will Vegeta, Goku and the others make it in time?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Damn it, if this keeps up, No. 17
and No. 18 will be absorbed by Cell!
Hurry up and come out of there, Vegeta!
The time for me to fight has come;
it will be against Cell, before
even encountering Son Goku.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"One Final Remaining Hope...
No. 16, the Wordless Warrior, Takes Action!!"
Amazing! So that's how strong No. 16 is!
"Next time"
"One Final Remaining Hope...
No. 16, the Wordless Warrior, Takes Action!!"