Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Kaio-ken times two!
A times two level Kaio-ken was no
use against the mighty warrior Vegeta.
Ultimately, Goku dared to risk his life
by taking upon himself a times three Kaio-ken.
May my body withstand this!
Times three Kaio-ken!
"Now, Goku! A Final Technique
With Everything On the Line."
Hmm? What is he planning to do?
No! Your body won't be able to
bear it if you go higher than 2x, Goku!
Times three Kaio-ken!
What?!
A-Awesome!
Why, you–!
W-Why, you–!
H-He can do this! He just
might be able to beat him!
Goku's fightin' power
readin' has risen, you say?
What on earth is goin' on?
Baba-san, please hurry up
and show us how the fight is going!
How is Gohan? How is Gohan?!
I-It's no use! The ki over there is too
strong, and I can't control the power!
You don't suppose Goku has unleashed
some technique he's been saving, do you?
Sure! If that's the case, then...
H-He just might win!
I, on the other hand,
have a bad feeling about this.
It's said that the flame of a candle
burns intensely just before it goes out.
It seems to me that Goku is
tremendously overexerting himself.
Don't say anythin' so ill-fated!
I-Impossible! How could his– how could
Kakarrot's battle power be higher than mine?!
Damn... He's a tough one.
If I don't finish this quickly–
Damn! My body can't–!
What're you doin', Goku?! You
should just put him away right here'n now!
H-How can I let this happen?! I am super-elite!
There's no way I should be
beaten by that lower-class warrior!
I... I am...
I am the greatest in the universe!
My whole body is aching!
Sure enough, it looks like performing
a times three Kaio-ken was asking too much...
If I dally around, I'll be
the one who goes down first!
Blood?
I had my noble blood shed over
fighting a piece of trash like that?
This will not stand! This
absolutely... absolutely will not stand!
I don't need this planet anymore!
I'm going to crush you,
along with the rest of the Earth!
You're going to what?!
Go ahead and try to dodge this, if you can!
Even if you spare yourself,
the Earth will be blown to pieces!
Dammit, he thought this through!
I ain't got no choice but to risk it!
Times three Kaio-ken...
...Kamehame-Ha!
Ka... me...
ha...
There's absolutely no way
you can stop my Gyallic Ho blast!
me...
Let you and the Earth
together turn to space dust!
Damn it, man! If I hafta die like this,
I should've eaten more meaty buns!
Ha!
W-What?! It's just like my Gyallic Ho!
Yow, that's hot!
What is this?
T-The power of the ki
from Goku and that other guy
is manifesting itself through the crystal ball!
Kaio-ken... times four!
No! Goku!
H-He's pushing back–
M-My body!
H-He did it... He did it!
Son! You did it, didn'cha?!
You bastard!
Yajirobe? What are you doing here?
What, you hadn't noticed?
For someone as good as you are,
ya sure fought desperately, huh?
I guess so.
Still, you done a good job
of blowin' that wicked guy away.
You sure are one helluva dude.
W-What? What's the matter?
I used a technique that was
too much for my body to take...
Well, it wasn't nothin' normal, all right.
More importantly, Yajirobe,
you'd better get out of here.
H-How come?
D-Don't tell me!
He's still alive.
If that's all it would have taken for him
to die, there wouldn't be any challenge.
S-Still, there's no problem, right?
You're stronger'n him, ain'cha?
Like I told you, I overdid it, and now my
body is in shambles. I could be near my limit.
O-Oh, yeah?
Well, then...
H-Hang in there!
Dammit!
Why?! Why is Kakarrot's
battle power higher than mine?!
Damn it to hell! I am a Saiyan! I am
the strongest in the entire universe!
At this point, as much as I dislike
how ugly it is, I'm using my last resort.
I'll transform into a Great Ape, and crush him!
The strength of my Great
Ape form is nothing to sneeze at!
Damn it all, we chose the day
of the full moon to come here,
so we could wipe out the
people on this planet quickly.
To think that I would have to transform
just to defeat Kakarrot– it's infuriating!
That's strange. The
moon should be out by now...
Saiyan, no matter how hard you look,
it won't do any good. The moon is gone.
The one named Piccolo feared this
might happen, and eliminated it long ago.
Still, Son Goku can't
have very much energy left.
Even if the Saiyan
doesn't turn into a Great Ape,
it doesn't change the
fact that he's still in a pinch.
Then again, he's become
weaker, too. The Genki Dama!
If you can just hit him with a Genki Dama,
the way he is now, you can beat him for sure!
That's strange. He's just
going around in circles up there.
Why ain't he coming at me?
It's not here! It's not here! It's not here!
Dammit, the moon isn't
anywhere! What's going on!?
So that's it! Dammit! He is one
thoroughly aggravating bastard!
Kakarrot must have taken out the
moon ahead of time! Then it's unavoidable...
My battle power might drop somewhat,
but there doesn't seem to be any other way.
I can't wait to see the look
of stunned panic on his face!
He's finally coming back down.
The only way I can beat
him is with the Genki Dama.
Am I going to be able to
mentally focus myself for that?
Kakarrot...
You might have thought you could outwit me
by getting rid of the moon, but it won't work!
The moon?
What are you talking about?
As if you didn't know! Are you aware of
why we can transform during a full moon?
Transform?
The light from the moon is
what gets reflected from the sun.
Sunlight contains Bruits waves only
when it is reflected back by the moon.
During a full moon, those Bruits waves
reach a level of over seventeen million zeno.
What is he talking about?
When over seventeen million zeno's worth
of Bruits waves are absorbed by our eyes,
it triggers a reaction in our tails,
and our transformation begins!
A limited number of Saiyans are
able to create an artificial full moon
that emits over seventeen million zeno.
Things are not going to go as you expected!
Even if you have eliminated the moon,
by mixing this planet's
oxygen with my Power Ball...
Sorry to keep you waiting, Kakarrot.
The time of your death has finally come.
A lower-class warrior like you should
not have challenged a super-elite to battle!
The moment that strange light
started glowing, his ki dropped.
What the hell is he
planning to go this far to do?
What?!
Burst open and blend together!
What is that?
What?! What have you done?!
I-It can't be! He's created a moon!
You're going to regret
losing your tail, Kakarrot!
Is this the end?
W-What's that?
Transforming himself into a Great Ape,
Vegeta resorts to the
final measure available to him.
Does Goku have any chance of beating him?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Damn, now I ain't even got
enough strength left to blow my nose.
This is the end for you, Kakarrot!
Each of you, share with me just
a little bit of your Genki energy!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Battle Power Times Ten!!
Vegeta's Great Metamorphosis."
Father won't be beaten!
"Next time"
"Battle Power Times Ten!!
Vegeta's Great Metamorphosis"