Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Not a single ray of light
penetrated that hell of darkness...
But now, having released
myself from that world,
the time of my revenge is again at hand.
I will see to it that those worms
who inhabit the Earth's surface...
...experience an even greater
bitterness than I was made to endure!
Nearly ten months had passed
since the climactic battle with Freeza
had come to an end.
And then, one day, a new
danger prepared to begin its assault.
"Terrible Happenings in Heaven!!
Garlic Jr. to Become Kami!?"
There's some!
Yo!
Kuririn-san!
Quite a haul there, Gohan.
Yeah. Until Father comes back,
it's up to me to bring home dinner every day.
Good for you.
Even so, this is a lot of fun.
Kuririn-san, why don't you try it too?
Nah, I, uh...
Okay?
This river is full of fish!
Let's do this together, Kuririn-san!
Now, hold, on, Gohan!
That's not why I'm here.
Oh, you'll get your clothes all wet, huh?
No, that isn't it...
Kuririn-san, what a
great car! You bought that?
Well, yeah, it's not much.
Why not?
We haven't done anything in a while.
I'll hang around with you a bit.
Right, then!
Kurin-chan!
Aren't you done with your errand yet?
Sorry, sorry! I'm coming now!
Kuririn-san, who is that?
Well, she's sort of, you know.
Maron is tired of waiting.
Sorry 'bout that!
Who is that little boy?
This is Son Goku's son, Gohan.
Her name is Maron-chan.
Son Goku-san?
Didn't I just tell you about him?
Son Goku, the master martial artist.
I wonder if you have.
Anyway, this little boy is sure cute.
Little one, how old are you?
F-Five years old.
You know what, Gohan-chan?
Your big brother and big sister
here are on their way to a date
at the Kame something-or-other House.
And so, we can't play
with you for a little while.
Sorry, okay?
M-Maron-chan! What are you...?
Oh, Kurin-chan, don't tell me
you're jealous of this little boy?
That's not it, but still...
Well then, one for Kurin-chan, too.
Anyways, Gohan...
Everyone's getting together
at the Kame House to visit,
since it's been so long.
Why don't you come too?
Sure, I'll go!
But I have to check with Mother...
Oh, yeah. Your mom sure is
fussy about these kinds of things.
Well, if she does let you, come on by.
Everyone will be waiting for you!
'Kay.
See you.
That other person must be Kuririn-san's...
Girlfriend! What do you know,
Kuririn-san finally found a girlfriend!
Father will be so surprised
when he comes back!
As strong as you are now, are
you still advancing your training?
Kami! What business do you have with me?
You haven't changed at all, Piccolo.
The reason I have appeared here...
...is because I'm thinking of having
you come sit on the Throne of Kami.
What's this?
My limbs are growing heavy.
You should be able to
serve as the Earth's Kami.
Both in strength and mind,
you are the only one there is
who can take my place.
I have no interest in the Throne of Kami.
Why don't you take a look around you?
The Demon Clan has
been becoming active lately.
It may be just a bad omen,
or something may already be happening.
In any case, you should get
ready for them, don't you think?
Piccolo...
Someone there.
That will be enough!
You're Garlic Jr.
It's been some time, Mister Popo.
Why are you here?
You are child of Garlic, who competed
against Kami-sama and Kami's throne.
But you're supposed be sealed
in your own created Dead Zone.
That's right.
If it hadn't been for Son Goku,
not to mention his son,
everything, including the eternal
life I got from the Dragon Balls,
would have gone according to my plan!
But I will come back to life
as many times as it takes...
...to realize my revenge against Kami.
I will be the absolute ruler!
C-Can't move.
This is one of the specialties
of the demonic Four Monarchs!
Be a good fellow and give up.
I give up.
Then answer my question. Where is Kami?
Don't know. Mister Popo really don't know.
Lying to us will do you no good.
Mister Popo not lie.
Worthless fool!
Not even your great power
will work within that light.
I doubt you'll be able to escape from there.
You get to live.
You won't object if I wait
here until Kami returns.
I'll at least let you live that long.
Cheers!
What do you know?
There's more to Kuririn than we thought.
Look at this guy!
He ignores his training, and
manages to find such a cute sweetheart.
"S-Sweetheart" is a bit strong,
I wouldn't say that just yet.
Oh? You mean we aren't sweethearts?
In that case, I could go for this guy as well!
Is that so?
Oh, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Yamucha!
Yamucha-sama...
J-Just kidding! Don't take it so seriously!
I mean, right?
Nuh uh, I was serious.
Oh, no!
Hold on, this has gone far enough.
Just how do you feel about Kuririn?
Huh? How do I feel about Kuririn-chan?
Maron doesn't know!
Now that I think about it, Kuririn
might be better at this than I thought.
I envy him.
We have to settle this matter now.
Hey, Kuririn!
I am your master.
What is the matter?
This is sort of out of the blue...
In other words, I'm something
of a father figure to you.
However, I do not remember
giving you my permission...
...for you to be seeing a young lady like this.
But sir! Didn't you just congratulate me?
That's right! Now you're
sounding high-handed!
Where's the harm in it, Master-sama?
You didn't let me finish!
It so happens that where this
young lady is concerned, there's–
Say, Turtle-chan, could you stop
calling me a young lady like that?
I have a name, it's Maron-chan!
Oh, I see.
Well then, Maron-chan,
as far as you're concerned,
there's one condition.
Condition?
It couldn't be...
What is it, Turtle-chan?
Maron-chan, you have to let me
Pafu-pafu your hooters, just a little bit!
Ow, ow ow, ow!
What are you thinking?!
Really!
T-That was a joke, guys! A joke!
I said no, an' I mean no.
No matter what?
No way. The longer you're
hangin' around Goku-sa's friends,
the faster you get stupid.
How can you say that?
Didn't you make a promise to your Ma?
You said you'd make up the
studyin' you'd missed before.
But...
You've already used up your playin' time.
You'll study until evenin'.
That's a good boy. Study hard!
What's this?
Who's there?
G-Garlic Jr.! What are you doing here?!
I welcome you to my temple, Kami.
I had heard that you fools in the
Demon Clan were up to something,
but I did not think it was because
you had escaped from the Dead Zone!
I see your arrogant manner
of speech hasn't changed any.
Mister Popo! Mister Popo! Where are you?
Perhaps this is what you are looking for?
Even having successfully guarded
this temple for many hundreds of years,
this is how Mister Popo winds
up when matched up against me.
What does someone like you,
who mistakes his own level of status,
come to this temple for?
Garlic Jr.! I can't believe you
still aspire to the Throne of Kami?!
What do you mean, you can't believe it?
I will replace the likes of you,
and rule over this domain!
You insolent fool!
You expect me to just
surrender the Throne of Kami?!
Interesting.
You sound as if you're about to
show me what you're capable of.
So let's see what it is to
have the power of a Kami!!
What?
Kami! Submit, and kneel down before me!
I'll let you be one of my servants, if you like!
Don't be absurd!
I'm going to keep you alive for now.
After all, I need to use the Dragon Balls again.
T-The Dragon Balls?
For the time being, I'm
going to make you experience
all the pain and suffering I felt,
until I revive my father Garlic!
I'm sorry, Mother. I'm a bad boy.
Hey, cut it out, Haiya Dragon!
You want to come with
me to the Kame House?
Kuririn-san, we'll be right there!
It's here! This is it!
Garlic Jr.-sama, what is it?
This is what my father Garlic had
taken from him by the previous Kami,
"Aquamist."
The water of oppression!
Inside this container is the Aquamist fog,
the essence of the evil in mankind's heart.
Anyone who inhales this mist will find
themself reborn as a Demon Clansman.
The world will be turned
into a hellish, demonic place!
And there, reigning over
it from the highest point...
...will be Garlic Jr.-sama, yes?
That is correct!
Having overtaken the Throne of Kami,
Garlic Jr. proceeds with his ambitious plan.
However, no one is yet aware of
the reality of what has happened!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Bad news! Thanks to Garlic Jr.'s weird mist,
Chichi, Old Man Turtle Hermit
and the others are acting strange!
It took quite a bit of effort
to find you, son of Son Goku!
How about it? Why don't you
come to the Heavenly Realm with us?
You're quite welcome!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Black Mist of Terror...!!
Everyone Turns Demonic."
As if I would join you!
"Next time"
"Black Mist of Terror...!!
Everyone Turns Demonic"