Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
The Dragon Balls were
falling into devilish hands.
Meanwhile, Goku, while
on his way to Planet Namek,
received some unexpected good
news from Kaio, in the Next World.
That's awesome!
You mean that each of them has arrived
there together at your place, Kaio-sama?
They all want even tougher
training than what you went through.
"Listen to Me, Goku! Hands Off Freeza."
Can I talk to Goku?
Place your hand on my shoulder and speak.
Yo, do you hear me, Goku?
Yeah! I'm glad to hear you're all doing okay.
Yeah, but the gravity here has us beat.
Our bodies are so heavy,
we can barely even run.
Yeah, I know, I know.
But I'm heading for a place called
Planet Namek, where they have Dragon Balls,
and I've started training under
even more incredible gravity than that.
I've got to get a whole lot stronger
in the next five and a half days,
or we're going to be in bad shape.
Huh? Why? Has something happened?
I was injured really bad,
so Kuririn, Bulma and Gohan went to
Planet Namek to search for the Dragon Balls.
But that Saiyan, Vegeta, had also gone
to Planet Namek to find the Dragon Balls.
–W-What?!
–So, did they get themselves done in by him?
No, it appears that Vegeta still ain't
discovered Kuririn and the others yet.
But that ain't all. There's
something even more unbelievable.
They said there are these other
strange guys who are after the Dragon Balls.
The weird thing about
them is that they were wearing
the exact same outfits Vegeta was.
What's more, they said that one of them
has a ki that's far greater than Vegeta's.
W-What?!
What? Has something happened?
E-Even greater than Vegeta, who
was too much for even Goku to handle?
B-By any chance, was his name Freeza?
I don't know, I ain't heard,
but once I know, I'll tell you.
If it is Freeza, then
this is exceptionally bad...
G-Goku, I'm going to
check out Planet Namek for you.
Could you, Kaio-sama?
Let's see, which direction is Planet Namek in?
Yamucha, tell us what's going on.
I'm definitely sensing a tremendous ki.
Now to find the source of this ki...
F-Freeza!
What, you know him, Kaio-sama?
Goku, this foe is more than just too
much for you, he's the worst of the worst.
There is no way you can handle this opponent.
Huh? W-What do you mean by that?
Listen to me, Goku. This is an
order from Kaio. Do not go near him.
When you get to Planet Namek,
take the other three aboard and
get out of there immediately. Got that?
I'm not just saying this for your own sake.
I'm saying this for the sake
of everyone on Earth, Namek,
and many other planets as well.
If you launch some shoddy
attack on Freeza and get him angry,
something terrible is going to happen.
You have to leave that guy alone.
Is he really that incredible a guy?
I'd kind of like to have a look.
Absolutely not! Do not go
near him! Do you understand me?!
But still...
"But still" my spongy hind end!
Goku, whatever it takes, gather the
Dragon Balls, and bring us back to life.
Piccolo!
I'm going to build myself up even more
than you did here, and go to Planet Namek.
All right!
The two of us will blow away
this ridiculous whatever-his-name-is.
Don't be absurd! You guys
don't know a thing about Freeza!
There's no time. Hurry and start training us.
If you're planning to fight
Freeza, I cannot teach you.
Promise me that you won't go to Planet Namek.
All right.
You mean it, right? I'm trusting you.
That goes for you, too!
There's no way I'm going to
keep a worthless promise like that.
I won't be able to surpass Goku
by doing the same training that he did.
I'll have to pick up the points of the training,
and then hone the techniques on my own.
All right, how about we get started?
Here we go...
Let's do this...
First of all...
...try to make me laugh with a pun.
I will allow anyone who
passes this test to train under me.
Even if he has told me not to mess with
him, there's no harm in getting stronger!
All right, let's try jumping
all the way to fifty-times gravity!
Hey, if we keep flying at this pace,
how long before we arrive
at the Grand Elder's place?
We should be able to
make it in another five hours.
Damn, I can't find anywhere
that has multiple powers.
What does that mean?
Aren't there any more villages?
There are two powers moving.
That's strange... one of them doesn't
feel like a Namekian, or one of Freeza's men.
That's disconcerting.
Maybe I should go check it out.
Meanwhile, on Kaio's World...
...a fierce battle of puns was unfolding.
Sure enough, the ones who had trouble
with this test were Tenshinhan and Piccolo.
I am chagrined...
Ten-san, hang in there!
Tenshinhan...
(mumble, mumble, mumble)
And I can really make him laugh with that?
You'll be fine. This is my ace-in-the-hole gag.
It is, huh?
All right,
I'll be right back.
Ten-san, fight!
Here I go!
Bring it on.
Here goes!
Y-You think... you think...
You think...
Ten-san! Hang in there!
Have faith in yourself! This one
is definitely going to go over well!
Huh? What was that?
This is different! His determination
is different than the others up to now!
Now!
You think up your nose
is secret, but it's (s)not!!
is secret, but it's (s)not!
What's that? A secret up my nose?
I-I'm not sure I understand it,
but in any case, it is funny, huh?
W-What should I do? Should I laugh?
I did it!
You did it, Tenshinhan!
Ten-san!
–You did it! You did it, Ten-san!
–Well done! Good for you!
This is nonsense!
Stop, Dende!
It's Vegeta! He's discovered us, all right!
He's coming straight
toward us at incredible speed!
Hide! Hurry!
Huh?
W-What happened? He changed direction.
There's another large ki out there!
He went in that direction!
This power is Zarbon, no doubt about it.
I've been waiting for him
to move out on his own.
28...
29...
30!
Damn... I finally made it to 30...
That's fifty-times gravity for you...
Now then, to begin your
conditioning. I should warn you,
my conditioning is un-condition-ally severe.
I just said another one!
H-Huh?
You guys want to go home?
–That's funny!
–That was funny! That was funny!
Yeah, wasn't it though? Wasn't it
though? You can laugh even more.
Laugh!
That was great! That was great!
Go ahead, laugh!
Okay, let's get started right away.
Hey! Bubbles-kun!
First of all, you are going
to catch Bubbles-kun here.
Oh, is that it?
Easy, easy.
I'm not so sure. It took even
Son Goku three weeks to do it.
Goku?!
It took him three weeks?
Question!
What is it?
If we catch that monkey,
will you train us, Kaio-sama?
That's wishful thinking. After
this, you have to train with Gregory.
You'll train with me after
all that is done. Understood?
All right.
Okay, run, Bubbles-kun!
–Wait up!
Wait up! Wait up!
I'll fly.
Good luck!
Now then...
W-What the–?!
Is this what you call training?
This is laughable.
I don't remember giving you
permission to participate in the training!
Hmph! I don't wish to undertake any training
under you if it undermines my own dignity.
Under-take any training under me...
if it under-mines your dignity...
You made a triple, did you?
Piccolo, you passed the test. I will train you.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, what are
you all standing around for?
Laugh! Laugh! That was funny!
That was funny, right?
If only I had a Scouter,
a village would be easy to find.
That's... Vegeta!
Yo, it's been quite a long
time, hasn't it, Zarbon-san?
I have disposed of Dodoria.
Next, it's your turn.
What?!
Y-You disposed of Dodoria?
Without any trouble.
Unbelievable.
You'll find out once we go at it.
You'll realize how strong I am.
Vegeta, why are you
turning against Freeza-sama?
It's a simple matter.
I've never liked that Freeza bastard.
Up until now, I've been
pinned down by his power,
and had no choice but to do as he said,
but then I unexpectedly
learned that I could gain eternal life.
You mean the Dragon Balls.
You think I'm about to let Freeza have them?
Once I have obtained eternal life, my
chance to beat Freeza will come along for sure.
You fool. Do you think you can
beat Freeza-sama with just eternal life?
It's too bad you don't have a Scouter.
I have gained more power than you
could imagine over my many battles.
You're the one who doesn't understand.
Freeza-sama's ability far
transcends even your level.
I'm through with all of this pointless talk!
I heard from Dodoria that
Freeza is afraid of Saiyans.
I'm going to show you
that Saiyan power, right now!
You really are full of yourself.
What Freeza-sama was afraid of
was the Saiyans banding together.
You can't do anything all by yourself.
Well, let's see about that.
He deflected it!
Incredible! It's a clash of ki against ki!
Vegeta and someone else
are banging into each other!
H-His opponent is probably the
one who was at that Freeza guy's side.
T-They're both monsters. There's
no way I can square off against them.
I hope the two of them
end up flattening each other.
All right...
Hold on to me tight!
This is our chance!
We'll hurry to the Grand Elder while
the two of them are fighting each other!
If I fly as fast as I can, we'll
get there a lot sooner! Let's go!
What's the matter?!
Zarbon-sama, of all people! Your movements
make you look like you're standing still!
Damn it!
To think that you'd be
so helpless at this level!
You've surprised me. You have
indeed made magnificent progress.
But as a result,
you have awakened my true power,
which has been dormant for many years.
Zarbon's expression has suddenly changed.
Exactly what is this hidden,
fearsome power of his?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
What is this weird sensation I'm feeling?
Even as far away as I am,
I sense an incredible battle.
Unlike Saiyans, we do not transform
into something unnecessarily large.
Our power just increases. Overwhelmingly so!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Nothing but Goosebumps! The Handsome
Warrior Zarbon's Devilish Transformation."
Father, it looks like Vegeta is about to lose.
"Next time"
"Nothing but Goosebumps! The Handsome
Warrior Zarbon's Devilish Transformation"