Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
In the face of Cell's
bottomless power, even Trunks,
who had gone beyond Super Saiyan,
was utterly powerless to do anything.
The fate of the Earth was as
a candle in the wind. However...
I have one final question.
How is it you were able to power
up that much in such a short time?
If you had more time, is it possible
you could become even stronger?
How should I know?
I couldn't tell unless I tried it.
So then, it's not impossible, huh?
Very well. Then, in order
to alleviate my boredom,
I will hold a martial arts tournament.
What was this? He is going to
hold a Tenkaichi Tournament?
With extraordinary confidence in himself,
Cell has suddenly changed the situation around.
"A Final Battle Closes In on Goku!!
The Mystery of the New Tenkaichi Tournament."
My biggest aim, of course,
is to see the faces of humans, struck with terror!
Yes, yes! That's the sort of face.
Dammit!!
T-Thank goodness! Somehow, he's still unharmed!
B-But what happened? Where did Cell go?
Hey! Wait for me!
Dad...
What happened to Cell?
I can't beat him... I couldn't beat him.
W-What the hell happened here?
I'm sorry. I was not able to do anything.
Hmph. Of course not.
There's no way the likes of you
could have beaten Cell in his perfect form, right?
T-That's just not so!
After all, Trunks has so much more power than y–
Kuririn-san!
Ah, there, there! There, there, there, there!
Hey there, you guys!
Don't just stand there, hurry
and go help him! Trunks is–
Trunks is going to die, you know!
Don't worry! He got through it without being killed.
–Really?!
–How's that?
M-Miserable Cell! What kind of guy are you?
At the time, Trunks' power was
indisputably higher than Cell's!
How in the hell did he
overcome that difference?
It looks as though I, too, will have to go in
there next–into the Room of Spirit and Time!
M-Martial arts tournament?!
T-That's what he said?
Damn him!
He's using us to amuse himself!
But who's going to participate?
He's an opponent even you
guys couldn't do anything against!
I...! I...
Once Goku-san comes out,
I plan on going back into the
Room of Spirit and Time and train again.
Neither you or Kakarrot will be necessary!
Once I use that room for
one more day, it will be settled.
Me too...
I will join the tournament too!
N-No. 16...!
P-Please, take me to the Capsule Corporation.
To the place where mom is, you say?
T-That's right.
There, I will have her repair
me so that I can fight again.
You'll see, I'm sure to be of some use.
Don't be ridiculous!
You're one of Doctor Gero's
Artificial Humans, aren't you?!
Wai–!
Sure thing.
I'll take you there, and ask her for you.
Kuririn-san!
You don't have to worry, Trunks.
I don't think this guy is bad.
But...!
Those other two,
that were swallowed up by Cell,
weren't all that bad, either.
They are indeed different
from the Artificial Humans
that were in your future,
by their very dimension.
And besides, right now, we need
all the strong allies we can get, right?
Here goes...
I owe you one.
Hmph. Hurry and come on out of there, Kakarrot!
No matter what you've done, it's useless.
If I can just go into that room one more time,
we'll get by without having Cell lord it over us.
I'm not about to lose...
I'm sorry, Father.
I fell asleep before I knew it.
You've sure worked hard, Gohan.
That's enough for today, now rest.
But then, what will you do, Father?
I'm going to go try to train a little longer.
T-Then I will do so too! Please, take me with you!
All right, I'll finish for the day, too.
Father...
But then, Gohan...
Tomorrow we're going to
have even harsher training!
We have to get you to aim even higher
than Super Saiyan as soon as we can!
R-Right!
So, should we get something to eat?
Yes!
Here, thanks for waiting.
Drink your fill, okay?
Oh, my! Vegeta-chan, it's been so long!
You're as handsome as ever!
My, this gentleman over
here is handsome as well!
Are you a friend of Vegeta-chan?
B-By all means, I'm pleased to meet you.
Pardon us. Is Bulma-san here?
Oh, what's that now?
–Um, I said Bulma-san...
–Yo, Kuririn!
If you're looking for Bulma, she just contacted us.
She said she was on her way here now.
Then she's not yet back from
the Heavenly Realm? I see...
Hey!!
Muten Roshi-sama!
We got a message that everyone would
be returning to the Capsule Corporation.
Staying at the Kame House,
there's no way of knowing
what the situation is, and all.
Where's Gohan-chan?!
He's, you see, still at the Heavenly Realm.
Still, huh?
Let's see... that's funny... then this here is...
So that's it.
A Tenkaichi Tournament, huh?
Yes. That's what Cell said.
It will be held ten days from now.
He said he would let us know
the location and everything later.
I wonder, will the matches will
be held like in the tournament?
No. I'm not entirely sure
about it all, but apparently,
the format will be one fighter
challenging Cell at a time.
Miserable Cell!
Is that what he told you? I get it, then.
It must just be his arrogance,
now that he's obtained
the ultimate in strength.
Still, by choosing the Tenkaichi Tournament,
he's being rather sharp, isn't he?
I can't wait to show what I've got!
It has you fired up, huh Yamucha-sama?
Yeah!
You can say so, but you were
beaten in every single one, huh?
Turtle Hermit-san, what is this
Tenkaichi-whatever Tournament, anyhow?
Oh, yes indeed!
Well, allow me, as one who has
won the Tenkaichi Tournament,
to explain it to you.
Huh? Muten Roshi-sama,
you've won it before too?
He's talking about a long
time ago. A really long time ago.
Long ago, there was a contest
held among all the masters of the martial arts,
to determine who among them
had risen to the highest peak,
and was the Tenkaichi,
the best martial artist under heaven.
The first time Goku and the
others participated was during,
as I recall, the 21st Tenkaichi Tournament, right?
It was Goku's first appearance,
and yet he managed to reach the final round!
However, his opponent was too much for him.
He was unfortunately beaten by
another master, named Jackie Chun.
And then, five years later,
the 22nd Tenkaichi Tournament was held.
It was at this time, you see,
that Tenshinhan and Chaozu
first appeared before my eyes.
And so, as Goku and
Tenshinhan competed for victory,
and by a narrow margin, Goku lost!
What a lower-level fight!
That's why everyone here
could compete in this tournament,
given your level of ability.
Now, the 23rd Tenkaichi Tournament,
which was held three years afterward–
that was one awesome
and tumultuous tournament!
After all, Goku got married,
Piccolo, using the name Ma Junior, entered,
and Kami-sama possessed
a human and entered too!
It was no longer the kind of tournament
that any ordinary person could enter!
So then, in the final match,
Goku and Piccolo put on a battle,
with the fate of this world in the balance!
In the end, it was Goku who won,
and became the strongest man on Earth!
However, the fighting ring was lost,
and the Tenkaichi Tournament
has not been held since then.
And that was... let's see, how many years ago now?
Huh, Kuririn?
Ah, is that so?
That must have been something terrible.
Even so, why would Cell do something like this?
Why, indeed? Even by winning
the Tenkaichi Tournament,
he can't rule the world.
Cell said he didn't have any
interest in ruling the world.
The purpose of the tournament
was to confirm his own strength,
as well as to plunge the
whole world into terror, he said.
And besides, it would serve as exercise
to draw out his strength even more.
Damn. He's sure gotten full of himself!
All right, then! In that case, we'll enter too,
and put his nose out of joint!
Yeah!
You'd better give up such pointlessness.
Small fry such as yourselves
will serve no purpose at all.
Well, in any case, now we can relax.
Why does Chichi-san say we can relax?
How should I know?!
Don't you get it?
If he's goin' as far as holdin'
a Tenkaichi Tournament,
then Cell is goin' to obey the rules!
Which means that if he
kills you, it'll mean him losin'!
We'll get through this
without anyone dyin', right?
–That's right!
–In that case, maybe I'll enter as well!
Maybe I'll enter as well.
Don't tell me you're still
clinging to your former glory!
An old guy like you would–yow!
However, with a rule like that, the
Earth will be saved from this crisis, won't it?
Piccolo-san is around and all, and pretty soon,
Goku-san and Gohan-san will be
coming out of the Room of Spirit and Time...
Yeah!
That's right, huh?
Just a second!
Even supposin' we can't stop
Goku-sa from wantin' to enter,
how come you have to have
Gohan-chan enterin' in too?!
But, Chichi-san, as you just said,
there's the rule that says you
can't kill, so there's no danger...
Whether there's any danger or not,
I've got no mind to allow Gohan-chan
to be participatin' in any tournament!
B-But...
The Earth has already been saved from its crisis.
Cell is settin' up his Tenkaichi Tournament
so that only those who want to fight have to!
T-That may be so, but...
That's why I'm not allowin'
Gohan-chan to fight any more!
When Gohan was born, Goku-sa agreed to that!
Now then, it's time for your milk!
Goku-sa, I'm going to make
this boy into a great scholar!
A scholar?!
That's right.
The world's at peace now.
If he were to become a martial artist,
he'd be servin' no purpose at all.
I-I suppose not...
It's true! I can't let my guard
down to any one of you here!
You'd all inspire Gohan to
be one of your delinquent pals!
–Delinquent, she says?
–How awful!
A-Am I a delinquent too?
Now then, as for the tournament grounds...
Well, this area will do, I suppose.
How about I make the ring a little
larger than the Tenkaichi Tournament ring?
Next...
As I thought, the stone here
appears to be of fine quality.
Fine. It is a bit plain, but
I'll think of something later.
Now then, how about I head
over to the television station?
Cell, and his unusual way of thinking–
will the devilish Cell indeed obey
the rules of the Tenkaichi Tournament?
There is a sense of hell about
this ultra-Tenkaichi Tournament,
as it awaits its warriors.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Trunks, are you sure Cell said
he would give more details on TV?
People of the world, I have wonderful news.
I have decided that if you lose
the tournament that I will be holding,
I will kill every last person in the world.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"100% Ratings!! The Cell Games Call for
Death with an Exclusive Live Broadcast."
There's no way we're going to lose!
"Next time"
"100% Ratings!! The Cell Games Call for
Death with an Exclusive Live Broadcast"