Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
With three hours remaining
before Goku returns to Earth,
the world meets with its greatest
threat ever, in the form of a revived Freeza.
Shall I say it plainly for everyone?
This is the end of the Earth.
All right!
Everyone spread out and kill off
the Earthlings here, one by one.
Yes!
However, just then...
Can we help you with something, Earthling?
I have come to kill you.
"Freeza Halved by a Single Stroke!!
Another Super Saiyan."
What did he just say?
I have come to kill you.
He said he's come to kill us, Papa.
It sure must be nice to live in ignorance.
Oh, I know you, all right.
You're Freeza, aren't you?
There's no reason to be so surprised.
I know everything about you.
What an honor.
To think that my name is already known...
...on a planet as far removed as this one.
Unfortunately for you,
you apparently haven't heard...
...that I'm the most powerful
being in the universe.
I also know that you are going to die here.
Such irresponsible talk.
Take care of him!
The rest of you go finish
off the other Earthlings.
Hey, you guys! You're better
off not taking such futile actions.
Or else you guys will die here too.
Kid, you're finished.
Hey! Hold on, he's all mine.
His battle power is only 5.
Piece of scum.
This will hurt a bit, but just be patient.
It'll be over quickly.
Why you rotten punk!
Freeza-sama...
You're not so bad after all.
What? What's the matter, everyone?
All of a sudden, an
incredibly large ki appeared...
...and in an instant, a
bunch of other ki vanished.
What in the world could be going on?
What do you guys mean?
What's happening over behind that mountain?!
Impossible! This ki...
It's Saiyan!
You do pretty well, don't you...
...for an Earthling, anyhow.
Next, it's your turn.
This is a surprise. Did you hear him, Freeza?
I think he's going to try to kill us next.
This brat doesn't know his place.
How about I teach you an important lesson?
Those who are only half as strong as they
ought to be are the ones who die soonest.
You mean like yourself?
What did you say?!
Having been reduced to that ridiculous form,
it must have taken a lot of
nerve coming all the way to Earth,
just so you could be killed.
You've got quite a mouth on you, kid.
Papa, he needs to be punished.
I would say what he has cost
you here already is worthy of death.
It's more than you deserve,
but I will serve as your executioner.
You should be honored.
You two will be killed by me
instantaneously. This I know.
This you know?
That's a rather unique expression.
Come at me with everything
you have, right from the start.
I won't go as easy on you as Son Goku did.
Son Goku?
That's the name of the Super Saiyan, Papa.
I see now, so you're one of his friends?
I've never met him. I only know of him.
You only know of him?
You just got finished saying–
that you were going to kill
off all the Earthlings here,
before the Super Saiyan
arrives, in order to mortify him.
That's exactly what I said.
You're going to be one of them.
Of course, since you've
killed all my men, it means that I,
Freeza will have to take
matters into my own hands now.
Such a miscalculation.
What do you mean?
I can purge the Earth of all its
vermin for you in the blink of an eye.
That's not what I meant!
Your miscalculation, the one I'm speaking of...
...is that Son Goku is not
the one and only Super Saiyan,
but that there is also another one, right here.
What?!
Well, this is a surprise!
I admire your ability to hold a bluff for so long!
It can't be!
What's this?
What kind of ki is this?!
What's going on?!
This is just like it was on Namek!
It's Father!
What?
It's the same ki that my Father had back then!
That means...
A Super Saiyan? Impossible!
There's another Super Saiyan, besides Kakarrot?!
Now there's two of them,
and I'm not among them?!
This is a Super Saiyan?
Those eyes!
Those are the eyes!
What are you so frightened of?
Burn in hell!
It's started!
Damn!
Don't fly!
I told you, they'll have Scouters with them!
If we're discovered, we're finished!
If we want to get closer, we'll have to walk!
Kuririn-san!
Gohan, where is Goku and what is he doing?
Much as I hate to say it,
there's not a thing we can do!
Once Goku finally returns,
Earth may not even be here, dammit!
Vegeta, surely you can manage something?
Shut up!
Unless you want to get killed
with the rest of us, go home now!
You managed to return safely from Namek.
No matter how big an idiot you
may be, you should know the situation!
Idiot?
Vegeta, you can't accuse
Bulma of being an idiot.
That's right, Yamucha!
Yeah!
She's just the world's biggest rubbernecker,
not to mention biggest shrew.
Hold on! You're not being any help at all!
Huh? Oh, right!
I've had just about enough of you, Yamucha.
And the rest of you, what's so funny?
That's probably the last laugh we'll ever have.
Ah, hell.
Hold up!
I can't believe they would
just leave a lady behind like this!
Bulma-san, let's go home now.
We've come so far, how can we leave now?
Who do you think you're talking to?
I've been in scenes this
dangerous many times before...
...and I've managed to come
through them every single time...
I'm Bulma-sama!
So then, let's go!
Hey, Vegeta! Take me with you!
You're on foot anyhow!
Freeza, we won't be served
if you destroy the planet.
This Son Goku guy won't be able to return.
I know that, Papa. I didn't
put everything I had into...
You can't afford to think...
...so little of me as to ration
out your power like that.
Not since you're going to be killed by me.
Why you smart-mouthed kid!
Take this!
Freeza!
The planet is going to crumble!
What?!
What's this?!
Now what? Huh? What's happening?
Hey, what's going on?!
What kind of fight are they having?
Not too bad.
Freeza being alive was certainly unexpected,
but who could that young man be?
His power may be greater than even Goku's.
I have absolutely no data on him.
At this point...
We'll just have to wait to see what turns up!
Hey... why you...
Foolish Freeza.
It looks as though your arrogant
conceit is what will cost you your life.
A fight is something
to be finished all at once.
Well then, as you wish,
let's finish this, all at once.
Oh no!
Freeza intends to blow him away,
along with the whole planet!
That's ten times the energy he
used to destroy the planet Namek!
Freeza! Are you trying to
obliterate the whole planet?
We can always finish Son Goku off in space!
What the...?
Everyone! Get down!
The planet's going to explode! Freeza, let's go!
What's this?
What?!
Impossible!
Why aren't you dead?!
What's the matter? Is this all you've got?
You did it, Freeza!
Looks as though he was
no match for us after all.
I got in some good exercise
before Son Goku showed up.
Freeza!!
You challenge me with
such a low-level attack?!
What's this?
There's another Super
Saiyan, in addition to Goku?
Who can this young man be,
who so easily cut Freeza clean in half?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Whoo! He took Freeza apart in no time flat!
His strength is awesome! Who on earth is he?
Cold the Great, now it's your turn.
I have to finish this up,
and go to meet Son Goku-san.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Heya!! It's Been a While...
Son Goku Returns."
Father, welcome back!
"Next time"
"Heya!! It's Been a While...
Son Goku Returns"