Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Day by day, Gohan continues to grow.
However, he still has far to go.
The Saiyans arrive in eleven months.
"Don't Cry, Gohan! His First Fight."
Oh, no! It's night already!
All right, now...
Mother!
It doesn't hurt, it doesn't hurt!
This is what works best.
No, Father! Let's go
home and take some medicine!
It'll be fine. Here.
It hurts! It hurts!
All right, one more to go!
Looks like it's all over.
I would've liked to have gone
up against that guy one more time.
Oh, well...
You're not very cheerful, huh?
You, huh?
Hitting three consecutive
home runs is incredible, isn't it?
Is there something
you're not satisfied with?
I'm not a baseball player.
I'm a martial artist.
I know that, but unless you have
a job, you can't make a living, right?
All right! Lucky, lucky! Yamucha-san?
After the next guy, you'll be up!
I'll be counting on you to smash it!
There's a bonus in it for you!
Sure. Just leave it to me, coach.
I'll be sure to hit a
home run, just you watch.
T-Two million zeni?! Damn, that's a lot...
I'm counting on you!
Sure, sure.
That's pretty demanding...
Play ball!
I don't care... if it...
hurts you... let him hit you!
Get hit by the pitch...
and load the bases!
Strike!
So that's it, huh?
If you want to get hit so badly!
D-Dead ball!
W-Why, you! You hit
me on purpose, didn't you?!
Don't give me that!
You were trying to get hit!
Why you bastard!
You want to go at it?!
You mustn't, Yamucha-sama! If you
go in there, people are going to get hurt!
It'll be okay! I'll go
easy on them, okay? Ha-ha!
Ha-ha... But still...
Here, here! Here! Here!
You bastard!
Here, here!
This one can handle himself!
Kuririn!
Nice to see you after so long.
But why?
I'll explain it all later.
In any case, please come with me.
What?! You say Goku has died?!
Him and this Saiyan both lost to each other.
But still, that's just like Goku.
Goku...
Oh, but please don't be
all that worried about him.
We can bring him back to life
with the Dragon Balls, after all.
Come on, hurry!
This isn't good, Yamucha-sama.
She's still mad about you
standing her up on your last date
because you didn't have any money.
T-This doesn't necessarily mean that
things are all patched up between us, okay?
This is a state of emergency, so I'm
just working together with you temporarily.
Yeah, I know that much.
If you were to apologize,
though, that would be another story.
Who, me? It doesn't bother me that
I'm not together with everyone else!
I don't care who comes attacking,
I can take them on myself well enough.
T-That might be so,
but it would be a shame!
Kami-sama said he was going to
specially train us up in the Heavenly Realm!
What?! Really?!
T-Training with K-Kami-sama?!
That's okay. You don't have
to come if you don't want to.
W-What are you doing? Let's go, Pu-Erh!
Don't dawdle around! Come on, come on!
Ooh, that hurts!
I wonder how many days it has been.
If I don't step on it, a year will
have gone by just like that. All right...
Help!
But then, no one's going to help me.
I can't run away here.
That looks painful!
Don't be scared, don't be scared.
All right, now...
Ready, set... come on, you!
Ooh, yow... yow...
You mean it was stuck in this deeply?
I've got it!
Just hold on. It's almost done.
See?
It doesn't hurt, it doesn't hurt.
This is what works best!
Here. This ought to be enough–
Sure enough, it's just like I read in books.
There are dinosaurs that
don't eat meat. All right, then...
It's been a long time
since I've been this fired up!
The fighting is going to start up again, huh?
And there's only a slim hope of us winning.
No, that's not necessarily so!
This time, we'll have Piccolo,
and Goku should be coming
back to life even stronger, after all.
On top of all that, we're going to be
able to undergo Kami-sama's training!
T-That's right, huh?
Depending on how our training goes,
even we can still become stronger!
All right, let's do it! I don't
care who these Saiyan guys are,
I'm going to make sure that
they're the ones who are beaten!
That's the spirit, Yamucha!
What's this? They're
getting along fine after all.
Don't be jealous, don't be jealous!
Must be nice...
I know! Once he's feeling better...
Great! That'll be great!
I've gotten quite a bit stronger too, huh?
All right, then!
All right!
It's no use.
I'm back!
Here, I've got lunch! But this time,
leave some for me, okay? Don't eat it all–
You, huh?!
Let go of him! He's hurt!
Let him go!
Shoot!
Gohan learns for the first time
how harsh the laws of nature are.
However, he cannot shrink back now.
The Saiyans will not wait for him!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Once Yamucha-san and the
others are trained by Kami-sama,
those Saiyans will be a piece of cake, huh?
Damn, I'm tingling all over!
Don't sell those guys' abilities short.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Saiyans, Mightiest
Warriors in the Universe, Awaken!"
Father, do you really think
I can become a great scholar?
"Next time"
"The Saiyans, Mightiest
Warriors in the Universe, Awaken!"