Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
The Saiyans, the mightiest
warriors in the universe,
were drawing closer and closer to Earth.
I give up. How far does this road go?
It's like there ain't any end to it.
At this rate, a year will have
passed before I meet this Kaio-sama.
When you're not eating
or sleeping, you will fight me!
Set your mind straight!
You can't mean it. I'll die.
Then get stronger!
Even stronger than me! And...
...stronger than the Saiyans
who will be coming in six months!
"Last Stop on the Serpentine Road!
Are you Kaio-sama?"
Do you want to die?!
Yow-ow-ow-ow-ow!
Wait!
Don't forget that your
opponent wants to kill you!
I know, Piccolo-san...
Nyah-nyah!
Is that all the jumping power you've got?
You're even softer than your father.
Well now, shall I finally
put you out of your misery?
Die, Kakarrot!
S-Stop picking on...
...my father!
That little brat!
Wake up... Kakarrot...
What are you doing over there?
Wake up...
Wake up... Kakarrot...
You little brat! What the
hell has gotten into you?!
Damn!
Why, you–!
You dirty brat!
What's the matter?
Nowhere left to go!
H-His tail!
That's it, all right...
It was half a year ago that I pulled it out.
And now it has grown back.
Which means... it can't be!
How can this be?
You little brat!
Die!
Wha–?
What?!
A-At this rate, I'm done for!
Begone!
What?!
What's up with that moon?
Cheers!
My, my, we've finally gotten them together.
Now we'll be able to bring Goku back to life.
We can take a breather now, too.
Now all we have to do is
wait for those infernal Saiyans.
You say that, but originally, when
Goku was a baby, he was a Saiyan too,
who was sent here from Planet Vegeta
in one of those round vehicles, right?
N-No he wasn't! That
might be the way he was born...
...but Son-kun is an exemplary Earthling.
Right, Turtle Hermit-san?
Er, of course he was.
What's the matter?
The moon is out.
Oh, you're right.
It's been a while, huh?
Something about that moon...
Don't get too carried away, you dirty brat!
T-That's Saiyan blood you've got, all right.
The power I've got right now
won't do any good against the Saiyans.
Let go of me!
Damn...
Dammit! At this rate, the Earth is
going to be destroyed by that brat!
W-What's that?
Wake up... Kakarrot...
So that's it.
The thing that's behind that moon...
...is the pod that Son
Goku came here in as a kid.
It's all over now!
Sorry about that.
I'm going to make sure that I draw
out those dormant abilities of yours.
Geez, you sure are a lot of trouble.
A tail!
Hooray! I'm there!
Huh?
There ain't anything here.
You've got to be kidding me.
What's that?
He's there! That's where Kaio-sama is!
This is it, all right. There's his house.
What?! What?!
What's wrong with the ground?
Dammit!
Incredible... It's like I'm being
sucked in by some outrageous power!
I-It's no use! It feels like my
body is as heavy as lead! Dammit!
I've finally... reached... here...
and I'm going... to meet
Kaio-sama... no matter what!
A little farther... A little farther...
But before that, let's
find me something to eat.
K-Kaio-sama? Are you Kaio-sama?
Despite how he looks,
I'm sure he must be incredible.
G-Good day. I'm Son Goku.
I ask that you train me.
Kaio-sama, before we do,
can I ask you for an apple?
Wow, Kaio-sama, impressive!
You climbed up there easily!
Kaio-sama, sorry, but pick me
another one. I'll catch it this time.
All right, whenever you're ready!
I caught it! I caught it!
Kaio-sama, teach me
martial arts, okay–I mean, please?
Is that training?
You're saying I should move like that, right?
This is definitely hard...
K-Kaio-sama, what's the
matter with the ground here?
What are you doing?
Is this curious man the real Kaio-sama?
When does Goku's training begin?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Whoo! My body is so heavy,
I can't move the way I want to!
Surprised? My training is a bit "straining"!
Also, I'm so hungry, so hungry!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Battle with Gravity!
Catch Bubbles-kun."
Father, do you really think
I can become a great scholar?
"Next time"
"The Battle with Gravity!
Catch Bubbles-kun"