The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Vegeta had run out of actions he could take
against the overwhelming
power of his greatest foe, Majin Boo.
But then...
Take good care of your Mama.
Trunks-kun!
Uncle, how come?!
At last, Vegeta prepared himself for death,
as he resolved to lay down
his life in battle against Boo.
In order to defeat you,
I'm going to make sure
you can't restore yourself,
by blowing you to tiny bits!!
Farewell! Bulma... Trunks... and... Kakarrot!
"The Nightmare Revisited!!
Majin Boo Has Survived."
V-Vegeta!
Vegeta!
Piccolo!
It's too late! That's the mark
of Vegeta's life burning out!
You said it yourself, didn't you?
That Vegeta is laying down his life,
and for the first time,
fighting for someone else?
Videl-san, you're sure that Gohan and
Goten went off to where these horrible
Madoshi and Majin Boo guys
you were talkin' about are, right?
Yes.
Gohan aside, how come
you didn't stop Goten for me?
I blame you for this, Videl-san!
I'm sorry. I never would have thought
that Goten and Trunks would go too.
Videl, don't worry about it too much.
After all, those two little
urchins aren't the kind to listen
to what you would have told them anyhow.
Moreover, Goku and the others are with them.
There's nothing to worry about!
Right.
That aside, you're sure this is the right way?
Yes. They should be way in front of us.
All right! I'm speeding up!
Why... Why would Vegeta do such a thing?
Vegeta!
Impossible!
It can't be!
It's not so! There's some
kind of mistake! Vegeta...!
For him to do something,
like killing that many people...
Bulma, don't worry so much about it!
The Dragon Balls are meant for times like this!
It's okay! Everyone who died
can be brought back to life!
That's not the problem here, is it?!
Hey now, no crying!
Hey! Fly this thing right!
Sorry, sorry!
Y-You know, at the time, there
was something strange about Vegeta.
He was filled with the same kind of evil Vegeta
had back in the past when he was so terrible.
Yup! He wasn't normal!
I wonder if he's returned to being the
Vegeta he was when he first came to Earth.
Hey! Didn't I just tell
you to fly this thing right?!
It's not my fault!
Damn! What the hell is this?
It's like the whole sky is being pulled apart!
What was that just now?!
A great explosion went off
somewhere in the distance.
What's this? My heart is trembling...
I-It can't be! Vegeta...!
I-It's no use! It looks like that
shock gave us engine trouble!
I can't control it!
What?!
Yamucha-san, do something!
Dammit!
I-It's no good!
I'm leaving her with you!
What happened?
Vegeta...
Vegeta's ki has completely vanished.
Kuririn, take these two
back to their homes for me.
I'm going to go see how it turned out.
I'm going too!
That's right, there's nothing I can do by going.
Be careful!
Kuririn, it won't do for me
to keep quiet about this...
Afterward, tell the family.
Tell them... what?
I don't know about Goku, but Gohan...
Gohan has already been
killed by Majin Boo, it seems.
Y-You're kidding!
That's what I heard. Vegeta said so.
–I leave it to you.
–H-Hey!
It can't be... Even Gohan? How do I tell them?
Yamucha, what was that blast back there?
I'm not sure. It was an
incredible blast, wasn't it?
Ah, thanks to No. 18-san, we've been saved!
This is incredible.
Vegeta...
So that's it.
However much damage he takes on,
Majin Boo can regenerate himself.
You've blown him into so many
pieces as to keep him from doing so.
Vegeta... you've sacrificed your very self...
For the first time, you fought
for someone else, and died.
You've extinguished yourself...
For you to die, and leave nothing behind...
A fitting end for the high pride of Vegeta...
We've been saved by him, have we?
D-Damn...
Babidi!
Hmph! Still alive, are you?
As weak as you are, you sure are persistent!
Looks like you survived
this with your barrier.
M-Majin Boo...!
Struggle around, will you?
I'm going to finish you off!
What?
The fragments from Majin Boo...!
W-What?!
I-Impossible!
How can this be?! Majin Boo is alive!
B-Boo...!
Majin Boo...!
You been buried?
N-No, no! Look closely! Closely!
What happened to your feet?
Never mind about that, quickly, quickly...!
You'd think they'd be kind
of important, though, huh?
H-Hey! Return me back to normal!
Back to normal?
You should be able to do it!
Hurry up! I'll die, you know!
No reason I couldn't do it...!
What are you doing?! Do it now!
I could do it...
Do you want to get sealed up again?!
Hurry and do it!
All right, nice work, Majin Boo.
But then again, those bastards!
They're the ones who did this to me!
That green guy and those two runts!
You're absolutely going to pay for this!
I won't wipe out this whole planet at once!
I'm going to make you suffer!
We'll show them how terrible
Babidi-sama and Majin Boo are!
Being on the ground is too dangerous!
We're taking these two to Kami's palace!
Piccolo! What do you mean?
What happened to Vegeta?
What happened to Majin Boo?
Piccolo, d-don't tell me...!
Majin Boo has survived.
Th-That can't be! What about Vegeta?
Not even a trace.
Which means, you're saying
Vegeta died for nothing?!
In any case, we're taking
these two to Kami's palace.
Y-Yeah...
Our only star of hope now is these two...
faint hope though that might be.
We're turning this planet to hell, Majin Boo!
Until those guys show themselves,
kill everyone there is! Kill! Kill!
Gohan-san... Please... please be alive...!
Madoshi Babidi and Majin Boo
have both been restored.
However, it is undetermined whether Gohan,
who Kaioshin is relying on, is alive or dead.
Is there any remaining
means of resisting Boo now?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
This is bad. Gohan and Vegeta ain't around,
and Boo has started running wild.
One more to go, and we'll have
all the Dragon Balls collected.
Ah! What do we do?! The Dragon Ball
is inside that monster's tummy!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Struggle of Videl and the Others!
Find the Dragon Balls."
Guys, don't do anything
too crazy while I'm not around!
"Next time"
"The Struggle of Videl and the Others!
Find the Dragon Balls"