Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Ka... me...
ha... me...
Ha!!
The clash between Goku
and Cell had finally begun.
The intense exchange between them
left those in the audience dumbfounded.
Son Goku, huh?
Indeed, he is skilled at fighting.
He's one or two paces
removed from the others.
This guy looks to be unimaginably strong.
If I get even the slightest bit careless,
I'll be finished off in an instant!
The look in Goku-san's eye has changed!
Goku is about to release his true power.
An unyielding full-power
battle is about to get underway!
"Direct Hit to Earth!!
Cell's Extra-Large Kamehame-Ha."
Incredible!
It's unbelievable!
What amazing power...!
I-Impossible!
Y-You mean his ki is still rising?
W-What could that have possibly been just now?
Just at the moment when it
appeared that the unnamed warrior's
entire body lit up, it was
almost as if something burst...
What could it mean?
Even now, it appears that
there is some sort of amber glow
rising around the vicinity
of the unnamed warrior.
I-It's a trick.
Father...
Th-The same sort of thing
just happened with Cell...
Hmph! These petty
tricks appear to be in fashion.
Y-Yes, of course.
If those weren't tricks, what else could they be?
Here it comes...
Those two are both going to hit
each other at full power, right away...
Now?
Yeah.
Very good, Son Goku. This is what I was after.
Battles get interesting when the
opponents' abilities are somewhat close.
Yeah. I think so too.
Th-This is now his...
Kakarrot's true power...?!
I-Incredible! Goku-san is
extraordinarily incredible, all right!
Th-That really is an awesome ki!
He's certainly been working at it!
I wonder why everyone is so surprised.
Sure, this is incredible, but still...
H-Hey, did you get all that?
Don't be preposterous!
I can't follow anything as fast as that!
Y-Yeah, I suppose not...
That battle was also at remarkable
speed, wasn't it, Mister Satan?
It wasn't too bad, huh?
This will be entertaining, Son Goku!
W-What...?
Is that...?
I-It couldn't be...!
Shishin no ken!!
Geez! You mean Cell has
also taken Tenshinhan's cells?!
Why, you...!
Mister Satan, could you explain...?
You're already going to
the finishing moves, huh?
But then, this technique
ain't going to work on me.
Is that so?!
What the hell am I looking at?
This technique had the drawback
of having your power cut in half
by turning into four individuals!
But his speed and technique are the same as
when he was a single individual, aren't they?
No. I hate to admit it,
but Cell has made this technique
even more his own than I did!
Then again, Son Goku hasn't fallen behind.
Son Goku, are you somewhat
aware of my power now?
Yeah. Not bad.
But then, my perfect, flawless
power is still more than just this.
I-Is that...?
Sheesh, this time it's my technique, huh?
Take this!
I've been waiting for this.
For you four to split up, I mean!
H-He got him!
That's Goku-san for you!
Going after their time lag like that...
Hmph! Idiots!
Those are among the very
basics of the basics of fighting.
Never mind him, get a
load of Cell's dormant power.
Cell hasn't lost any ki at all!
Th-That can't be...!
Y-You're kidding, right?
K-Kienzan discs, huh?
–That Kienzan disc...!
–It's as if he's controlling it like a Sokidan blas t!
That's neither a Kienzan or a Sokidan...
That's the final technique that
Freeza used on Planet Namek.
Doctor Gero, you miserable fool!
What kind of monster have you brought forth?
Freeza's cells tell me that
you're planning to come up to me,
and at the last second,
knock me down. However...
I'm not falling...
for that trick!!
I took that into account as well!
You ain't going to beat me by
just using other people's techniques!
Borrowed knowledge doesn't go far, after all.
That might be true.
In that case, I'll make this the last one.
He raised his ki to its maximum level!
What is he planning to do?!
Ka...
me...
Stop! If you launch a Kamehame-Ha
in that raised state of power...!
ha...
me...
S-Stop!
Ha!!
Over here, Cell!
A-An explanation...?
How? That Kamehame-Ha
should surely have hit you.
Yeah, I couldn't have escaped it.
I get it.
You've suddenly appeared
and vanished before, as well.
Instantaneous Movement. I can do it!
Instantaneous Movement? I see.
That's a problematic technique, huh?
I want to ask something too.
If I hadn't jumped up into the sky,
would you have kept shooting
your Kamehame-Ha like that,
and destroyed the Earth?
Well, that's a good question.
But then, I knew that the only
thing you could do was jump up.
I see. It looks like you're pretty smart yourself.
Then again, I will say this:
I would think nothing of destroying the Earth.
It would just make things
less amusing for me, that's all!
And when it comes to speed,
I'm pretty sure of myself.
Cell's speed is astonishing!
Does Goku have any chance of winning?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Everybody! Hurry and get away from there!
Cell is planning to blow up the ring!
With the whole land as our ring,
there wont be any ring-out losses.
You either give up, or you die!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Defeat or Death!?
Goku's Turnabout Ploy."
Father, are you serious?
Are you really going to shoot the earth?
"Next time"
"Defeat or Death!?
Goku's Turnabout Ploy"