The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Majin Boo, while searching
for Goku and the others,
who had escaped to the holy
region of the Kaioshin Realm,
was wandering through space, and
finally arrived at the Grand Kaio's world.
Boo is planning to destroy
the Grand Kaio's world too!
We're the ones he's after!
We'll raise our ki and let
him know that we are here!
Th-That's it! All right!
You've had it!
At length, Majin Boo appeared in
the holy region of the Kaioshin Realm!
A battle with the entire
universe on the line now begins!
"Seize the Future!!
A Decisive Battle with the Universe at Stake."
Hmph. On this planet,
we can fight as hard as we want!
Kaioshin-sama, please, I want you to take
everyone and move to some other planet.
It appears that this ain't going to
be finished with half-hearted fighting.
I don't want to be any trouble to anyone else.
R-Right, understood!
What are we going to do with you?! Okay, fine.
This Kaioshin Realm won't be destroyed
over anything reasonable, after all.
Goku, Vegeta, you fight him as hard as you can!
Thank you, old timer.
Good luck, Goku-san, Vegeta-san!
Now then, are you ready?
Please touch part of my body.
–Like this?
–Okay, here we go!
–Where are we?
–One of the planets in the Lower Realm.
Here, even if the Kaioshin Realm is
destroyed, we should not be affected.
Sure is overrun by grass. Well, I guess
it's better than having nothing but rocks.
Let's see...
Those Saiyans sure are troublesome.
They tossed away those precious
Potara, and judging from their manner,
they don't appear to be of any
mind to merge with Fusion, either.
W-Will they be able to win
against Majin Boo like that?
Well, if the two of them
put their powers together...
All right! How about we try smacking him one,
to see if we can do anything about this?
Yeah.
Who's going to go first?
All right...
–Let's decide!
–All right!
Rock, Scissors, Paper! Tie, go again!
Again! Again! Again!
I did it! I won!
They're planning to fight one at a time!
I-Imbeciles! Can't you fight together?!
Your opponent is Majin Boo!
Kakarrot! I'm going to have a
good hard look at the way you fight!
Okay! Your turn might just disappear, though!
I can say this now, but the truth is,
I could have beaten that chubby
Boo back when I was at Super Saiyan 3.
But I wanted those young guys
to do something about him instead.
For the sake of what would
happen on Earth afterward.
Vegeta, that jerk, he's not listening!
Here goes, Boo!
He's being considerably tranquil this time.
He's sleeping!
Damn it, because of that despicable guy,
both the Earth and my friends were wiped out.
I won't let him get away with it!
H-He's a strange one.
Now I've done it!
I forgot to bring that human
named Satan from the Kaioshin Realm!
Doesn't matter. Leave him be.
What's this? What's going on?
Oh, it's you, is it?
You know what?
Where did everyone else go?
I-It's him! And Goku, too!
Where in the world are they?
It's the Kaioshin Realm.
The holy region of the Kaioshin Realm,
where even us Kaio find it difficult to go.
Now Boo has moved there, instantaneously.
The reason he went there
without destroying this planet first...
...was because he wanted to find
Goku and them as soon as he could!
Is that it? So thanks to Goku
and the others, we were spared.
Kaio of the North,
what are you babbling about?
What in the world is the matter?
You too can spy on things far away, right?
If you look, you'll soon understand.
Let's see...
The holy region of the Kaioshin Realm.
It's the guy from before!
Impudent bastard!
You bastard... Do you even feel like going at it?
He's won, he's won!
Our blond big brother has won!
Did he get him?
Awesome, Goku! That was
right off the bat, you know!
All right...!
Has Goku-san won?
No. It will take more than
just that for Boo to be defeated.
Sure enough...
That bastard!
I-Is this dream still going on?!
This is one powerful dream!
Damn! Hang in there, blond big brother!
Don't you lose! It's a dream,
but you must not lose!
I'm astounded... I'm astounded! What a fight!
O-One of them is that Son Goku fellow,
who came here quite
a while ago to train, right?
Right. The same one who competed for victory
against Paikuhan in the Anoyoichi Tournament.
Since then, he's become
far and away the strongest.
And the other one?
That's Majin Boo.
You've heard about him, right?
Long ago, he ran roughshod over the universe,
and gave four of the
Kaioshin-sama such a hard time.
That's Majin Boo, the one
who Madoshi Bibidi created?
The legendary essence of evil,
most wicked in all of history?
That's the guy who earlier
came and attacked here?
Paikuhan, thank goodness you weren't killed!
You bastard... Mess with me, will you?
I-Is this the power those two have?!
This is a whole different league!
Grand Kaioshin-sama, what are you doing?
What is he thinking? Ain't no way
I'm just going to silently look on!
What?
What is this?! What's wrong?!
Is this the end of the
world and the Other World?!
I-It's all over!
Not even Goku-san is a match for him!
Boo will wreak havoc on the entire universe!
Look, don't worry.
It looks a little like Goku
is considering something.
He's measuring Boo's power.
That's the sort of fighting he was doing.
It's the end of this world!
It's the end of the Other World!
It's the end of Mister Satan!
Majin Boo, you are one dense guy,
but your power, speed, and
powers of recovery are all incredible!
You're on a whole different
level from all the Boos up to now!
You're ridiculously strong!
There, look! Goku is finally getting serious!
Hmph, so Kakarrot has
finally decided to get down to it?
So then, the fight starts now!
Finally, Goku becomes Super Saiyan 3.
The climax of the fight, with the
entire universe at stake, is about to begin!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
You're strong all right, Boo.
Even fighting you at full
strength, you'd do me in.
Kakarrot, in the end,
I was unable to surpass you.
You're the only one who
can fight with Majin Boo!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Vegeta Takes Off His Hat!!
Goku, You Are No. 1."
You can't lose, Father!
For Vegeta-san's sake, as well!
"Next time"
"Vegeta Takes Off His Hat!!
Goku, You Are No. 1"