The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Gohan! I'm entering, too!
Father!
It's been a long time, huh everyone?
Y-You're really going to be
at the Tenkaichi Tournament?!
What's this? Goku is coming
back from the Next World for one day
in order to participate in
the Tenkaichi Tournament!
Goku, too?!
It's been a long time
since we've seen Goku, huh?
At the Kame House, Kuririn and No. 18,
who had distanced themselves from fighting,
and were living in peace and quiet,
decided to enter the tournament as well.
Vegeta and Piccolo, who
heard the news from Gohan,
had their fighting spirits
unusually fired up over the matches,
after going so long without fighting.
Goten! This is terrific!
You'll be able to see your pa for one day!
Roughly one month
remained before the tournament.
Gohan had at last plunged
himself into a period of training.
All right, shall we get started?
"Even Gohan is Surprised!
Goten's Explosion of Power."
What an incredible ki!
He's been at it since yesterday,
and instead of growing weaker,
he's getting stronger and stronger.
It must be because Goku-san will be
participating in the Tenkaichi Tournament.
J-J-Just a minute!
Hang on! You're going too fast!
I haven't even done any warming up here!
I'm going to go even harder!
Oh! Working up a sweat so early
in the morning, huh? Way to go!
–Thank you for the meal.
Okay, Goten, let's head out!
Uh-huh!
–We're off!
Goten!
Don't get in the way of your
brother's trainin'. Understand?
After all, we need to have your brother
do well at the Tenkaichi Tournament,
and make sure he gets plenty of prize money.
We're hittin' the bottom of Pa's fortune already.
I won't be in the way.
Really? In that case, okay.
Goten, what are you doing?!
Hurry up, or you'll be left behind!
Wait up!
Be careful, Goten!
Goten! Where are you?!
Maybe I ran a little too fast for him.
That tickles! Cut it out! Cut it out, I say!
Big Brother! It's a dinosaur!
He's a friend of mine!
Come on, stop it, I tell you!
What's the use?
Come to think of it, Mother always said
that his innocence was just like Father's.
Hey! Big Brother's going on
ahead and starting his training, okay?
What?!
Send Goku back, you say?
You already gave him
your permission, Uranai Baba?
I certainly have. There's no particular
reason why I should turn him down.
N-No reason, you say? It's going to be
difficult to accommodate this, though...
Goku has been bored, not being able
to undergo the Grand Kaio's training.
That's when the news of the Tenkaichi
Tournament being held came along.
Oh, for crying out loud...
If you're going to complain,
then how about giving
Goku his training right now?
T-T-Training?
W-Well, I, uh... I do have my own
circumstances to consider, and all...
Well, if Goku says he wants to go
back on that day, that should be all right.
Big Brother! Big Brother!
Wow, isn't this cute?
W-What is it?
See? It's a bug.
Y-Yeah...
Big Brother! Big Brother!
See? I found a lizard!
Look, what are you doing, Goten?!
We didn't come here to play!
Why don't you do some training, too,
by doing some pushups or something?
You're distracting me so
I can't concentrate, you know!
For crying out loud!
Big Brother! Big Brother!
Geez! Now what is it, Goten?!
Brother! I caught an amazing dinosaur!
Watch out!
Are you all right, Goten?
Oh, he surprised me.
For heaven's sake, what are
you doing? That was dangerous!
Don't you do anything else!
Just sit there and do nothing!
Okay. Understood, Big Brother.
Goten!
Could you help Big Brother out in his training?
Uh-huh!
That should do it.
What are we going to do with
all these stones, Big Brother?
We're going to use them in my
training to get back my sense of reflex.
What's a sense of reflex, Big Brother?
You're going to find out right now.
Goten, stand behind this line,
and throw those stones at Big Brother
as hard as you can. Do it like you mean business.
Mm-hmm, understood.
All right, ready, Goten! Throw them!
It's okay to throw them from this close?
Actually, you can throw them from even closer,
but we'll do it from there at first.
You're sure it's okay? You won't get hurt?
I'll be fine. Just throw as hard as you can!
Okay, here goes, Big Brother.
All right, come on!
Ready, set...
Go!
You were right!
Incredible! That's my Big Brother for you!
Okay, I'm going to start
throwing more and more.
J-Just–hold on, hold on,
hold on, hold on...!
Maybe I should have you throw
from this line, after all, okay Goten?
Yeah, okay, Big Brother.
All right, I'm getting comfortable with this.
Goten, you can start coming closer!
You can come even closer!
W-What's the matter, Goten?
Say, is it okay if I become like you, Big Brother?
What do you mean, like Big Brother?
I want to turn into that Super Saiyan thing.
Sure, you can turn,
but I think that it might still be a
bit too much to ask of you, Goten.
Turning into a Super Saiyan
comes after doing the proper training.
That's right, after you've overcome
harsh, painful training is when you'll first–
G-Goten... s-since when
have you been able to...?
I forget.
U-Unbelievable.
Big Brother and our late
father had to struggle fairly hard
to become Super Saiyans.
Say, Goten, how would you
like to spar with Big Brother?
Do you know what that is–sparring?
Mm-hmm! Mother used to teach me
a lot when Big Brother was studying.
Mother did?
Perhaps Mother has changed a
little since Father passed away.
She did say it was okay if I took
a break from school to train, too.
Say, Goten...
Does Mother know that you
can turn Super Saiyan, Goten?
Come on, Goten! Your late pa
would laugh at you for doin' just this!
Yow-ow-ow-ow...!
Mother! I'm sorry!
Mother...
Now even Goten-chan has turned delinquent!
I showed her once, and she got mad at me.
She said I looked like a delinquent,
so I couldn't do it any more.
Mother hates us being Super Saiyan, after all!
All right, that's the way, Goten. Come on!
Ah, no fair, Big Brother!
It's no fair for you to fly!
How come?
How come? Playing no fair is no fair!
What is it with you?
You can't possibly not be able to fly, can you?
Even though you can turn Super Saiyan?
No, I can't fly!
Then you've done things all out of order, huh?
Big Brother, if you're thinking of flying,
then you have to teach me
how to do it too, or it isn't fair!
You got it, you got it!
Don't get so upset, Goten!
I'll teach you how to fly!
R-Really?!
Yeah!
Wow! Yahoo! That's great!
I-Is that... Don't tell me...
V-Videl-san...!
Th-That's right! Videl-san
asked me to teach her how to fly!
Big Brother, what's the matter?
Nothing, it just looks like you're
going to have another pal, Goten.
Another pal?
Listen, Goten, there's going to be a girl
from the same school that
Big Brother goes to coming here.
We can't let this girl see how strong we are.
And we especially can't turn
Super Saiyan, no matter what.
Ah, I get it. It's because she'll
think we're delinquents, right?
W-Well, close enough, I guess.
Come on, let's hurry home!
You know, Big Brother, you're
amazing. I didn't hit you once!
I've still got a long way to go, huh?
Even so, Goten, you've got
an incredible gift for fighting.
You surprised me! Big Brother
didn't know you were that good!
If you train really hard, maybe you
can enter the Tenkaichi Tournament, too!
Really? Then again, Trunks-kun
is even more amazing than me.
When we play-fight against
each other, I'm no match for him!
Is that right? So you
guys play together like that?
Uh-huh! It's lots of fun!
If I don't watch out, the little
squirts are going to pass right by me.
Now listen, answer me truthfully.
You're sayin' there's no way you came
to invite Gohan-chan on a date, right?
I told you I didn't, didn't I?
H-Hey!
Mother, we're home!
Welcome back.
Videl-san, I'm surprised you found this place.
It was easy, if you look at the class rolls.
Ah, I see.
Never mind that, what's the meaning of this?
Submitting a notice of
absence from school like that–
You promised me you would
teach me how to fly, right?
U-Uh, of course I'll teach you.
Gohan-chan...
Is it true that this girl is enterin'
the Tenkaichi Tournament, too?
I-It's true, Mother. It was from Videl-san here
that I heard about the Tenkaichi
Tournament in the first place.
In that case, all right.
Now don't you go doin' nothin' lewd to Gohan
and tellin' him it's out of thanks!
There's no way I would do that sort of thing!
You!
You're not, by any chance,
thinkin' of enterin' the
Tenkaichi Tournament together...
...as an excuse to get
married to Gohan-chan, are you?!
No, I'm not thinking that!
And why would I go to the Tenkaichi Tournament
to get married in the first place?!
Well, after all, my mother and father
got married at the Tenkaichi Tournament.
Oh, dear! Goten-chan, how utterly embarrassin'!
W-What a weirdo...
The Tenkaichi Tournament
where I fought Goku-sa...
And then our marriage...
They're all such good memories.
But even so...!
When it comes to you and
Gohan-chan, that's another story!
I told you, such a thing happening isn't possible!
Geez, stop saying such foolish things!
What?!
Only one month remains
until the Tenkaichi Tournament.
Are you sure you should be
keeping company with Videl, Gohan?
It doesn't look like we'll be able to
train in peace for a while like this, huh?
Then again, as for Goten...
For his small size, Goten is sitting on
an incredible amount of latent ability.
I really shouldn't be letting
myself slide like I have been.
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Awesome! To think that she
would be able to fly after just one day!
This Videl girl really is something else.
Your brother is finding learning
to fly a lot easier, isn't he?
I'll be back tomorrow, too,
so make sure you teach me right.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Ah, You're Flying!!
Videl's Introduction to Bukujutsu."
Aw, I can't do my own training!
"Next time"
"Ah, You're Flying!!
Videl's Introduction to Bukujutsu"