Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Come forth, Dragon, and grant us our wish.
Following a difficult battle
in which they defeated Cell,
Gohan and the others called forth
Shen Long, and before anything else,
brought the people who had
been killed by Cell back to life.
And then, as their second wish,
they tried to bring Goku back to life as well.
However, as they did, a message
reached them from Goku in the Next World.
Since I've saved the Earth and stuff,
they're going to treat me special.
Ordinary folks, and bad guys
like Cell become just spirits,
but they're going to let me keep my body.
There's also fighting experts
from the past in the Next World here,
and it sounds like it's going to be lots of fun.
Maybe it ain't fair to Chichi and Gohan,
but you don't need to bring me back to life.
There you have it. Bye, now.
Once you all die, I'll see you again!
Bye-bye!
"New Days...
Father! I'm Hanging In There."
So, what is the matter?
Speak thy second wish.
I shall grant thee any wish.
What should we do?
Does anyone have anything?
If we don't decide soon,
Shen Long is going to disappear.
Have ye no wish?
Th-The girl I'm seeing now wants
this necklace that's kind of expensive.
I suppose that's out?
Just kidding!
Well, what will ye do?
Art thou finished?
S-Shen Long,
could you return the
Artificial Humans No. 17 and No. 18
back to the original humans they used to be?
That I cannot do.
The two Artificial Humans'
power greatly exceeds my own.
I cannot return them to the
original humans they were.
Th-That fool!
H-He can't do it, huh?
Kuririn, why No. 17, too?
After all, he's dead, isn't he?
No, the first wish was to bring all people
who had been killed by Cell back to life.
It wouldn't be any wonder that
No. 17 had come back to life, too.
Is that so? But still...
Well, can you at least
remove the explosive devices
that the two of them have
fitted inside their bodies?
K-Kuririn...
That would be possible.
All right!
Kuririn-san...
I have removed the explosive devices.
And so, farewell.
Kuririn-san, why would you
wish for something like that?
A-After all, you feel sorry for them, don't you?
I mean, having a bomb inside
their body, and everything...
That was kind of you, Kuririn-san.
Yamucha-san, I'm sorry.
I just helped myself,
and so you couldn't give
your girlfriend that necklace.
D-Don't be silly! That was just a joke, you know!
Y-You can't go using Shen Long
for something as trivial as that!
You got me, you got me!
It was just a joke!
Thanks, Yamucha-san.
W-Why that...
Be that as it may, Kuririn, why
did you remove No. 17's bomb, too?
It's true, I was fond of No. 18,
but No. 18 is better matched with No. 17, right?
S-So I...
There's no helping you, huh?
Th-This sounds like that
"love" business. I don't get it.
N-No. 18?!
You idiot! No. 17 is my twin brother!
Twin brother?
Kuririn, you've got it made! He's her brother!
She can't marry her brother! You've got it!
But don't go getting any ideas!
I'm not grateful or anything
about that bomb business!
Got that, baldy?!
See you later.
Oh? Hey, Kuririn!
If she's saying "See you again,"
that means there's a little hope, doesn't it?
R-Really?!
C-Calm down, Kuririn!
I've got the most experience
in love out of any of us, after all.
Th-There is some hope...!
Then again, Kuririn, she may be a monster,
but just because she has a cute face,
you shouldn't get your hopes up.
The competitive rate is pretty high, after all.
I don't get this one bit.
Piccolo, I suppose love would
be a bit too much for you, huh?
I guess I can only be halfway happy.
I am going to miss having Goku around.
Yeah...
I'm heading home.
Chaozu is probably worried about me, and all.
You're going home already?
I doubt I'll ever see the rest of you again.
Everyone, take care of yourselves.
You too.
Goodbye. Give Chaozu-san my best.
Yeah. Gohan, there's no
way I'll ever forget Son Goku.
Take good care of your mother.
Right!
Trunks, with your power the way it is now,
you should be able to easily defeat
the Artificial Humans in the future.
Good luck!
Right. Thank you for everything you've done.
Bye, now.
–Goodbye!
–See you later!
Well, I guess we should go home, too.
Trunks-san, when are you leaving for the future?
I'm thinking of getting a good night's
sleep tonight, and leaving tomorrow.
All right, we'll come see you off tomorrow.
Okay.
Piccolo-san, are you going to live here?
Yeah, that's my plan.
Would it be okay if I came
to visit once in a while?
You bet.
Everyone, thank you for all that you've done.
Okay, see you later, Dende.
Be sure you come visit, okay?
See you later, Popo-san.
All right! Let's take off for a new tomorrow!
Goodbye!
Well then, I'll be going to the
Capsule Corporation tomorrow, okay?
See you later!
W-Where's Dad?
Ah, when you got killed,
he became extremely angry.
Without any concern for
himself, he went after Cell.
I-Is that right?
My father did?
Mother...
Goku-sa died, did he?
Turnin' down bein' brought back
to life–that's just like Goku-sa, too.
Mother, don't cry.
I'm always able to feel Father.
Father is alive, after all.
It's true. Gohan's right.
Chichi, Goku-sa decided this for himself.
Let him do as he wants.
Take care, okay?
Right.
Goodbye!
Be careful!
Take care!
See you later!
Father...!
One month after the end of the Cell Games,
peaceful days had once
again arrived on the Earth.
Gohan-chan, I have a snack for you!
He must have gone out with Pa.
He went out the window
again. What am I goin' to do with him?
His poor manners are just like Goku-sa's.
I'll have to give him a good
scoldin' when he gets home.
It's nice takin' a walk on
a nice day like this, huh?
But don't tell Chichi I said so.
You've got it.
The peace really has returned, huh?
Well, how about we find a
present for Chichi and head home?
All right!
H-Hey!
Where are you goin'?!
Someplace I used to play with Father often!
W-Where is that?!
Grandpa, hurry!
It has to be here.
Grandpa! I caught one!
You're here, all right!
Gohan, you sure are Goku-sa's son.
You're just like Goku-sa in that regard!
Gohan! Behind you!
If you want some of this,
just hold on, I'll share it with you.
That's bad manners!
Don't you understand
when I say you can't do that?
That's what you get for having bad manners.
That's my grandson for you.
I guess he didn't figure on Gohan
being the strongest guy on Earth!
He's walking! He's walking!
Trunks-chan is walking!
One-two, one-two...
Hang in there! Hang in there, Trunks!
You're doing so good at walking!
Oh, Trunks! Are you okay?
His sense of pride is just like his father's.
Okay, okay, Trunks! Now, stand up by yourself!
Way to go, Trunks!
We now bring you this special program!
We present to you this feature,
detailing everything there
is to know about Mister Satan,
the ultra-gifted combat sportsman,
and strongest man on Earth,
who has saved the world and all of mankind!
You're the best, Satan!
Good evening, ladies and gentlemen.
Tonight, for the first time on TV,
we bring you everything there is to know...
...about the ultra-gifted combat sportsman,
and strongest man on Earth, Mister Satan.
And now, the man who saved
us from the terrible Cell Games,
here is Mister Satan!
What do you mean, strongest man on Earth?
He's the strongest one when it
comes to being a fraud, maybe.
Oh, my! It looks like Mister Satan
is about to show us his
trademark roofing-tile breaking!
W-What's this?!
Tonight, there are 20 tiles, piled up high!
This is incredible!
Mister Satan, as I recall, before the Cell Games,
you faced the challenge of 15 tiles,
and unfortunately left the last
one of them unbroken, didn't you?
I'm not the same person that I was then.
Since then, I've been secretly
undergoing special training.
Incredible! That's our hero, Mister Satan!
He has continued his
conditioning without anyone knowing!
Let me borrow this a second.
You good kids watching this on TV,
don't you dare try doing this yourselves.
Promise me.
That's just what you would expect from
the world's strongest man, Mister Satan!
What marvelous care he exhibits!
He's not just man of strength!
Once again, a single tile remains!
But amazingly, amazingly,
he has cut his way through 19 tiles!
What a fearsome destructive force!
I'm glad I set my video to record while
I'm out, because that was a showstopper!
Although, that still hurt quite a bit.
He is indeed every bit
the man that defeated Cell!
Kaio-sama, Mister Satan is quite the actor, huh?
There's always a man
like that around someplace.
Oh, well. It doesn't affect me.
That's right. By the way, Goku...
What?
It's about time we started
building us another house.
You're right.
But Kaio-sama, where do you find
a carpenter here in the Next World?
There's one right here.
Bubbles is going to build it?
You, Kaio-sama?
You and I are going to build it together!
Oh, so that's it, huh?
Then again, Kaio-sama,
I may be good at breaking things,
but I ain't very good at making stuff.
I'm not expecting much from you.
Here is good. We can build here.
Here, huh?
Okay then, why don't we get started?
Elsewhere, around that same time,
Trunks in his time machine was
about to arrive in the world of the future.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
In the future that Trunks returned to,
the Artificial Humans No. 17 and
No. 18 are still running amuck.
Not to mention Cell.
Don't you dare be beaten, Trunks!
Cell, I won't let you go back
into the past! You will perish here!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"One More Conclusion!!
I Will Defend the Future."
Hang in there, Trunks-san!
"Next time"
"One More Conclusion!!
I Will Defend the Future"