The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Madoshi Babidi conspires to
gather the greatest energy in the world,
and revive a sealed-up Majin Boo.
To return Kuririn and Piccolo,
who had been turned to stone,
back to normal, Goku and
the others enter the spaceship.
In order to proceed to the command
center, where Babidi and Dabura are,
they must defeat the opponents
that appear at each of various Stages.
Papparapa!
Vegeta easily beats Puipui,
breaking through Stage 1.
I-I can't believe it.
Is this Super Saiyan thing really that strong?
Now, at the second Stage, the
space beast Maju Yakon appears!
"Goku's Power Wide Open!!
Blow Away Yakon."
That's an unusual guy that's come out, huh?
Which one of you should I devour first?
I'm gonna be your opponent.
You're huge, but somehow, you
ain't too smart-looking, are you?
C-Could this be Y-Yakon... Maju Yakon?
Maju Yakon?
Yes. He's incredibly strong,
one of the fearsome
demon beasts of the universe!
G-Goku-san, single-handedly, you couldn't...
Yakon! Take their energy from them!
Hurry and revive Majin Boo for me!
That was close!
He's enormous, yet still so agile!
Which is why I spoke earlier!
Let us all fight him!
Ah, no. I think everything will
be all right with Father by himself!
I-It couldn't be!
You've fled well. But that
won't happen this time!
What a surprise! You can
shoot those sickle-like claws out?
He's jittery, he's jittery!
This will be an easy
victory for Yakon, indeed!
Let's shake him up even more,
and end this fight all at once!
Good, Yakon!
Yakon, as impressive as ever!
You can kill all three of
them, except for Kaioshin!
Take in your fill of energy!
This will ensure the return of Majin Boo!
In order for you to
finish this battle quickly,
I'm taking you to your beloved
pitch-black world of darkness,
Planet Ankoku!
Babidi-sama, even without
sending them to Planet Ankoku,
Yakon will be sufficiently victorious.
I suppose.
However, if they fight inside the spaceship,
and supply any strong shock to it,
Majin Boo might emerge
with his power only partly intact.
If we're going to do this at all,
we want him at his
original strength, don't we?
Quite so.
Well, shall we go for it?
Papparapa!
What, it's a rock?
Hey now, I can't see a thing!
This really is completely dark!
What a fix...
This is my cherished Planet Ankoku.
I can see quite well!
You're scratching your head, right?
Huh?
Planet Ankoku?
Y-Yakon's home planet.
It is far out in space,
where sunlight cannot reach it,
and so it is always completely dark!
You're mine!
One down...!
Where are you?!
Right here!
C-Can you tell what is going on?
Yeah, more or less.
Can you see?
You're taking us too lightly!
I may not be able to see with my eyes,
but I can still understand your motions.
Through subtle changes
in air current and so on.
Besides which, there are
many different ways to see you.
For instance...
What's this?! What's going on?
He's different than he was before!
Oh, he is merely glowing.
Say, bring me an energy meter!
The most powerful meter there!
Right!
Now it's bright. That's Father for you.
How's that? Now you understand, right?
It doesn't matter to me how dark it gets!
I see. I know now that the
darkness is of no use to me.
What, you don't seem at all nervous...
Babidi-sama!
T-Three thousand kili?
H-How does an Earthling have
an energy of three thousand kili?!
Three thousand kili...
With only two or three hundred kili,
one could destroy a planet or two...
Most peculiar. There is no reason
mankind such as this should exist on Earth.
Maybe the meter is malfunctioning?
However, supposing it
really is three thousand kili,
Yakon cannot win against him!
Yakon's energy is only
eight hundred kili, after all!
How long are they going
to make us wait, anyway?
I wonder how long it will
be before they start again.
What's going on?
"Food"
Delicious!
So good!
–Another serving!
I'm full, I'm full!
That was good!
Trunks-kun, excuse me,
but would you pay for this?
Oh... I don't have any money!
But Trunks-kun,
what about your prize money from
winning the Tournament Junior Division?
I still haven't gotten it!
They said I would get it when
everything's over, after an awards ceremony.
What should we do?
Y-You there!
Yikes, they found us.
Run!
Meal thieves!
Owie, owie, owie!
Hey, there...
Goten-chan, so this is where you've been!
Hold it!
Pay up!
Uh, these people will pay you! So long!
Victory is mine.
Wh-What's this?!
Huh? It's gone back to
complete darkness again!
Wrong! He's been turned from
a Super Saiyan back to normal.
Tasty!
I've never eaten light so delicious
and with such volume before!
You eat it?
M-Maju Yakon eats the energy of light!
Goku-san, your energy as a Super
Saiyan is undoubtedly his greatest food!
Father, you can't turn
Super Saiyan any more!
Apparently that guy eats the energy of light!
That's right! That was
the best light just now!
If it were possible, I wish
you could treat me yet again!
You're a strange one!
Fine! I will treat you some more!
What?
Here goes!
What is he thinking?
Father! I'll fight too!
With the two of us, we can win
without turning Super Saiyan!
Nah, I'll do this by myself.
You stay out of it.
Yea! I'm so happy you're
so stupid! I will feast again!
I-It really is stupid!
Wh-Why is he being so
particular about fighting by himself?
This is not a game!
Be quiet and let him do this!
Kakarrot has some kind of idea. He's no fool.
I'm being sucked in!
You expect me to give in?!
Yakon, you fool!
What am I supposed to do
with you sucking up all his energy?
What a waste!
Unless the energy is taken
from him by inflicting damage,
Majin Boo can't absorb it, you know!
I-Incredible!
Father, you did it!
So that's it...
Wha–?!
Impossible!
It's open, it's open!
We can go on to the floor below!
Right!
Kaioshin-sama, hurry up!
H-He exploded! Yakon!
How come he exploded?
He was a fool.
It appears he played
right into the enemy's hands.
He ate more light energy
than he could contain.
No! It was weird there!
At the last moment,
Yakon puffed up all of a sudden...
That was awesome, Father!
That incredible ki, right
when you defeated that monster!
Yeah, I guess.
So, that rotten Kakarrot has
indeed overcome the wall as well...
The Super Saiyan wall...
during those seven years he
trained in the Other World...
These aren't your ordinary guys after all!
It is well. As you wish,
I will quench your uneasiness, Babidi-sama.
I will go to Stage 3 for you!
There, in short time,
I will fill Majin Boo's ball
with their energy at any cost.
D-Dabura! If you are beaten, then it's all over!
You're sure you have a chance of winning?
Chance of winning?
I am Dabura, King of the Demon Realm!
Come three thousand kili,
come four thousand kili,
there does not exist a man in all
the world with greater power than I!
In the second Stage, Goku also
easily beats down Maju Yakon.
Does the word "pinch"not
appear in Goku's dictionary?
So, I wonder what kind of
guy will come out this time.
Gohan, it's your turn now!
Right!
However, Dabura, King of
the Demon Realm of Darkness,
is to appear next!
Also, it's finally Gohan's turn...
All right, I'll stick it to 'em!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
What's happening at the Tenkaichi
Tournament while we're off fighting?
I'll put on a show as
I defeat that masked goon,
then gently force the
delicate lady out of the ring.
The spectators will find it mesmerizing!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"A Great Miscalculation!!
Satan vs. Three Super-Warriors!?"
It doesn't look like Satan-san
realizes how strong his opponents are.
"Next time"
"A Great Miscalculation!!
Satan vs. Three Super-Warriors!?"