Godzilla directly ahead! Target lock!
Fire!
Keep to your posts!
- Prepare to launch missiles!
- Preparing missiles!
It's an Earthquake!
Fire into the glacier!
Repeated wars and
environmental disruptions...
As science advanced,
Earth's environment paid the ultimate price.
Giant monsters began to appear.
A race of mutants, seemingly human,
emerged as mankind's enemies.
But later joined forces with
them to fight the monsters.
The Earth Defense Force (EDF) is born.
Possessing special physical abilities,
more mutants began to appear.
The EDF organized a special military
unit consisting of humans and mutants.
This elite unit is called
Organization-M.
But the greatest enemy of the EDF...
...plunged the world into
a crisis of extinction.
It appeared for the first time in 1954.
It's name is...
We can't maintain this. We must surface!
No! Stay on course.