The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
At the hand of Madoshi Babidi,
the mighty, wicked
Majin Boo was restored to life.
As his instincts directed him,
Boo even destroyed the Earth,
as he pursued the utmost in destruction.
However, by using the power of the
Dragon Balls, Goku restored the Earth,
and then used the ultimate Genki Dama,
made from Genki that had
been gathered from all mankind,
to finally defeat Majin Boo.
Once again, peace had returned to Earth.
And then, ten years passed by...
"Grandpa Goku! I Am Pan!!"
Sheesh, this is no use.
Going like this just feels too sluggish.
All right...
Let's go!
Excuse me!
Trunks!
How nice of you to come!
It's been a while, hasn't it?
Good day, Chichi-san! Um, is Goten here?
Goten? He left with Goku-sa
early this morning. I know!
Gohan probably knows where they went.
Is that right? Well, I'll go try asking Gohan-san.
Thank you very much!
Good day!
Um, excuse me...?
Next, let's take a look at the
weather situation for the Paozu area.
The atmospheric depression that
brought some rain with it last night
–Yo! Welcome!
–was carried away by winds out of the west,
leaving the sky completely clear
this morning, without a cloud in sight!
It's a pleasure, Gohan-san.
I can't break away right now.
Could you take these for me for a second?
Ah, yes!
You know, there's nothing
but difficult-looking books here.
I have to put together the materials I'm
going to use at the next academic meeting.
Oh, set them down on that table there.
Gohan-san, you've completely
become a scholar, huh?
I suppose.
Pan! Go clean up your room! Pan!
Oh, welcome, Trunks-kun!
Videl-san, sorry to intrude.
Really, that Pan just
leaves her room so messy...!
Come, brave warriors!
This is the world combat sports
super champion, Mister Satan!
I will accept challenges from anyone!
I'll be waiting for you on the grounds
of this year's Tenkaichi Tournament!
The Tenkaichi Tournament starts tomorrow!
Really, I declare... I don't
know what to do with Papa.
He's all right, isn't he?
After all, Satan-san magnificently
saved the earth, and is everyone's hero.
You could say he saved us,
but using the Dragon Balls,
everyone's memories have been erased.
Nobody remembers what it was
that Papa saved the earth from.
More importantly, Trunks,
didn't you need something?
Oh, right, right. Do you know where Goten is?
Goten is on the mountain out
back training with Dad and the others.
Vegeta-san and Bulma-san are there too.
Papa and them are here too?
Good grief, would you
look at this father and son?
Geez, you're not showing any mercy, Father!
It's been a while, huh Bulma, Vegeta?
It hasn't been just a while!
I mean, really! If we were to leave you alone,
you'd never come to see us, would you?
You've been that way since long ago.
That ain't so!
We just saw you a mere
five years ago, didn't we?
That's five years! Five years!
Everyone else got together, but you said
you had to train, and couldn't come, right?
Th-That's true, but...
W-What?!
You've become a total auntie, huh?
Hush, you!
Even looking like this, people
often say "Ma'am, you're so young!"
You Saiyans are monsters
for never changing at all!
We Saiyans are a warrior race.
As such, our youthful period
lasts longer, so that we can fight.
Maybe next chance, I'll ask
Shen Long to make me young again.
By the way, Kakarrot,
when you say you're entering the Tenkaichi
Tournament tomorrow, are you serious?
Yeah, I'm going, I'm going. I decided today.
Vegeta, you enter too!
Why?
Why, all of a sudden, have you decided
to enter this tournament in particular?
Because there's going to be someone
else that appears to be strong entering too.
I've been interested in him for
a long time, and this morning,
he arrived at the tournament grounds.
What's this?
I don't feel any ki that's all that strong.
That's because he's got
his ki completely reigned in.
But I can more or less tell.
This guy is definitely strong!
You're kidding, right? There's no
way this guy could be. Is he an alien?
No, he's an Earthling.
An Earthling?
You're not going to tell me he's an
Artificial Human or something, right?
He's an ordinary human.
What was that?
Such a thing isn't possible!
How can there be a human who can
put up a decent fight against you guys?
Trunks-kun!
Yo!
Oh, you've come too?
Mm-hmm. What's this, Goten?
Looks like you're training, huh?
Are you planning on
entering the tournament too?
Father told me to enter. I told him
I don't want to, but he's forcing me.
I'd made a date for tomorrow, too.
Hey, stop complaining. You can
have a date anytime, can't you?
We're both put upon by how
weak our children are becoming, huh?
It's true! Well, that just goes
to show how peaceful things are.
Back already, huh?
My, it's Pan-chan!
Grandpa, I flew around the Earth!
All right! Terrific! That was pretty quick, huh?
I'm all ready for tomorrow now, right?
T-Tomorrow?
Pan-chan, you're not by any chance
thinking of entering the tournament, are you?
Mm-hmm, that's right.
But as I remember,
the children's division is gone
from the tournament these days, right?
Are you thinking of matching
up together with the adults?
Well, she probably can't win, but
she's sure to get up to someplace good!
Right now, the one with the
most guts in our house is Pan here.
This sounds like it will
be fun. Maybe I will enter.
Hey, Trunks, you enter too.
That's an order. Unless you want
your allowance cut in half, that is.
Nice going, nice going!
It sure is terribly bustlin' here.
It's not so much a
tournament as it is a festival, huh?
Say, say...
What is it, Pan?
Grandpa, let's go look around!
Sure we will... Say, there's still some time, right?
Yeah. We got here pretty early, after all.
All right, shall we go?
Father!
Grandpa, hurry, hurry!
Hey, Pan! Hold on! Hold on! Pan, I say!
Here.
Hey, you! Hold it right there!
Hey, hey! Move it, move it!
That was easy!
Okay, thank you!
Huh? Pan...?
You pipsqueak! Get in my way,
will you? You're a nuisance!
My ice cream...!
What?! You got something to say?! Huh?!
W-What is it?
Y-Yikes...!
Don't do it, Pan...!
My ice cream...
Pan!
The doggies are licking it!
My, my...
There, there! Here, Grandpa will
give you his, so don't cry anymore.
Hold it!
Oh, they're here, they're here!
Yo, everyone! You're all looking good!
Don't "you're looking good" us, Goku!
Training is fine and all, but at
least contact us every once in a while!
I haven't heard so much as a peep from you.
Sorry, sorry! Actually, Bulma yelled
at me about that same thing yesterday.
You're the same as ever, huh Son?
Piccolo, aren't you entering?
There's no way I could
fight against you any more.
Today, I wanted to have a look at
just how strong you guys have gotten.
Father, you'd better hurry. They're
going to close entry applications soon.
Let's go, Grandpa!
Well, see you later, then.
Yeah, we'll be in the stands!
Okay!
You know, it's rare for
there to be a grandfather
for whom the word
"grandfather" seems so out of place.
Let's go with the same
strategy this time, as always.
Boo-san, you'll become the
Challenger Champion, and fight against me,
the Super Champion, but end up losing.
And as is the custom,
please be sure to hold back all of your
power when fighting the other challengers.
If you're too strong, there won't be
any more challengers next time, after all!
I know, I know.
What now, more of my fans?
And I told them not to let anyone in.
Yo.
Oh! Well if it isn't Goku-san!
Good day, Grandpa.
And my cute little Pan-chan, too!
Have you been well?
Your whiskers hurt!
Did you come just to cheer your grandpa on?
I'm going to enter the matches too.
It shouldn't be surprising, but
everyone passed the preliminaries.
It's been a while!
What's this?!
Don't worry! If one of us wins
through, we'll let you have the victory.
Really?! You really will, right?
Y-Yeah...
However, somebody
besides us or Boo may win, too.
Not again, not again!
There's no way that something
like that could happen, is there?
Say, Satan-san, everyone
else has come to the stadium,
but there aren't any seats left, so they
said they wanted you to do something.
Is that right, is that right?
Something like that is an easy
matter to handle! Just leave that to me!
Huh? What's with those guys?
W-What is this...?
Hold on, is he serious?
S-Sure enough, we'll be able to
see well enough from here, but...
we're not on display!
I-If I'd known it was going to
be like this, I would have entered.
Geez, Papa...
This is embarrassing.
They've got to be kidding, putting
us here. Let's have them move us!
Um, I'll go ask my Papa.
Mama, this is a good view!
Indeed!
Well, they had a nice place
like this all along, didn't they?
Thank goodness!
Yeah, yeah, I was worried
what was going to happen.
Somebody is coming out!
Okay then, we will now hold the drawing
to determine the pairings for the matches!
Ladies and gentlemen,
please greet them with applause!
This is everyone who admirably managed
to pass the preliminaries
and advance into the finals!
Long ago, when we fought here,
I was the one that won, huh?
I won't lose this time!
–It's Boo-sama!
–Boo-sama! Boo-sama!
Boo's gotten popular, having
participated every single time.
At last, the Tenkaichi Tournament begins.
Who is this incredible
guy that Goku spoke of?
The heated battles are about to get underway.
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
I hate to ask, Boo,
but could you change the lottery
numbers with your magic for me?
I simply have to fight that boy first.
What do you mean, Kakarrot?
Don't tell me that boy
really has that much power.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"I Am Oob!
Now 10 Years Old, the Former Majin!?"
Huh? You say that boy is
the reincarnation of Majin Boo?
"Next time"
"I Am Oob!
Now 10 Years Old, the Former Majin!?"