Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Goku was displaying
overwhelming strength.
However, the depths of
Nappa's power were still boundless.
The fierce fighting continued.
That punch just now was for Chaozu.
"Father is Awesome! Kaio-ken,
the Ultimate Finishing Technique."
Damn you...
This is for Yamucha!
Why, you–!
I-Incredible!
You dirty brat!
I don't even have to dodge this one!
W-What?!
H-He defused it with just a kiai shout?!
D-D-Dammit!
This is for Tenshinhan!
How?! How does Kakarrot have this much power?!
What?!
And this is for Piccolo!
Dammit!
Awesome! You really are awesome, Goku!
Yeah!
Dammit! Dammit!
Dammit!
I see... Impressive...
You really are extremely tough, huh?
I am an elite warrior
from a distinguished family!
I'm not about to be looked down
upon by a lower-class warrior like you!
You'll pay for this! I'll kill you!
You miserable fool! Cool that head of yours!
If you'll compose yourself and think about it,
you'll find he's not the kind of
opponent that you can't take, Nappa!
Calm down!
You're right!
Thanks to you, my eyes have been opened.
That simple-celled fool! At this
rate, it looks like I will have to step in.
It's true, I was pretty upset. Now it's
time to show you what I'm really made of.
Are you ready for this, Kakarrot?!
That's more like it. I can't wait!
Talk tough, will you?
He's not just talking tough. He's got
assurance and absolute confidence in himself.
G-Goku...
Father...
Son-kun, pound that guy into a pulpy mass!
H-Hey!
Hey! Don't be so rough with this!
Who cares if a crystal ball or two gets broken?!
It's an important tool of my trade!
With Kami-sama dead, and us not knowing
whether the Earth will be destroyed or not,
you can just stuff your trade!
How dare you say that!
Now see here!
Would you two quit it?!
It doesn't matter, does it?
Yeah! While you two are at it
there, Goku could be getting done in.
Rubbish! Son-kun is obviously doing all right!
You think he's going to lose
to those guys?! No way! No way!
Don't hit my crystal ball!
Hey, shut up, already! Give that here!
A little brother does not
take his older sister's things!
I see you!
Whoo! This is a lot better, ain't it?
This is a lot better, huh?
I'm going to put a stop to that
irritatingly smart mouth of yours!
You're finished now!
What kind of guy is this?!
He countered at that close range!
That would have been
trouble if I'd taken that one head-on.
I-Impossible! That was–that was my
greatest technique, and you brushed it aside!
You really are one tough bastard.
You should have taken at least
a little damage from my Kamehame-Ha.
–We ain't getting anywhere like this.
–Enough! Get down here, Nappa!
You're getting us nowhere!
I'll take care of him for you.
What?!
You're pathetic!
To think that I would have to trouble
myself to take action against Kakarrot there.
He's finally coming forward, huh?
Even that big guy is scared of him.
Father...
D-Dammit...
T-To think that I should have
to yield your execution to Vegeta...
But brace yourself! Your life will
only last for a moment against Vegeta!
He is a warrior gifted enough to take
upon him the name of Planet Vegeta, after all.
Since he ordered me to,
I'll leave you to Vegeta.
But I won't be content to withdraw like this.
Oh, no! He's going after those two!
It's no use! I won't make it in time!
Kaio-ken!
What?!
What just happened?
Goku! How did you–?
Dammit!
I doubt he'll be able to fight anymore.
Take him, and disappear from
the face of the earth right now!
What was that just now?! For an instant,
his speed and power suddenly increased!
G-Goku, how did you do that?
Was that a technique you
learned from that Kaio person?
Yeah. It's called Kaio-ken.
By controlling all of the energy within
your body, you can momentarily amplify it.
If you do it right, your speed, power,
destructive and defensive
forces all increase many times over.
T-That's awesome!
Even after getting that much stronger,
you can become many times stronger than that?!
Yeah.
What are those guys talking about?
Goku, that was mean of you!
This is no time to be playing around.
If you have something like that up
your sleeve, then use it right at the start!
Sorry, but I can't do that.
If I don't restrain my ki just right while
I'm controlling it, I could wreck myself.
In short...
You have done well to
master the Kaio-ken technique,
which even I could not handle,
to this degree. However,
I must stress once again that you must
not overuse Kaio-ken at your current level.
If you mishandle your control,
you will end up ruining your body.
Do your best to limit yourself to 2x power.
Remember, using Kaio-ken any higher than that
will place too great a burden upon your body.
In other words, your body won't
be able to keep up with the Kaio-ken,
and it will bite back
for what you're doing to it.
Understood clearly.
–...and that's the story.
–I-Is that right?
V-Vegeta... h-help me...
T-Thanks...
Not at all.
W-What are you doing, Vegeta?! Vegeta!
I don't have any use
for Saiyans that can't move!
W-What a ki!
F-Father!
W-What's going on?!
Die!
V-Vegeta!
W-What a beast! He even killed his own man!
Gohan... Kuririn...
Both of you, go back to Kame House right now.
R-Right...
Gohan, you heard him. Let's go, now.
B-But...
Gohan, he's just too terrible.
We won't do any good being here.
On the contrary, our being here will
distract Goku, and we'll just be in his way!
Really, Father?
Sorry, yeah. His strength appears
to be even greater than I thought.
O-Okay, I understand.
Oh yeah, Goku, as long as you're at it,
could you fight in some other place?
It would be wrong to mess up everyone's bodies,
in case they ever come back to life.
They ever come back to life? With
Piccolo dead, Kami-sama is dead, too.
The Dragon Balls have disappeared forever.
I hate to say it, but nobody
is ever coming back to life again.
I know that...
Kuririn-san, you don't think–?
What?
I'll go into the details later.
T-That is, if you're able to beat him, Goku.
I f I can beat him, huh?
Right. In any case, I have to beat him.
What are you doing? What happened
to all that energy you had before?
Did you get scared, and now you're
discussing how you're going to run away?
Now then, to change
locations and give it my best, I guess.
Just let me take care of this.
Goku, I feel bad about
always leaving our fate up to you.
Don't you dare die now, my friend.
Right.
Father...
Gohan...
Once your daddy comes back
alive, let's go fishing again, okay?
Okay.
Looks like you know that
it won't do any good to run.
We're going to change
the location of our battle.
Suit yourself. It will all end up the same.
Father...
Vegeta... Has there ever
been a foe this powerful before?
The curtain now rises on a fierce deathbattle,
with the fate of the
Earth and our friends at stake.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Looks like it's finally
time for us to fight, huh?
You should be thrilled.
A lower-class warrior such as yourself
is about to be toyed around
with by a super-elite, after all.
W-What a ki! It's as if
the whole earth is shaking!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"A Hot, Unbounded Battle!
Goku vs. Vegeta."
Father won't be beaten!
"Next time"
"A Hot, Unbounded Battle!
Goku vs. Vegeta"