The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
At Stage 3, it was Dabura who
stood in the way of Goku and the others.
Gohan challenged the demonic
king with his power wide open.
However, upon feeling the evil in
Vegeta's heart, Dabura abandoned the fight.
Babidi is planning to use Vegeta,
causing Goku and the others
to fight amongst themselves.
"Vegeta, Prince of Destruction, Revived!!
Intrusion at the Tournament."
Dabura... someone supposed to be a
demonic king, has abandoned the fight?
What on earth could his intention be?
It's you whose intention I want to know!
How could you fail to
take down a guy of his level?!
If you were even a paltry member of
our fighting race, once you started a fight,
you'd make sure to take your
opponent's last breath from them!!
You're all too soft!!
Every one of you, fighting behind
the mask of justice–it disgusts me!
It's power that commands the fight!
The strong are the only ones
who survive, while the weak die!
Power is everything!
But–
Take a look at Piccolo and them!
It's only because they were weak
that they were turned to stone!
Hmph! They're a disgrace!
That's right! If I'd only defeated Dabura,
Piccolo-san and Kuririn-san would
have been returned to normal...
Let it stand at that, Vegeta. Gohan
did everything he could, after all.
Like I told you, Kakarrot!
I want to put an end to this playing around
so I can hurry up and
settle my score with you!
Dammit, I'm at the limits of my patience!
Never mind Babidi, and never mind the Majin!
I'm going to vaporize this whole spaceship!
–This is where it ends!
–That's reckless, Vegeta-san!
If you do such a thing,
Majin Boo will be revived!
Majin Boo is a monster who
does nothing but create destruction
and slaughter again and again!
He is quite literally a demonic being, as
four of the Kaioshin were no match for him!
Shut up!
If Majin Boo is revived, then mankind...
no, all living things, will be put to death,
and the Earth will unmistakably
be turned into a planet of death!
Be silent!
How many people are killed...
What may happen to the Earth...
It's no concern of mine!
What kind of person are you?
Why don't you cut it out, Vegeta?!
Kakarrot!
Still, something strange has happened, huh?
Yeah. This should have been
the perfect chance for them
to obtain the energy they
need for Majin Boo's revival.
So why did Dabura...?
I ain't sure what it means, but
I'm certain he said something like
"I myself do not need to fight,
I've found a good warrior."
Found... a warrior...
H-He can't mean...!
You're right! He's different from the others!
It's just as you said. His
heart is filled with wickedness!
He hasn't come here for any just cause at all!
Right.
Bravo, bravo, Dabura!
So then, let us have them
fight amongst themselves.
The energy we obtain from them
will most assuredly revive Majin Boo.
We're going to have you serve us!
Vegeta-san!
–Dammit!
–I knew it!
Kaioshin-sama, what on Earth is...?
Vegeta-san! Shake it off!
Babidi is attempting to
use the evil in your heart!
Babidi using... the evil in his heart...?
That's right! Madoshi Babidi can
manipulate the evil-hearted at will!
You can't mean...
the warrior Dabura found is...?
Vegeta-san, empty your mind!
You must not think of anything!
W-Worthless fool! That's easy for you to say...!
Good, good! You're ours now!
All right, while we're at it,
let's also draw out his hidden
power, beyond his limits!
W-What's this?
Incredible power!
Vegeta-san!
No, Vegeta-san! Don't let
that guy manipulate you!
Gohan!
Vegeta-san...
What a ki! I can't get near it!
Babidi, you...!
Vegeta-san!
Vegeta...
Hey, Vegeta!
Please, wait!
It's too late!
I-It can't be...
I'm Champion!
Way to go, Mister Satan!
Yea, Mister Satan! You're so cool!
We cannot allow you in
the ring! Please go back!
Everyone, please return
and sit in your seats at once!
Sit down, if you please!
Vegeta!
Vegeta-san, snap out of it! Vegeta-san!
I never...
I never expected Babidi to go
about setting us up against each other!
Great, great! He is now my servant!
Why don't I let them fight somewhere nice?
Papparapa!
–W-What?
–He's about to move us to another location.
We're at...
...the Tournament grounds.
This is no apparition, this is
unmistakably the Tournament grounds!
W-What's with them?
They just suddenly appeared!
Goku! No doubt about it,
it's Goku and the others!
What's happening here?
Goku-sa! And Gohan too!
Vegeta!
Unbelievable! Now they come
back to the Tenkaichi Tournament,
when the winner's already been decided!
What am I goin' to do
about the family budget?
I know!
Just beat up Mister Satan
now and take the prize money!
That's preposterous!
Preposterous? If he beats
the Champion to a pulp,
in front of everyone here,
no one's goin' to object!
I-I suppose that's true...
Hmm? W-Wait a second,
there's something strange here.
You're a bit late, aren't you, party of Son-san?
Where on Earth have you been?
Watch out!
So, what was his name again? Er...
Right, right, right! Vegeta!
Take the energy from those guys!
Battle with all your might!
You can even kill them if you want!
Silence! My only objective is Kakarrot!
I don't care about anyone else!
Vegeta... you...
How about that guy? He still
isn't completely under my control!
This is a first! Well, I guess it's okay...
V-V-Vegeta!
Vegeta! What the hell is he thinking?
Th-Th-They're... those guys from...
those guys from that one time...
Y-You mean... th-they survived?
H-Hey!
What?
You idiot!
Aw, hell!
Oh, no!
Unbelievable!
Th-This can't be!
It's not true! This is some
kind of mistake... Vegeta...
Vegeta...
Vegeta has been controlled by Babidi!
Is this the fateful confrontation at last?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Babidi! Change us to a place
where no one else is around!
I have decided to fight Vegeta!
They've started fighting amongst themselves!
The return of the Majin is
now just a matter of time.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Super-confrontation of Destiny!!
The Clash of Goku vs. Vegeta."
Vegeta-san did it on purpose,
so that he could fight Father!
"Next time"
"The Super-confrontation of Destiny!!
The Clash of Goku vs. Vegeta"