Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
At length, the armed
forces took action. However...
Prepare to attack!
The foolish must be given their punishment.
Stop!!
...they were unable to do
anything before the monster Cell.
Elsewhere, Goku said...
I'm going to head out for a bit,
in search of a Namekian who
will become our new Kami-sama!
Our Kami-sama will be restored,
and the Dragon Balls will be restored as well!
In order to search out the
location of the new Planet Namek,
he instantaneously moved to Kaio's planet.
Goku?
"Dende's First Task!!
The Dragon Balls Restored."
Good day!
Oh, how good of you to come,
how good of you to come!
Goku-sa went off somewhere
right in the middle of our drive!
What in the world is he thinkin'?!
Everyone throughout the
world, this is your Monarch.
A-As you have witnessed
from that earlier broadcast,
the combined forces of our military
were dealt a destructive blow by Cell.
I am accountable for everything.
I am terribly sorry.
There was nothing else
that we could have done.
To be completely honest,
there is nothing we can do.
However, please do not panic.
A savior, such as the young boy who
defeated Piccolo Daimao so long ago,
may yet appear again.
Let us pray to Kami, our god.
You can pray, but there is no Kami-sama.
So that's it, huh? Artificial Human Cell?
That is indeed something terrible.
You know, there are all sorts of
terrible things that happen around you,
one after another, huh?
Mm-hmm.
That's why I was thinking, why don't we
have another Namekian become Kami-sama,
and then get the Dragon Balls restored?
It sure would help me
just knowing which direction the
planet where the Namekians are is, though.
You got it. I'll give it a shot.
Let's see...
It sure would be nice if
we succeed in finding them.
Mister Popo, you know,
seems awfully lonesome ever
since Kami-sama has been gone.
I guess that's to be expected, though,
living all by himself in that temple.
Of course he would be! That's just what you'd–
Shut up!! Keep quiet!
I can't concentrate, you know!
A-E-I-O-U!
Geez, be serious, would you?
Sorry, sorry.
I found them, I found them!
This time for real. This direction.
Really? Thank you!
All right, this way, then?
Even far away, if I at least
know which direction to look in,
I might be able to latch on to their ki...
Incredible! Instantaneous Movement, huh?
When did you come to learn that technique?
Oh, I know! Instantaneous Movement
is the specialty move of the Yardratians!
You had the Yardratians teach it to you, huh?
That makes sense.
You know, that must be convenient, huh?
Be quiet, would you?!
Oh, don't mind me!
I did it! This is the ki!
Without a doubt, this is a Namekian ki!
Thank you, Kaio-sama!
W-What?
There are a whole bunch of Piccolos here!
G-Grand Elder-sama...!
W-Who are you?
Um, my name is Son Goku,
and I've come from Earth.
You're the Goku-san who fought
Freeza on Planet Namek, and saved us all.
Planet Namek blew up, though...
It seems that Earth is in
quite a terrible uproar, huh?
You know about how
Cell is running rampant?
We don't know any details,
but there is an evil ki that
spreads even here, to our planet.
Well, that saves me some explaining.
The truth is,
I'm here looking for someone
who would become our Kami-sama.
A Namekian, who will restore our Dragon Balls,
so we can bring back to life
the people that Cell has killed.
There's a guy named Piccolo,
who says he originally
came from Planet Namek.
Piccolo? Ah, you must
mean the child of Katattsu.
It sure would help us out if one of you
would come to Earth and be our Kami-sama.
Go to Earth?
Yeesh, Earth, huh?
I get you.
In that case, we have just the right person!
Really?
Hey, Dende!
Come over here.
R-Right!
This is Dende.
He is good friends with your son,
Gohan-kun, as well as Kuririn-san.
Ever since then, he has been longing for Earth.
He's always saying "I miss them,
I miss Gohan-kun and the others."
That's great! But unless you
can handle the Dragon Balls...
It's all right.
Despite how he may look,
Dende is a brilliant Dragon-type.
I'm sure he will become a fine Kami-sama!
Is that right? Gotcha.
Nice meeting you, Dende.
R-Right. That goes for me, too.
Well, let's leave right away.
Thanks. We'll take responsibility
for looking after Dende.
Farewell, everyone!
Take care!
Steady on, Dende!
Goku-san, we pray for Earth's peace.
Yeah, thank you.
Kaio-sama! It went great!
This is Earth's new Kami-sama.
Well then, see you later!
Hey! I just came from
the new Planet Namek!
D-Dende?!
This person new Kami-sama?
Yeah.
Y-You're sure that Dende
can serve as Kami-sama?
It'll be fine, I tell you!
Wait here for a minute.
I'm going to bring Kuririn and
Gohan here right away. All right, then...
People of the world, we
have wonderful news for you!
That ultra-gifted combat
sportsman, our hero Satan,
has decided to enter that
tournament of death, the Cell Games!
Here is our superhero, Satan!
Satan! Satan!
Satan! Satan! Satan!
Who is that guy?
He's the world champion of combat sports.
Are you sure you'll be all right, Mister Satan?
Your opponent, Cell, is capable
of annihilating even whole armies.
That was nothing more than a trick.
He planted explosives there ahead of time.
I figured that out right away.
When compared to a combat sportsman,
it's almost as if he's an amateur!
I, Satan, will be sure to
crush this crazy sham artist!
Got that, people of earth?!
–Way to go!
–Satan!
Satan! Satan!
Good grief, there's no helping this idiot.
Goku-sa, where in the world did
you go, leavin' the rest of us behind?!
C-Chichi, just a minute!
Kuririn, Gohan, come with me, would you?
I brought back our new Kami-sama!
You know Dende, right? The Namekian?
Huh? Dende?
Gohan-san! Kuririn-san!
It's true! It's Dende!
It sure has been a long time!
It's great that you came, Dende!
Say, is it true you're going
to be Earth's Kami-sama?
Y-Yes.
Sure you are. Ever since
long ago, you've had promise.
Now we can see each other every day!
So then, Dende...
Are you truly able to handle the Dragon Balls?
It's all right!
That oldster Namekian said that
Dende was a brilliant Dragon-type.
Oldster?
H-He means the Grand Elder-sama.
R-Right, right.
The Grand Elder-sama vouched
for him, so there ain't no mistaking it.
Given a hundred days, I believe
I can have the Dragon Balls ready.
A hundred days?! Is that how long it takes?!
I know!
If you have the Dragon Balls
you used previously on Earth,
and a model of the dragon,
I can restore them right away!
Really?
The previous ones should have turned to stone,
and are scattered across the Earth's surface.
There is dragon model, made by Mister Popo.
That's great!
So, we've got it made, don't we?
All right!
So, how about it?
Will we be able to have three wishes granted,
like it was when we were on Planet Namek?
Yes!
Then, like before,
will it be possible to bring
many people back to life
and such with just one wish?
For example, "Please bring everyone
who was killed by Cell back to life."
I-It's not as though I can't do
something like that on my first casting,
but it does mean that there
can only be two wishes granted.
Huh? Is that all it takes,
and it will be all right?
Yes.
That will be fine.
Make it so they can do that.
Understood. Now then,
I'll need the model of the dragon...
Mister Popo, go bring us the model.
Right.
Mister Popo made this.
Such an interesting shape for a dragon!
Well, I'll give it a try now.
Dende, good luck!
Take it easy doing this!
Right!
There, I think the Dragon
Balls that were turned to stone
and scattered about have now been restored.
Really?
Outstanding!
Well done! He certainly does
appear to possess a brilliant power.
All right.
Well, I'll go borrow the Dragon
Radar from Bulma, and gather them up.
We'll leave you to it, Goku.
Yeah. Gohan, you don't
need to do any more training,
so until the Cell Games start,
you stay here and play with Dende.
B-But...
It's okay, it's okay, don't worry.
Ah, Goku-san, can I ask you something?
Huh? What is it?
Goku-san, your composure–by any chance,
is it because of some
weakness you've discovered in Cell?
That's it, right?
Nah, I doubt that guy has any weaknesses.
Well, I'm off.
Oh my, Son-kun!
Hey, this Artificial Human
is one incredible construction!
Doctor Gero may not
have been much of a person,
but he definitely was a genius.
Anyhow, Bulma, I'd like
to borrow your Dragon Radar.
I brought back a new
Kami-sama from Planet Namek.
Wow, nice going, huh?
Sure thing, it's in that drawer over there.
Thank you.
Oh, there it is!
Looks like it's working fine.
As long as I have this, I can tell
the exact location of the Dragon Balls.
Okay, I'll just take this with me.
Oh, just a second!
That's too bad,
I wanted to ask how Trunks was doing.
I guess it's okay...
Around here, maybe?
Oh, yeah! It's right nearby!
This place is a bit spread-out, huh?
Gohan-san, have you heard anything?
Goku-san has clearly stated
that Cell is stronger than he is,
and that he doesn't know of any weaknesses.
And yet, how is it that he's so cheery?
Father hasn't told me anything, either.
He just keeps telling
me to look forward to this.
Look forward to it?
But look, if he says to look forward to it,
then surely there must be
some chance of winning, right?
It could be just ordinary defiance.
It's definitely around here somewhere...
Hey, you! There are sandstorms
that blow through this area!
Watch yourself!
So that's it!
The Dragon Ball got buried deep
in the ground from the sandstorms!
Thank you!
All right...
What is it? What's happening?
Is it a whirlwind? Whoa...!
Here it is! It really has become a Dragon Ball!
The Dragon Balls have been restored.
And so, time passed, with everyone
harboring their own speculations.
That's two that I've found...
Only a short time remains
before the Cell Games.
This is boring.
Perhaps when I said
ten days, that was too long.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Puzzle rings, huh? I ain't very good at these.
You can't just yank them apart, either.
Hey, Goku! Why are you casually
playing with those puzzle rings?
They're getting away
with all of the Dragon Balls!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"A Hard Problem for Goku!?
Take Back the Dragon Balls."
It really is hard to get all
the Dragon Balls together.
"Next time"
"A Hard Problem for Goku!?
Take Back the Dragon Balls"