Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
In order to protect No. 17,
No. 16 at last steps forward.
No. 16 fights evenly balanced against Cell
with his incredible power. However...
I can regenerate myself, at
least to an extent such as this!
"No. 17 Swallowed...
The Transforming Cell Is a Super Gourmet."
Then in order to keep you
from becoming your perfect form,
there's nothing I can do but
squash the very life out of you?
Such a thing is impossible, however.
I won't know until I try.
I do know.
Hell's Flash!!
What an incredible shockwave! What's going on?
Unfortunately, it's not Piccolo.
His ki vanished a bit earlier.
Is it Cell?
Or is it No. 17 and the others?
In any case, I have to hurry
and bring back the controller.
That's the only thing I can do right now!
F-Father!
Yeah. I felt it too.
T-That Cell guy's ki has suddenly gotten small!
I don't know who you are, but keep it up!
Until the time when Vegeta
and Trunks finish their training!
U-Unbelievable!
He's that strong?
N-No. 16...
Incredible...
Are you still here? I thought
I told you to get away, No. 18!
It's okay now, isn't it?
You've taken care of him!
I haven't beaten him at all!
He has to have taken damage,
but he's not the kind of
opponent to die from such an attack!
No. 17, while you have a chance!
You get out of here too!
Get out of here, you say?
You've got to be joking!
He's given me a rough time of it,
and you expect me to run off
without scaring the hell out of him?!
He's taken damage, right?
Then I will finish him off with my own hands!
Come on out, you monstrous freak!
What's the matter,
weren't you going to absorb me?!
I will neither run nor hide!
Not until I've squeezed
your life's breath from you!
No. 17, behind you!! It's Cell!!
As you wish, I've come forward!
Oh, hell!
H-He swallowed him!
Run away, No. 18!
What are you doing?! Run!!
You'd better get out of here too!
That Cell guy's ki has billowed up incredibly!
This isn't good!
No. 17 or No. 18–one of them
appears to have been absorbed by Cell!
Come on, let's get out of here, No. 18!
W-What incredible speed!
This is bad. This is really bad!
Did you think you would
be able to escape from me?
Forgive me, Chaozu. I just might die.
Even I myself am surprised
by my magnificent speed.
Of course, this is due to absorbing No. 17.
I wonder how my power is.
Oh, it appears to have
gone up quite a bit as well.
Now then...
That's good.
You at least understand
that trying to escape from me
is an utter waste of effort.
You're a sharp one.
And so, now it's your turn.
Together, let us create the perfect form!
Just try coming any closer!
I'll blow myself up if you do!
If I die on you, you're screwed, right?!
Do you hear my voice, No. 18? It's me, No. 17!
I've now joined bodies with Cell.
It's a great sensation! It's wonderful!
You should have yourself absorbed right away!
Only by doing that can we
become the ultimate life form!
N-No. 17...
D-Don't fall for it, No. 18!
That is Cell!
He's only using No. 17's voice!
You keep your unnecessary
remarks out of this! Be silent!
Robots cannot understand our feelings.
Come, No. 18. There is no losing your way.
Hurry and become one with us,
and obtain the greatest of powers!
Then we will carry out
Doctor Gero-sama's will...
...defeating Son Goku, and placing
the entire universe in our hands!
You are not No. 17!!
We hated Doctor Gero for
reconstructing us as he pleased!
Under no circumstances would
he ever say "Doctor Gero-sama!!"
Having come to this, I will absorb
you, even if I have to force you!
Cut out the useless resistance!
For you to launch an energy blast,
you will need a moment to charge it.
There's a possibility
that I can move sooner than
that and prevent your suicide.
Give it up!
Dammit!
Small fry! What the hell is it you're trying to do?!
Shin-Kikoho!!
This ki...!
It's Tenshinhan-san's ki!
D-Don't tell me Tenshinhan is taking on Cell!
What are you doing?! Get out of here, now!!
Why, you!
Can you fly?
Yeah, more or less.
Cut it out! Stop it already! Stop it, Tenshinhan!
If you use the Kikoho technique
any more than this, you'll die!
Cell has at last absorbed No. 17.
Stop it, Tenshinhan!
Not even Tenshinhan's
Shin-Kikoho has an effect on Cell...
...as he approaches his perfect form!
Will the Saiyans, Vegeta,
Trunks, Goku and Gohan, be in time?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Maybe I ain't got the power now, but Cell,
just you wait one day, and I'll
be sure to thoroughly defeat you!
What can you do in just one day?
You just watch on wistfully
as I achieve my perfect form.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Tomorrow, I Am Going to Pulverize You!!
Goku's Challenge."
Don't blame us if you end up in tears tomorrow!
"Next time"
"Tomorrow, I Am Going to Pulverize You!!
Goku's Challenge"