Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Vegeta, who had recovered
his strength surprisingly quickly,
was headed for Planet Namek
to search for the Dragon Balls.
Elsewhere, Bulma and the others were
held up on a Planet Namek that was illusionary,
as were, of course, its Dragon Balls.
Will Gohan and company be the
ones who obtain the true Dragon Balls?
Or will it be Vegeta? Or perhaps...?
"A Tough New Enemy!
Freeza, Emperor of the Universe."
Dammit!
Don't worry, you're just entangled in them.
Just wait until evening,
and you'll get loose all on your own.
Who are you guys?
Is this not Planet Namek?
It doesn't have any fancy name like that!
This scummy planet is
like a big trash heap in space.
It doesn't have any cities, or people,
or anything decent to eat or drink.
We were forced down on this planet
when we got caught in some cosmic tides.
Our spaceship was smashed up, and we were
at our wit's end when you folks showed up.
We were going to swipe your
spaceship and get out of here right away,
but unfortunately, there is a
gigantic cosmic tidal current in the way,
and we couldn't move.
So, you're saying that you
were just killing time up to now?
That's right. While you were out,
we probed you to find out about Earth,
the secret of the Dragon Balls,
and even what Namekians looked like.
Then, the lake, and the giant,
and the ice cave were all...
Illusions that we made you see.
W-What kind of despicable joke is this?!
It was pretty thrilling, wasn't it?
Get bent, you bastards!
A-As hectic as things are right now–!
Don't be mad. In exchange
for taking your spaceship,
we just let you have a
bit of a dream, didn't we?
It's better than being killed, right?
Yeah, we aren't the
barbaric type. We're more gentle.
The cosmic tidal currents
move just a little bit each day.
But once in a very rare while,
an opening appears in them.
An opening?
Yeah. And this fog is our indicator of that.
As long as this fog is out, we can escape.
What are you doing?!
We're going to search for the Dragon Balls.
We never thought anything
in the world could be so amazing.
This time, you guys stay here.
You'll wait until someone else
comes down on this planet. Later!
J-Just a minute!
Hey!
Bulma-san, what are you doing?!
Hurry and go after them!
Are you saying I should get
our stuff back by myself?!
W-Well, the way things are...
Hey, by the way, you do
know how to fly this, don't you?
It's simple. You tell this thing
to fly, and it flies, all on its own.
That's amazing.
Okay, let's take off! Open the door!
Hey...
What's the matter?! Open the door!
All right! They don't know
how to open the door, do they?
–How are you coming, Gohan?
–No good!
They're squirming all over,
and I'm getting nowhere!
Kuririn-san!
D-Darn it!
All right, now!
Kuririn-san...
All right...
What is this?
If we don't hurry it up,
the fog is going to lift!
Why didn't you make sure to look into this?
Shut up! We just need to
bring the girl with us, right?
Huh? Ah, h-hold on...
We did it!
Yahoo!
Come on, open it!
We can't afford to dally around! Once the
opening in the cosmic tidal currents closes,
there's no telling when it will open again!
L-Listen, let's all go together, like friends.
You're saying you want to come with us
back to our planet? It will take fifty years.
Huh? Fifty years?!
Hurry it up! Hurry, or else!
A-All right.
"Piccolo"
All right!
So, there's a password, is there?
Take care, now. There is food
to eat, if you're not too fussy.
Like snakes, and lizards.
They can be pretty good,
depending on how you cook them.
"Piccolo!"
What?!
Whew, you're here at last.
I hate snakes.
D-Damn it, if that's how it's going to be...
Oh, wow, they're weaker than I thought.
You're right.
I told you, we're not
barbarians, like you guys are.
Oh, no!
The fog is about to lift! We have to hurry,
or the tidal opening will close! Let's go!
Thank you. If it weren't for you,
we wouldn't have known how
to get out of here. See you later.
Bulma-san, where is the
opening in the cosmic tide?
I can see it now. It's where
that gas is blowing through.
It's almost closed!
It's all or nothing.
Here we go!
We got through!
We've slid in safe!
Now, we have to make up for lost time.
Destination: Planet Namek. Full speed.
How strong those guys were!
They were too much for us.
I wonder when the next
one will come down here.
At that moment,
Vegeta was hastening along his route
toward Planet Namek from a different direction.
I won't let Freeza have it his way any longer.
I will make sure I get the
Dragon Balls, just you watch!
Say, Goku-sa...
W-What?
It's been a month already, huh?
Y-Yeah...
I forgot to give him some nail clippers.
I'd send him some if
there were a delivery service.
Y-Yeah, I guess so. That's too bad, huh?
Y-You were standing guard, huh?
Thirty-four days after blasting off from Earth,
Bulma and the others had finally
arrived at their destination of Planet Namek.
We made it! There it is! There it is!
Wow, it sure is pretty.
It's the real one this time, right?
No question about it. The computer
says that this is the genuine Planet Namek.
We got here four days later than we planned.
It's just like those kids said.
It's a good thing we took that shortcut.
Everything turned out all right, didn't it?
I guess so. Now, we're going to land,
so sit down and fasten your seatbelts.
There's going to be quite a jolt.
Commence landing in a suitable location.
We did it! We've landed on Planet Namek!
We're here!
Hang on, now. I'll examine the
composition of the atmosphere.
I made sure to install some sensors.
Wasn't that prudent of me?
We'll be lucky enough if
there's some level of oxygen here,
but I also prepared some atmospheric masks,
though that will limit our
time out there to roughly...
This looks sort of like the place
where I trained with Piccolo-san.
Yeah, where we first fought the Saiyans, right?
I suppose a place that was similar to his
home would instinctively be more settling.
Piccolo-san...
You guys don't ever learn
from your previous lessons, do you?!
How can you just waltz on out here like this?!
You sure are as scary as ever.
For crying out loud. Well, it's okay,
as long as there are Dragon Balls here.
Please...
Look! I'm reading them!
Hooray! Now we can finally–
What are you doing?
Oh, I was wondering if we weren't
being tricked again, so just to make sure...
It's for real, I tell you!
Yow! All right!
Hooray!
–Hooray, hooray!
–Hooray, hooray, hooray!
Kuririn-san, there's a
strong ki coming from over there.
A ki?
You're right.
I'm sensing a lot of them.
Yeah, and they're all incredible ki, too.
W-What does it mean?
Oh, come on, what are you talking
about? Those are the Namekians.
With Kami-sama and Piccolo
being as strong as they were,
it's not at all strange that
the Namekians from their home
would have incredible ki, too.
But still...
Those ki do feel a little bit evil, huh?
It's okay, I tell you. Kaio-sama said that
Namekians were gentle by nature, didn't he?
There are four Dragon Balls
gathered together in that direction.
Come on, let's go meet the Namekians.
Oh, yeah. Yeah, you're right.
They must be Namekians.
I shouldn't have gotten so jittery, huh?
H-Haven't we seen that someplace before?
It's a Saiyan spaceship!
I knew it!
It can't be!
Again? Are you serious? How?
Gohan, mask your presence! We'll be detected!
R-Right.
I-It's Vegeta. He's the only one it could be.
Dammit!
Has he already healed?
Come to think about it, he
knows about the Dragon Balls, too.
What do we do? It's hopeless. The only
thing we can do now is return to Earth, right?
Isn't that so? Let's hurry back.
If that guy gets the Dragon Balls, it's over.
Bulma-san, please contact Earth and tell
them about this, then go on back by yourself.
Me and Gohan will stay here
and try to collect the Dragon Balls.
But...
It's okay. We'll have the Dragon Radar.
Isn't that right, Gohan?
Right.
All right.
Once I get back to Earth, I'll bring
Son-kun on board and come back for you.
The round trip will take a little
over two months, though. Wait for us!
It's okay! Two months will pass like that!
I mean, it's only sixty days! 1,440 hours!
86,400 minutes! 5,184,000 seconds!
Right?!
R-Right. A little more than two months, right?
Freeza, you bastard! I won't let
you snatch them away from me!
I should be able to handle
everyone besides Freeza,
but I don't stand a chance of
winning if I fight him head-to-head.
Whatever happens, I have to get the
Balls away from him and gain eternal life.
Tch! To think I'd be stuck
using a Scouter again...
This way, huh?
He's brought Zarbon and
Dodoria with him too, has he?
W-What was that?
S-So now what? Mm-hmm... Mm-hmm...
Right. So tell that to Son-kun and the others.
Do you read me? Just
don't tell Chichi-san. Got that?
Right... right... mm-hmm...
I already told you... are you listening to me?
No, tell everyone but Chichi! Sheesh!
Right! Got it?! We're counting on you! Goodbye!
Good grief...
What's the matter, you two?
Huh? What?
W-Why is there another one coming?
T-That's what I'd like to know.
Here it is, Freeza-sama.
Oh, very good, very good.
Now there are three more, yes?
At last, the evil hidden hand, Freeza, appears.
Will Gohan and Kuririn indeed
be able to collect the Dragon Balls?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Damn it, I can't just sit around here like this!
Freeza is doing whatever he pleases
to our star of hope, Planet Namek!
I must say, Vegeta certainly is reckless.
Imagine, coming out in
open rebellion against me.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Vegeta's Ambition! I am the
Greatest Warrior in the Universe!!"
Father, our spaceship has been wrecked.
"Next time"
"Vegeta's Ambition! I am the
Greatest Warrior in the Universe!!"