Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
In order to surpass being Super Saiyan,
Son Goku, together with Gohan,
had entered into the Room of Spirit and Time,
to undergo some full-fledged training.
Get angry! Pop off, with a bang!
Elsewhere, Artificial Human Cell
was matching up against
the abilities of a reborn Vegeta.
The battle found Vegeta,
who had obtained power far beyond
that of Super Saiyan, winning hands-down.
So, this is your level after all?
Apparently, during my training,
I opened up too wide a
gap between our powers...
Impossible! You're Vegeta,
aren't you? Am I wrong?
I am Super Vegeta!
"Dangerous Pride!!
A Challenge to Cell's Perfect Form."
Dad has this won.
Super Vegeta, you say? W-What's that?
It'd be too much trouble to explain in detail.
Imagine whatever you like yourself.
Swagger around as Super Vegeta, will you?
In the future, you have been
killed by Artificial Human No. 17!
I have absorbed the
power of No. 17 as well!
Even a child would understand
which one of us must be stronger!
Hmph. So this is what "yelping
as much as a weak dog" means.
If you've got the time to brag, spend
it figuring out how to defend yourself.
However hopeless that might be.
Cell has changed quite a bit from before.
I-Is that what he calls his perfect form?
Has he already gotten No. 18 and the others?
A-And after all the trouble
Bulma-san went through to make this!
Will it have been for nothing as well?
T-That's Dad's Gyallic Ho attack!
Your cells are also within me!
Take this!!
Dad!
V-Vegeta!
I-Incredible! Vegeta!
Vegeta has this won.
I can't believe it.
That's just what I had expected
of you, having obtained my cells.
However, although you may
be able to mimic my Gyallic Ho,
there was no way you could get
past the difference in our powers.
Enough!
For you to not understand such a thing,
does it mean that the
inside of your head is hollow?
I won't allow something
like this to happen!!
I-Impossible!
W-Why?!
Awesome!
He's become ridiculously strong!
His body has also become larger...
He's not the same
Vegeta he was up until now.
Is this a new Vegeta?
What sort of training
do you suppose Vegeta
did in the Room of Spirit and Time?
Will Son also emerge with
power even greater than Vegeta's?
Son will not get a turn at this rate, huh?
Vegeta is going to
finish this by himself.
You see, Trunks? Your father is incredible!
He's going to beat Cell, after all.
You know something,
I didn't need to work overnight.
The emergency shutdown
controller won't be necessary now, huh?
Gohan! Get angry! Pop off, with a bang!
Pop off, with a bang!!
I must have fallen
asleep without realizing it...
Father?
Ka...
me...
ha...
Ha!!
Father!
Gohan, you're awake?
F-Father,
I'm embarrassed to have fallen asleep.
Gohan,
the gravity is ten times greater
during the afternoon, it's 50°,
while at night, it's minus 40°,
and under these terrible conditions,
we have to train for a whole year.
That has to be tough
for a child like yourself.
When it's time for you
to rest, it's okay to rest!
I-I've rested long enough.
Father, please train me!
Father, please!
I'm in a hurry to become a
Super Saiyan, like you, Father!
When I first came in here,
I didn't have your high spirits.
Gohan, you ready?
Yes!
W-Why? He's not supposed to be an
opponent worthy of me to begin with...
What the hell has happened?
W-Why has Vegeta's
power risen to this extent?
T-This sort of thing...
D-Dammit, this sort of
thing can't be happening!
You stupid scum!
I'm... not going to let this folly take place!!
It's overwhelming.
There's too much difference in their powers.
There is a new history being made,
entirely different from our own history.
I-Is that...
Trunks?
He has become quite a bit more brawny.
I hardly recognized him.
For him to become like this in just one day,
it must mean that Room of Spirit and
Time or whatever is one awesome room.
Okay, raise your right leg high, now!
One-two, one-two...
We currently have nothing further to report...
Let your day continue to be tranquil, with...
What's the deal?
Nobody has any more
news about what's happening.
Ten-san, how are you doing?
My Goku-sa is around, so you can relax!
My Goku-sa is sure to be
managin' somethin' or other!
I want Ten-san to hang in there too.
Still, isn't that the
Muten Roshi-sama we all know?
He has completely maintained his composure!
Nothin' too fantastic about it.
At best, he's just havin' some
kind of lewd dream or somethin'.
Goku-sa, don't be worryin' about
what comes after, just stick with it!
I have to get you to settle this quickly,
and then let Gohan-chan
get to studyin', after all!
Gohan sure does have himself quite a mother.
Don't he? Everyone says so!
Take this!
Have you run away?
It will be you that dies!
I will now savor the greatest feast of all!
That's kind of you to say,
but I'm most unpalatable!
I'm going to suck you!
You expect me to become your fodder?
This will do fine.
At this rate, once Dad defeats Cell,
it won't matter what
becomes of No. 16 and No. 18.
We won't even need the help
of Son Goku-san and Gohan-san.
Incredible!
There's no comparison!
Come!
Where are you hiding yourself?
Dammit! Where are you?!
It would appear as if you have
received quite a shock, huh Cell?
Why don't I tell you of an
even further shocking fact?
Over there is a guy named Trunks.
Though not to the same extent as myself,
he also possesses a power close to mine!
It seems that even with you
putting out all the power you've got,
this is what your level is.
How damned disappointing! You pantywaist!
Here I came, wondering what
an exceptional guy you must be...
But now, somehow killing you
has become such a frivolous matter!
Damn it to hell!!
Damn it all to hell!!
My perfect form...
if only I could become my perfect form!
That sort of guy wouldn't be so...
Damn! Lousy No. 18! Where are you?!
No. 18?! Is she here?
Cell is absolutely no match before
the overwhelming strength of Vegeta.
For him to become his perfect form,
he must absorb Artificial Human No. 18.
However, Cell has not
realized that No. 18 is right nearby.
Damn it all! Damn it all!!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Vegeta is planning to wait for
Cell to achieve his perfect form.
He's gotta be kidding!
I have to use this controller
to somehow destroy No. 18
before Cell spots me!
Now is my only chance.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"I'm So Distraught!!
Kuririn's Handiwork in Destroying No. 18."
Kuririn is susceptible to women.
I wonder if he'll be all right.
"Next time"
"I'm So Distraught!!
Kuririn's Handiwork in Destroying No. 18"