The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Astounding!
In a single day, Majin Boo has turned
roughly 80 percent of the Earth to ruins!
However, there is still one last
remaining hope for the Earth.
The world champion Mister Satan has
now stepped forward to put down Majin Boo!
Die!
You're funny, so I'll make you my servant.
Th-Thank you so much...!
Don't get too carried away, fatso!
You get this straight now!
Don't you underestimate me!
"I've Stopped Killing!!
Majin Boo's Good Boy Declaration."
Say, Kaioshin-sama,
They've been like that for some time now.
Can this 15-generation-previous
or whatever Kaioshin-sama...
...really draw out Gohan's
incredible power for him?
W-Well... I think it will be all right...
He certainly seemed to
be quite sure of himself.
U-Um, Kaioshin-sama...?
Kaioshin-sama!
W-What?
You were just sleeping, weren't you?
D-Don't be ridiculous!
There's no way I would go to sleep!
I was undeniably awake!
That I don't believe.
Well, it may have looked
that way, to an amateur.
And Kaioshin don't
generally tell lies, you know.
Okay, this is no time to be
speaking of the unnecessary, right?
Let's continue, let's continue.
"This probably won't work."
That's what Gohan was quick to conclude.
All right! We're about to begin!
It's Super Saiyan Fusion!
Right!
Now listen. This time, even if your
Fusion is successful, do not get carried away!
You know Majin Boo's strength now, right?
We know!
All right. Do it!!
Okay, your ki are exactly
the same. Begin the Fusion!
Fusion Ha!!
A-Awesome! He's awesome!
They did it! It's a complete success!
Your ki is certainly something incredible,
but what about your movements?
Show me a bit of what you got.
You sure that's okay?
Showing you here in a place like this?
W-What?!
I can't be sure the buildings
here won't get all broken up!
I'll do it down on the ground!
W-Wait!
Yahoo!
It's no good! His over-inflated
attitude hasn't gotten any better!
Sheesh! What insane speed he has!
Maybe I overdid it a little on the speed.
Think I'll take a quick break.
Let's hurry, Grandma.
If we don't hurry and get away from the city
and someplace within the mountains,
we'll be found by Majin Boo!
I wonder if our grandchildren
in the city got away safely.
G-Grandma! What's the matter?! Hey!
Yea! I hit her in one shot!
Th-This still isn't right, young master!
You fool, does that concern me?
The whole world's people
are being killed by Majin Boo!
Just suppose Majin Boo
was the one who killed them!
I've always wanted to try
shooting humans! It's the greatest!
I'll let you shoot the old geezer!
Go on, do it! That's an order!
Right...
Hey, not too bad, was it?
See? Feels great, right?
Let's go on killing away like that!
Yes, that wasn't bad!
Yahoo! The city!
If we go to the city, there will be plenty
of scumbags who have still survived!
You're so slow! Have you finally arrived?
I went around the Earth many
times over, and even took a short nap!
Go flying off on your own, will you?
I've been looking for you!
You can tell simply from
my speed just now, can't you?
What wildly incredible power I have?
You sure do. However...
Which means, our test is over!
W-Wait!
I've decided to put him away
right now, that annoying Majin Boo!
Hey! You fool!
What an impossible jackass!
You can only stay merged for
another minute, you numbskull!
Lousy Majin Boo! This isn't going
to go the same way it did last time!
You're going to be sorry
you ever came across me!
Yea!
Yo, yo, yo! Majin Boo! It's me! Show your face!
Who's there?! Who's talking bad about me?!
Hey!!
There, you see? It's just your imagination!
Is there anyone that would
say anything like "Yo, yo" to you?
As if he were snuggling up
to Nello, Patrasche died as well.
The townspeople learned about what
had happened, and reflected to themselves,
"Ah, we have done such a cruel thing!"
That was funny! How fun! How fun!
"A Dog of Flanders"
Er, where are you off to?
Gonna go kill more people.
You wanna go with me?
N-No, I'll stay here and, um,
cook something until you come back.
Really? Your stuff is yummy,
so I look forward to it!
Of course! Be expecting some
top-notch delicious cooking, if you please!
Well, I'm off!
See you back later!
Good luck!
Stupid bastard! Don't get
too carried away with yourself!
Laugh it up now, while you still can!
With as much dynamite as this, no matter
if he is Majin Boo, he'll be blown to bits!
There's enough destructive power
here to blow up a tank, in any case!
I just have to push this remote
control switch, and it's "The End!"
I will have been the
one who saves the Earth!
I'll just hide it in here!
Hurry on back here, Majin Boo!
Yahoo!!
Die! Die! 38! 39! 40!
How do you like that?!
But still, young master, if Majin Boo
were to come here now, we'd be in trouble!
They say that near here
he has built himself a house!
You fool! If that guy were
to come here, it's no big deal!
I've got a powerful bazooka here!
I am a hero after all!
H-He's back here already!
I-I deeply apologize! I-I am still
in the middle of making your meal!
Hey, here.
I-Is something the matter with that dog?
He doesn't get afraid. He won't run away.
No matter how much I listen,
I don't know what he's saying.
Do you know?
I-I do not know what he's saying, but
it appears his leg is injured, does it not?
That is why he does not run away.
Oh, is that it?
I'll heal your injury for you,
so you get scared and run away!
There, run away!
I'll kill you.
What's with him?
He doesn't run away, even
though his injury is healed.
He is overjoyed at having you help him!
He has taken a liking to you, Boo-san!
Does he like me?
That's right! He likes you, he likes you!
His tail is wagging, right? He is delighted!
He's like you. You like me too.
Th-That's right!
I'm kind of happy.
Here! Eat this choco!
Oh, no, no! Choco will not do!
It has to be dog food or something!
Dog food? What's that? I don't know that!
I know! Shall I go buy some dog food?
O-Okay, I'll go buy some,
so please wait here for me!
Okay!
This is my cha-ance!
You're finished!
Now you're finished, Majin Boo!
H-He looks so happy...
Well, that's okay. I can do this a bit later.
The puppy is there too,
and all... Damn it all...
There, you see? He's happy to eat this!
Yucky.
U-Um, Majin Boo-sama,
can I humbly ask you one thing?
What is it?
W-W-Why is it you k-kill people
and destroy buildings and such?
Because it's fun!
Th-That's all?!
They said I can do that to play,
both by Bibidi and Babidi.
A-And who are they?
Those unpleasant guys that made me!
Y-You mustn't listen to
those disagreeable guys!
I-It won't do to have you
killing and destroying and so on!
N-No, that's fine! That's all fine,
if you find it to be fun!
I-I am so sorry!
You think it's wrong for me to do so?
Y-Yeah, well...
Okay, I'll stop!
Y-You're not going to kill anyone any more?
Mm-hmm.
Y-You're not going to destroy anywhere else?
I-I-I did it! I did it!
I really am the hero! Just what you'd expect!
Just what you'd expect from
the world champion, Mister Satan!
Here... Young master, it's around here!
Majin Boo's house!
What, are you still afraid? I told
you, this won't be any big deal!
R-Right...
How engaging! It's us who are going
after him, and we're going to kill him!
He brought the ball right back, see?
Great! Great!
All right! Once again! Once again!
Go!
That's one down!!
Huh? Young master,
that fellow with Majin Boo there,
it's Mister Satan!
H-How can this happen?!
A single, unfeeling shot
from a heartless villain...
Will all of Mister Satan's efforts be in vain?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
How can this be?
Thanks to a couple of bad apples,
the reformed Majin Boo's
evil portion has swelled up!
Satan, you and the dog run away.
If you stay here, you're gonna die.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Run Away, Satan!!
An Angry Majin Boo Emerges."
The smoke that blew out of
Majin Boo is making another Majin Boo!
"Next time"
"Run Away, Satan!!
An Angry Majin Boo Emerges"