Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
There is one minute
until Planet Namek explodes!
Thanks to Super Shen Long, Gohan
and the others were able to return to Earth.
Very well, I will make it clear to you.
I am the one who is going to survive!
Before this planet explodes,
I will defeat this guy with my own hands!
"Pathos of Freeza! Once He
Starts Shaking, He's Unstoppable!!"
There's no way I'm going to lose to a monkey!
Not to a mere Saiyan monkey!
Goku! Goku!
Kaio-sama, what has happened?
It's even! Goku is matching
up evenly against Freeza!
However, there's under a minute
left until Planet Namek explodes.
If the fight continues like this,
it'll be just what Freeza wants.
What exactly do you mean?
Freeza, as emperor of the universe,
has likely never had a foe that has
given him as hard a time as Goku has.
When Freeza got anxious
during his fight with Goku...
I can survive even in the vacuum of space.
But you Saiyans cannot live there.
Disappear, together with the planet!
Father!!
But Planet Namek was
not immediately destroyed.
I restrained my power too much, did I?
That's because you were fearful of
being caught in the explosion of the planet.
As a result, I've hung on to life.
Hung on to life, you say?
You don't seem to understand at all, do you?
You have avoided the
planet's instantaneous explosion,
but I've completely destroyed its core.
Do you understand what that means?
Five more minutes!
Five more minutes, and then Planet
Namek will undergo a great explosion,
vanishing into space dust!
The better part of that five
minutes has already passed!
There's no more time!
When Planet Namek is
destroyed, Goku dies too.
However, Freeza will remain alive.
He can survive in any location!
How's that?!
I am not losing to the
likes of a lowlife Saiyan!!
Not to a mere Saiyan!
Y-You monkey!!
What is that you're doing, Bulma-san?
Fortune-telling!
I was taught how to do
this when I was a child.
When you wish for a
traveler to return home safely,
you lay three leaves inside
a circular ring and burn them.
It's said that if the
leaves burn completely up,
the traveler will return safely.
Oh? We're foretelling
what Goku-san will do, right?
See? They're burning!
I'm sure they'll all burn up!
Goku-san is coming back, isn't he?
That's right! This fortune is sure to come true!
Telling fortunes is nonsense!
Father is certain to come back!
You're right!
Father will beat Freeza,
and certainly come back!
Dammit! How long must I be
bothered with the likes of this Saiyan?!
How's that, you monkey scum?!
Is this all you've got?
What?!
I asked you if this is all you've got!
Enough impudence!!
You monkey scum!
Not to the likes of a Saiyan...!
Dammit!
I'll repay you for this
ten-fold–no, a hundred-fold!
I'm stopping.
W-What was that?!
Stopping, you said?
What has happened?
W-What do you mean, you're stopping?
In reaction to your using
your 100 percent power,
you've passed your peak,
and your ki is falling rapidly.
I've begun to think that it's
useless to fight you any further.
I'm already feeling satisfied,
and your sense of pride is in tatters!
After all, someone has come
forward and surpassed you,
when no one in the world was
supposed to have been able to.
And what's more, that someone...
...was a mere Saiyan!
There ain't any reason to kill you,
now that you've started trembling.
You should go on living with the shock
you have undergone here, in tranquility.
I'm going back to Earth.
I can still barely make it in time.
Freeza, don't you misbehave any more!
I don't want to see your face again.
Don't mock me!
Don't you mock me!
A-Am I...
Am I...
...to have lost?!
You're an impossible fool!
I had given you one last chance!
It will pursue you no matter how far you go,
and cut through any substance!
That this should be your final technique!
You disappoint me, Freeza!
Hmph! I see through your strategy!
You'll come toward me, evading at the
last moment and causing it to hit me, right?
You think I would fall for
such a worthless tactic?!
Goku, there's no time!
Planet Namek is going to explode!
Father!!
Only moments remain until
Planet Namek's great explosion.
Will the goddess of victory
smile on Goku? Or will it be Freeza?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Somehow or other, I'm going back to Earth.
Freeza, you're going to share
the same fate as this planet,
which you yourself have destroyed.
Goku! What are you dawdling around for?!
Hurry and take off! Take off!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Goku's Declaration of Victory!!
As Freeza Destroys Himself..."
Father has won!
"Next time"
"Goku's Declaration of Victory!!
As Freeza Destroys Himself..."