Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Now!!
W-What?!
Th-This can't be–!
At last, Gohan had defeated Cell.
The battle was over, and
peace had returned to Earth.
Please bring those people who
were killed by Cell back to life!
That is a simple matter.
However, Goku did not come back to life.
Once you all die, I'll see you again! Bye-Bye!
And so, Trunks used his time machine
to return once again to the future.
"One More Conclusion!!
I Will Defend the Future."
Peace had returned to the Earth.
However, in the future that Trunks came from,
the menace of the Artificial Humans
No. 17 and No. 18 still continued.
Mom, I'm home!
Welcome back, Trunks.
Hold on, now...
What's going on here?
You're quite a bit taller, aren't you?
Yes. Mom, in Kami-sama's Temple,
there's this place called
the Room of Spirit and Time,
and if you train in there, you can
pass an entire year in just one day.
I'm not entirely sure how that can be,
but in any case, I'm glad you got back safely.
So, how did it go?
Judging by the look on your face,
I'm guessing it went well.
Yes.
That must have been rough.
I see. So Son-kun ended up dying after all, huh?
But Gohan-kun avenged him, right?
Yes.
I also fought alongside Dad.
W-With Vegeta?
It turns out that Dad
wasn't just some cold person.
When I got killed by Cell...
Dammit!
...he got serious, and became furious.
S-Sure he did! Isn't that what I've told you?
Yes.
Eh? Vegeta did? So he
did have that side to him...
We interrupt this program
for an Artificial Human report.
No. 17 and No. 18 have appeared again.
They are currently attacking
at Point BBN-49, Parsley City!
Those miserable Artificial Humans!
This time, for sure...!
Trunks...
It's all right.
This is the reason I went to
go see Goku-san in the past.
This time for sure, I've got to
avenge Gohan-san and all the others!
It's not just the past–I've got
to bring peace to this era, as well.
Be careful, Trunks. Don't overdo it.
Right!
You're acting just like a brat.
To think you would get so upset
over losing at some computer game.
Shut up! You keep quiet!
Those two killed my wife and children...
Dammit...!
You're a pretty good shot, huh, geezer?
Should I give you a reward?
You want one, don't you? Eh?
Y-You devil!
Who's there?!
Trunks?
No. 17! No. 18!
This is the end for you!
I'm going to put you away!
What, you're still alive?
You know, nobody can pull off
wasted effort the way you can.
No. 17, I'm in a rotten mood!
I can go ahead and polish him off, can't I?
Because I'm sick of him!
It will mean one less
thing to amuse us, but okay.
Do as you like, No. 18.
This will be more fun than some computer game.
Watch out, No. 18!
Damn it!
Now you've done it!
What's wrong with you?
That was pretty sloppy, No. 18.
Damn! You're going to pay for that!
You've progressed quite a bit, huh?
Getting No. 18 genuinely angry at you, and all.
In the past, where I went in my time machine,
you were somewhat good people.
But here, in this time period,
you continue to destroy cities for
no reason, and torment everyone!
I cannot allow that to go on!
What are you blathering about?
Let's get him, No. 17!
Th-This can't be...!
H-How could No. 18 be
done in by the likes of you?
That was for all of my friends you've killed.
And this... is to avenge Gohan-san!
To hell with you!
It's over.
No, not yet...
There's still one crucial person remaining.
And so, the months passed by.
No. 17 and No. 18 were gone,
along with the destruction they caused,
and peace had returned somewhat.
In the cities, reconstruction had begun.
And then, the amount of energy required
by the time machine for a round-trip journey
to the past had finally been stored up.
Mom, I'm going to go report to
everyone that I defeated No. 17 and No. 18.
Trunks, be careful. Tell everyone I said hi, okay?
Okay, Mom.
Mom, get inside the house.
What is it? A visitor?
Ah! It must be a girlfriend, right?
When did you manage that, you sneaky little...?
I know you're there, Cell!
You're planning to kill me,
turn back into an egg,
get aboard my time machine,
then go back into the past, and
absorb No. 17 and No. 18, aren't you?
All to achieve your perfect form.
What?! H-How could you know that?
That plan is going to fail.
And then, it will all be over.
My plan will fail, you say?
Hmph, because of the likes of you?
Cell, in your perfect form, you did
indeed have astounding strength.
But as you are now, even I'm
strong enough to defeat you!
So that's it.
You've been to the past, haven't you?
I see. That explains why
you're so surprisingly informed.
Be that as it may, I don't see
how you could defeat me now.
Trunks, I know all the data
about you via the spy robot.
With your power,
you could not even defeat
No. 17 or No. 18, let alone myself.
Well then, why are No. 17
and No. 18 no longer around?
So that's why.
Then you're the reason why
those two have disappeared, huh?
Damn... You killed No. 17 and No. 18.
What you've done was uncalled-for!
Thanks to you, I cannot achieve
my perfect form in this era!
I'm going to have to kill you after all.
I'll kill you, then use the
time machine to go to the past,
and absorb No. 17 and No. 18 there!
It would be bad if we fought here in Metro West.
The reconstruction has
progressed quite a bit.
We're going to change locations!
What a rookie. It appears
you've gotten a little better.
But you're making a laughingstock
of yourself for trying to defeat me.
I am the ultimate Artificial Human
created by Doctor Gero-sama!
There's no way that anyone
in the world can defeat me!
We'll see about that.
There's no chance I'm
letting you go back into the past!
Enough!
Th-This isn't supposed to be!
Damn... I am the ultimate Artificial Human.
There's no way I should be losing to that child!
Cell! Not you...
For the sake of peace on Earth,
I cannot permit your existence!
W-Why, you...
If that's how you want it, you
can be stunned by this technique!
Ka... me...
ha... me...
May you be completely obliterated, Cell!
D-Damn it all.
Damn it all...!
Now, it's all over. Thank you, everyone.
Thank you, Goku-san.
Come on, Bubbles, Gregory!
Try catching me, already!
You guys are hopeless.
You ain't been exercising enough
lately, and have gotten too fat!
All done!
I'm impressed, Kaio-sama!
Whoops! Kaio-sama, I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
I don't have the heart to build it again.
Kaio-sama, this works out perfect, doesn't it?
I didn't feel like living here in the first place.
Let's go somewhere!
I know! Where are those
masters of the Next World?
The masters of the Next World?
No fair!
You promised you'd take me
to where the masters of the
Next World were, didn't you?
Or do you not know where they are?
No, of course I know where they are.
But Goku, over there, there'll be...
Let's go!
I want to meet these masters
of the Next World right away!
And so, Goku and Kaio-sama's
tour of the Next World began.
Who were these masters of the
Next World that awaited Goku?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Say, Kaio-sama, what kind of dude
is the number-one guy in the Next World?
Now, see here! You can't refer to him as a dude!
He is the Grand Kaio, the
greatest man in the Next World.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"A Deep Impression!! There They Are!
The Next World's Awesome Dudes."
Huh? Father, you're going to
Hell with one of the other masters
to put down Cell?
"Next time"
"A Deep Impression!! There They Are!
The Next World's Awesome Dudes"