The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
This is the purely evil, absolutely
most powerful, ultimate Majin Boo!
And this is the only thing
left that can lay him to rest...
Do you hear me, people of the world?!
Raise your hands to the sky!
Vegeta has bet everything
on a Super Genki Dama,
with the assembled Genki of
all of Earth's people. However...
Something I don't trust about this, you know?
Yeah. Who do they think
is going to raise their hands?
It doesn't have anything to do with us, anyhow.
W-What was that?!
It's your Earth!!
How long are you going to act so
spoiled before you're finally satisfied?!
I-It's no use any more! Please! Help Boo out!
Listen, Earthlings!
Why don't you... why don't you
lend us your power for a change?!
Hurry, everyone on Earth!
Send your genki to Goku!
The Boo we're relying on
can't hold out any longer!
"Ultra-Impressive!! The Genki Dama
From Everyone is Finished"
There hasn't been the
least bit of Genki gathered,
except for that of Goku-san's friends.
V-Vegeta-san, can't you use a
more polite manner in your request?
Nah, that would probably be asking too much.
He's like one big lump of pride, after all.
P-Please...
W-What was that?!
I'm asking you... please, raise your hands...!
Vegeta... you're...
I-I'm asking you...
...please...
...raise your hands!
M-Maybe I should raise them up and see.
H-Hey, don't do that!
It'll definitely make trouble!
Don't do that, I said!
I-It couldn't be...! M-My power really was...!
Th-There, you see?!
This is a trap of the devil!
E-Everyone, be careful!
Sounds like it really will suck out your power!
It looks painful!
Everyone, be sure you don't
raise your hands! Don't be fooled!
You fool! Who do you think
is going to listen to you?!
Say, this isn't that Babidi
or whoever guy, right?
You dirty bastards!
Th-This is bad! The chubby
one is on the verge of dying!
Th-This is too awful! Even for
a dream, this is going too far!
–Boo!
–Damn, it's all over!
Damn it all, I can't take it any more!
What the hell are you doing?!
Stop that, you...!
I hit him...!
That's not what I...
N-No, s-s-see, I...!
This ain't good!
That dirty bastard! He's found us out!
Kakarrot! I'll do what
I can to buy a little more time!
You'll have to convince
those idiots on Earth now!
Buy time, you say? You just came back to life,
and ain't got sufficient ki yet, do you?!
M-Make fun of me, will you?
Vegeta!
K-Kakarrot!
H-Hurry...!
C-Convince those idiots on Earth...!
Everybody on Earth! I beg you!
I beg you, share your Genki with me!
We need everybody's help!
Raise your hands to the sky!
Quickly!
N-Noble Father, that voice just now...!
Mm-hmm! We finally learn
the identity behind these voices!
It is Son Goku and friends!
They fight for us, against Majin Boo!
Can you hear my voice?!
Everyone! Share your Genki with me!
It is indeed Goku-san's voice!
Come now, Upa!
Hold your hand toward heaven!
Right!
Come, the rest of you as well, quickly!
Goku-san, please make
use of our power as well!
Geez, what is it with him?
From one thing to 'nother, that
guy sure does tough it out, huh?
Really, I gotta bow my head to him. Y'know?
I see. So that's it, huh?
It's been a while since I've heard his voice.
–That one from before, you know?
–Yeah, that was a pretty good one.
Yes, that will do nicely.
This is the ki that I have raised up
through all of the training I've done.
Take it all!
We're counting on you,
Son Goku! Be sure you defeat Boo!
Everybody on Earth! Share more,
even more of your Genk i with me!
It's Son Goku! It's Son Goku! Snow!
You're right! That's definitely him
all right! That sure takes me back!
What? That's Son Goku?
Yeah, from back then!
We sure are hungry!
Now, hurry! Hurry and
raise your hands to the sky!
Hey, the voice on this guy
sounds like he's trustworthy.
Don't be fooled by the voice!
It's definitely one of Boo's cronies!
He's right! It's too suspicious!
They haven't been making
their identities clear to us!
If we do as that voice says, then
something awful is going to happen to us!
It's no use! It just got a
little bit bigger from that!
Vegeta!
Don't you have it backward, there?
The one who's going to defeat you...
...is going to be me!
Hurry! Hurry and give me your Genki!
Why?! Why doesn't anyone understand?
Th-This can't be! Most of the people
on Earth aren't sharing their Genki!
They've already been
hammered by Babidi and Boo.
Seeing it from the Earthlings' side,
it's only natural they can't trust anyone.
All right, let's go into the city too!
We'll all split up, and go
around convincing the city's people.
Right now, that's the only thing
we can do for Goku and Vegeta.
Understood. Let's go right away!
Yeah!
Everyone! Please, raise
your hands toward the sky!
Please! Raise your hands toward the sky!
If we don't, then something terrible
will happen to the Earth again! Please!
Please! Please!
Mister!
This isn't the time to be doing
that! The Earth is in trouble!
Look, enough! You sure are some
annoyin' brats! Stop gettin' in my way!
Everyone, raise your hands!
Look to the sky and raise your hands!
Here! I'll give you these, so
go off playin' somewhere else!
We got these!
H-He's here!
Run!
Hey! Hurry it up, everybody!
Don't you care what happens to Earth,
and the rest of the universe,
you stupid bastards?!
What was that? Stupid bastards?
That's a pretty insolent attitude
from someone asking for something!
Just ignore them. Ignore them.
It could be that the whole Majin Boo
thing never really happened, couldn't it?
That's right! It's entirely possible
we've all been hypnotized as a group!
That's it, that's it! Oh, well...
W-Why, you all...!!
That's enough out of you all!
Why don't you cooperate, already?!
Does this mean you will also not listen
to the request from me, Mister Satan-sama?
It's Satan!
Say, that was Mister Satan's
voice just now, Mama!
Mister Satan?
Satan?
Hey, that sure was Mister Satan's voice!
What does that mean?
That's really Satan! It was his voice!
C-Could it be that the one fighting Majin Boo...
is Mister Satan, then?
I'm sure it is! It has to be!
It's our hero, Satan!
Th-That's right! I wanted to keep it quiet,
but it's no use, now that the secret is out!
I will defeat Majin Boo for us.
So could you folks quickly lend me your power?!
W-Well, we've got no choice, right?
Unless I say it like that,
they won't trust us, after all.
Besides, our first priority is
to defeat Boo there, you know.
I knew it! I knew it! It's him!
That voice was Mister Satan!
Satan! Satan! Satan! Satan!
Here it comes, here it comes!
I'm beaten. You've got
me beaten, Mister Satan!
All right! That's it! Go!
Go!
Go on! Go on!
Just a little bit more until there's a full tank!
Just a bit longer!
Hold out just a bit longer, Vegeta!
Hey! It's still not enough!
Is there anyone who
hasn't raised their hand yet?!
I-It's no use...!
It's done! It's done!
After Satan's part, which
nobody had anticipated,
the Super Genki Dama is at last complete!
Get back, Vegeta! Here it goes!!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Rats! The Genki Dama is finished,
but my strength is failing me!
At this rate, Boo is just gonna push it back!
I know! Dende, what about Polunga?
Use the third wish to
replenish Kakarrot's strength!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Son Goku is Strongest After All!!
Majin Boo is Eliminated."
Father's power is back!
The long battle is almost over!
"Next time"
"Son Goku is Strongest After All!!
Majin Boo is Eliminated"