Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Goku still has not recovered
from his heart disease.
Additionally, the Artificial
Humans seek Goku's life.
However, there is an absolute
terror, even greater than this crisis!
The monster from the future
has sucked out the life's
essence of one person after another!
In order to oppose him,
Piccolo merges with Kami-sama,
becoming a reborn Namekian
warrior with enormous power!
A fierce battle has already begun between them!
"A Life Form of Evil and Destruction!!
His Name Is Artificial Human Cell."
Ka...
me...
T-That stance! It can't be...!
ha...
me...
How can this be?
Ha!!
It's the real thing!
Your life is mine!
I struck your arm, did I?
The outcome is still the same.
I will take your powerful life's essence from you!
Still, who could it be that
Piccolo is fighting now, anyhow?
I don't think there's any
mistaking that it's the monster
that hatched after riding
back in my time machine.
Why do you suppose that
thing has Goku, Piccolo, Vegeta,
not to mention Freeza and his father's ki?
Why indeed.
Damn! Just what exactly is going on?!
Goku-sa is gettin' just about over it, huh?
Isn't that great, Mother?
G-Goku-sa?
Father!
Huh?
He's gone back to sleep.
But he should be opening his eyes soon, right?
A-yep!
I'm going to go tell Oolong-san and the others!
Guys!
We have received word that currently,
the armed forces at Metro West have at length...
...commenced an emergency
mobilization toward Gingertown.
Armed forces?
In consideration of the safety
of the neighboring districts,
it is hoped this will allow
area citizens some peace of mind.
It would be nice if there
were no further casualties...
This information just in:
Please watch, as we have
images of one of the tank divisions
as they head toward the scene.
The images, please.
Currently, we seem to be having
trouble connecting with our remote unit...
Ah, they're waiting?
We appear to be connected.
T-That's him!
Hey, you up there!
You are completely surrounded!
Surrender yourself,
without any useless resistance!
You dare interrupt my meal?!
Dammit! Attack! Attack!
We got him!
He's still alive!
What?!
You miserable cockroaches!
Dammit!
Fire missiles!
That was quite the annoyance.
So then, shall we continue the meal?
Kami-sama...
Something the matter, No. 16?
There's been a fluctuation in
that power reading from before.
It appears a conclusion has been reached.
From before?
You mean that one with the
power that rivaled our own?
That's right.
Are you still saying that?
Your power radar is malfunctioning, No. 16.
There's no way in the world a
power level that rivals ours could exist.
Don't make me say it again.
You were lucky to get away.
But not having use of one arm, it
seems the advantage has been reversed!
Certainly true.
My balance is thrown off like this,
making it quite difficult for me.
Unfortunately, it would seem you have won!
Not even you can help
admitting when you're beaten!
Rejoice! Once I absorb the
magnitude of your life's essence,
I will have drawn much
closer to my perfect form.
Perfect form?!
You will be of great
service to me. Aren't you glad?!
Before I am to be absorbed by you,
you have to tell me something!
What in the hell are you?!
Why is it you have Son Goku,
Freeza and everyone's ki,
and are even able to
perform the Kamehame-Ha?!
Very well.
You're going to die anyway. I'll tell you.
My name is Cell. I am an Artificial Human.
A-Artificial Human?!
I was born of the computer used by Doctor Gero.
Doctor Gero again!
A long time ago,
Doctor Gero began collecting
the cells of the greatest warriors,
to research how he could synthesize
an Artificial Human from those cells.
However, because it was taking too much time,
he gave up on it partway through.
But the computer continued its operation.
Piccolo...
Son Goku...
and Vegeta's cells were collected at the battle
when Vegeta first came to Earth.
Hmph, Goku from that period of time, huh?
That explains why your Kamehame-Ha
before wasn't all that great.
Further,
we had the good fortune of
obtaining Freeza and his father's cells
when they came to Earth.
We could have taken the
cells of that guy Trunks as well,
but there was already enough from the Saiyans.
H-How did you collect the cells?!
There wasn't anyone
suspicious there at the time!
You should have heard this from Gero,
how all your actions have
been examined via a spy robot.
There is a small robot, similar to myself.
No one is likely to have noticed it.
That's what took the cells.
Take a good look!
It's here even now, relaying the data
of our situation back to the computer.
It probably wants to take your cells as well!
You bastard!
It's too late to destroy it now!
The necessary cells have already been collected,
and the experiment has begun!
Indeed, it will be twenty-four years
from now when I will be completed.
Impossible! Doctor Gero's
laboratory has been destroyed!
There is still a room beneath the
laboratory where the computer is!
So that's it.
Once you came to this era,
why has it taken you three years to
change from an egg to the way you are?
Once I return myself to an egg,
I require three years
underground to mature again.
That's how much time it takes.
That's all I have to say.
It's about time you let me absorb you.
One last question!
For what reason did you go to the
trouble of coming here from the future?
In order for me to become my perfect form,
the absorption of human
essences alone is not enough!
It is necessary for me to merge with
two essential specialized life forms.
The computer has told me that
those two specialized life forms were...
...the Artificial Humans that Doctor
Gero had created, No. 17 and No. 18!
What?!
However, in the future,
where I was, for some reason–
perhaps they were defeated by that Trunks guy,
I don't know–No. 17 and No. 18 weren't around.
But luckily for me, Trunks had his time machine!
After killing Trunks,
I used the time machine to come to
this era in search of No. 17 and No. 18.
W-Why did you choose this era?!
Well now, Trunks' time machine
was already set for this era.
All I did was push the switch.
So that's it.
Trunks must have set the time
machine so he could come tell us
that somehow he had
destroyed the Artificial Humans.
A-And then he came along...
The computer also told me this...
Once I become my perfect form,
I will have a terrible power,
far beyond imagination,
in the palm of my hand!
For what reason?!
Why is it you seek to have
that much overwhelming power?!
What reason?
You ask such a nonsensical thing!
The computer had been
input to create a strong being,
one to the very limits of its consideration!
Or for that matter, it may be what
the blood of the Saiyans, Freeza,
and Piccolo that flows within me seeks!
I get it.
So then, are you satisfied?
My gratitude.
Thanks to you, all of the
mysteries have now been solved.
You've been quite informative!
Y-You did all that to get me to talk?!
I will not allow you to
become this perfect form of yours!
For you to have inherited my blood
and not realize that I could
re-grow my arm makes you an idiot!
The situation has reversed!
However, the beast's depth
of power is still unmeasured.
Z Warriors, do not allow the
monster Cell his perfect form!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Cell is having a free-for-all while I'm asleep.
Once I've recovered, I'll beat him senseless!
I will acquire No. 17 and
No. 18, no matter what!
I will achieve my perfect form,
and gain the ultimate power!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Piccolo's Grievous Mistake!
Cell Turned Loose on the City!"
We have to catch him, quickly!
"Next time"
"Piccolo's Grievous Mistake!
Cell Turned Loose on the City!"