Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
I-It's a Saiyan spaceship!
It's Vegeta. He's the only one it could be.
Dammit!
Freeza, you bastard! I won't
let you snatch them away from me!
What?!
W-Why is there another one coming?
Planet Namek was everyone's star of hope.
However, now it had been
changed into a star of misfortune,
as it swirls with Freeza's rapacity.
"Vegeta's Ambition! I am the
Greatest Warrior in the Universe!!"
This is bad... this is definitely bad...
There aren't supposed to be any other Saiyans.
W-Who could it be?
Now there are three more, yes?
Hold them with care, Dodoria-san.
It appears that Vegeta is after them, as well.
Freeza-sama, Kewie, who is
pursuing Vegeta, has just landed.
And as for those two large
power readings that appeared earlier,
they suddenly disappeared, and remain so.
We are searching the area
where the readings were located,
so we should soon
discover what their source was.
Well, the issue here is the
disposal of Vegeta, who has defied me.
In that case, you need not worry.
Kewie should now be heading
after Vegeta to deal with him.
Those two have always hated each other,
and their abilities are roughly the same.
In any event, Vegeta is not
likely to come away unscathed.
Vegeta, you're not getting away from me.
I've found you, Vegeta. I'm
under orders from Freeza-sama!
Are you reading me, Vegeta?!
Now I can kill you out in the open!
Don't make me laugh,
Kewie. You think you can kill me?
I'm waiting here for you, so get here fast.
What are you, blind?
Take a good look at your Scouter.
My battle power is clearly higher than yours!
We can't stay here, in any case, can we?
I'll leave the Dragon Balls up to you.
Okay, well, I'm going
back to Earth, so good luck.
Bulma-san, just a minute.
What should we do, Gohan?
S-Should we go back to Earth now, too?
After all, it looks like
we've got one more foe now,
and even if we do have the Dragon Radar...
Oh, I mean, I'm fine and all,
but it wouldn't be right if
anything were to happen to Gohan.
B-But Kuririn-san, if we do that,
then he'll get the Dragon Balls.
Well, if we yield the
Dragon Balls to him this time,
we could always use them next time.
That would be okay, as long as he
doesn't kill Shen Long, like Piccolo did before.
Kuririn-san, someone is coming!
I-Is it a Saiyan?
N-No, it's not Vegeta. This ki is weaker.
This should be the area
where the readings disappeared.
Must be Namekians.
Who is it?
Probably Namekians.
T-They're not Namekians!
Hmm? W-What is that?
Those aren't Namekians! Who are they?!
That doesn't matter. We were ordered
to just kill anyone who was on this planet.
Look at what they're wearing!
Those are just like what the Saiyans
were wearing. Yet... they're not Saiyans.
I haven't a clue what it means,
but I've got a bad feeling about this.
R-Right... Any way you look at
them, those are not friendly faces...
Gohan, build up your ki while
keeping your presence masked.
Right.
Do you see that? These guys are
common trash, with barely any battle power!
They're just tourists.
We won't get to have any fun if they run away.
Take care of their spaceship first.
All right.
Oh, crap! Our spaceship!
These guys are so unlucky to
have come here at a time like this.
Gohan, release your ki.
These guys aren't all that tough!
Hey, did you hear that?
Not all that tough? Does he mean us?
W-What kind of battle power ratings are these?!
Let's do it!
Right!
Hey, nice, nice!
That was not nice!
What are we going to do about that?
Is something the matter, Zarbon-san?
Yes, Freeza-sama. It is about
the search that was ordered earlier.
It would seem that
they are no ordinary people.
Their battle powers rose momentarily,
then once they had defeated our pair
of scouts, their readings disappeared again.
Ho, that is curious. It does
not appear to be Vegeta, either.
Correct, the readings are different from Vegeta.
Their battle powers were both around 1,500.
1,500, you say? We could leave
them alone, and nothing would come of it,
but their attitude does not
seem to be very good, does it?
The next time they are found, eliminate them.
All right, just a little more...
Goku-sa...
Chichi...
What are you doin'?
Oh, you know, I was bored, so...
Really... How about you realize
somewhat that you were seriously injured?
If you don't lie there quietly,
you're goin' to open your wounds up again.
Ow! Yow-ow-ow-ow! Don't be so rough!
Yow-ow-ow-ow! That hurts! That hurts!
Never mind that, I wonder if Gohan-chan is okay.
I hope he's washin' his
hair, and usin' that rinse.
His hair is so shiny and all,
so he has to look after his cuticles.
Is he usin' his hair dryer?
His hair dries out so fast,
and he has to take care of it right...
Gohan...
It's hopeless! It's all over!
We'll never get back to Earth now!
Uh, Bulma-san, for the time
being, let's get away from here.
It's dangerous here. Someone
even stronger might come along.
That's right. Those many ki
that we sensed weren't Namekians,
but appear to be friends of Vegeta,
so we need to go hide somewhere.
Things will work out somehow.
I'm sure the Namekians
will repair the spaceship for us.
How nice that you can be so optimistic!
Bulma-san...
Hmph, you're finally here, are you?
You imbecile.
It looks like the time has come
when we can finally settle things
between us as fellow rivals, huh?
But it looks like you've let yourself go.
You've got no chance of
beating me with that battle power.
Fellow rivals, you say?
Well, let me show you a little something.
When I was on Earth, I learned
something interesting from them.
What, how to run away quickly?
How to control my battle power!
H-How to control your battle power?
Take a good look at my battle
power rating on your Scouter!
I-Impossible! You and I have
always been evenly matched!
You idiot! I have been fighting
in actual combat constantly.
The battle on Earth was
such that it nearly killed me.
Did you think I would
remain equal with you forever,
as you just sat around
in comfort at Freeza's place?!
19,000... 20,000... 21,000... 22,000!
What happened, Zarbon?
I-I think it was a malfunction,
but the rating on my Scouter, which was
set on Vegeta, had just risen above 22,000...
22,000, you say?
That really was a malfunction.
Your Scouter is an older model, after all.
I'll find out his true rating for you on mine.
What's his rating?
T-This is absurd... Could my
newer model be malfunctioning, too?
He's gone up to 24,000...
If he's at 24,000... Are you saying that
his battle power is even higher than ours?
I-It couldn't be. His battle
power would just barely reach 18,000.
It is nothing to be surprised about.
Vegeta has been fighting
on the front lines, you see.
He probably came upon
some sort of new skill on Earth.
But...
It is only 24,000. If the
two of you fight together,
it is a rating that you can
sufficiently beat, is it not?
Vegeta probably wants to obtain
eternal life with the Dragon Balls,
the same wish that I have.
Unless he does so, there is no way
that he can prevail against me, you see.
Vegeta never has been respectful toward me.
He went to Earth without my orders,
and he even appears to be
after my position for his own.
Though I must say, this is brash of him.
To think that he would come
out in open treason against me...
W-Wait, Vegeta! I just had a great idea!
Let me work with you. I can lend you a hand.
I-I didn't like Freeza-sa–
I mean, Freeza before this, either.
T-That doesn't sound bad, does it?
If you team up with me at that battle power,
I think we could somehow
manage Zarbon and Dodoria.
Spout more of your worthless lies, will you?
You are one thoroughly disgusting bastard!
It's no lie, I tell you!
Believe me, Vegeta!
Oh! Freeza-sama!
What?!
Miserable fool!
No matter how much his battle power had risen,
nobody could stand up
to being taken unawares by that.
You wish.
What an utterly pathetic strategy,
coming from someone like you. I'm astounded.
W-When did you manage to–?
Having an elevated battle power means
that my speed has been elevated as well.
In other words, you have
now gotten me thoroughly angry.
Die!
That was one foul firework.
V-Vegeta's 24,000 rating
is the real thing, all right.
He did in Kewie with no trouble at all.
It is of little import. Now, we
search for the fifth Dragon Ball.
Thanks to their Scouters,
they'll know exactly what my actions are.
Even if I were careless
enough to get too close to them,
I might be able to take Zarbon or Dodoria,
but there's still no way I can beat Freeza.
Judging by the transmissions I heard
over the Scouter between Freeza and his men,
these Dragon Ball things don't work
unless you have all seven of them together.
All right, I'll search out just one of them.
Once they have gathered the remaining six,
I'll look for an opening
and take theirs from them.
If things go right, and I get
them all, I'll gain eternal life.
Once I do, defeating Freeza
will no longer be just a dream!
There is a reading of around
ten Namekians in that direction.
Very well.
It would be nice if they
had the fifth Dragon Ball.
Please make sure not
to let your guard down.
It would seem there are some mysterious
others out there, in addition to Vegeta.
Yes, sir.
Now, let us be going.
With him gone, I'll be number one.
The whole universe will be
ruled by Vegeta-sama the Saiyan!
Bulma-san, we have to hurry a little bit more,
or they're going to find us out here!
You guys can fly, right?
Take me with you, and fly.
I wish we could do that, but
we're walking to mask our presence.
Flying through the air requires a lot of ki,
and the enemy will know where we are.
Bulma-san, there's a good place.
It will be hard to find us in that hole.
H-How long am I going to
have to live in a place like that?
Kuririn-san...
Do you sense any ki over there?
You're right. It feels different
from the ki we felt earlier, huh?
It could be the Namekians this time.
Hide! There's another ki
coming this way from that direction!
What is this ki that is coming
toward them at top speed? Is it Vegeta?
Or is it Freeza and company?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
I'm so excited!
To think that there's someone
out there even stronger than Vegeta.
I'm going to Planet Namek!
He's an idiot. He's got
zero chance of beating him.
He ain't normal, that's fer sure.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Goku's Power Unleashed!!
Six Days to the Far End of the Galaxy."
Freeza, just you wait! My father is coming!
"Next time"
"Goku's Power Unleashed!!
Six Days to the Far End of the Galaxy"