Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Three years from this time,
on May 12, at around 10 a.m.,
on an island located 9 kilometers
southwest of Metro South,
a terrifying pair will appear.
They will be monsters,
both possessing a power so great,
it will be unthinkable
that they are of this world.
The fearsome enemies that Trunks,
the youth from the
future had told them about,
as well as his hellish future–it was for
these reasons that Goku, Piccolo, Vegeta,
and the other Z Warriors desperately
continued their special training.
The Artificial Humans will appear in three years.
There is no time for the warriors to take off.
Until one day...
"License Mastery?
Goku's Newest Trial."
Cut it out! I ain't all that tasty!
Stop!
That cloud looks like Old Man Turtle Hermit.
Father, look!
Oh, you caught us a
huge one there, Gohan.
Chichi's sure to be happy.
Taking these breaks
from training is useless!
That's the couple from
the next mountain over.
Mother, we're home!
I have a present for you.
Welcome home, Gohan-chan.
We sure worked up quite a sweat today.
Gohan, wanna hop in the tub with me?
Okay, Father.
Piccolo-san, will you join us?
Hey, Chichi, we'll be in the tub.
I've had enough already!
This ain't even funny!
You don't make Gohan-chan study,
and spend all day doin'
nothin' but trainin' with Piccolo!
As for me, I was just chased by a wild boar,
and had a real terrible time of it!
Yet with you, Goku-sa, you
play all ya want without any fuss!
You know, sometimes I see the
husband from the next mountain over,
an' how they have a nice Air Car
they use for fetchin' their shoppin' in!
But we don't have that kind of car,
and even so, I ain't got a license.
So, you can just get one!
These days I bet you're the only one
who don't have a single license, Goku-sa!
Piccolo ain't got one.
You expect I would have such a thing?!
So then, starting tomorrow,
you both are goin' to the driving
institute in town and learnin'!
It'll be a good chance for you two
to expand your knowledge of the world.
W-What?!
H-Hold on, Chichi, this is so sudden!
No more discussin' it!
Startin' tomorrow, you two
are takin' a break from trainin',
and you're gonna start goin' to the institute!
If you don't, neither
of you get anythin' to eat!
You got that?!
So this is the institute
that Chichi was talking about?
I don't see why you had to bring me into this.
Sorry, sorry. The truth just kind of slipped out.
Let's just get our licenses
quick and go back to training.
Well, I suppose that's the only way.
You know, the power of that earthling,
silencing the strongest man
in the universe, is formidable.
Which one of you is Goku-san, then?
That's me.
You will be under my supervision.
I hope you will treat me well...
Whoa, whoa, whoa, are you okay, old timer?
I'm fine, I'm fine! This
happens all the time, after all.
Then you must be Piccolo-san,
whom I will be supervising, right?
So now, I will first
demonstrate what it is to drive,
so please watch carefully.
I'm supposed to learn
driving from this chatterbox?
Don't forget your seatbelt.
Dammit...
What?!
Here we go!
Open your eyes wide and watch closely!
W-What is the deal with this woman?!
What incredible speed...
Well, why don't we get going too...
Forgive me, but Son-san, wasn't it?
Could I get you to open my door?
Vegeta-chan hasn't shown
himself around here lately.
Mama misses him.
For some reason, he seems to be
staying overnight inside the spaceship.
You know, those Saiyans have
such wonderfully tough bodies.
Lately, he's been training
under a gravity of 400g.
He can do that because
he's a deviant maniac for battle.
Damn. You just watch this, Kakarrot!
I wonder how Father
and Piccolo-san are doing.
Gohan-chan!
How admirable, Gohan-chan!
You've been studyin' hard all along, right?
Thanks to Goku-sa and Piccolo,
you've gotten so far behind, you know?
While those nuisances are out of our way,
study up as much as ya can!
You're tickling me, Haiya Dragon!
I've got an idea!
Nicely done, Piccolo-san.
Okay, try pulling out again.
Why don't you hurry and get going?
I've forgotten how to make it go.
Not again! You know, in
my 70 years as an instructor,
you're the only one to
have a memory this poor.
Sorry, old timer.
Try stepping on the accelerator.
Akuseru?
No, I took a bath before I came.
No, not asekusai, the accelerator!
[asekusai: smells of sweat]
There's a pedal under your right foot, see?
That's the accelerator. Next to it is the brake.
How long before you
finally remember this?
So that's it.
W-What?!
I made a mistake!
What are you doing?
Right now we're supposed
to be backing! Backing!
That's what I meant to do!
The brake! Step on the brake!
Let's see, the brake is on the left, so...
Cut in the steering handle!
Cut in the handle!
A-Are you sure?
Of course I am! Hurry up!
I cut it!
It's going to take you about
three years to get your license.
But I ain't got that much time!
See, if I don't train, then
the Artificial Humans will...
Idiot.
Over there, Haiya Dragon!
Ready? Go forward. Forward.
Right! Leave it to me!
All right, now press it down little by little...
Yahoo! I actually made it move forward!
Didn't I tell you just a little bit?
Goku! Are you trying to compete against me?!
Fine! I'm not losing to the likes of you!
That's the way, Piccolo-san!
Father!
You have quite a talent for this, Piccolo-san.
What?!
Hang on...
These Air Cars sure are dangerous.
Very well, today we'll start
teaching you on public roads.
If you start driving
recklessly like you were earlier,
we will immediately expel you.
You can't possibly get your license,
and I'm going to treat you as such.
See here! Don't take your
hands off the steering handle!
Minus one point.
Just a second now...
You mustn't look to the side!
Looking sideways is minus two points.
You're kidding!
You can't stop suddenly like that!
What about the people following after you?
That's minus ten points!
I'm leaving this to you, Piccolo!
Thank you, mister! Good-bye!
See ya!
Sorry, old timer!
We didn't mean to slip out in
the middle of our practice like this.
Huh? Looks like I just can't
manage whatever it takes for driving.
Maybe I don't have the talent.
How can you say that?
So, you mean you'll let
us continue our practice?
You were marvelous! Marvelous!
I am so impressed by what you did!
Really? Well, let's get our practice
going again right away, old timer!
Out of the question.
There's nothing we can teach to you!
What?
S-So, our licenses?
What are you joking about?
With the power you two have,
you don't need licenses, do you?
It's the truth!
What did you say?!
You didn't get your license?!
N-No.
Mother!
Chichi! Are you okay?
And so, in no time at all,
three years had passed.
Gohan-chan, Goku-sa,
Piccolo-san, you all be careful!
You're sure you don't
wanna take lunch with you?
N-No, thank you.
Thanks anyway.
Well, let's go.
Because of the Artificial Humans,
the future I live in is a hellish world.
Too strong... They're too strong!
Finally, the time for battle had come.
We're counting on you, Goku!
We're counting on you, Super Warriors!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Yajirobe's Sky Car has been shot down!
Was it the Artificial Humans?
I didn't sense their ki at all!
This is bad. We'll just have to
search them out visually. Damn...
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Murderers Who Leave No Trace –
Which Ones Are the Artificial Humans!?"
They've descended into the city!
"Next time"
"Murderers Who Leave No Trace–
Which Ones Are the Artificial Humans!?"