Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Freeza's secret weapon, the Ginyu
Special Corps, had at last gone into action.
Where are you, you punk kids?!
Come on out, or you'll be sorry!
Vegeta was burning with rage after Gohan
and the others took the
Si Xing Qiu Ball from him.
However, by then, Bulma and the
others had moved their hiding place.
Further, in order to have
Gohan's dormant power drawn out,
he was headed to the Grand
Elder's place, along with Kuririn.
"Watch Out, Bulma!!
Si Xing Qiu Falls into Freeza's Clutches."
W-What?! What was that?!
I've found you!
V-V-V...
How dare you make a mockery of me!
Where is the Dragon Ball?!
There.
Where is it?!
I-I told you... it's right there.
If you won't tell me,
then I'll just have to do this!
What are you talking about?
I've been telling you, haven't I?
It's there! It's there! Why don't you get it?!
It's there, I tell you!
It was a dream, huh?
Damn it...
If the device that kid was holding
really is something that
can seek out Dragon Balls,
then I can't be careless about leaving here.
They wanted these six, too.
All I can do is wait for
them to make their move.
Freeza is starting to get pretty impatient, huh?
That means I've destroyed the
spaceship's power, and he can't move.
Even assuming that he radioed
to have more Scouters brought here,
it would take three or four
days for them to get here, at best.
I'll have to settle this before that time.
If I can just acquire eternal
life with the Dragon Balls,
then depending on my strategy,
I'm sure I will be able to defeat Freeza.
Now, when he doesn't
have a Scouter, is my chance.
That miserable Vegeta!
W-What is with all these earthquakes lately?
That's it! I've had all I can
take of this crazy planet!
Damn, it's going to take quite a bit
of time for us to get there at this speed.
But if we use any more ki than this,
that Vegeta bastard will
find us, no doubt about it.
It looked like he had gotten even stronger.
Right now, even with the two of us
going at him together,
there's no way we could beat him.
But then, do I really have
enough power to rival Vegeta?
I wouldn't think so.
Well, I had this much latent power,
so with you having Saiyan blood,
I think we're okay to expect quite a lot.
Probably, anyway.
It's not like I have to go in and get it, right?
Even in the water like that,
it's still right nearby,
the same as if it were on shore.
Once Kuririn gets back,
I can just have him go get it.
Sure.
D-Don't tell me it's Vegeta!
What do I do? If Si Xing Qiu
falls into Vegeta's hands,
he'll have all seven Dragon Balls,
and be granted eternal life.
If that happens, then no matter
how much training Son-kun has done,
he'll have no chance of winning.
And that's not all.
Yamucha and the others won't
be able to come back to life, either.
And I'll never be able to return to Earth.
All right...
Let's see, as I recall, it was this one.
Taking the fight to Vegeta, or
whoever it is, is better than waiting around,
rotting away on this planet.
Let's see...
This is for missiles, and
this is for the laser cannon.
Okay...
There it is!
I get it. You're the culprit, huh?
Well then, I'm not going to hold back.
I did it!
Yahoo!
Ka... me... ha... me...
Ha!!
S-Senzu... senzu...
Whew! I have to be more careful.
I got a glimpse of the Next World there.
If I'm dead, I won't be
able to train worth crap.
I'll be there in just over two days.
Well, I guess I should
keep at it a little longer.
That's a good boy. Just stay still.
That's a big pearl!
Something like that would be...
Be a good boy there for
just a little while, okay?
All right...
Huh?
Hang on a minute!
There it is!
H-Hold on, here... What is this?
It's almost as though they
were imitation Dragon Balls, huh?
What in the world could this be?
In any event, the first order of
business is to get the Si Xing Qiu Ball back.
My Capsule! My escape Capsule!
It's gone... it's gone!
You're kidding me!
It was there just a moment ago!
Where is it?! Where did it go?!
There it is!
It will take more than that to defeat Bulma-san!
Geez, like I've been telling you,
that's my Si Xing Qiu there, not yours!
They were eggs!
Watch out!
What are you doing?! Run!
I'm not doing this for you!
I'm doing it for the Dragon Ball!
I've had it with living like this.
Where are the other Dragon Balls?
Where is Vegeta?
No matter. Once you go before Freeza-sama,
you'll talk, whether you want to or not.
Freeza?
Come on!
Bulma goes from one crisis to another.
And has one of the Dragon Balls
once again passed into Freeza's hands?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Whew! A Kamehame-Ha at
100 Gs also has 100 times more force!
That was a close one!
What are you doing, Son-kun?!
Hurry up and get here!
Don't you care that a spunky young girl...
is about to be killed by Freeza on this planet?!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Charge!! The Kaio-ken and
Kamehame-Ha of an Indomitable Spirit."
Father! Hurry! Hurry!
"Next time"
"Charge!! The Kaio-ken and
Kamehame-Ha of an Indomitable Spirit"
Father! Hurry! Hurry!