The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
To become the mightiest of Majin,
Boo absorbed Gotenks and Piccolo!
Majin Boo and Gohan's
ferocious battle continued...
Not yet, not yet!
As long as I have time remaining,
I will have you entertain me!
Elsewhere, as Goku returned to life
in exchange for the life of the elder Kaioshin...
Here! Put one of these
Potara earrings on your left ear.
Have Gohan place the
other one on his right ear.
Just by doing that, you two can
combine together, like you were in Fusion.
What will come of the Potara, mysterious
items received from the elderly Kaioshin?
"The Miracle Happens Once... Will the
Super Combination With Gohan Come About?"
Can we really combine just by
putting on these Potara things?
Of course you can! And the
effect is even greater than Fusion!
These are the treasures we Kaioshin
have kept up our sleeves
since long ago, you know!
I-I did not know...
There really is no helping the folks nowadays.
That's why you've gotten
so weak, for a Kaioshin.
Kibit, did you know about this?
No.
Look, just try it out!
You've got them too, right?
Kibit, you take off your left one.
I will do my right one...
R-Right.
We're going to hit each other!
I-Incredible! This is incredible power!
W-Whoa...!
Goku-san, I can fight too like this!
Let us go to Earth together!
Don't get carried away!
No matter how strong
you may have become,
you're still nothing special, at best!
You're bound to be
absorbed by Boo. You stay here.
O-Okay...
These certainly are awesome, old timer!
So, how long can we stay combined?
The Potara don't have that
sort of shortcoming! It's forever!
There's nothing to return
you back to normal again!
Never... return?
What a fix... Staying combined
with Gohan that whole time...
If it were possible, then
I for one would have returned...
You mean to say, old-timer, that you
combined with someone using the Potara?
Y-Yeah.
A long time ago, I used to be more handsome.
Then this nasty old witch took my
Potara when I wasn't paying attention...
What's this, an earring?
And here you're a man!
Let me borrow this for a second!
This sort of thing is more
suited to a pretty gal, like me.
...Which is how I came to
be like this. And, as a result,
I'm also able to do some
mysterious things, as you've seen.
Well, I guess it's this or nothing.
I wonder if perhaps, once peace is restored,
I'll have to start going
to Gohan's school like this.
What's the matter? Are you finished now?
D-Dammit!
W-What's going on?
I-I do not know. Gohan-san seems to
be getting considerably knocked around.
Gohan-san!
It's okay! I will heal you!
You're all worn out! I'm getting tired of this.
It's just about time I finish you off.
What's that guy doing?!
Gohan-san...
Dende...
Thank you, Dende!
Impossible! He's been restored to
the way he used to be! Who is that runt?!
The size of your ki has not changed.
It doesn't appear as if
you have powered up any.
You've just slightly prolonged
the time you will spend suffering!
Damn...!
While I'm at it, that annoying runt as well!
Oh, no!
D-Dammit, I'll shoot it down!
H-How's that?! Do you see
now, the power of my .45?!
W-Who's there?
T-Tenshinhan-san!
So, it was you, Gohan.
You've gotten tougher, huh?
Unbelievable. I didn't recognize you.
I'm surprised at the
change in Majin Boo, as well.
So, the annoying small
fry have increased again?
Nevertheless, small fry are,
after all, still small fry!
Kiko-ho!!
That didn't hurt in the least.
I-It's hopeless! Our dimensions are
too different! I won't be any help at all!
Shall I get around to settling this now?
I'll destroy the whole Earth, and
you small fry along with it, with this!
Try to avoid it, if you can!
F-Forgive me, Majin Boo! Die!!
Oh, yeah! Should I use these Potara
things after I've turned Super Saiyan?
No. Don't do anything you don't have to.
Once you've combined using the Potara,
you're going to be like that a long time.
That Super Saiyan thing
is too hard on the body.
You'd probably shorten your own lives.
Ah, really?
If you're going to become Super Saiyan,
it's better to do it after you've combined.
And even if you don't do so,
the power from just the
Potara should just be enough.
Wow, that'd be great.
That's right. You can only
use the Potara once, after all.
You can't do it over and over. Got it?
Goku-san! This is awful! Majin Boo
is planning to finish everything off!
Oh! You're right! This is bad!
Hurry, Goku-san!
Well, bye!
Everything, be gone!!
I-I'm sorry, Majin Boo!
F-Father...? What are you
doing in the lower realm?
Boo's body has been torn apart...
Th-They were my bullets.
Forgive me! I had no choice!
Majin Boo! Forgive me...!
I'm sure I've met you before.
That's it. You're the guy that
did those odd transformations.
Now what? Have you come,
planning to help? Ridiculous.
Don't you understand that fundamentally,
I am on a different
dimension now than I was then?
Act all big now, while you can!
I'm using a little item here
that gives an exceptional power-up!
What?
Of all the things you might have said...!
W-Why, you...!
That guy just now also appears to
be quite an expert, but with one kick,
that's how he ends up.
An exceptional power-up item, you say?
What nonsense! You're exaggerating!
To be frank, no matter what you might do,
there's absolutely no way
you can even damage me!
You sure hurried to put your body back
together, considering that, didn't you?
You're not thinking something
is going to happen, are you?
Small fry! You sure seem to
want to get killed! Very well!
Gohan! Here!
Pick it up! Gohan! Hurry!
Right!
Put that on your right ear!
You'll combine with me, and we'll defeat Boo!
W-Where is it?!
What?! Combine with him? So that's it!
Even if you do so, I think it'll be worthless,
but just to make sure, let me intervene.
I'm going to kill you first!
T-T-Time out for a second! Wait, please!
That stupid lunk!
It's hopeless!
Here goes!
D-Dammit!
It's useless!
Gohan!
Find it right away!
Right!
Here it is!
Damn!
You're not that bad.
Where is it?! Where is it?!
Now to finish you!
N-No, dammit!
S-So that's it!
The half-pints have returned
to normal from their Fusion!
Piccolo is coming out strongest!
You ran out of time! Too bad for you!
Boo, your power has dropped quite a bit!
Here it is!
Father!
Th-This is Kaioshin-sama's, right?
What was I supposed to do with it again?
H-Huh?
That's a bit disappointing.
With you like this now,
Gohan can beat you without going
to the trouble of combining with me!
It's a good thing I took out
some insurance, just in case!
Insurance? What do you mean?
This part that was cut off. Why do you
think I haven't returned it to normal?
D-Dammit, no!
Th-This can't be!
Y-You just can't do that, you know!
That's it! It's all over!
What will happen?
I don't know.
This is great! I'm much
more powered-up than before!
But this time, there is no time limit!
I-I can't combine with Gohan now!
I-It's no use! I'll have to
do it with someone else...!
T-Tenshinhan is down...
M-Mister Satan?
At length, Majin Boo has also absorbed Gohan!
Will Goku's merging companion
be Mister Satan after all?
What will you do, Goku?!
Can you beat Majin Boo?!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Hurry up and put that Potara on, Vegeta!
What are you making a fuss for?
Everyone has been devoured by Boo!
What are you waiting for? Hurry!
If you guys lose now, it will
mean the end of everything!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Merged!! Vegeta's Pride And Goku's Rage."
All right! It's the birth of
the invincible hero, Vegetto!
"Next time"
"Merged!! Vegeta's Pride And Goku's Rage"