Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
That there is Earth, Papa.
It couldn't be...
And yet, it surely is...
How can this be?!
This ki...
You think I could be mistaken about this?
You stupid fool!
It's not just one... there's
another... impossibly large ki.
Impossible!
I'm certain that Goku took care of Freeza!
What's this? Freeza survived!
And now, he brings with
him an even greater power!
The Earth is now in its greatest pinch ever!
"I Will Defeat Freeza...
The Mysterious Youth Awaiting Goku."
Why is this happening?
This is the worst, Father!
That's Kuririn-san's ki.
Yo!
Kuririn-san, have you sensed it?
Yeah. But, then again...
There's no way I could have missed this.
Not after having gone
through what his ki did to me...
Die!!
Goku!
So what does this mean?
Freeza wasn't killed by
Father after all, Kuririn-san?
That's what I'd like to know.
Nothing is adding up.
It doesn't hurt to travel through
frontier areas like this once in a while.
You sure are all fired up, aren't you, Freeza?
You needn't work yourself up
so much for such an opponent.
I'm just so excited, I can't help it, Papa.
It's nearly enough to make
me hop up and down in here.
Where does Vegeta get his speed from?
It's all I can do just to keep up!
If Freeza has survived, that means
Kakarrot went too easy on him, as I feared.
But never mind that,
who is this guy with Freeza,
the one with the ki so much larger than his?
Ten-san! Could this ki be...?
King Cold-sama, Freeza-sama,
we are about to land.
They should probably come
down around here somewhere.
You sure about that?
Anyone who doesn't know
him can keep their mouths shut!
At least I've actually fought against this guy.
Hey!
It's Bulma!
Vegeta, Yamucha, yoo-hoo!
Down's-a-daisy!
Yamucha-sama!
What do you guys think you're doing here?
We came to see this Freeza.
After all, when I was on Namek,
I didn't get to see him once!
You came to see him?
Surely you know how dangerous he is!
Sure I know, which is why we came!
If Freeza wanted to, he could "BOOM,"
blow up the whole world, right?
It doesn't matter where we are.
So that's why I wanted to have a look at him.
I thought she was just a vulgar
woman, but she's got plenty of guts.
Tenshinhan! Chaozu!
Vegeta! Are you back here on Earth again?
Sounds like you got
something you want to say to me.
You bet I do.
I've got plenty to say to you.
After all, we were killed at your hand.
I can't fathom how Yamucha
can stand to live together with you.
You runt.
What?!
Hey, hold on now!
This isn't the time and place for this.
What's happening is terrible. Is it Freeza?
Yeah, apparently so.
Hey, you two!
Don't just stand there talking, mask
your battle powers now, you pinheads!
Those guys will have Scouters with them.
That Namekian is doing an excellent job of it.
Better than I expected.
Namekian?
Piccolo!
How long has he been there?
Gohan! Everyone's down there!
Piccolo-san's there too!
Everyone else has been able to sense it.
Hey, everyone!
Yoo-hoo, Kuririn, Gohan-kun!
Gohan!
Is Goku...?
So, he's not back yet, huh?
They're here!
–Oh, hell.
They're landing over there!
It's unmistakable. That's Freeza.
He's survived!
Not only that–
There's definitely someone
else there, besides Freeza.
King Cold-sama, Freeza-sama!
The landing sequence is complete.
Listen up, guys! Do not fly!
Approach on foot, so they
don't pick us up on their Scouters.
Are you going?
Yes!
Just a second...
This Freeza has a ki as
unbelievably huge as that one?
It's not just that. It gets much, much stronger.
And you guys... fought
against someone that strong?
You've gotta be kidding!
Even if we get closer, what can we possibly do?
He's an unbelievably powerful beast!
And there's two of them!
There's nothing we can possibly do!
So what are you going to do?
Stay here and rot? Be my guest.
Everyone knows there's nothing we can do.
Shall I say it plainly for everyone?
This is the end of the Earth.
So this is Earth?
Not a bad planet...
I am the Super Saiyan who has come
here from Earth in order to kill you.
I am Son Goku!
I am the greatest in all the universe!
I am Freeza, emperor of the universe!
And so...
You...
You stinking monkey...
You must die at my hand!!
You...
...must be...
...killed by me!!
You damned fool!!
I can't... believe...
...I was beaten by... that stinking monkey...
King Cold-sama, the planet
Namek has indeed been obliterated.
It appears to have been blown
into a million pieces, destroying it.
Under the circumstances, it appears
that Freeza-sama was lost as well.
I can't believe I lost Freeza.
Are you saying there is
someone stronger than our clan,
famed as the strongest in the universe?
If such is the case, then I, Cold, vow
to squeeze the life right out of them!
What is this?
Send a lifeboat! Bring Freeza back quickly!
Curse you, monkey!
We'll be going to Earth next, Papa.
Earth? Why go to such a place?
So that we can kill the Super Saiyan.
What?!
I will take the unbearable
pain of my body's injuries,
as well the pain to my damaged pride,
and return it to him many times over!
The Earthlings don't matter to me,
but I'll be sure we snuff out
the life of the Super Saiyan.
No matter what steps need to be taken.
The being with the greatest
power in the universe...
...must be from among our clan.
Papa, if the two of us fight him
together, we're sure to beat him.
What with my power-up and everything,
I may be able to take care of him by myself.
So, then, there are three hours
before the Super Saiyan returns.
Shall we wait for him, Freeza?
Of course we will, Papa.
However, when he gets here,
I want him to be mortified,
so we'll kill all the Earthlings first.
There's a considerably
large number of people here,
but three hours should be enough time.
Take this, Son Goku!!
I've returned from the depths of
hell itself to have my revenge on you!
Damn.
I've just been brought back to life,
and now I have to die again?
All right!
Everyone spread out and kill off
the Earthlings here, one by one.
Go!
Can we help you with something, Earthling?
I have come to kill you.
A mysterious young man suddenly
appears to stand against Freeza's forces.
Who can he be? What of Goku?
And what of Earth's fate?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
A huge ki appeared all of a sudden,
and wiped out Freeza's men.
What in the world is going on?
Your miscalculation, Freeza,
is that Son Goku-san is not
the one and only Super Saiyan.
There is also another one, right here.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Freeza Halved by a Single Stroke!!
Another Super Saiyan."
It's possible that he's
even stronger than Father.
"Next time"
"Freeza Halved by a Single Stroke!!
Another Super Saiyan"