The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Fusion Ha!!
That was perfect! He's being born!
W-What?!
Having gone through the special
training for the merging technique Fusion,
handed down by Goku to Goten and
Trunks in order to defeat Majin Boo,
the two of them merge and give birth
to the superhuman warrior Gotenks.
Overconfident of himself,
Gotenks took off by himself,
but was all-too-easily defeated by Boo.
I got beaten up all over!
W-What?!
Everybody, everybody...
Stop!!
Now die!!
In just one day, Boo's intensive attacks
have eliminated roughly 80 percent
of the Earth's cities and population.
Gonna kill more and more!
"The Final Weapon is Engaged!?
Satan Will Save the Earth."
Just as if he were a little child,
Majin Boo seems to enjoy
killing those who oppose him or,
of course, run away from him.
The majority of them are killed
by his blasts, and occasionally,
when he becomes hungry,
he turns them into candy
and such and eats them.
All the while, the Earth has
not silently looked on, but rather,
military forces have mobilized
against him countless times.
However, unable to do anything
before Majin Boo's power,
the military has been
obliterated at every turn,
and now, there is no one
left who will stand up to him.
However, the people remaining
have not entirely lost hope.
The reason being, the people have
learned through radio broadcasts
that there is still a savior who has survived.
And so, the people have
waited for their savior to awaken.
It is he who even defeated Cell,
the greatest warrior in the world–
no, in the universe!
He who can take pride in his
undefeated legend, the mightiest man...
The champion, who has
been resting within a shelter
to recover from the fatigue
of the Tenkaichi Tournament...
The awakening of Mister Satan!
Satan! Satan! Satan! Satan!
Do not worry. I will be sure
to defeat Majin Boo at any cost.
If you would please, be careful!
Looks like everyone knows it.
The only one who can defeat Majin Boo
is the strongest combatant
in the universe, Mister Satan.
Damn you, rotten Majin Boo!
The next time we meet...!
Now see here. If you move,
I can't swab this on, you know!
That hurts!
What are you talkin' about?!
You brought this on yourself!
Listen, Goten, you're all I've got left.
So you can't be doin' that sort of
recklessness you were pullin' earlier!
Got it?
Y-Yes...
You too, Trunks.
R-Right...
That's right!
You are the last hope the Earth here has!
Learn your lesson from this, and
refrain from doing anything else so rash!
Piccolo-san?
What is it?
My Papa was awfully strong, right?
Do you think I can surpass my Papa?
I want to defend the Earth, here,
the same way my Papa tried to defend it!
And so, for that reason as well, I have
to become even stronger than my Papa!
Trunks...!
Within your two bodies...
Within your two bodies flows
the same warrior blood that
has come to create possibility
from impossibility many times over.
You can surpass him,
at some time. I'm sure of it!
Now, let's start training!
Right!
Stick with it, Trunks!
Goten-chan, you stick with it too!
That is Majin Boo's house?
Y-Yes, so it seems, Mister Satan.
All right, I'll go alone from here.
Leave this entirely up to me!
You guys can go back
and wait for the good news.
Very well, if you please...
Please defend the
peace of this world for us!
U-Um, Mister Satan? What's in the bag?
This? Let's just say this is a secret
weapon to defeat Majin Boo, just in case.
Oh, a secret weapon? How promising!
Everyone can rest assured!
All right, shall we start off
by talking him down, then?
I'm going to make him regret that
the strongest warrior in the universe,
Mister Satan, is here on Earth!
That got them!
See here! Come on out, Majin Boo!
Mister Satan has arrived!
What's the matter?! Huh?
Can't you come out, you dirty coward?
In that case, I'll come to you.
Prepare yourself!
I'm going to give it to you out-and-out,
through-and-through, and over-and-over!
U-Um, Mister Satan?
Have you strained your throat or something?
He can't hear you with that soft a voice!
Ahem, yeah, um, you see, it's like this...
I know! In that case, how about I say it for you?
Hey, hey, Majin Boo! Why don't you
get out here?! You're finished now!
You idiot!
If you speak in that loud a voice,
he can hear you, you know!
Apparently, he didn't notice.
Really! You guys being here is just
holding me back! Go back, go back!
Well then, if you'll excuse us.
Be careful! Please take care of the Earth!
Tell the press corps for me that I,
Mister Satan, will protect the peace!
Well, now that those annoyances are gone...
I-I wonder if Majin Boo is home.
Maybe he's not home...
He's not here!
Did you get scared off by me, Majin Boo?!
There's nothing I can do, huh?
After all, if he's not here,
there's no way I can fight him!
That's all there is to it! I'll go home!
Nothing I can do but go home, huh?!
You idiot! You tubby!
A fart goes "Boo," pun intended!
I-I-I'm so sorry, Majin Boo-sama!
Everything I said just now was untrue! Untrue!
Actually, I respect you, Boo-sama,
from the bottom of my heart!
Why, you! Startle me,
will you?! You...! You...! You...!
Do you think that someone as
I would be anxious about Majin Boo?!
Yoo-hoo!
W-W-Why it's Majin Boo-sama!
Good day to you!
I'm so pleased to meet you.
Yes, yes, by all means, by all means!
What kind of candy do you
wanna be made into and eaten?
Hard candy? A biscuit? A gummi?
No, no! Please, wait just a moment!
Majin Boo-sama, I have a
wonderful present for you!
H-Here! It's nothing special, but–
I don't need something that's
nothing special! I'll kill you!
N-N-No, it really isn't something
that's nothing special! See?
Luxurious chocolates! Be my guest!
Choco, huh? What's "luxurious?"
Th-That means they're
very expensive and delicious!
He ate them! He ate them! You fool!
That choco is loaded with deadly poison!
Soon you'll be writhing in pain and... huh?
Yum! This is yummier than human choco!
I-Is that so?
Ah! My next present is this! A Game Poy!
–What is it?
–Watch, watch! You move
like this to beat your opponent!
This is hard!!
L-Let's put in an easier cassette!
I get it. This is pretty hard too!
All right! Now! It's now or never!
Die!
Yea!!
"The End!!"
Hey! That was kinda fun just now!
W-Why that's great, great...!
You're funny, so I'll make you my servant.
Th-Thank you so much...!
I'll give you these. They're
hard candy made of people.
They're yummy! Here, eat them!
Y-Yes, thank you very much!
I humbly accept them!
Delicious! These are quite
appetizing. Most certainly!
What?
Is someone there?
I... Uh... I thought for a moment
I saw what looked like somebody...
Well, let's kill 'em!
S-Splendid...! Great... that was great! Great!
Er, if it is all right with you,
could you let me take a
picture together with you?
Please, as a memento.
That's it! A little more like
...please, sprawl yourself out.
Like this?
Pardon me, but taking
pictures like this is in fashion!
For now, at least
I have a nice photograph!
Boo-sama! Are you feeling hungry?
I'm very good at cooking! Boo-sama!
It's just about time, right?
Goku-san! It's finished!
I got bored and fell asleep!
You can have a seat now.
Your efforts have been
appreciated, honorable forefather!
How about it? Gohan,
have you gotten any stronger?
Don't be foolish! The ceremony has just ended.
The power-up will take another twenty hours!
Let's begin.
Listen, it's a simple matter.
You just have to sit still
there and concentrate your mind.
Sit still yet again?
Just put up with it!
Just by doing this, power beyond
your limits will become yours!
That's a small price, isn't it?
There's no time, right? Let's begin right away.
Understood.
The ceremony completed,
Gohan now enters the power-up.
Elsewhere, where Mister Satan is...
Now, now, my delicious
cooking is ready! Help yourself!
Oh, you must be tired!
You've been working so hard!
Don't get too carried away, fatso!
You get this straight now!
Don't you underestimate me!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
I have to say, this is unexpected.
Who'd have thought that Satan
and Majin Boo would become friends?
I did it! Majin Boo promised me
that he wouldn't kill anyone else!
I really am the world's hero, Mister Satan!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"I've Stopped Killing!!
Majin Boo's Good Boy Declaration."
Huh? Are you sure we can believe that?
"Next time"
"I've Stopped Killing!!
Majin Boo's Good Boy Declaration"