The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Gohan-kun!
Videl-san...!
How cowardly of you!
As of now, there is a new hero
in Satan City–the Great Saiyaman!
Satan's daughter, Videl,
had suspicions about the Great Saiyaman's
true identity being Son Gohan.
"A Case of Robbery!!
The Culprit is Saiyaman!?"
Where could Chibi have gone?
When we came to check on him
two days ago, he was here, Big Brother.
He just barely hatched from his egg,
so he shouldn't be able to fly just yet...
Come to think of it,
I don't see the Toto couple, either.
All right, why don't we go
look around a little more?
No matter how many times I watch it,
it's still terrific, if I do say so myself.
Videl, if your goal is to be a
great champion like your papa,
you'll have to train even more.
The Tenkaichi Tournament, huh? What fun.
But Papa, the champion before
you was said to be pretty strong, too.
Oh, that Son Goku fellow?
He's a peculiar man,
who used nonsensical tricks.
However, when it comes to actual
power, he can't hold a candle to me.
If we had fought at the last tournament,
there's no doubt that your
papa would have beaten him.
Son... Son Goku...?
Goten, you didn't find him?
I wonder if something happened.
At a circus show, which opened today,
a baby monster is drawing smiles.
This rare baby was caught by the promoter,
Mr. Musuka, just the other day,
and is as eager to please the
spectators as they are thrilled to see it.
Ah! It's Chibi!
Tomorrow, on Sunday,
there will likely be even greater
numbers of people crowding in to see it.
What does he mean,
eager to please? He's frightened!
He must have been snatched away
while the Toto couple wasn't around.
They wouldn't have kept
quiet about it otherwise.
I feel bad for Chibi, Big Brother.
Don't worry about it, Goten.
Let Big Brother take care of it.
This must be it.
Chibi! Poor thing... I'll make sure I rescue you.
Um...
Mister, are you the one in the
highest position at this circus?
What do you want?
Please put Chibi back up in the
mountains, if you wouldn't mind.
Don't be absurd. We're doing
shows in Metro North next.
This thing is something
I went to a lot of trouble to find.
I intend to have it make
me a bundle from here on.
Make you money?
For you to not only kidnap Chibi,
but to also use him to
make money is just too cruel!
You shut up! I'm the one who caught it!
I can do whatever I want with it!
Dammit, who are you to get in
the way of me making money?
I'll have to wait until nightfall.
Chibi must want to hurry back
to where his mother and father are.
And I'm sure the Totos
are worried about Chibi, too.
Hold on a minute!
What if the Totos are even now
looking for their missing Chibi?
If that's the case, then
this could become terrible!
You behave yourself.
Chibi, don't worry, it's me. It's Gohan.
You're all right now.
Come on, let's go back where your parents are.
All righty...
Who are you?!
I am a champion of justice!
You sneak thief!
It's not like that!
It's dangerous to be swinging
something like this around!
W-What kind of guy are you?!
Okay, let's go.
One... two... three...
B-Bad news! Musuka-san,
the monster has been taken!
W-What?!
H-Hey, what's the matter?
Don't give me such a hard time!
Can it be that you're afraid to fly?
I'll guess we'll have to run away on foot, then.
You're still a baby, so what else can we do?
But someday, you'll have to
start flying by yourself, Chibi.
That's the culprit! Arrest him!
Even if he is the Great Saiyaman,
he won't get away with this!
Return the baby monster peacefully!
I can't do that!
All right, now!
If we don't get out of the city soon...
Hold it there, Great Saiyaman!
It stuns me that a champion
of justice would act like a thief,
Great Saiyaman!
You're calling me a thief?
Videl-san, please understand.
This fellow is still a baby.
It's best that he be taken back to his parents.
Otherwise, something terrible will happen!
Hand over the monster quietly.
If you insist on refusing, then I'll
take the monster back from you by force.
You never know, you could lose,
and have that mask removed,
Great Saiyaman.
What are you waiting around for?!
Arresting thieves is the police's job, isn't it?!
It's okay. We can leave this up to Videl-san.
Who is that girl?
That's Mister Satan's daughter, Videl-san.
The daughter of the world's
strongest man, Mister Satan?
Of all the times for Videl-san to be around...!
What do I do?
Please stop this, Videl-san!
Have you lost your nerve?
Or if you're just
underestimating me because I'm a girl,
I'll show you how greatly mistaken you are!
I do want to know your true identity,
but I'm also interested
in just how strong you are.
This is the perfect opportunity.
You don't need to restrain yourself.
That's nice of you to say, but...
I'm not going to hold back against you!
H-H-Hold on–
I should have expected as
much from you, Videl-san.
If nothing else, you're far
stronger than Mister Satan.
F-Forgive me.
What are you apologizing for?!
Now's my chance!
Why, you... Defy me, will you?
–Chibi!
–Never mind him, worry
about yourself, Great Saiyaman!
It's not like that!
It's not like what?
If I don't get Chibi back home soon,
something awful could happen to the city!
It's the truth, Videl-san!
It's no use trying to run away
from me with a story like that!
Please understand, Videl-san!
That's it. That's more like it.
Otherwise, it wouldn't be any fun.
How on earth do I get her to understand?
Chibi...!
Be quiet, you miserable freak!
T-That's done it...
M-Monsters!
F-Fire!
Stop! The Toto couple is
only here to get their baby back!
Videl-san, I'm begging you, take Chibi away!
As long as we give them their Chibi back,
the Toto couple should calm down!
Y-Yeah...
Come on, hurry! Otherwise,
something terrible will happen!
A-All right.
Don't shoot!
Settle down, Totos!
Here, we're giving Chibi back
to you, so stop being so angry!
You're friends with those monsters?!
Yeah. We've played together since I was little.
Even though they're worked up right
now, they really are gentle creatures.
Although I'm transformed,
they should know that it's me.
Toto! It's me! Have you
forgotten?! It's me, Goha–
I-I mean...
You weren't by any chance
about to say "Gohan," were you?
Videl-san, get out of the way!
No way! You're Son
Gohan-kun after all, aren't you?
Well? I'm not letting go until I make sure of it!
What are you talking about, at a time like this?!
Toto!
W-What are you doing?!
I'm not about to let you take
away my precious moneymaker!
I'll blow you away!
Don't!
Watch out, Videl-san!
Toto, forgive me!
Don't worry, Chibi.
Your father is just knocked out.
Great Saiyaman...
Videl-san, I'll ask you to
handle everything else here. Bye!
How nice for you, Chibi! You're not
afraid to fly with your mother, huh?
Gosh, you sure are good-humored.
Dammit! Next time, I'll catch all of you!
You do that, and I'll definitely
see that you pay for it.
You've picked the wrong opponent now.
You should probably give it up.
Hey! Thank goodness you're all safe!
Big Brother, thank you!
Oh, no, I'm late!
Morning, Son Gohan-kun.
Ah, Videl-san, good morning.
Thanks for yesterday.
Not at all. I'm glad you weren't hurt, Videl-san.
You can't hide it any longer.
The true identity of the Great Saiyaman...
...is you, Son Gohan-kun!
O-Oh, crap! And I was so
perfectly disguised, too...
I thought your voice and the
way you talked was suspicious.
Be that as it may, why did you go to all
the trouble of wearing that strange outfit?
Well, I... if I'm to get along
together with all my friends,
it would be bad if they
found out how strong I am.
Which is why...
Friends?
Uh, well, you know...
Hey, you're the Golden Warrior too, aren't you?
Ah, no, that's someone else!
Are you sure about that?
It's the truth!
That part at least absolutely can't get out.
Well, okay then.
Videl-san, would you keep
this a secret from everyone else?
Sure, depending on how the situation develops.
Oh, and Son Gohan-kun, you're
going to enter the Tenkaichi Tournament
that's taking place in another month, right?
Huh? The Tenkaichi Tournament?
Right. It's a tournament to determine
the champion of combat sportsman.
They're holding it again after a long break.
My papa was the champion at the last one.
And before that, it was a
mysterious man named Son Goku,
although I don't know his face.
Same last name as you.
It's not very common these days
to have your name divided into first and last.
I think this man Son Goku
might be your papa. Am I right?
U-Uh, well...
This girl is pretty sharp, huh?
I knew it.
Of course you'll be entering
the Tenkaichi Tournament.
If the last champion's daughter and the
previous champion's son end up fighting,
I think that would have to be interesting.
If you can knock out a monster with
just one blow, I'm sure you'll do fine.
N-No, I'm going to pass.
I'm not very interested in that sort of thing.
If you don't enter, I'll let everyone know
that Son Gohan-kun is the
Great Saiyaman's true identity!
Y-You wouldn't!
What's the matter?
You can enter as the Great Saiyaman,
and no one will know.
Y-Yeah, but...
You want to be exposed?
All right, I'll enter.
Hurray! Then it's settled!
Everyone else seems weak,
and I wanted an opponent
that would be challenging.
Now I've had it. Things have
been turned upside-down.
Ah, and Son Gohan-kun...
–Was there something else?
–Say, teach me how to fly, okay?
It's not fair, you being the only one who can fly.
Okay, Videl-san.
See you later. I'm looking
forward to this, Son Gohan-kun.
I'm no match for Videl-san.
One predicament follows another,
and Gohan is utterly at a
loss as to how to deal with Videl.
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
The Tenkaichi Tournament, huh?
Sure has been a while.
If Gohan and Vegeta
are entering, then so am I.
Oh, man! If I'd known
I'd be seein' Goku-sa again,
I would've gone to a beauty salon!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Goku Returning to Life!?
Entry into the Tenkaichi Tournament!!"
Whoa, I have to go tell Kuririn-san
and Piccolo-san about this, too.
"Next time"
"Goku Returning to Life!?
Entry into the Tenkaichi Tournament!!"