The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
What is it you're planning?
What are you thinking?
Sorry, but no matter what,
I want to fight with him.
Both him and me, in the first round,
while we're both at 100 percent strength.
The Tenkaichi Tournament
was proceeding smoothly.
The incredible guy that
Goku was talking about...
...was none other than Oob,
the reincarnation of Majin Boo.
N-Neither my father...
...o-or my mother...
...are piles of poo!!
"Even Stronger!!
Goku's Dream is Super-Huge."
What?!
He's fast!
I'm starting to get excited...!
There's no doubt about it!
You're the reincarnation of that evil Boo!
Come on, come on, what's the matter?
I can't lose! I absolutely cannot lose!
I made a promise to Father and
Mother that I would win the tournament,
and bring back the prize money for sure.
Ain't you coming?
In that case, I'm going to go at you!
Oh, my!
Contestant Oob can do nothing in the
face of Contestant Son's ferocious attacks!
He is being hammered!
Impressive... Little by little,
he's catching up to my speed!
I can't believe it. That kid is learning
how to fight while he is fighting!
What?
You're kidding, right?!
W-What is with that boy?!
U-Unbelievable...
To think that he's fightin'
on equal terms with Goku-sa...
Can it be that the incredible guy
Son-kun mentioned is this boy?
Nice going! Nice going, kid!
Go! Go!
You're sure it's okay not to watch the matches?
It'll be fine.
After all, it's going to be
either Goku or one of the others,
or you, Boo-san, that
will win their way through.
And Boo-san, there isn't anyone that
can stand up to you and the others, is there?
I get it!
What is it?! What is happening?!
W-What?!
They're even! They are even!
Both Contestant Son and Contestant
Oob are not retreating one step!
S-Stop this, please!
The ring is being destroyed!
Sure enough!
It would seem to be just as Goku said.
He apparently is the reincarnation of Boo.
Yeah, that's the only thing I can figure.
Contestant Oob has incredible power!
Even with his small body,
he is easily tossing Contestant Son about!
This is for what you said earlier!
–Grandpa!
–Look out!
Grandpa, hang in there!
Goku-sa!
Son-kun...!
Father...!
Oh, dear! Is Contestant Son down?
Awesome, kid!
You really got me that time.
All righty! Come on!
What sort of guys are those?!
You'd better back out too!
If you don't want to die, that is!
Where are you going?
Knock-san, are you still going to participate?
Yeah... I was only going to the
restroom. I'm just about to leak out!
Um... I'm just... uh...
I hear somebody calling for help!
It's the voice of a young girl,
being frightened by evil!
Wait right there!
Right now, Captain Chicken, the
Ambassador of Justice, is coming!
That makes two people
forfeiting their matches in the finals.
I'm not about to lose...
I made a promise... I'm not about
to lose... I'm not about to lose...!
I'm not about to lose... I'm not
about to lose... I'm not about to lose!
I am not about to lose!
Th-That's impossible!
Y-You're floating!
Ka... me...
...ha... me...
Father!
That's right, you still haven't learned
how to fly through the air yet, huh?
That's only normal, since
you haven't had a teacher,
and you probably never
even thought about it.
I'm sorry about saying those bad
things earlier. Forgive me, okay?
I wanted to know what you were capable of.
If I hadn't done so, it didn't seem like
you would have gotten serious with me.
Just as I expected, you are
who I thought you would be.
You're impressive! Awesome!
But you ain't accustomed to using your power.
This is the first time you've
ever fought like this, huh?
Let's see, now...
All right, I've decided.
I'll go live together with
you at your place from now on,
and teach you how to fight.
Once I do that, you'll become much,
much stronger. That's okay, right?
S-Stronger? B-But...
What's wrong?
That's impossible. Our family is poor, and all.
That's why I insisted on
coming here, for the prize money.
No problem, no problem.
Don't worry about money.
I'll get some from Mister Satan.
He makes quite a bit
from being a hero, after all.
B-But...
There's no reason to be so reserved.
Besides...
From now on, if the time comes
when there's some emergency,
you're the only one who will
be there to protect the peace!
Wait there a second!
F-Father!
Guess what? I'm going to go live together
with him at his place so that I can train him.
–G-Goku-sa!
–Son-kun!
I don't know how many years it will take,
but I'll come home every once in a while.
Look after things for me, okay?
U-Um, Father, why in the world...?
See ya!
Father!
Goku-sa!
–Father...
–Goku-san...
Grandpa...!
Grandpa!
What's the matter, Pan?
Is it true? What you just said, is it true?
Yep!
No! Not being able to see you,
Grandpa–I don't... I don't want that!
Hey, hey, hey, Pan. It ain't like
we'll never see each other again.
I said I would come
home once in a while, right?
Really?
Yeah, I promise! So don't cry.
All right, that's a good girl.
Don't you guys skip out
on your training, either, now!
Just like with him,
the peace of the Earth from now
on rests on your shoulders, after all.
Right!
I'm going to train too!
And I'm going to get a lot
stronger, just like you, Grandpa!
All right, that's the spirit!
Now, then...
Sorry about this, Vegeta.
And after I talked you into
coming all the way out here...
Hmph. In puny matches
such as these, neither you or I,
or that Oob kid there, could go at
it to the best of our abilities, anyhow.
Ain't that the truth!
See ya!
Well, let's go! Hop on my back!
R-Right... L-Like this?
Your house was on an
island to the south, right?
Yes.
Hold on to me tight, Oob!
Right!
All right! Here we go!
Yahoo!
C-Contestant Son?! Contestant Oob?!
What are we supposed
to do about the matches?!
–Grandpa!
–He's gone!
–W-What's going on?
–Bye-bye!
–H-He's not serious...
–He can't be...
Training, he says? Hey, what does that mean?
He's gone!
What in the world was Son-kun thinking?!
Really, he's always done whatever he pleased!
It's been a long time since
I've seen Goku as happy as that.
You're right.
Hey, what's going on?
Beats me, I don't know what's up.
Kakarrot, I can understand your reasons.
You're not training that kid,
the reincarnation of Boo,
just for the sake of keeping peace.
So, Oob...
Y-Yes?
Once your training is complete,
let's you and I have a proper
match against each other again, okay?
O-Okay.
To tell you the truth,
that's what my biggest goal is!
Ain't you excited, Oob?!
To be able to come across
someone so incredibly strong?!
Yes!
Sure you are!
"Cancelled"
All right! Let's go get stronger!
Yes!
No, no! You say "Ohh!"
Ohh!
One more time! Let's go get stronger!
Ohh!!
Son Goku, the warrior who has
continually fought and overcome limits
in order to keep the peace on Earth, as well
as the universe, now makes his departure.
Come back soon, Goku!
Everyone is waiting for your return!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)