Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
In the Next World, Goku had
come to live on Grand Kaio's World,
where the most supreme,
most powerful Grand Kaio lived.
Many of the Next World's martial artists
lived and trained on Grand Kaio's World.
"I'm the Best in the Next World!!
Heroes of the Ages Assembled."
And he sent Cell flying in the blink of an eye!
Paikuhan is really awesome!
Okay, I get it, I get it.
I'm just saying, he's really strong.
Paikuhan isn't the only one who's strong.
Hey, you guys!
You called, Kaio-sama?
This is a newcomer, Son Goku.
He's pleased to meet you.
Pleased to meet you.
Goku, these are the martial
artists from the North Galaxy.
That means, they are your seniors.
Migoren here fought bravely
against fiendish aliens 700 years ago.
Sate defended his home planet from a
collision with a meteor 3500 years ago.
And, like you, Olivue here came from Earth,
and he is still immortalized
as a hero in mythology.
Everyone else here was an outstanding
martial artist when they were alive.
These mighty men have been
training here for many thousands of years,
in order that Grand Kaio-sama might train them.
You've got to train that much
before Grand Kaio-sama will train you?
That's right.
Only those who Grand Kaio-sama
considers qualified receive that honor.
Is that so?
The Next World isn't going to be all that easy.
Kaio of the North has died!
He's gone and died, after all!
W-What's this...?!
Kaio of the North has died!
What a happy occasion!
It's not a happy occasion!
And what are all of you here together for?!
I called them here.
After all, a Kaio has died,
and they've got to see this!
Positively!
We'll have a big blowout to commemorate it!
You don't have to make any fuss!
Who is that together with
the Kaio-sama of the West?
They're both Kaio-sama, as well.
Kaio-sama of the South,
and Kaio-sama of the East.
There sure are a lot of Kaio-sama, ain't there?
There are four galaxies, you see,
divided into north, south, east, and west.
Above them, you've got Hell,
and the Serpentine Road,
and then far above them,
there are the four Kaio's Worlds,
from which each of the Kaio watch
over the galaxies they preside over.
And then, higher than the Kaio's
Worlds, higher even than heaven,
is Grand Kaio's World here.
So that's how This World and
the Next World are made up, huh?
I didn't know any of that.
We found out about it for the
first time when we died, too.
What do you know, you really are dead, huh?
You don't have to keep
saying that, you pesky old biddy!
What did you call me?! Just you say that again!
Hold on! Now, now, you
two, calm down, calm down!
Never mind all that, for
the first time in 300 years,
all four Kaio are here together.
How about after all this time,
we hold a martial arts tournament
between the four galaxies?
A tournament?
An Anoyoichi Tournament?
[Anoyoichi: Best of the Next World]
Nice idea there, Kaio-chan of the West.
Yes, sir! Thank you very much!
In that case, I will personally
give lessons to whoever wins.
R-Really?! You will, Grand Kaio-sama?!
Personally?
Give lessons?
Well, is it okay if you ain't
been training for a long time?
I've never even hoped for such a chance.
It's like a dream.
You know something, it's been a long
time since we've had a tournament.
I know! Everyone, come on...!
In here.
This will be just right for our arena, won't it?
Incredible!
Magnificent!
Positively!
A-All right! I'm going to go at it and win this!
And what's more, I'm going to
have Grand Kaio-sama train me!
Just a minute, you!
You're thinking of participating?
Of course I am.
For someone so new, you shouldn't
think so little of the Next World!
Kaio of the East, Goku may be a
newcomer, but he has considerable power.
If you're willing to say that much,
how about I give him a test?
If you can beat me in a race,
I will approve your
participation in the tournament.
Here we go again...
Positively...
Kaio of the East always wants to race,
for whatever reason she can come up with.
That's okay, isn't it?
Let's let them do it. I love this fun stuff.
It's starting! It's starting!
I'm starting to get fired up!
Good luck in there, Goku.
That biddy is the last person I want to lose to.
We'll let the end of this training
ground be the finish line. Ready?
You betcha!
Hang in there, Goku!
Go when I say!
Ready...!
Yahoo!
This youngster's not too bad, is he?
But then...
...that's far enough!
Yahoo!
It looks like they're running pretty fast.
It's just about time, I guess...
Geez! What a persistent boy you are!
That's the finish line!
Hii!
Grand Kai...
...o-sama!
The results of this contest are in.
The winner is...
I made it!
...me!
Eh? You can't mean it!
It's clear to anyone that was watching, right?
I got here all the way from that distant doorway.
You can't mean it!
Grand Kaio-sama, I didn't
know that you were participating!
I never said I wasn't participating.
"Kaio of the North Dying Commemorative
Anoyoichi Tournament"
I'm impressed by you Kaio-chan
folks. You built us a fine ring.
Listen up! If you lose, you'll pay for it!
You're our top contender.
Give it your all, Paikuhan!
Of course.
Paikuhan is entering, too? Wow, I'm so excited!
This fight is going to be a bit different for you
than any Tenkaichi Tournament
you've ever been in before.
Be careful how you go about this.
Right.
Ladies and gentlemen, we
apologize for the terribly long wait.
We now convene the Kaio of the North
Dying Commemorative Anoyoichi Tournament!
And so, to begin with, we will hear a
word of welcome from the Grand Kaio-sama!
All of you here, today, we hold
a tournament after a long absence.
To those of you who are fighting, as well
as those of you who are cheering them on,
let's all have an enjoyable time of it!
Thank you very much. Now then,
allow us to explain the rules.
There are four entrants from each galaxy,
and their pairings were
determined earlier by lottery.
This is how it will be determined!
The contests will be one-game
matches, without any time restriction.
Falling out of the ring,
crying,
or saying you give up constitutes a loss.
Further, blinding strikes,
strikes to critical areas, and other
such dirty moves are not allowed.
There is no need to worry about
anyone in the Anoyoichi Tournament dying.
You're already dead, after all!
And so, everyone, let's all
please have a good, safe fight!
The winner will receive,
of all things, some private,
one-on-one coaching from Grand Kaio-sama!
I think I'd rather have something
yummy to eat, instead of private coaching.
Stop horsing around!
Do you want to be the winner?!
Do you want to train with Grand Kaio-sama?!
Are you sure of yourselves?!
Okay then, we'll move right
on ahead to the first match.
First off, we have Contestant
Olivue, from the North Galaxy,
and Contestant Chapchai, from the East Galaxy!
Win, no matter what! You got that?!
Hang in there, Olivue!
The guys from the East Galaxy
have great speed! Watch out!
He's fast!
Oh, my! This is incredible!
Due to his extreme speed,
it looks like Contestant Chapchai
has a number of different bodies!
The Zanzo-ken technique?!
Ah! How can this be?!
Contestant Chapchai divided himself!
However, ironically, it proved to be his downfall!
Contestant Olivue wins!
What's the deal with this guy?
And now, from the North Galaxy,
a new face, Contestant Son Goku,
and, from the South Galaxy,
the formidable Contestant Caterpi!
What kind of fight will this turn out to be?!
Watch yourself, Goku!
Oh, crap!
You're finished now!
Goku!
Contestant Caterpi launches a tickle attack!
How sneaky! How utterly sneaky!
Now, say you give up!
The South Galaxy is a peaceful one...
You give up? Sure you do! Say it!
I can't let myself say it!
Y-You're remarkably weak, huh?
What? How dare you say that!
All right, if that's how you want it...!
You'll be sorry afterward!
I don't think I will be.
What could this be?!
Contestant Caterpi has started to transform!
W-What is that?
He's turned into a chrysalis!
Caterpi is transforming into his ultimate form!
K-Kaio of the South, if I could ask,
when will Contestant Caterpi
hatch from his chrysalis?
In about 1200 years, I would say.
I-I can't wait that long!
I-I can't wait, either. Son Goku wins this match!
W-What just happened?
At last, the tournament in
the Next World had begun.
Will Goku be able to advance his way up?
Goku could not even guess what kind
of opponents he would face from here on.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Whoo, everybody's got their
awesome techniques, huh?
The Next World is a big place, all right.
This is no time for you to be gawking.
You're up next against my boy Aqua, you know.
Don't blame me if he beats you to tears!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Grand Kaio's World Gone Wild!!
Goku Kicks Up a Whirlwind."
Father, show them your power!
"Next time"
"Grand Kaio's World Gone Wild!!
Goku Kicks Up a Whirlwind"