Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Goodbye, Gohan.
Father!!
However, Cell was alive!
I'm not playing around any longer.
I'm going to put an end to this right away.
Let you and the whole Earth cease to exist!
"From Goku to Gohan...
The Spirit of the Father is Handed Down."
The Earth will be blown away.
Everything will be blown away.
It will all become the darkness
of space, with no traces remaining!
It's no use! I can't win!
Cell has returned with tremendous power!
Father, I'm sorry. I couldn't
defend the Earth against Cell.
If only I hadn't overdone things,
I would have been able to defend the Earth...!
It's a trick! An incredible trick!
C-Cell is giving off a strange glow!
The area around him is like a typhoon!
It has become a windstorm!
I, your announcer, will carry out my mission,
and continue this broadcast,
even if it is not getting through!
How can this be? To think that
I've become excess baggage...!
Me, a warrior-race Saiyan...!
S-Sorry about that, Gohan!
V-Vegeta-san just apologized...
He's realized that there's
absolutely nothing we can do now...!
Gohan...
Dammit!
I hate the fact that we are powerless!
–Kami-sama, what is it?
–I-Incredible power!
I've never felt power like this.
Cell? What will happen?
Gohan-san...
Grand Elder-sama, what is going on?
On that faraway planet of Earth,
where Dende is, there's an ominous ki...
Earth may be done for.
I am perfect.
I never imagined I could come this far.
Is this the ultimate perfect form
that Doctor Gero was aiming for?
Doctor Gero, how long are you
planning to continue your research?
Oh, is it you guys?
If this is for defeating Son Goku, then...
I think we're all that will be needed.
Don't touch that!
This is research toward
the ultimate Artificial Human.
Ultimate?
Will he be even stronger than us?
Of course!
He will be on a whole different level.
You will be like children,
and him an adult, comparatively.
Now hurry back to your
storage capsules and go to sleep.
Otherwise, I will push the
button on your controller again!
You fool!
But then in time, you will be swallowed,
and then, you will become a part
of the ultimate Artificial Human...!
You're talking nonsense.
He's surprisingly cute, isn't he?
So this is the ultimate Artificial Human.
Something must have been
the matter with Doctor Gero.
This isn't really fair to you,
but I doubt that this laboratory
will be needed any longer.
"Snip."
I'd like to get some new clothes.
It's not very fashionable
wearing the same thing all the time.
However, even after Doctor Gero died,
I continued to be cultured by his computer.
Cell, you are the ultimate Artificial Human,
made from cells gathered from
the most accomplished of warriors.
You will absorb No. 17 and No. 18,
and achieve your perfect form.
Several years later, I came forth on the earth.
At the time, it had already been turned
into a dead planet by No. 17 and No. 18.
Even so, I took in what
little living energy remained,
and continued to grow, in
order to reach my perfect form.
However, for some reason,
no matter where I looked,
I could not find No. 17 or No. 18 anywhere.
No matter what, I desired
to achieve my perfect form.
In pursuit of No. 17 and No. 18,
I returned once again to my larval state,
and using Trunks' time machine,
I came back ten years into this time period.
Come on out, you monstrous freak!
I will neither run nor hide!
As you wish, I've come forward!
Damn it all!
That is how I reached my perfect form.
However, at the time,
I still had not realized the ultimate
strength that Doctor Gero was after.
Doctor Gero's ambition
wasn't about something small,
like defeating Son Goku.
It was to develop ultimate strength,
with which to rule the world–the entire universe.
And during this fight,
I've come to understand that.
That is to say, like Piccolo,
having the ability to regenerate,
so long as there is still a tiny nucleus,
along with the ability of the Saiyans
to power-up even greater than before,
after being saved from the brink of death,
as well as having a merciless,
cold-blooded, unfeeling heart, like Freeza,
put together, they all served
as Doctor Gero calculated.
The only thing he was mistaken
about was the destruction of the Earth.
But several more years into the future,
the Earth would be destroyed anyhow,
and I could use Instantaneous
Movement to go to another planet.
Perfect strength...
It is beyond what I could have imagined.
Damn. Is there really nothing we can do?
Is this how the Earth comes to an end?
I've already stored up enough
energy to blow away not just Earth,
but the entire solar system!
C-Cell's strange glow is getting brighter,
and the ground is trembling violently!
Wha–What exactly is happening?
We do not understand this!
It's a trick! A trick! A trick!
What's goin' on?!
The TV's not showin' anythin',
and the ground is shakin'!
Gohan-chan! Gohan-chan!
–Gohan-chan!
–C-Chichi!
Now's the sort of time when
it's important to calm down!
That's easy for you to say, but I can't do that!
Gohan-chan! Gohan-chan!
Chichi! Chichi!
Chichi! Are you here?!
That voice...
Uranai O-Baba!
Ah, you are here!
Chichi, I wanted you to
see what your son was up to.
And since the TVs aren't showing anything,
I thought you might be worried.
Hurry! Hurry up and show me!
Hurry!
Now, now, take it easy.
Gohan...?
Gohan! What's wrong with your arm?!
Chichi!
Gohan...
What's wrong, Gohan?
I know, show me your final resistance!
Do it! I know that my resistance is futile.
Father isn't the only one I'm going to
let die–we're all going together!
How dull.
What a disappointing end
this has turned out to be.
Well then, how about I help myself to
bringing about the end of everything?!
It's over... It's all over...
The Earth will be wiped out...!
Don't talk such foolishness!
Gohan, it's not like a Saiyan to give up! Gohan!
Father! W-Where are you?
The Next World.
I'm having Kaio-sama help me talk to you.
You've got the blood of the warrior
Saiyan race flowing through you.
Slam him with a Kamehame-Ha
as hard as you can!
If you do, you can beat
him for sure! I guarantee it!
B-But right now, I can only use one arm,
and I've got less than half of my ki left...
Who is he talking to?
You're so terrified that
you're talking to yourself, huh?
That's all right, you can win!
Believe in your own power, Gohan!
Right now, you're the
strongest one in the universe!
U-Understood, Father!
I'll do everything that I can!
Me and Kaio-sama are having a
good time of it here in the Next World,
so you have yourself a
good time there on Earth, too!
You've put me out.
I'm so sorry, Father.
Because I got too carried
away, I got you killed...
Gohan, it's nothing to be sad about.
Your father may be dead,
but whenever you think of me,
we'll always be together.
But...
If that's what you think, then avenge me.
Now, let Cell have it!
Right!
Gohan...!
H-He's set his mind to fight back!
Ka...
me...
ha...
So you've finally come around, huh?
What is it, Kami-sama?
Gohan-san, hang in there!
Gohan-chan...
I-It's no use! He can't win!
Gohan's ki is too weak, too weak!
Burn in hell!!
Gohan engages in a final, last-ditch struggle!
Was that image of Goku that
appeared behind him an illusion?
Or something else?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Gohan, you're still worried
about damaging the Earth,
and ain't putting out all of your power!
Let your power explode!
Gohan, you are me and Goku-sa's son.
You can't let yourself be beaten by Cell!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Battle is Over...
Thank You, Son Goku."
I did it, Father!
"Next time"
"The Battle is Over...
Thank You, Son Goku"