Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Im... possible...!
And you call yourself a Super Saiyan?
Freeza conceals bottomless power.
Can it be that even with Vegeta's
explosive power-up, he is no match for Freeza?
"How I've Waited for this Moment!!!
Son Goku Revived."
Running away?
What?!
No way!
His speed is...
Damn! To think that Freeza
still hasn't gone all-out yet...
What a monster!
Vegeta, quite frankly, using
the attacks and speed you just did,
there's no way you can win against me.
As I recall, you said something
about being a Super Saiyan.
If you are as you say,
does that mean that's the best
the "strongest in history" can do?
Up until this point, I could see him...
Don't make me laugh.
The Super Saiyan is then no
more than a trivial legend after all.
Does this mean I've reached my limit?
Have I not yet become a Super Saiyan?
Or for that matter, is Freeza an
opponent not even a Super Saiyan can beat?
Nonsense! There's no
reason that should be so!
Vegeta...
How can such a thing be?!
Such a thing... could never be!!
You fool.
I see you!
I see you, Freeza!
Vegeta, you...
Vegeta isn't blasting away blindly,
he's carefully aiming every shot!
And yet Freeza is decidedly
keeping clear of them.
They're both unbelievable!
Piccolo...
Piccolo-san...
What?!
I-I am...
I am a Super Saiyan!
Burn in Hell, Freeza!
Are you trying to destroy
the whole planet, Vegeta?!
What?!
It's just about time, I suppose.
I can't have him getting too carried away.
H-How could he...?
He bounced all that
back with just a simple kick?!
Vegeta had to have launched
that attack at his full power!
He's incredible! He's more than incredible!
And now, you will experience
a pain even greater than hell.
This time, you'll let me lead off.
Mildly.
Vegeta...
For the first time in his life, Vegeta is
trembling, from the bottom of his heart.
Both from genuine terror, and
from his conclusive frustration.
He's even shedding tears
over his fright and hopelessness.
This is another first.
Here goes. Are you ready?
Vegeta–Vegeta has
already lost the will to fight.
Vegeta!
Don't!
He's had it.
Vegeta, I can't have
you giving up after so little.
You'll have to go through more than this...
...for a terror greater than hell's.
Well? Have you started to
regret how foolish you've been?
You lower-life-form, nothing-in-
your-mind-but-fighting Saiyan-san?
I thought you at least were
different, and I pampered you,
but you're just like the others who
performed their foolishness, aren't you?
If you hadn't turned against me,
we would have gotten by
without having to go through this.
V-Vegeta!
If you want to save him, feel free at any time.
Piccolo and the others,
faced with the terror of Freeza, whose
battle power is of a different dimension,
seem to be bound in place or something,
all three of them unable to move.
Vegeta's ki is rapidly shrinking...
and he was supposed to
have gotten incredibly stronger.
Is this Freeza that strong?!
I'm healed!
I've gotten stronger!
It's like the power is welling up inside!
Unbelievable! And here
I thought I'd reached my limit.
It's enough to scare me!
But you know, it feels good!
Even at a terrible time like this.
My apologies, Gohan, Kuririn, and Piccolo!
I'm coming now! Something
might just become of this!
Goku at last recovers.
How eagerly has this
moment been anticipated?
You're the only one left
who can still offer resistance to
the overwhelming power of Freeza!
We're counting on you, Goku!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Vegeta, for you to cry...
for you to beg of me, must
have been awfully difficult, I bet.
Kakarrot... defeat Freeza
for me... by your Saiyan hand...
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Such Regret...!!
Vegeta, Pride of the Saiyans, Dies."
Freeza is afraid of Saiyans!
"Next time"
"Such Regret...!!
Vegeta, Pride of the Saiyans, Dies"