Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Dammit, I can't let myself
lose to the likes of him!
The terrifying Freeza...
What is this last card that Goku is playing?
This Genki Dama is the
last thing I wanted to use.
There'll probably be too much force to it!
It will be hard not to squash the planet itself!
What's this you're doing?
You're still thinking of trying
some kind of nonsense, are you?
What can you hope to
do as worn out as you are?
G-Genki Dama!
It can't be! That giant thing?
"Keep the Chance Alive!!
Piccolo's Suicide Support Strike."
What is it? What is he doing?
Why is he just standing there like
that, not showing any movement?
Grass, trees, and animals of Namek,
as well as all living things in
the universe, share your Genki...
just a little bit each is fine...
share your Genki with me, please...
You guys don't know how strong Son-kun is!
From the time he was little,
he endured rigorous
training under the Turtle Hermit!
He also won the Tenkaichi
Tournament, and such.
He takes care of the bad
guys in the blink of an eye!
Get it?!
If Son-kun goes all-out, that strange
alien would be finished with one blow!
You're friends with that alien, aren't you?
If you are friends, then it's in
that alien's best interest for you
to stop him before Son-kun gets too serious!
How about you go persuade him?
Make that clear to him! Make it clear!
I-It's huge! Man, is that huge!
Is it really all that huge?
The one on Earth was about this big.
This one's about fifty meters in diameter!
No matter what he's done,
he couldn't have made
that large a Genki Dama with
just the energy of this planet.
Goku must be gathering ki
from planets all over the place!
Freeza still doesn't seem to have realized it.
Why doesn't he attack
with that ball right now?
Unless he gathers more
ki and makes it even bigger,
he won't be able to defeat Freeza.
That must be what Goku's thinking.
F-Father, hurry! Hurry!
Planets of the universe, lend me your Genki!
What's wrong?
You're planning to do
something, aren't you? So do it!
That is unless, are you supposed to
be raising your hands in surrender?
All the time it takes to gather the ki required
is this technique's greatest weak spot!
Don't let him find out about
this for a little while more, please!
ReaCoom!
Butta!
Jheese!
Ghurd!
Together we are...
The Ginyu Special Corps!
That's it! That's it!
Yeah, no matter how many times we do it,
our Special Fighting Pose is terrific!
It's a small planet, but still
quite a nice place, isn't it?
How about we make this our
secret hideout for the time being?
That's a good idea.
We, the Ginyu Special Corps,
will control the Next World as well!
These jerks are warped!
These are the guys that were able to
toss even Vegeta around like child's play,
the Ginyu Special Corps!
Vegeta?!
Are you folks colleagues
of Vegeta-chan, then?
Then this won't take long.
We are the Ginyu Special Corps,
who collect nebula for ourselves.
We're not at all like Vegeta!
That's right! If my luck hadn't turned on me,
I would have taken that
monkey scum out with one shot!
Well, we don't need to dwell on the past.
In any case, we've come to like this planet.
You're going to let us stay here.
You guys are an annoyance!
You'll have to leave!
Don't you ask such a selfish thing!
You guys get out of here!
Yeah, yeah!
These young men here
want to have a go at us!
Interesting! And just as we're here
wanting to get rowdy on someone!
Whoa, before we do,
hasn't the Commander always
said that once we get to a new planet,
we should try out our techniques first?
Because the effectiveness of some
techniques depends on the place?
That's right! Okay then...
Dammit! How dare you
destroy someone else's things!
So, now it's my turn.
Nicely done!
Ghurd's telekinesis is as good as ever!
Well then, last comes me!
ReaCoom Eraser Gun!!
That he should have that kind of force
on this planet, with its ten-fold gravity...!
Looks as though we can use all
our techniques on this planet too!
What's all this commotion?!
Kaio-sama!
I will not admit those of
you who disrupt this planet!
I will have you leave immediately.
Huh? Some strange old man has come out!
Old man, does this mean you
want to play around with us?
You guys wouldn't be
able to lay one hand on me.
You seem to enjoy your jokes.
Why don't you test me
to see if I'm joking or not?
Okay, then!
Goku's Genki Dama...!
Cut it out already!
How long do you intend
to just stand there like that?
Good question. How long indeed?
Damn you!!
H-He's found out!
No! Not yet!
So, what's the matter?
You were going to attack me somehow, right?
Are you trying to make a fool of me?
A little more...
So, what are you going to do?
G-Goku!
Father!
Gohan, Kuririn, give over
what remaining ki you have to me!
Give it to me, now!
Right!
Hey, don't be in such a rush!
Don't toy with me, you monkey scum!
Don't think about anything else!
Concentrate your ki!
Right!
I don't know what you Saiyans are thinking.
It's the same as it was back then.
You're a most unpleasant group.
I have no intention of continuing
this uninteresting battle any further.
I'm going to finish both
you and this planet off at once.
Just another runt will have died,
and the Saiyans will be completely
eliminated from this world!
The Super Saiyan was nothing
more than a bedtime story after all.
That's not the sun! What is it?!
He found it!
W-What is that?!
It couldn't be... a mass of energy?
Y-You did that?!
All right, that's enough.
Save a little ki for yourselves.
Looks as if he's finally found it out.
Gohan, Kuririn, you two stay here!
No matter what happens, stay back!
H-He's been forming that up in the sky?!
Where did he find that
much remaining power?!
It's no use! Even if I use the
Genki Dama now, he will avoid it!
Besides which, that ball still ain't
enough to defeat Freeza, dammit!
You were planning to
take me by surprise with that?
You're so pathetic!
However, even this desperate
measure has become worthless!
Too bad!
Damn!
Be gone!
Piccolo!
Goku, hurry up and complete
this "Genki Dama" of yours!
I owe you one!
Make it fast, Goku!
With the power I have, it was all
I could do just to blindside him!
Gotcha!
Are you still lurking about,
you miserable Namekian?!
So, let's stop the chatter
and blow all these guys away!
Ah, wait! I'm leaving this up to you guys!
Y-You wouldn't!
Our opponents are awfully tough!
Ten-san!
Piccolo accomplishes a flawless support strike.
Goku, now is the time! Make
that super-giant Genki Dama full!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Everyone in the universe,
thank you for giving me your power.
Hurry it up, Goku! That Freeza
bastard is really angry now!
Take this, Freeza!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Incredible Destructive Force of
the Genki Dama!! Who Will Survive!?"
Father! Piccolo-san!
"Next time"
"The Incredible Destructive Force of
the Genki Dama!! Who Will Survive!?"