Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Goku had not returned,
but Earth was the very
picture of peace. However...
Having sought Kami's throne previously,
but instead finding himself sealed within
the Dead Zone by Goku and his friends,
Garlic Jr. returns!
With the help of this mist,
all living things will
undergo a demonic rebirth,
resulting in the world's
descent to an utterly hellish state!
"Black Mist of Terror...!!
Everyone Turns Demonic."
Garlic, my father,
I was able to carry out your will, and
have taken the Throne of Kami as my own.
All that remains is for me to use the
Dragon Balls to resurrect you to this world.
By that time, the Earth will be overrun
and controlled by the Demon Clan!
Father, please wait just a little while longer.
Haven't you found them yet?
Please, forgive me.
Even now that I possess Kami's water mirrors,
which can project any
point in the Lower World,
to think that I still cannot locate them...
You two have something to do with this.
I'll pay you back a hundred-fold
for everything you've done to me.
You'll slowly and steadily experience
a suffering worse than that of hell.
Particularly when it
comes to Son Goku and his son.
Gohan-chan!
Gohan-chan!!
Gohan-chan's gone off an' turned delinquent!
He's been enticed by Kuririn,
that friend of Goku-sa's.
If he spends too much time
playin' at Muten Roshi's place,
his lechery will rub off on him!
Oh, my Gohan-chan!
Pretty soon we'll see
everyone, right Haiya Dragon?
What's the matter, Haiya Dragon?
What are you doing, Haiya Dragon?
Really, what are you up to?
You're a strange one.
Squirrel-kun!
Haiya Dragon!
What's the matter, everyone? Stop!
They're usually such gentle
animals! What's going on?
Mister Popo, it won't do
any good for us to struggle.
All we can do is wait for help to come.
But Kami-sama, Garlic Jr. used Aquamist.
Doing that, everyone
will turn into Demon Clan.
Both he and his father
are beneath contempt.
He's repeating what happened before...
If only Son Goku were here.
Garlic Jr.-sama! We've found him!
What?!
It's the son of Son Goku!
We've found you, kid!
Bring that kid here!
If we just capture him,
Son Goku is sure to show himself!
Kuririn! Be sure to catch us
something good for supper!
We're counting on you!
Yamucha-san, how about
lending a hand out here?
You said not to worry about it,
that you were going to do this yourself
to show that cute girlfriend of yours!
Hi, Kurin-chan!
I'll help you out there.
Maron-chan!
Oh, yeah!
A young woman's skin is so fine...
It's so bouncy!
Kurin-chan!
Maron-chan!
Kuririn, look out!
Where is Gohan?!
I know he's here somewhere!
Chichi-san!
Muten Roshi-sama, now's the most
important time for my Gohan-chan.
I don't want him associatin' with
any of his strange delinquent friends,
if you please.
D-Delinquent friends?
By that, do you mean us?
A-yep.
Just a minute there, Auntie.
Auntie?!
Everyone here is having such a nice time,
we wish you wouldn't
be such a wet blanket.
Did you just call me
by the name "Auntie?"
Oh, if that's the way it came across,
then I apologize.
But in any case, Auntie,
be it Gohan-chan or Rice-chan
or whoever, the boy isn't here.
You're gonna pay!!
How dare you, another woman,
look someone as young and beautiful
as myself in the face and call her Auntie!
W-W-W-Wait just a second, Chichi-san!
You can't seriously fight against this amateur!
Old man Turtle, you really are a perv!
Kurin-chan!
Maron-chan, come on, come on! Look!
Kurin-chan, the Auntie was
just about to show me something.
Let go of me! Lemme go!
Let me fight with that young missy!
Let go!
Oh, Pafu-pafu, pafu-pafu!
I'll fight her! I'll make that young
missy pay! Let us fight! She has to pay!
Maron-chan, it's a
dangerous thing to get her mad!
How come?
She is the one person even
Super Saiyan Goku is afraid of,
making her the most
powerful woman in the universe!
And who is this Goku person?
Look, how many times
have I explained it to you?
Son Goku, who's my friend.
Oh, whatever.
Kurin-chan, wait!
I won't let her get away with it!
Not in that terrifying
swimsuit she's wearing!
She's a devil woman!
Everyone's going to be
so surprised to see me.
Kuririn-san!
Huh? Gohan!
Maron-san, good day!
That's right, your name
was Gohan-kun, wasn't it?
He's who all that was about.
Hey, Gohan, you didn't tell
Chichi-san you were coming, did you?
You don't mean, don't tell me...
That's right, your mother is already here.
And she is reeeally mad!
What should I do?
It's okay, though.
Kurin-chan said he'd
apologize to your mother for you.
Pretty good, huh?
M-Me apologize to Chichi?!
There's no way I'd do that!
Is that so, Kurin-chan?
I guess I've overstepped my bounds, huh?
J-J-Just a second...
I'm going home.
All right, all right.
Kuririn-san!
That's my Kurin-chan!
We're almost there, Gohan.
Kurin-chan, hang tough!
Mother!
Chichi-san, please forgive him!
Gohan wasn't trying to be bad!
I'm sorry. I left without
saying so, and I apologize.
Chichi-san! You didn't have to go that far!
What do you think you're doing, Auntie?
Not again!
Mother...
Maron-chan, you just
had to go and say that again!
This is my fault?
I'm sorry! I'll do my studies,
and listen to what you say,
and even help around the house!
What's the matter with you, Mother?
What do you want, old man?!
Go away!
Kurin-chan, help me!
W-W-Wait just a second,
we can talk this out!
I know that Maron-chan must have
said something to upset you, but...
She has so many other
cute qualities about her.
What's wrong with all of you?!
Mother!
Kuririn-san!
Be careful, Gohan!
There's something wrong with everyone!
Mother...
No! Stay back! Go away! Don't come closer!
Maron-chan!
So, you didn't breathe the Aquamist, hmm?
How lucky for you.
It took quite a bit of effort
to find you, son of Son Goku!
Who are these monsters?
G-Gohan!
You're the ones who did
this to my mother, aren't you?!
That's right, kid.
Change my mother back!
Impossible. To reverse the effects of
the Aquamist requires Ultra Holy Water.
Ultra Holy Water?
However, the Holy Water can only be
found in the Temple of the Heavenly Realm.
How about it, kid?
Why don't you come to
the Heavenly Realm with us?
You're quite welcome!
What?!
Looks like he's going to make a go of it.
However, he's no match for us.
I can't move!
Didn't we just say you were no match for us?
Who's there?!
Piccolo-san!
If it isn't Piccolo-san.
We've been waiting for you.
I had heard that some crude Demon
Clansmen were out messing around.
It's you guys, is it?
Garlic-sama is waiting for you.
He said he has much he wishes to say to you.
What? Did you say Garlic Jr.?
Piccolo appears as Gohan faces danger.
Is there any way to rescue the Earth...
...from the plans of that
embodiment of the devil, Garlic Jr.?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Gohan, hurry to the Heavenly Realm!
You have to get the Ultra
Holy Water before sunrise,
or you'll never be able to
change everyone back to normal!
That sounds like fun, doesn't it? I'm coming, too.
Maron-chan, the place we're
going isn't going to be so carefree!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Heavenly Realm is the Battlefield!!
Piccolo Becomes Devilish Again..."
I'll get rid of Garlic!
"Next time"
"The Heavenly Realm is the Battlefield!!
Piccolo Becomes Devilish Again..."