The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Boo, having absorbed Piccolo's
brains and Super Gotenks' power,
has transformed into the
mightiest Majin Boo of all!
What do you think, Gohan-kun?
Look! Wonderful, isn't it?
As long as you were out absorbing people,
wanting to make yourself first-rate material,
it would have been a lot
easier to have just absorbed me!
You don't seem to understand at all, do you?
Without an opponent, what am I
to do once I become the strongest?
What?
I am definitely going to blow
you away! That is my greatest goal!
I see, so that's it. You've convinced me.
What's the matter?
Are you trying to buy time by hiding
yourself there, while you hold your ki?
Which would mean that
you've realized at least this much–
that there's no way you
can stand up to me like this!
We'll see!
"For the Sake Of the Entire Universe...
Return to Life, Son Goku."
What's the matter?
Weren't you going to kill me?
You've got to watch your
opponent's movements more closely!
You were taught that in
training, right? By Piccolo?
S-Shut up!
Where are you looking?
W-What does this mean?
After being powered-up that much,
Gohan-san is being so one-sidedly beaten!
Gohan...!
Gohan-san!
That was Piccolo's technique, right?
Makankosappo, isn't it?
However, the force was much higher.
It was in a whole different league.
Don't you think?
I have obtained this, the
strongest power in the universe...
...for the purpose of killing you!
W-What's that now? There's another
Boo that has come out of Boo's mouth!
How come? How come?
I am at a loss to say...
W-What is that?!
Die!!
Don't do it, Gohan! Don't touch that thing!
To say it in the same style as Super Gotenks,
Super Boo Kamikaze Attack, I suppose.
I wanted to try a bit more of this,
but it doesn't appear to be necessary.
Truly a shame.
Oh... To think that you could have
taken that head-on and still be alive!
You're really something.
K-Kami-sama! Let me
have life, even after I've died!
I'm not dead! We survived, Wan-chan!
Wan-chan is gone!
I am the mightiest in the universe!
I am, absolutely! I will not
allow anyone to surpass me!
Wan-chan?!
O-Over there!
D-Dammit, this is hopeless!
Gohan is going to get killed like this!
I had not taken this into account...
Okay then, Son Goku, you go and help him!
N-No, I can no longer...
He's right, honorable ancestor.
Son Goku can in fact never
go to the temporal world again.
I know that.
I will give you my life to replace
yours. Then, you can return to life.
G-Grand Kaioshin-sama, your life... to me?
Y-You mustn't!
That the Grand Kaioshin-sama should
grant his life to a human, of all things!
How can that be?!
In that case, the whole universe is finished.
Majin Boo will surely come here as well.
Th-Then, at least, let it be my life!
K-Kaioshin-sama!
I was unable to prevent Majin Boo's revival,
nor could I contribute to Gohan-san's training!
I want to be able to be at least that much help.
You need not go that far. You're still young.
I would only live another
thousand years or so anyhow.
Honorable ancestor...
O-Old-timer...
W-What did you say?!
Is this true?!
Mm. It's a good thing I thought ahead,
just in case, and left his spirit the way it was.
I've even given him a body.
Please, let this be of some help.
I don't think this is the
proper thing to do either,
but it cannot be helped
if we are to save the Earth.
Hmph. For you to have to
rely on a miscreant such as I...
However, with Majin Boo as my opponent,
I don't think I can fulfil
your faint expectations.
Okay, Uranai Baba, I hate to have to
do this, but take him to Earth. Hurry.
Understood.
M-Me take him?!
The Earth–no, the universe is in crisis!
Why does a weak old woman such as myself
have to go to where
that terrifying Majin Boo is?!
I'm counting on you.
On me, now? How pitiful.
Farewell, then.
That was this Gotenks' technique as well.
How does it feel, to be done
in by your own pals' techniques?
G-Gohan-san!
This is one of your techniques as well...
You must be happy to be killed like this.
This was all too easy!
You're a tough one.
Oof...
H-Honorable ancestor...
So then, farewell.
O-Old timer...
Thanks so much. I definitely ain't
going to let your life go to waste!
All right! Hurry up and go!
What are you doing?! Come on, come on!
Are you trying to make my death in vain?!
I told you, it is no use muffling your ki.
You just don't know when to give up.
Are you wanting to live
even one second longer?
What's wrong? Hang in there!
You're getting awfully weak.
Not yet, not yet! As long as I have time
remaining, I will have you entertain me!
H-Hey, he's getting beaten!
He's getting beaten up!
Y-You should take the dog and run
far away! You'll be caught up in this!
Hey, if it comes to that–and
as a martial arts champion,
I hate to have to use it–this
.45 will start spitting fire!
How about that?!
Well, I'm off!
Just a second, Son Goku!
Going off is fine and all, but once you go,
how do you intend to beat Majin Boo?
I hate to say it, but I don't think that
the two of you could beat Majin Boo now.
Um...
Ah, yeah! Fusion! Me and Gohan
will do Fusion! Then we'll win for sure!
Fusion... Mm, that thing
those little guys were doing?
I doubt that Majin Boo would just wait around
while you guys go through the nuisance
of posing through that Fusion business.
Th-Then what should we do?!
Grand Kaioshin-sama, it was you
who told me to go give it to him!
Which is why... Here!
Put one of these Potara
earrings on your left ear.
J-Just what sort of
purpose will that thing serve?
Good question...
By putting this on, will it make me stronger?
I ain't getting that sense at all.
Have Gohan place the
other one on his right ear.
Just by doing that, you two can
combine together, like you were in Fusion.
Really?!
Goku, having been returned to life
in order to save the entire universe,
takes possession of the Kaioshin's
precious merging items, his Potara.
Will they really be the trump
card needed to beat Majin Boo?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Gohan, put this Potara
earring on your right ear.
You'll unite with me, and
we can defeat Majin Boo!
Fool! Do you think I'm going to sit back
and let you just do as you please?
I'll eliminate you before you can!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Miracle Happens Once... Will the
Super Combination With Gohan Come About?"
Once we combine, we'll be
like this for the rest of our lives?
"Next time"
"The Miracle Happens Once... Will the
Super Combination With Gohan Come About?"