Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
"Conk!"
Now then, let's hurry and
get the Cell Games started!
Who will go first?
As expected, will you, Son Goku, lead off?
Yeah, that's right.
Son Goku is about to take the stage.
The battle, with the destiny of
the Earth hanging in the balance,
is now about to begin!
"Fight Time, Goku!!
The Ultra-Tense Cell Games."
Th-The hope of all mankind,
Contestant Satan, has lost!
Could this mean the end of the Earth...?
It's finally time, huh?
Yeah.
Come on, let's see it, Kakarrot!
It's you, right off the bat, huh?
I was hoping to save the
most enjoyable for last, after all...
I hear you can use all of our techniques.
More or less.
Oh? Mister Satan!
Um, how did you come to lose?
I-I just missed my footing a little, that's all.
Huh? Your... footing?
That's right!
Um, it looked as though you were sent flying...
This is why it's so
awkward having laymen around.
When a master of Satan-sama's
stature misses his footing,
this is the sort of severe thing that happens.
I-Is that right?
That's right!
But there's no need to worry!
After a short breather, I'll go
at him again like I really mean it!
Just leave it to me!
H-He still doesn't realize
the difference in their levels?!
He's the world champion of stupidity!
The puzzle as to why Goku-san
is so unusually composed is about to be solved.
People of the world, rest at ease!
Mister Satan may have inadvertently slipped
and landed out of the ring earlier,
but after a short break,
he will fight Cell once again!
While Contestant Satan is resting,
one of the people from that nonsensical group,
which utterly refuses to listen to our warnings,
apparently means to fight!
Let's leave them alone, already.
Once a fool, always a fool, after all.
What do you think, Mister Satan,
upon looking at this unknown warrior?
Utterly hopeless. Just by looking at his stance
and his build, you can tell he's a rank amateur.
Goku's incredible, huh?
Y-Yeah... He's left nothing unguarded.
That's not all.
Even now, as he's standing in front of Cell,
he's still standing naturally.
If anything, he's just
looking forward to this.
Which means that Goku-san
has his Super Saiyan state
completely under control, right?
Well now, if I were up there against that man,
I'd beat him in just two seconds.
The only thing I can think of
is that he's completely crazy.
He probably won't even
last five seconds against Cell.
Good grief, this won't
be much of a break at all!
He really is a troublesome fellow, huh?
Yeah, well, without some
entertainment such as this,
my own match wouldn't
be as stimulating, would it?
Come.
Up to now, it's been dead even.
But then,
neither one of them has even
started breathing harder yet, right?
Th-The fight that this
unnamed warrior just put up...
it wasn't, by any chance, incredible, was it?
How about it, Satan-san?
Um, Satan-san...?
Regarding that fight...?
Well, it wasn't bad, I suppose.
He's capable of more than I thought,
but he's overexerting himself considerably,
and he's probably reached his limit.
H-He's out of bounds!
Did he get him?!
How was that?
Were you able to experience
the sensation of victory somewhat?
Don't make your ruse so transparent.
We know that there's no way
you're going to be done in by just that.
You weren't showing off very much
of what you've got up your sleeve,
so I thought I'd try teasing you a little.
You didn't show very much off yourself, huh?
I'm going to start showing
you now, little by little–
the true difference
between our two powers, that is.
I look forward to it!
You appear to enjoy fighting, huh, Son Goku?
Just as one would expect
of a battle maniac Saiyan.
The same appears to be true of you.
In my case, it depends on the opponent.
Same with me.
They've vanished again.
What in the world has happened?
Both of them have vanished.
Mmm... It's a trick that
makes use of an optical illusion.
The two of them are camouflaging themselves,
and are lying down on the floor.
Is that right?
There's no way that Mister Satan,
whose kinetic eyesight is sharp
enough to see the seams on a fastball,
could be mistaken.
But still... I don't understand this at all.
Um, Mister Sata–huh?!
Satan-san? Uh, Satan-san? Satan-san?!
Where did you go?! Satan-san?!
This is startling!
Mister Satan has also disappeared!
Mister Satan was right here!
Well, as you can see, even I can
easily perform a trick such as this.
Wow, I didn't notice it in the slightest!
Where did he bring that piece of cloth from?
I heard he spent last night making it secretly.
Watching those guys is funny!
Kuririn-san!
S-Sorry.
S-Still and all, what speed!
I can barely keep up
with them with my eyes!
They're surprised at this level? What a laugh!
There's some sort of
commotion going on over there.
The kids over there must
be playing on their own.
Here they come!
They've appeared!
There, you see?
They were hiding there, all right!
This is that incredible power–
the moment I felt this,
I got flipped up into the air!
M-Me too. What could this
overwhelming sort of power be?
They're using nothing but petty tricks!
What do they think the martial arts are?!
This is bad!
There's nowhere to go!
Cell has gone completely on the offensive!
Why?
Why doesn't Father get serious?
Hmph, I knew it. Kakarrot is
just playing around with Cell.
Although, Cell seems to
be up to the same thing.
That's an old trick, huh?
Ka... me...
ha... me...
Ha!!
So then, that should be enough
for the warm-up exercises, right?
Yeah.
Th-That was just warm-up exercise...?
Th-The full-fledged death
battle is about to get started now...!
Son Goku, huh...?
Indeed, he is skilled at fighting.
He's one or two paces removed from the others.
This guy looks to be unimaginably strong.
If I get even the slightest bit careless,
I'll be finished off in an instant!
All right....!
The look in Goku-san's eyes has changed!
He's coming at me at full power.
At last, Goku will fight at full power!
With his full-blown strength...
there is no doubt that
this will be a fierce battle.
Which way will the victory go?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Stop, Cell! If you launch a
Kamehame-Ha with that much power,
you're putting the earth at risk!
Do you really think that concerns me?
Take this!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Direct Hit to Earth!!
Cell's Extra-Large Kamehame-Ha."
Look out! Father, you won't
be able to get clear of that!
"Next time"
"Direct Hit to Earth!!
Cell's Extra-Large Kamehame-Ha"