Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Goku's desperate battle
has pushed him beyond his limits.
However, Vegeta's bottomless power
has even allowed him to create a moon,
so that he could transform into a Great Ape.
"Battle Power Times Ten!!
Vegeta's Great Metamorphosis."
Just a little farther till we're at
Kame House. Hang in there, Gohan.
Right.
H-Hey, over there...
T-That's the direction we just came from.
What could it be? It's awfully bright. A star?
No, it doesn't appear to be a star...
This can't be!
T-This is impossible!
W-What is that? There's
a tremendous ki rising up.
Father's ki hasn't risen again, right?
N-No. This nasty feeling is
coming from the other one's ki.
And you know, that's an incredible
amount of ki. What's going on?!
F-Father...
Gohan!
I-I'm going back.
I'm going back.
G-Going back? You mean to where Goku is?
I can tell... Father is in trouble.
He's going to die if this keeps up...
What are you talking about, Gohan?
There's no way Goku–
your father is going to die, is there?
Besides, even if we go back there,
we can't do anything against
a guy with a ki that incredible.
Yeah, I know.
Even so...
Even so!
I absolutely have to go back there!
Hey!
Wait up, Gohan!
How about it, Kakarrot?
You're finished now!
What's going on?!
A Great Ape? A Great Ape monster?
Let me give you some good news.
A Saiyan who has become a Great
Ape has ten times more battle power!
Goku, there's a great ape monster
that comes out during the full moon.
You must not go outside. As long
as you stay asleep, you'll be safe.
I-I'll make it so that tail
of yours never grows back.
It's something of a nuisance.
S-So that's it! I finally get it!
H-How awful...
The monster that crushed Grandpa to death...
...and the monster that showed
up at the tournament grounds,
and busted everything up...
...that was me?!
I'm sorry, Grandpa. This guy is incredible.
I'll probably have to use up all of
my ki, or I won't be able to beat him.
Once I die, and go back over to
the Next World, I'll go apologize to you.
What is that monster?!
I-It's outrageously huge!
That monster's clothes're the
same as the Saiyan's! Is he that Saiyan?!
I'll show you, Vegeta!
I'm going to feed you your fill
of me and the Earth's Genki Dama!
You're at last going to use
the Genki Dama, are you?
Still, with your body as ragged as it is,
this is going to put
too much of a burden on it.
K-Kaio-ken!
What's the matter?
Can't you even get away?
Die!
What is it?
Is anything appearing?
I'm starting to see some light.
Goku's ki has subsided.
Goku-sa has won, right?
–Goku!
–Son-kun!
Goku-sa!
I-Is he dead?
No, he is not dead.
What the hell has happened?
I-Impossible!
You mean the Saiyan has
transformed, even without the moon?!
It's hopeless now! There's no
way he can stand up to that monster!
What about Gohan-chan?!
What's Gohan-chan doin'?!
Where's Gohan-chan?!
There's someone else there...
It's Yajirobe!
What is he doing?!
Come on, Yajirobe! Why
aren't you helping Son-kun?!
Hey!
G-Gohan-chan...
Chichi!
Father!
Goku, he's your son, all right.
What's the matter, Kakarrot?
Can't you manage anything?!
H-He's so fast for as big as he is!
I don't have enough time to mentally
focus so I can create a Genki Dama!
And even if I went to a times five Kaio-ken,
it wouldn't be any use against him!
Hmph. If you're not going to
come at me, then I'm coming after you!
I-I just need ten seconds!
I need some time to concentrate!
T-That's it!
Tenshinhan, I'm going
to borrow your technique!
Taiyo-ken!
Now, while his eyes are blinded by the glare!
M-My eyes! My eyes!
All right... At this distance...
T-The Land...
the Seas...
and...
all living things...
Each of you, share with me just
a little bit of your Genki energy!
I beg you!
Dammit, that was an insolent stunt!
J-Just a little longer...
Just a little more, and
I can form a Genki Dama...
W-What's he doin'?
He's starting to get his sight back.
Still, at this distance,
I'll be able to launch the
Genki Dama before he can attack.
Dammit!
Where are you?!
Where are you?! Where did you go?!
It's useless to run away from
me! I can sense your presence!
Dammit!
I've gathered the Genki energy together.
Why, you!
He found me! Please,
let there be enough time!
I-It's done. I've collected the
Genki energy from all earthlings.
All right!
Take this!
W-What was that?
What happened?
I-I never expected him to attack like that...
T-That was an awful miscalculation.
What a development... The Genki Dama
I worked so hard to make has vanished...
Hmph, you're a tough bastard.
But you appear to be
near your limit. I can tell.
H-He's got me. There ain't
no way even I can win now.
I used up most of my
ki on that Genki Dama.
Now what are you going to do?!
Goku's ki is shrinking fast!
F-Father!
Hurry! We're almost there!
Whoops! Sorry, sorry!
Looks like I carelessly
stepped on you and crushed your leg.
Well, this time, I'll
carelessly crush your heart.
This is the end for you, Kakarrot!
Even if you were to come back to life
again, this planet won't be here when you do!
D-Damn... I'm utterly defeated...
I never imagined there'd be
this much difference in our power...
I'm glad there was
someone so strong... but if I die...
it'd be so frustrating...
Die!
That's what you call the weasel's last fart...
Now, I ain't even got enough
strength left to blow my nose...
D-Do as you like...
W-Why, you...!
Kakarrot!
How dare you... how dare you scar my face?!
I'm going to squeeze you to death!
Having been wounded,
Vegeta was burning with anger.
Will Goku be crushed to death like this?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Gohan, your daddy's whole body
is a mess. I can't move anymore.
Fight in my place.
What's the matter? Isn't a
Super Saiyan supposed to be strong?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Don't Die, Father!!
This is the Depth of Gohan's Power."
I can't, Father! He's too
strong! I can't beat him!
"Next time"
"Don't Die, Father!!
This is the Depth of Gohan's Power"