Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Burning with ambition to achieve his perfect form,
Cell has launched an indiscriminate
attack, in order to absorb No. 18,
who has hidden herself together with No. 16.
Elsewhere, having finished their
training in the Room of Spirit and Time,
Vegeta and Trunks were
headed toward Cell at ultra-speed.
Cell, it appears you're making
quite a show about going into action.
Son Goku and Gohan, father and son,
have entered the Room of Spirit and Time.
Will they indeed be able to surpass Super Saiyan?
"Suddenly Full-Throttle!!
The Super Power of a Radiant Vegeta."
It's no use, no matter how well you're hiding!
You won't get out of this by
concealing yourself, No. 18!
Are you saying that that
isn't him being serious?!
Yeah, I am.
At this rate, it's only a
matter of time before he finds us.
You sure are an odd one.
No. 18... No matter what,
I will absorb you and
become my perfect form.
That is the reason I came
here from the future, after all.
That's the level of Cell's battle power?
Kakarrot and you guys,
what were you so frightened of?
Dad's ki has risen.
To think that he's capable of
putting out that much ki so easily!
I don't know how much Vegeta
and Trunks have powered up,
but Cell's power is nothing ordinary.
He's of a different dimension!
If Cell were to absorb No. 18
and become his perfect form
before Goku finishes his special training...
...then not even Goku can beat him.
It could be the end.
Damn! My entire life, one
day has never felt so long!
You're a fine man!
What are you wavering about?!
Son-kun is the strongest in the universe!
He will win for sure!
That's just how it's
going to be! You got that?!
Oh, there, there, don't cry!
Trunks, you're a big boy,
right? You're fine, you're fine!
E-Everything is snow-white!
M-My body feels heavy too,
and it's so hot that it's hard to breathe.
Once the doorway to the outside is closed,
any contact from the outside
world is completely shut out.
See? You can't sense either
Cell's ki or Vegeta's ki any more, right?
It's true! I don't feel a thing!
Over there is the bath and the toilet.
This is the food storeroom.
There's a year's worth of food in here.
What do you think?
So, even my big-eating
father will be all right, huh?
Gohan, we've covered just about everything.
Right! It looks like I'll be
able to make it through like this.
Really? Go take a look out back.
You'll understand
what I meant when I said...
...it was too tough for me to stay
here even a month when I was a kid!
W-What's going on?!
We're inside a room, yet
the place is this expansive!
What's more, there's nothing there!
I hear it's about as big as the Earth!
I-It can't be!
You haven't come out, huh?
You must surely be on one
of the islands around here.
It seems you understand that it
won't do any good to escape underwater.
Anyhow, it appears I can't do anything else
but examine the entire ocean in this area.
Don't shoot!
You will be detected by Cell!
Dammit!
He's finally arrived at the next island over!
Calm down!
Cell is only looking for
anything that leaves the islands!
Just sit still like this and hang on!
You at least will be spared!
That single island there is all that remains.
One left...
He's coming!
Calm down!
Don't give up until the end!
If you are absorbed,
it will be the end of everything!
Well, you better come on out, No. 18!
You're... Vegeta!
So you're Cell?
Land!
Vegeta...?
What have you come all this way for?
Don't tell me you've come to make jokes,
such as you have come
to defeat me, have you?
I haven't come to defeat you.
I'm going to knock you into so many pieces
there won't be anything left afterward.
Me? You?
Amusing.
I'm shocked to think that
my cells were being used...
...by a repulsive monster such as yourself!
I wonder if you were supposed
to have turned out a little better.
They're being used by me,
the strongest in the universe!
Just for that, you should be honored.
Not so, monster!
You are not the strongest in the universe.
That would be me,
the prince of the Saiyans, Vegeta!
What is he, stupid?
What can someone who was
so utterly helpless against me
now do against Cell?
Trunks, huh?
There's been quite a change about you.
Well, it doesn't matter to
me how many of you may come.
If you like, shall I wait
for even more to arrive?
He's just a spectator.
I alone will be sufficient to bury you.
What was that?
Did you say that you alone were sufficient?
That's right! Got any problem with it?!
I've got no problem.
I'm just astounded by
how absurd you're being!
Cell is right!
No matter what may happen,
Vegeta is no match for him!
Still, No. 16, this may be our chance to escape!
Hey, No. 16!
Wait! We only move
once the fighting has started.
Besides which, it's strange.
Vegeta's battle power
has gone up a great deal
since that time previously.
Ridiculous!
There's no way it could change
all that much in this short a time!
He didn't look like he was
holding back or anything...
Watch very carefully, Cell!
I'm going to erase that disagreeable
little smile of yours for you!
Dad's planning on changing right off...
...into that.
It's begun! His ki is rapidly...
...rapidly increasing.
S-Such a terrific ki...!
Let's have a look, Vegeta,
at this power that goes
even beyond Super Saiyan.
Be careful!
If you go too far away,
you might not be able to find
your way back here, get lost and die!
R-Right!
The temperature varies from
50 degrees to minus 40 degrees.
The air is about one-fourth that of Earth,
and the gravity is about 10 times
greater in this pure-white world.
It's gonna be awful!
O-O-One year in a place like this?
Gohan, we start training right away!
We didn't come here to play!
How about it? Awfully terrible, ain't it?
This is the first time you've
ever done gravity training, huh?
Well, you'll get used to it soon.
Right!
First of all, Gohan, we're
going to make you a Super Saiyan.
–S-Super Saiyan?
–Yeah.
I-I'm not sure I can
become a Super Saiyan...
Of course you can!
You've inherited genuine Saiyan blood!
We've got to make you a Super Saiyan.
Then we'll start the full-fledged training.
But, isn't it possible that
I will get in the way
of your training, Father?
Yeah, at first.
But then, Gohan, if you can so
much as become Super Saiyan,
you'll be much more
help to me as a drill partner!
You are my son.
Have faith in yourself!
Okay?
R-Right!
Okay.
Naturally, I intend to obtain
power beyond Super Saiyan!
I want to be stronger
than anyone else, after all!
But Gohan, I intend to
have you even surpass me!
M-Me surpass you, Father?
That's right. That's my ideal.
I'm positive it will happen!
I-I wonder...
Trunks-san said, you know,
that in the future I will become a Super Saiyan,
and get killed by the Artificial Humans.
What are you talking about?
Things have already changed
considerably from Trunks' future, ain't they?
I'm here, alive and well.
Besides that, the you that died in
the future never trained in here, right?
That's right!
It's all up to your own determination!
Father, if you please!
All right, that's the spirit!
I'm going to be far more hard
on you than Piccolo was, you know!
–Prepare yourself!
–Right!
D-Don't tell me it's still increasing!
What is that?!
How can Vegeta have that kind of power?
I don't believe it!
Is training in the Room of Spirit
and Time as magnificent as all this?
Say, what's wrong?
What's happened to Vegeta?
Trunks is okay, right?
W-What is this?!
Without a doubt, he has
surpassed Super Saiyan.
Vegeta's super power explodes,
exceeding even that of the monstrous Cell!
Can this be the power
that surpasses Super Saiyan?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Nice going, Vegeta! Incredible power!
All right, Gohan, let's not get left behind.
What's the matter, Cell?
Take this more seriously!
If you're this weak, then all that
training I did will be meaningless.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"On Your Knees, Cell!
I Am Super Vegeta!!"
Wow! His power is incredible,
but his self-confidence is amazing, too!
"Next time"
"On Your Knees, Cell!
I Am Super Vegeta!!"