Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Goku, will allowing Gohan to become
angry really release his true power?
Now that the senzu beans have been
taken, and No. 16 has been destroyed,
is Gohan the only hope of saving the Earth?
Son Gohan, apparently you
still haven't come around, huh?
But you watch, I will make
you angry, no matter what!
Now then, my Cell Juniors,
your opponents are those seven
who are on that rock over there.
Do them harm.
If you like, you can kill them. I don't mind.
An even greater battle is beginning!
These guys are terrifyingly strong!
"The Tragic No. 16!! An Enraged
Super Gohan Begins Taking Action."
This can't be!
Damn it all!
Dammit!
Over here!
Th-The unnamed warriors
are fighting the seven monsters
that have newly appeared.
It is a very intense fight.
I'm not entirely certain what is happening,
b-but at any rate, it
appears to be quite dreadful!
Mister Satan, what about you?
Your stomachache seems to have subsided.
W-W-What are you talking about?!
I just haven't been vocal about it!
Oh, is that right?
Because it's me, I can
endure this level of acute pain!
A normal person would
have passed out long ago!
Oh! Impressive, Mister Satan!
Uh, what about your stomachache?
Um, should I go get some medicine?
Shut up! You keep quiet!
G-Goku!
Tenshinhan! Yamucha!
Goku has used up all of
his strength fighting with Cell!
Help Goku out!
Yamucha!
Thank you.
This is hardly the time
to be expressing gratitude.
Piccolo!
Kuririn-san!
S-Stop...!
Except for Trunks,
nobody can be brought back
to life with the Dragon Balls!
Oh? Your ki has started to
swell up ever so slightly, huh?
Good. Apparently, you've started to feel angry.
Unless you show your true power soon,
nothing else is going to mend matters.
Take a good look.
Vegeta and Trunks are barely holding their own.
And with his strength gone,
Son Goku is at risk, too.
What strength they have!
How can I be having
trouble against these runts?!
Dammit...!
I'm sorry, everyone...
I-It wasn't... it wasn't supposed to be like this...
E-Everyone is going to get killed...
If I really do have some
incredible power hidden inside me,
I wish I could release it!
I wish I could use that power to defeat Cell!
B-But... I don't know how...
I don't know what to do to get
angry enough to release that power!
W-What kind of guys are these?
Damn...
Am I to keep taking
on these runts forever?!
To hell with you!!
Those guys just aren't normal.
Say, this isn't worth risking our lives over!
Those guys aren't human!
Y-You're right.
Any more of this would
indeed be too risky, huh?
Let's pull out of here, while we can.
M-Mister Satan, let's run away, too!
Absurd! Why should I, the
champion, have to run away?!
Then, we're going to stay here like this?
N-No... We're going to the hospital for a bit,
and once my stomachache
is better, we'll return here.
All right! With that decided, let's go!
W-Wait!
Please wait!
P-Please...
Before you pull out, carry
me over to where that child is.
He's just a head, but he's talking...!
They're monsters, all right!
P-Please... f-for the sake of the Earth...
Y-Y-You've got to be kidding!
Cell is standing right next to that child!
That's right!
How can you ask Mister Satan
to go to such a dangerous place?
Y-You want to help out a little too, don't you?
I-I hear you're the world
champion of combat sports, and all.
M-Mister Satan is the champion of humanity!
He doesn't get involved in
fights between you monsters!
Don't be ridiculous!
They may be monsters or whatever,
but they are no match for me!
I just need to go to the hospital first...
Please... Champion...
Mister Satan! You don't have
to stand up to that monster!
She's right! Let's hurry up and go!
You have to get to a hospital, quickly!
Mister Satan...?
All right. I'll do it.
You'd better not! You'll be killed!
Be quiet! Those guys
with names we don't know–
and even that child are fighting!
If the champion ran away,
he'd be a laughingstock!
Mister Satan...
I-I just need to carry
you over near to him, right?
Yeah, thanks.
–I-I'm so scared!
–Once you get close enough,
you can just toss me there.
R-Really...?
S-Stop...!
I'm asking you to stop, aren't I?
Just a little bit further now...
All right, Cell Juniors!
That's enough playing around!
You can kill them if you like.
Good. A little more... just a little more...
Do it! Kill them!
A-All right, here goes...
N-No. 16...
O-Oh, no!
I put too much force into it,
and threw him too far!
S-Son Gohan...
It is no sin to fight for what is right.
There are opponents with
which you cannot talk things out.
Set your spirit free to your
anger. I know how it feels.
You just can't take it any longer.
That's good advice. However, I'm...
I'm doing things my way.
Gohan...
Nature, and the animals that I, too, liked...
D-Defend them for me...
I'm counting on you...
Nobody asked you, you factory defect!
The time is fulfilled,
O messiah, O messiahs...
(yuduliya-vele yuduliya-vele)
(yuduliya-vele yuduliya-iyaliya)
Ah, bringing with it a bottomless terror,
Ah, an evil soul draws near.
I cannot lose now, this is
the dividing line of destiny,
Gohan...!
I can only go ahead,
and stake my life at dawn.
It's in my hands! Whoa, whatever it takes,
I am going to go beyond myself!
At last...
Whoa, I'll gather my strength,
At last, has Gohan's
fury exceeded its bounds?
And blow this darkness away!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
All right, Gohan is finally good and angry!
His power is even more awesome than I thought.
Impossible! I don't believe it!
We've been having all this
trouble fighting these runts,
and he kills them in a single blow!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Devastating True Power!!
The Cell Juniors Pulverized."
I'm little crybaby Gohan no longer!
"Next time"
"Devastating True Power!!
The Cell Juniors Pulverized"