The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Majin Boo has been revived.
With his overwhelming power,
Majin Boo has defeated Dabura,
as well as Gohan, in a moment's time.
M-M-Magnificent!
Incredible, Majin Boo!
To think how easily you defeated Dabura there!
Utterly magnificent!
Elsewhere, knowing of the Majin's revival,
Vegeta hits Goku unaware, and
resolves to head off to fight alone.
However, at that moment,
Majin Boo had Kaioshin cornered!
"The Terrifying Majin!!
Death's Dread Draws Near Gohan."
Great! Great, Majin Boo!
Get him! Get him! Get him good!
Gohan-san...
Th-This can't be!
Kaioshin-sama!
Outstanding, Majin Boo!
Kill him! Kill him!
K-Kaioshin-sama...
O-Okay then...
How about that?!
What?!
Yow!
Oh, my! Have you come all the way back here?
Well, well now...!
Oh, really? Does it hurt, Kaioshin?
Yeah, this is quite the misfortune!
Huh?! Again?!
What's wrong? What's wrong?
Are you taking a nap in a place such as this?
No one could think you're the one
who stands at the top of the world!
It serves you right!
I know! How about I strike the final blow?
Are you all right, Kaioshin-sama?!
Damn, and just as it turning out well, too!
What kind of guy is this?
I had no effect on him at all!
You're in the way! You get lost!
Gohan-san! Look out!
We can't see him any more!
Fly away, to the ends of the universe!
P-Please, be a-alive...
Hey! Did you do something just now?!
"Heaven"
Those guys... Those guys...
Who the hell are they?
I won't have it!
I absolutely forbid you to keep
company with this weakling boy!!
I've got to calm down!
Come to mention it, how was Videl,
who isn't part of that group,
able to fly through the air?
Ha! Is that it?!
It's so absurd, I'd never
even thought of it before,
but maybe humans are naturally able to fly!
Otherwise, there's no reason Videl was able to!
Ahem...
If those mysterious guys
are able to so much as fly,
then there's no reason the
world's strongest martial combatant,
Mister Satan, cannot!
That's not it, huh? In that case...!
Um, we're with the Mister Satan Fan Club...
This was nothing, here!
See, I was just developing
a new finishing attack, is all...
You had this coming to you, Kaioshin!
You've quite thoroughly
been an encumbrance,
but I am thankful to you!
After all, thanks to the
people you brought with you,
Majin Boo was able to be revived!
It's only a feeling of gratitude.
I'm going to kill you personally!
I'm sure my papa, who was killed
by you, will be pleased with me too!
Enough of this!
Hey, Majin Boo, you can finish off Kaioshin now!
Hey, Majin Boo!!
I'm hungry. Gonna eat 'im!
That's great! You can eat him, huh?
That means a death worthy of Kaioshin!
Okay! Majin Boo, eat up Kaioshin!
Gobble him up so that not
even one hair remains of him!
Dabura, are you still alive?!
And here, you've really
done it to me now, Dabura!
That's strange. It was
supposed to be right about here.
H-Hey, isn't that it?
–All right! Let's descend!
–Yeah!
Goten, let's stop being Super Saiyan.
We'll be found out if they sense us!
Yeah!
Huh? We don't know any of these guys!
That's not so! Look!
The one who's down over there.
He's that strange guy we saw at the tournament!
Oh, you're right!
Has he been finished off?
Say, Trunks-kun, which one is the Majin?
W-Which, you say...
...from here, we're too far away to me to tell!
Hey Goten, let's get a little bit closer!
B-But–Ah! Wait up, Trunks-kun!
Sheesh! I can't tell at all!
And where in the world do you suppose
Papa or Gohan and the others went?
Big brother...
Say, Trunks-kun...
What is it, Goten?
Look over there! See?!
What could that be?
All right, let's go look!
Piccolo-san!
Oh, it's a mannequin?
Ah, it gave me a start!
This is made of stone!
But why would there be a mannequin
of Piccolo-san in a place like this?
There's also a mannequin
of Kuririn-san over there!
This is weird!
Y-Yikes!
T-Trunks-kun!
O-Oh, no!
Looks as though they didn't notice us!
Babidi-sama, he–
Majin Boo is by no means the kind of
guy who will be a loyal follower of yours!
At some time... At some time,
he will definitely get out of hand!
The day when disaster befalls you will come!
Unless we dispose of him now, while
we can, something terrible will happen!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up!!
How could you do this to
Majin Boo?! My precious Majin Boo!
How dare you?! How dare you?!
Babidi-sama!
How dare you?!
M-Majin Boo! Are you okay?
W-What?!
Impossible!
Outstanding! Outstanding!
Just what you'd expect of
my papa's creation, Majin Boo!
I'm gonna eat you!
Having beaten Kaioshin, as well as Gohan,
with overwhelming strength,
Majin Boo closes in on Dabura.
Will Dabura actually be eaten?
And, at this time, what of Goku and Vegeta?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Dabura has been turned into a cookie?!
Hey, can he do that?
Ugh! I like eating cookies,
but I don't want to be eaten!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"'Gonna Eat'cha!!'
A Hungry Majin's Supernatural Power."
Vegeta-san has appeared
from out of the spaceship.
He's going to challenge Boo!
"Next time"
"'Gonna Eat'cha!!'
A Hungry Majin's Supernatural Power"