Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
As the mysterious youth
Trunks had forewarned,
the machines of mass destruction,
Artificial Humans No. 1 9 and No. 20,
had appeared, and the
time for battle has arrived.
It looks as though you've failed to investigate...
...the most important thing about me.
You guys lose!
You certainly have achieved
quite an increase in power.
However, it is still not
enough to overpower us.
To say nothing of myself,
at your level, it is unlikely
you could defeat even No. 19.
Oh really? Well, why don't I have
you show me this strength right now?
"Goku's Double-Shock!!
Caught Between Illness and Adversary."
Way to go, Goku!
Ooh, nice...
Awesome!
I hope everyone's okay.
Hi! Is Kurin-chan there?
Kurin-chan, it's me!
Oh, if it isn't Maron-chan!
Say, where's Kurin-chan?
There's nothing like the real thing...
Oh, yeah!
How's about a pafu-pafu or a tsun-tsun?
Maron finally realized something.
Once I lost true love, I understood it...
The only one I ever truly loved...
Was Kurin-chan.
Kurin-chan!
Kurin-chan...
Kurin-chan, where are you?
Kurin-chan, where are you?!
Kurin-chan... Kurin-chan...
Where are you?
Uh, Kuririn-san is currently
in a battle to defeat the people...
...created by the last of the Red Ribbon Army.
Red Ribbon? Oh, I get it!
Kurin-chan is going to give me
the red ribbon as a present, isn't he?
...and if things were to continue that way,
the Earth's future would be all messed up, see?
That's what the boy...
...who came back from the future
world in the time capsule told us.
In order to save the Earth
from this crisis, Kuririn has...
....gone off to fight these people that were
created by a survivor of the Red Ribbon...
Maron doesn't get any of this.
Well, why don't we let someone of
my age and wisdom explain it to you.
See now, do you know what
the Red Ribbon Army was?
What was the Red Ribbon?
Aah, you naughty old turtle man!
This all has to do with a
time when Goku was still a child.
Goku had gone on a journey to both
train himself and search for the Dragon Balls.
At that time,
there was this terrible military outfit
calling themselves the Red Ribbon Army,
who were determined to conquer the world.
Their boss, Commander Red,
was gathering the Dragon Balls
to serve his evil purposes.
Goku fought successively...
...against a number of Red Ribbon
operatives who attacked him.
I took his face off!
Have I done something bad?
And then, Goku attacked the Red
Ribbon's headquarters all by himself!
And that's how the Red
Ribbon Army was vanquished.
At least, everyone thought they were vanquished.
But there was someone who had survived.
Doctor Gero, a maniacal scientist,
secretly continued his research even
after the fall of the Red Ribbon Army.
As such, he created these Artificial Humans,
whose only desires were to kill and destroy,
intending for them to be
the ultimate murder weapon.
Those Artificial Humans are now running amuck.
So now Kuririn is assisting
Son Goku and his other friends...
...in the fight against those
Artificial Humans on that southern island.
Do you understand now, little lady?
Maron doesn't get it at all.
I feel it! What an incredibly large ki!
It's Father's ki.
Right. But there's only one.
I guess we really can't sense
any ki from the Artificial Humans.
Incredible. Such strength!
So that's a Super Saiyan?
It's a whole different dimension
from the rest of us. Far different.
I'm not so sure...
His increase in power is much
greater than our data forecasted.
This can't be happening.
This isn't good! At this rate,
No. 1 9 will expend all of his energy...
...before he can steal any additional power!
There they are!
Okay!
Father!
Don't worry, Goku's strength is incredible!
Especially as a Super Saiyan.
Incredible! Goku sure is strong!
Really. Maybe I was wrong about
them being able to drain one's energy.
Have you noticed it too, Gohan?
Yes.
Son Goku is rushing this fight for some reason.
He's acting as if he's
already near his full power.
So why is he making such a mess of things?!
Mess of things? Mess of things?
What are you saying?
Goku's got him completely at his mercy.
This is nothing! As a Super Saiyan,
Goku should be much more powerful!
Um, Yamucha-san says...
...that those Artificial Humans
are able to absorb energy.
Could that be the reason?
What? They absorb energy?!
Yeah. I had my face grabbed by one of them.
Then, without anyone doing anything,
it felt like my ki was being sucked out.
He did it!
–You did it, Goku!
–He did it, he did it! Yeah!
–Attaboy, Goku!
–Not bad at all!
Look at him! Even after that kind of beating,
he acts like nothing's happened!
He's an Artificial Human.
He probably doesn't feel pain or fatigue.
Dammit!
All right!
He absorbed it.
I was right after all! Those guys' hands...
Son! Don't shoot any more ki blasts!
These guys seem to be able to
absorb ki through their hands!
Don't let them grab onto you either! Got that?
He can take my ki?
They've got to be kidding!
Hey, there's something the matter with Goku.
Has he already had that
much ki taken from him?
No, he couldn't have had any
energy taken directly from him so far.
Good! That blast has allowed No. 1 9
to store up a great deal of power!
On the other hand, the amount of power
Goku is able to use at once is falling!
This is our chance! Go, No. 1 9!
Don't shoot, Goku!
Father...
Damn...
Hey, he really looks like he's struggling.
He must have had his ki drained from him.
I knew it! Father is sick! It's his heart!
What? His heart?
You mean like that guy
from the future was saying,
a viral infection of his heart?!
Goku!
Goku's condition is out of the ordinary.
Have the symptoms of a viral heart infection...
...finally begun to undermine
his physical condition?
Will Goku indeed be able to defeat these cruel,
fully-powered Artificial Humans?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Heh heh, nice save, Vegeta.
I was sure you'd show up.
Hmph, apparently, you
were watching the whole time,
but you are no match for us, either!
Just like Goku, there!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Might of Vegeta!
The Blood of a Super Saiyan Awakens."
All right, someday,
I'll become a Super Saiyan, too!
"Next time"
"The Might of Vegeta!
The Blood of a Super Saiyan Awakens"