Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
The hour of the fated
Cell Games had finally arrived.
Okay then, let's make
contemptuous faces at him! Nyaah!
And I'll give him a good spanky-spanky!
Welcome, all of you!
How about that?!
It's time!
"Just a Moment!!
The Satan Squad Goes On the Rampage."
Whoever goes first is fine with me.
Of course, that will be me.
It's only natural I'd be the one.
Don't do it, Goku.
These guys just won't understand,
even if you do tell them.
I can't let that happen.
You're gonna get killed!
Trust me on this, give it up!
Hey, cameraman, get a
shot of that dimwit over there.
Right.
It's almost as if I can hear the
voices of all the world in my ears,
saying "Oh, my word!"
Does this man realize what
he just said to Mister Satan?!
Of all the things to say at this moment,
"You're gonna get killed!
Trust me on this, give it up!"
That's what he said!
It's because of things like this
that ignorant bumpkins are an
embarrassment to the rest of us!
After all of our explaining who
Satan is, he still doesn't get it!
There's no helping those kinds of folks, huh?
He looks like him...
That man looks like him...
That child, who once upon a time,
saved us all from Piccolo Daimao...
However, he didn't have
the same eye or hair color.
It must be someone else...
Be that as it may, it's this man that concerns me.
N-No matter how I look at him,
I can't help but think that
he is that same Piccolo Daimao...
Look, it's all right, just let
those idiots do as they like.
Even if they are killed,
they can be brought back
to life with the Dragon Balls.
Ah, well, I guess there ain't much choice, huh?
Oh, it appears that he
has finally been convinced!
Which is to say, it's only natural.
Could he have realized
that his life has been spared?
They finally understand, huh?
This nonsensical group has been
nothing but an annoyance to Mister Satan!
As we pull ourselves together, the
match can finally continue once again!
Please wait, Sensei!
W-What's this?
A mysterious group of people
has appeared before Mister Satan!
Who in the world could they be?!
We've got more weirdoes showing up!
We are Mister Satan's finest pupils!
The world's most gorgeous
man, Caroni, the Swift!
The world's most staggeringly
strong man, Piroshiki the Mighty!
A-Apparently, these two are
acquaintances of Mister Satan.
Allow me to explain.
These two men are Mister Satan's
first and second pupils,
and are the next-to-greatest,
and next-to-next-to greatest warriors,
compared to the warrior who
boasts the greatest speed and power.
Oh, that is incredible!
And I am their beautiful manager, Pizza.
Sensei, there is no need for
you to get your own hands dirty
against such a rank amateur.
W-We can easily defeat him!
Hmm, perhaps so.
It might be a bit childish of me
to take on such a rank amateur myself.
I leave him to you!
People of the world, did you hear that?!
Mister Satan has clearly announced
that these two top pupils of
his will defeat Cell in his place!
And what promising
assistants they appear to be!
Our victory is now all the more assured!
Caroni and Piroshiki!
I've seen their pictures in magazines!
They're Satan's favorite pupils,
and have won a great
deal of fighting tournaments!
That's awesome!
Idiots...!
There's more of them now... those fools.
And so, the Cell Games resume!
First up is Mister Satan's top pupil,
Contestant Caroni the Swift!
And so, I, Caroni, will be your opponent.
Very good. Mmm, sweet...!
These are a parting gift for you,
as you are about to enter the ground.
–Caroni-sama!
–He's so cool!
Magnificent!
What a graceful, elegant,
yet bewitching technique!
Allow me to explain.
He is a master of the aerial death strike,
and can even snatch a
swallow as it flies through the air.
That is incredible!
As one might expect of Satan's top pupil,
his abilities are in a league of their own!
What's the deal with this guy?
That move must have floored
100,000 of my female fans.
And so, the Cell Games, with
the fate of the world in the balance,
have now begun!
The rules are simple:
if you fall outside of this ring, you lose;
if you give up, you lose;
and if you die, you lose!
Are you afraid?
Not to worry, the suffering
will only last a moment.
Beautiful... Rose... Flying...
Attack!!
Oh, my! What a super jump!
This is Caroni's greatest, most
inscrutable finishing technique!
This match has already seen its conclusion.
"Big Finish" time...
Incredible! He's still flying up!
I-Is he still flying up...?
He must be in superb shape.
W-What could that sound be?
W-What could have happened, exactly?
S-Surely, he must have jumped too high.
He's good at doing this, but he has
a bad habit of getting carried away.
Therein lies the reason
why he cannot surpass me.
That's correct!
I see!
–What happened?
–My Caroni-sama!
–Stupid jerk!
As luck would have it, Contestant
Caroni the Swift has lost by Ringout,
and though a gifted warrior,
he meets with valorous defeat.
Truly, this is a shame!
I-I will defeat Cell!
Allow me to explain.
His monstrous strength
rivals that of 20 elephants,
and he can flatten a bull with one blow.
T-That does indeed sound fierce.
F-Fantastic! What fantastic power!
W-What colossal strength!
Cell does not stand a chance against him!
They're on two completely different levels!
Knowing Piroshiki, he won't make
the same kind of blunder as Caroni did.
You have to feel sorry for Cell.
Oh, my! Contestant Piroshiki
has begun a ferocious dash!
This is Contestant Piroshiki's
Megaton Bull Crusher!
At this point, there's no one that can stop him!
What could have happened?
Contestant Piroshiki's motion has stopped!
I-I give up!
What in the world just
happened? Mister Satan...?
It's a trick.
He is considerably afraid of me, you see.
He has set up tricks all around
the dueling ring. Damned bastard...!
It's possible that he has soaked his entire body
with the smell of green peppers,
which Piroshiki despises,
or he might have rigged
nails to stick up out of the floor.
But I will expose his tricks!
So that's it! I don't know when
he might have done it, though...
What a dirty trick to use in a one-on-one fight!
I'm telling you, that's not it!
Those two were tossed around by Cell's ki.
Figure it out already, would you?
And so, having had his
beloved pupils beaten by foul play,
Mister Satan gathers his fury
and once again enters the ring!
He removes his cape...
...and now, he has removed
his glorious champion belt!
And so, our hero, Mister
Satan, has taken the stage!
This match will determine the fate of the Earth!
Our world combat sport champion Mister Satan
has gleefully commented to us that
he has been looking forward to this day!
Oh? Mister Satan has pulled
something from out of his breast pocket.
It's a capsule! He has pulled out a capsule...
Oh, it's his bag! An enormous
bag has come forth from the capsule!
Now then, what could be inside the bag?
Roofing tiles!
There were roofing tiles inside!
Mister Satan is delicately stacking the tiles!
Oh, man...!
Hey now, you don't suppose he's...?
The stack numbers... 15 tiles! 15 tiles!
He has taken 15 roofing
tiles and stacked them high!
And now, he's focusing his mind!
Mister Satan is concentrating his power!
Let's remain quiet for this now...
Oh, my! Only one remains!
Still, this is incredible!
What terrific destructive force!
14 tiles! 14 tiles have been shattered to pieces!
He's a genuine idiot.
Cell! Take a look at these tiles
that have been smashed to pieces!
In one more minute... this is how you will look.
Satan! Satan! Satan! Satan!
I've just gone numb! Such is the world's Satan!
I have just been intensely moved!
I nailed it! I absolutely nailed it just now!
It's a good thing I'm taping
this on my video recorder.
He's losing his nerve!
Even Cell, with all of his big talk,
can't help but lose his nerve
after seeing the destructive
force of Mister Satan!
However, it's too late
for him to make apologies!
The people of the world
will not forgive Cell's crimes!
All right, come on!
And so, Mister Satan takes up
a completely combative stance!
The world's number one
combat sport warrior by far,
Mister Satan, versus Cell!
The iron fist of justice
is about to burst upon Cell,
who has taken so many human lives!
Satan! Satan! Satan!
Come on, Mister Satan!
If possible, we'd like for
you to beat Cell by killing him!
Ah, there he goes!
Contestant Satan immediately
launches into some grand techniques!
His Dynamite Kick has erupted against Cell!
Has this match already been decided?!
Contestant Satan does
not let up with his attack!
He's raining blows upon him!
He's raining blows upon Cell!
Cell is helpless to defend himself!
He's strong! He's more than strong!
Such is our champion, Mister Satan!
Hey, now to finish you!
Stop pestering me!
"Conk!"
Huh...?
In all honesty, I was kind
of rooting for Cell just now.
Geez, he's still alive?
It looks like even Cell is
averse to killing that sort.
H-He fell outside of the ring...
U-Um... Contestant Satan has lost...
Now then, let's hurry and
get the Cell Games started!
Who will go first?
As expected, will you, Son Goku, lead off?
Yeah, that's right.
At last, Goku and Cell face each other.
The curtain now rises on the true
Cell Games, the ultimate decisive battle!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Cell is even more awesome than I thought.
If I get even the slightest bit
careless, I'll be finished off!
I was hoping to save
the most enjoyable for last.
Well, bring it on, Son Goku!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Fight Time, Goku!!
The Ultra-Tense Cell Games."
Father's ki is rising.
He's planning to fight at full power!
"Next time"
"Fight Time, Goku!!
The Ultra-Tense Cell Games"