The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
After a ferocious battle with Gohan,
Majin Boo went and blew his own body up!
How good of you to have gotten away, Dende!
However, shortly after
reuniting with Dende and Satan,
Boo once again came attacking.
Hey, pipsqueaks! Come
on out! I want to fight you!
You've got it backward, Boo!
I'm your opponent now!
What's the matter, pipsqueaks?
Are you afraid to fight me?
"Boo's Worst Foul!!
Gotenks is Absorbed!?"
What happened to all those
high spirits you showed earlier?
–What was that?
–You say we're afraid?!
You don't get it at all, do you?!
If we hadn't returned to normal earlier,
we would have completely won that fight!
I don't know about that.
You seemed to be pretty scared,
if that was supposed to be the case.
What was that?!
He said we were scared!
All right! What a fool! Let's get him!
This time, we'll get him for sure, Trunks-kun!
Of course we will!
Are we going stand here quietly
while being mocked by that punk?
W-Wait! There's something odd
about this. Don't you think it's strange?
Why...?
You think too much, Piccolo-san!
What kind of strategy could
come from an idiot like that?
Yeah!
H-Hey!
All right! Plenty of time has
gone by! We can do our Fusion!
Don't! You guys just be quiet and
watch on. I am going to defeat him.
You've got to be joking!
We can't just sit quietly after
having been defied that badly!
Big Brother, you just don't know how
strong we are when we go through Fusion!
We'll show you right now...
...so just give us some room!
That's right! Do it now!
That Fusion or whatever thing!
All right, let's go, Goten!
Yeah!
This time, let's start out
right away as Super Gotenks!
–Fu–
–sion Ha!!
Oh, so this is Fusion?
Yea!
Dum-dum-dum-dum! It's the
Grim Reaper of Justice, Super Gotenks!
I-Incredible...
For two people to become
one person... th-that can't be so!
All right!
If I can just add those pipsqueaks'
power and that Piccolo guy's brains...
I-Is this not a trick?
W-What is it, at a time
like this? Are you hungry?
Tough it out, I'm starving myself.
A-one, two, three, four...
Well, how about I give it to him now?
After all, I'm the one he designated.
But even so... it will be no
trouble at all putting him away!
Very well. But don't drop your guard!
Awright!
Y-You dummy! Where
are you going? Come back!
W-Wait up! Where are you going?!
Wait!
Here goes!
W-What?!
W-What is this?!
P-Piccolo-san!
W-Why, you! What have you done?!
You're mine!
D-Dammit, no!
A-Ah, hell! So that's what he was doing?
G-Get him, Gohan! Get him now!
Does that mean...?
W-W-What was that?! What's happened?!
P-Piccolo-san and Super
Gotenks were absorbed by Boo!
C-Can he do something like that?
What do you think, Gohan-kun?
My strategy succeeded without incident.
Now, look! Wonderful, isn't it?
This is that moment which will
never come again, no matter the future...
the birth of the mightiest of Majin!
That was dirty, you! How could
you pull those two into yourself?!
It's your fault! You're the
one who was stronger than me,
who should have been the absolute strongest!
From the time I could feel your
existence so far away, I began this strategy.
Perhaps there was
someone even stronger than I.
And so I thought
that if I were to absorb the Super
Gotenks or whoever the runts were
I was fighting with at the time into myself,
then no matter what matter
of fellow might show up,
my throne as the mightiest
of all would not be shaken.
However, it seemed that those
runts' power was limited by time.
That's what they said.
Get on with it!
I can only stay this ridiculously
strong for a little while longer, after all!
It will take another hour
before I can become like this again!
It wouldn't do for me to have them return
back to normal at the moment I absorbed them.
I waited for the next opportunity.
It was apparent that given an hour, they
could once again turn into this Super Gotenks.
As such, I disappeared for that long.
So that was it, was it?
However, for you to be standing
there babbling on like that,
your slow-wittedness doesn't
seem to have changed at all.
As long as you were out absorbing people,
wanting to make yourself first-rate material,
it would have been a lot
easier to have just absorbed me!
You don't seem to understand at all, do you?
Without an opponent, what am I
to do once I become the strongest?
What?
The previous Majin Boo said he was
definitely going to blow you away, right?
That is my greatest goal.
I see, so that's it. You've convinced me.
Now, then...
You'll have to allow me
to hurry through this fight.
Apparently this Super
Gotenks that I've absorbed
has quite a short
transformation time limit about him.
That's a fairly level-headed
determination, coming from you.
Looks like you were right
to absorb Piccolo-san as well.
I'm going to kill you. That's for sure.
Before you do... I'll kill you!
U-Um... Green-faced Kami-sama?
C-Could you see that just now?
Just now? You mean the fight just now?
Then they were fighting? For you
to be able to see movement that fast,
you really are Kami-sama, aren't you?
Y-Yes. I am being allowed to
serve as such for the time being.
I-I apologize for not saying so before,
but I am the world champion
of combat sports, Mister Satan.
Pleased to meet you.
Ah, it is I who am pleased to meet you.
Hmph. It appears you still aren't
putting out enough power to kill me.
Perhaps you first wish to test my abilities?
That's what I would expect
from this being Piccolo-san.
You've seen right through me, then?
This is going to be hard.
In that case, it's about
time I got down to business!
Come on!
So, what comes next?
Gohan-san! Behind you!
Gohan, tough it out!
Honorable ancestor! Can Gohan-san
really win against Boo? What do you think?
I don't know.
H-How irresponsible!
G-Gohan-san's ki has
disappeared! Th-That can't be!
Have you been beaten, Gohan?
This is pretty bad, huh?
What's the matter? Are you trying
to buy time by hiding yourself there,
while you hold your ki?
Which would mean that
you've realized at least this much–
that there's no way you
can stand up to me like this!
Having obtained Piccolo's
brains and Super Gotenks' power,
Majin Boo has been reborn!
What will become of Gohan's fight
against this strongest, most evil of enemies?
We'll see!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Damn it, even as powered-up
as Gohan has become,
it's still a one-sided beatdown!
Can't something be done?!
I had not taken this into account.
Okay then, Goku, you go and help him!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"For the Sake Of the Entire Universe...
Return to Life, Son Goku."
Father can come back to life,
using the Grand Kaioshin's life.
"Next time"
"For the Sake Of the Entire Universe...
Return to Life, Son Goku"