The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
During the fourth match
of the Tenkaichi Tournament,
between Kibit and Son Gohan,
Yamu and Spopovitch suddenly force
their way in and steal Gohan's energy,
and then head off toward Madoshi Babidi.
Goku and the others join
Kaioshin in following after them.
It's Babidi!
Dabura's together with him!
Your use to me...
...has now passed.
Madoshi Babidi at last reveals himself,
as well as the King of the
World of Darkness, Dabura.
"The Awaiting Trap!!
A Challenge from the Demon Realm."
That was so pathetic!
That last look on Yamu
and Spopovitch's faces!
Indeed, watching that is
one of my little pleasures.
We will be able to see many
more of those faces here on Earth.
You're right!
How awful!
How could they?
That's how he...
...how Madoshi Babidi works.
Babidi takes the strongest warriors
from all over, brings them together...
and uses his magic to make them obey him.
Once they're no longer useful to him,
he disposes of them like trash.
He intends on gathering the energy
to revive the sealed-up
Majin Boo the in same way.
Now then, Dabura...
Yes?
Just as I expected,
it seems Yamu and friend brought
plenty of grubs along with them...
...along with Kaioshin, who
so long ago killed my father.
They seem to think that
they are hiding from us.
In all... seven of them...
Even if we can't make use of
Kaioshin and Kibit's energy,
three of them appear to
have the wonderful energy
necessary for Majin Boo's revival.
I'd say so. Even with just those three,
we can probably obtain
more than enough energy.
To think that Majin Boo's
revival would come so quickly!
Lure the three of them
inside the spaceship, okay?
That's the surest way to
draw their energy from them.
Right. However, Kaioshin is
not likely to let that happen.
Polish off all but those three.
Then hurry back inside the ship.
I think those three will fly off the
handle and are sure to follow you inside.
I see. That is my role, then?
That's it. Don't polish off Kaioshin, okay?
He killed my father, after all.
Afterward, I'll kill him
slowly and surely myself.
I understand, Babidi-sama.
I will leave that pleasure for you.
Well, it's up to you now.
Right!
B-Babidi-sama! What about me?
Puipui, Dabura alone can
handle this. You come inside too.
I'll let you handle the first Stage.
Right!
Huh? They left Dabura alone and went inside!
Well, let's do this.
We've been found out!
Kibit!
Kibit-san!
Dammit!
Watch out!
Oh, no! Dabura's saliva is...
What?!
Why, you...!
Hey!
Wha...?
Kuririn-san!
Piccolo! Kuririn!
Piccolo!
What the hell's happening?
S-Stone...
Anyone who comes in contact
with Dabura's saliva turns to stone!
What?!
Piccolo!
You mustn't! You must not touch him!
Why not?!
If you touch them and somehow break them,
there will be no way to
return them to normal again.
It can't be! Damn you!
Damn you!
Go on home, now!
No one can defy Babidi-sama!
Ladies and gentlemen, please
quiet down! Please quiet down!
Until the situation becomes more clear,
the Tenkaichi Tournament
will stand in recess for now.
What are you doing?! Go!
Hurry and get it going!
Recess, huh? I wanted to
hurry up and have our match...
This is all your brother's fault!
He let himself be beaten
by those strange guys.
This isn't Big Brother's fault!
If it wasn't for that, the
matches would have continued.
Stop saying bad things about Big Brother!
Ow! Now you've done it, you...!
Ah, ouch!
What, what?!
What's the matter?
Are you all right, Mighty Mask-san?
Owwww...
Are you hurt?
No! I-I'm fine!
Snap out of it!
What about you! Hold still!
Ow! Watch where you're going!
I wonder if he's feeling okay...
Kuririn-san... Piccolo-san...
Kaioshin-sama, you just
said that if we broke them,
we couldn't return them
to normal, didn't you?
Well that must mean there's some way
to return them to normal, ain't there?
I-It's just...
...not unless Dabura were to die...
What now, that's a
simple enough way, ain't it?
Father, let's go! We are
going after all, aren't we?
We have to save Kuririn-san and Piccolo-san!
Naturally! Let's go!
Ah, wait just a moment!
We can't let ourselves
cater to the enemy's strategy!
Once we enter the enemy ship,
we play right into their hands!
We have to wait and
watch a little while longer!
I can't just leave Kuririn
and Piccolo like that!
Me either!
Sorry, man.
Just lingering around isn't
one of our stronger skills.
Of all the...!
All right, let's go!
Right!
They're here! They're here!
They really are simple fools, aren't they?!
They have entered our trap.
What's this? Where are we?
Sure is a tidy room.
There's a door over there.
Why don't we try breaking through it?
Yeah.
What's this? Kaioshin-sama,
you've come after all?
It's because you fellows are so reckless!
Once one enters this
ship, there is no leaving it!
At least not until we
defeat Babidi, I'm afraid.
Well, let's just defeat Babidi then.
Hmph! If we had to, we could
always destroy the whole ship.
You must not! Any strong
shock could awaken Majin Boo!
You are all taking Babidi
and Majin Boo too lightly!
Even though Majin Boo's
energy may be incomplete,
he should still have enough
destructive power to kill all of us
and destroy the Earth in a short time!
Now Kaioshin is here too? This is great!
You know, this really is a bleak room.
Babidi-sama... Babidi-sama...!
Oh, Puipui?
Yes. Isn't it just about time?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Well, take the energy from those
three and then come back down.
Right! Leave that to me!
Oh, I nearly forgot! We have
to inject this energy right away.
Come along, Dabura. We know how
this will turn out without watching.
R-Right!
Welcome! This is the first Stage.
First Stage?
What's that?
Babidi-sama is on the very bottom floor.
However, unless you pass
through the various Stages,
and defeat each of the warriors that
come out, you cannot proceed downward.
Your opponent for the first
Stage is me. Which means...
You guys are finished here!
Nah. I don't think that's going to happen!
Wh-What's this?!
This much energy in one session?!
We've collected nearly half of it all at once!
What's this?!
How many hundreds of people did
Yamu and Spopovitch gather this from?
Well, I did not ask them.
If they gathered this great
an energy in such a short time,
I guess I shouldn't have killed them.
Oh, it will be all right.
I think that with the energy being
collected from those three in Stage 1,
there will be nearly
enough to fill it up to the top.
If all goes well, Majin Boo's
revival can be realized within the day.
That is what we lured
those guys in here for, after all!
Let's see. You never know, Puipui may
have already taken care of all three of them.
Let's go, Dabura.
Let's see...
Huh? What, aren't they fighting yet?
Tie, go again! Tie, go again!
Tie, go again! Tie, go again! Tie, go again!
Wh-What are those guys up to?!
I did it!
Nice going, Vegeta!
All right then, I go first.
Uh, er...
You're thinking of fighting him alone?
Of course I am! Me by myself
is plenty against a guy like this!
Babidi-sama said to be careful
since you all have such strong energy,
but apparently, you're all just fools!
Are you sure it isn't this
Babidi guy that's the fool?
He didn't check things out very well,
and now he's going to
regret not realizin'...
...that the very strongest guys in the
universe were right here on Earth,
of all places.
Very strongest...?
You guys are the most full-fledged of fools!
We must not make light of the enemy!
Babidi only takes the strongest
warriors from the corners of the universe
and allies them to himself!
Hey, hey, it'll be okay, let's just
see about leaving this to Vegeta.
But...
There's no way you guys
are getting away from here!
And the damage you guys take will
be absorbed by this room as energy,
and directed into the ball
Majin Boo-sama is sealed in.
I'm relieved to hear that.
It means that as long
as we take no damage,
no energy will be taken, right?
That's right!
But unfortunately for you, that's impossible!
Not as long as I'm here!
What an unpleasant punk you are.
Enough talk. Let's get this overwith!
Bring it on!
This kid named Vegeta...
Vegeta-san...
The fight in the first Stage has finally begun.
Vegeta is quite sure of himself, however...
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
The first stage is underway! Huh?
Hu-uh? The room seems
different somehow. What's going on?
It was Babidi. Babidi
changed it with his magic,
to a place that benefits his fighter.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Don't Toy With Me!!
Vegeta's Breakthrough First Strike of Fury."
Vegeta-san's opponent is
so weak, it's making him angry.
"Next time"
"Don't Toy With Me!!
Vegeta's Breakthrough First Strike of Fury"