The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Was Vegeta's death to no end?
Accompanied by Majin Boo,
boasting his fearsome power,
the time that Madoshi Babidi
begins to unfold his plans for revenge
has drawn ever closer.
Piccolo and Kuririn took the
only remaining hope for Earth,
Trunks and Goten, to seek
shelter at Kami's Palace,
where Dende and Popo were waiting for them.
Elsewhere, having been taken by
surprise and knocked out by Vegeta,
Goku finally regains consciousness.
I can feel Majin Boo's ki,
but Vegeta's ki ain't there!
Don't tell me he got beaten! Not him!
I can't feel Gohan's ki either.
Piccolo and Kuririn are alive.
They must have been returned
from stone back to normal.
Those two might know what's been going on!
Th-That ki! It's...!
Yo!
Goku! Then you survived?!
"Enormous Hope!! A New Finishing
Technique for the Little Squirts."
...and that's how it is.
How can it be?
To think that Gohan, Kaioshin-sama,
and even Vegeta could get beaten!
Majin Boo's strength is, as feared by
Kaioshin-sama, beyond our imaginations.
If we leave him alone like this,
then there's really no mistaking it–
never mind Earthlings, every living
being in the universe will be wiped out.
But Goku, your having survived is the one
fortunate thing among all this misfortune.
Er, you have the halo there,
so you haven't really survived,
but I mean you haven't
died–no, that's not right,
you're dead, but alive...
Aaugh! This is getting me all mixed up!
Goku, you're the only one
that can defeat Majin Boo.
You can only stay in this
world for one day, right Goku?
There's still a little bit
of time remaining, and so,
you can manage something!
Kuririn...
I'll say this plainly.
It's no use. I can't beat him.
Th-That can't be!
I can't beat Majin Boo.
G-Goku?!
There wasn't hardly any difference
in power between me and Vegeta.
Vegeta gave all he had, yet
Majin Boo is still perfectly fine, right?
Sorry, but no matter what I do, I can't win.
So that's it? Not even Goku can help, huh?
I guess not...
Damn! If either Vegeta or Gohan had survived,
there might still be something we could do...
No, no matter how many of us
gang up, it probably would do no good.
Majin Boo isn't at such a level as that.
Naw, that ain't it. We could use Fusion.
W-What's this "Few–" whatever business?
Fusion!
Fusion... Merging together, right?!
You know about it, Dende?
Yes! I've never seen it, but when
I was on Planet Namek, I heard about it.
It's the specialty technique
of the Metamorans, they said.
That's it! I had one of the Metamorans
I met in the Other World teach it to me.
What kind of technique is it?
It's a unification technique
that can be used only if
the powers and body sizes
of two people are pretty close.
Unification technique?
In other words, by having
two people unite into one,
they become a new individual,
with awesome powers that neither
one of them could have on their own!
Yeah?
Come to mention it, Piccolo-san and Nail-san
also underwent a form
of merging, didn't you?
Ours was an assimilation.
Impossible... How can this be?
What incredible power!
What an unbelievably
fearsome power this is!
Is this what uniting with someone is like?!
I will win! Regardless of the
opponent, I cannot lose now!
I have now obtained the ultimate power!
Assimilation is certainly awesome,
but this Fusion thing
is even more awesome!
The Metamorans who taught me, right?
They were both weak, gentle little guys,
but once they used their Fusion,
they transformed into
quite a formidable warrior!
I've got a good understanding of it.
After all, in the case of Nail and me,
just by assimilating, we had quite a power up.
If either Vegeta or Gohan were alive,
you could have done this Fusion,
become some extraordinary warrior,
and fought against Majin Boo, right?!
Yeah. Of course, it took me
about a week to learn the technique.
Even supposing Vegeta
or Gohan had survived,
it would probably have been
impossible to teach it to them.
I can't stay in this world
more than a day, and all.
On top of that, I've been taught the
technique, but I've never tried it out.
There ain't anyone about the
same as me in the Other World.
In any case, it would've been impossible.
No, it's not impossible!
Kuririn, what do you mean?
Goku, you'll be returned to the
Other Side pretty soon, right?
But the dead Gohan and Vegeta
will be there too, won't they?
You can still do this Fusion, can't you?
Hey, yeah! There is that way!
No, it won't work.
Goku cannot come to this world once more,
even if he were to accomplish Fusion.
Two sleeping inside, Goten and Trunks,
power and size about identical.
Can they do Fusion?
It's too much for them, right?
No... Nice work, Mister Popo!
That's the way! There is that way!
Goku-san!
Way to go, way to go, Mister Popo! You did it!
But Goku, do you have time?
Yeah. I'll teach Fusion to the
half-pints up to the last minute,
but just that ain't going to be enough time.
Piccolo, why don't you take
over training them afterward?
You got it.
Yea! We've got hope now!
Those two pipsqueaks just
might be able to pull this off!
However...
It will take quite a bit of time for Trunks
and Goten to master this Fusion thing.
During that time, a
considerable number of people
will become casualties of Majin Boo.
They might all even be exterminated–
no, the whole Earth
could possibly be destroyed.
We'll have to risk it.
Whatever happens, we have to
be prepared to endure anything
until the pee-wees master Fusion.
Piccolo, even if they are exterminated,
as long as you guys have the Dragon
Balls, you can return things to normal.
That's right, huh?
There's still some hope remaining!
H-Hey! Majin Boo!
B-Boo! W-Watch out!
Stop!
B-Boo! Do something! Do you
want to get sealed up again?!
–-What's that?
–Some event, probably.
Majin Boo, enough already!
Bulma, let's hurry and call forth Shen Long!
Say, is this really for real?
Such a cute face, yet she's so skeptical, huh?
Videl-san, keep those
eyes peeled wide and watch!
This is somethin' you won't be seein' on TV!
But it's unbelievable that a
dragon can come out of those balls!
Bulma, you know the incantation
to call out Shen Long, right?
Of course! We're not going
to goof up the way Freeza did!
Bulma, yell that spell well!
Oh, dear!
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Old man!
This is no time to be making poor jokes!
Of all the...!
There's an incantation, huh? I guess that fits...
Bulma, hurry and summon
Shen Long so we can bring back to life
all the spectators killed by Vegeta.
I know.
Come forth, Shen Long,
and grant me my wish!
All right, in any case,
I'm going to go get everyone.
What? It's suddenly gotten dark!
I-It's...!
Shen Long is coming out? W-Why?!
Bulma-san is the one who
gathered the Dragon Balls, right?
She must not know the situation yet!
Why would she call up Shen Long?
That's it! Vegeta killed a bunch of
people at the tournament grounds!
She's trying to bring them back to life!
Th-This is bad! If all three wishes get granted,
it will be another year before
any more wishes are possible!
Okay, I'll go right away and stop them.
Damn, Bulma and the others'
ki are hard to search out...
Y-You're kidding!
W-What's that?!
Unreal!
I shall grant thee any three wishes.
A-Am I dreaming?!
Speak thy wishes now!
Um, how shall I word this...?
Such a hassle! Bring back to
life everyone that died today!
Oh, and leave out the bad guys!
That should do it, right?
Thank you!
Bring back those people who have died?
Is that really possible?
All right, I have granted the first wish.
We're not dead, huh?!
Banzai! We're back alive!
Here it is!
I shall now hear your second wish.
Aw, hell! I wasn't in time!
–Son-kun!
–Goku!
Goku-sa, where have you been?!
Where's Gohan?! Where's Goten?!
Chichi, there ain't time
for this! I'll tell you later.
Dende, can you hear me?
Yes.
I was a bit late.
Shen Long has already granted a
wish, but just one. What should I do?
I-Is that so?
In that case, please tell him the
other two wishes are all right for now.
If there's only been one, then we
can use him again in four months.
So that's it, got it!
Oh, and one other thing!
Everyone's gathered together here,
so tell Kuririn for me that
I'll bring everyone there.
Yes, understood.
Okay!
Shen Long! That's all the wishes
this time around! Thank you!
We'll be counting on you next time!
Well then, farewell.
W-What is it, Goku?!
What the hell is going on now?
I-I'm sure I'm supposed to
have been killed by Dabura...
Well, let's do this.
H-Have I come back to life? Unbelievable...
Where is Kaioshin-sama?!
Gohan-san...
...and that's it. Everybody, you're
coming with me now to Kami's palace,
where Kuririn and the
others are waiting for us.
Got it. In another four months,
I'll be sure to find the
seven Dragon Balls again!
Yeah, we're counting on it!
Okay, everybody, grab onto me.
I'm going to Instantaneously Move!
T-To think this world existed!
I'm not dreaming, huh?
Papa, Mama, what are you doing?
Hurry and join hands.
We can't bear to leave our animals
behind, so we're going to remain here.
W-What are you saying?
Surely seeking shelter for yourselves is
more important than your pets right now!
Right, Mama?
Bulma, if Mama is killed by this Majin Boo,
you can just bring us back
to life with the Dragon Balls.
Mama is staying with Papa.
Y-You can't be...
Son-kun...?
Bulma, if the worst happens, you
have to search for the Dragon Balls.
Huh? Videl-san, aren't you goin'?
Yes, I'm going! I'm going!
All right! Everybody, let's go!
So, let's go give our pet-chan s some food.
W-What was that?!
No sooner am I thinking it just
got dark than it's light out again!
Well, I guess none of that matters!
Majin Boo, shall we begin?
Are Babidi's plans for
revenge about to get underway?
What is the fate of the Earth?
The faint remaining stars of hope,
Trunks and Goten, still continue to sleep...
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Huh? I'm hearing something!
That voice–it's Babidi!
People of the earth,
I'm looking for some people
who put me through a
rather disagreeable time earlier.
If they don't come forward,
it will mean big trouble for the earth!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Goten and Trunks–
The World's Most Wanted."
Babidi, I'll make sure you pay for this!
"Next time"
"Goten and Trunks–
The World's Most Wanted"