Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
The terrifying, devilish hand of Garlic Jr.
has taken over the Throne of Kami...
...by turning all living
things on earth into Demons,
which even reached Piccolo and Kuririn!
But then, Piccolo...
Wait. Didn't I say I would
strike the finishing blow?
So you did.
Kuririn!
"Can't Wait Until Morning!! Kami-sama
Determines a Suicidal Course of Action."
You–how?!
You really expected me to do as you wanted?
Yeah, but you could have
pulled your punches a little.
I mean, poor Gohan!
He's trained hard enough that our level
of attack wouldn't have worn him out.
Kami-sama...
Piccolo-san...
There's no way I'm going
to be beaten by just that.
In which case,
I wish you had told us
earlier what you were up to.
Listen closely, Kuririn.
I'm going to rough up Gohan some more.
Garlic wants to finish Gohan off for himself.
As such, he's certain to
muscle his way in between us.
Then, when he lets his guard down,
we'll get the bottle that Kami is in.
And so, we were able to get through
this without creating any painful memories.
You know, Kuririn-san and Piccolo-san,
your acting was pretty good.
I was completely fooled.
With Kami being held prisoner,
this was the only way we could
have gotten close enough to that punk.
I'm sorry, Piccolo,
to have made you go
through all that trouble for me.
Don't misunderstand!
I didn't do all of this for you!
It's because with you in captivity,
I couldn't generate the power I would need.
P-Piccolo...
What are you dawdling around for?
Leave them to us, and
go get the Ultra Holy Water!
You got it.
Garlic Jr.! Your lust for power ends here!
I'm going to send you back into
that world of darkness once again!
Well, bring it on!
Even if you have managed
to obtain the Ultra Holy Water,
there's no way that you'll
be able to use it in time.
What?
Even if you unseal the Ultra Holy Water here,
how many hours do you suppose it
would take for it to cover the whole world?
Before it does, the sun will have risen,
and you will no longer be
able to counteract the Aquamist!
No matter what you do, you're out of time!
Your plan appears to have failed as well.
All that remains is for
me to create an ideal world,
filled with disaster and suffering.
The world, as I wish it to be!
D-Dammit!
Is... there nothing we... can do?
Kami-sama...
We've come this far. We'll be all right.
What's wrong with those people?
Why did they suddenly become so violent?
It's because of that black fog. I saw it.
In any case, I still have my eternal life!
No matter how you may struggle,
this world, filled to
overflowing with the Demon Clan,
will continue as I wish through eternity!
Piccolo-san...
It's okay, Kami-sama.
There is way to spread
Ultra Holy Water in short time.
What?
If use seven currents that cover whole world,
spreading Ultra Holy Water easy.
Really, Mister Popo?!
Really. There is hole at the bottom of
Heavenly Realm where currents gather.
Just pour Ultra Holy Water there.
Then we'll go there now!
But Kami-sama, there is great danger.
At bottom of Heavenly Realm is Shinsenkai.
Shinsenkai?
Yes, Shinsenkai. Place where
graves of former Kami are.
Very, very holy place.
If Kami-sama goes there,
give up being Kami-sama.
Perhaps even have spirit pulled out and die.
Is that so?
Kami-sama...
I do not care. Come, Mister Popo.
All of this is my responsibility.
U-Understood.
Popo guide you.
I'm counting on it.
I won't allow it!
Kami-sama!
You'll have to deal with me!
Piccolo!
Kami! Hurry and go! Go!!
Right! I'll leave this to you!
How long do you guys intend
to swear allegiance to Freeza?
Impossible! To be defeated by a single Saiyan!
It's laughable that you
would seek my life at your level.
This is what you get for
underestimating a Saiyan.
It's true for you as it was true for Freeza.
Kakarrot! Where are you?!
See you in hell!
Kienzan!
Don't toy with me!
Now to finish you!
K-Kuririn-san!
Take this!
Kuririn-san!
What's the matter? Are you finished already?
Piccolo! You and Kami are
of one heart and one body!
If Kami dies, you die as well, yes?
So whether he has his spirit taken
from him and dies in the Shinsenkai first,
or you lose your life to me first,
either way there's no possibility
of you surviving, is there?
Unfortunately for you,
I'm not as weak as you are.
I am not going to die!
What?!
Like I said before, you're
going to regret having eternal life!
Mister Popo, aren't we to the Shinsenkai yet?
L-Little farther.
Hmm?
Haven't you realized it yet?
That red star!
That is the homeworld of the Demon Clan,
which has revived me and
given me such great power!
The Makyo World!
It has returned near to Earth after 5,000 years!
And when it draws near,
the power of we, the Demon Clan,
increases many times over!
So then, why don't I show
you my true power now?!
W-What's that?! Garlic Jr.'s
ki has suddenly risen sharply!
This is bad! Gohan,
Kuririn, get out of here, now!
W-What?!
It's up to you, Popo!
Kami-sama! It's open!
He didn't have to do all that!
Piccolo-san!
Gohan, stay sharp!
You certainly did us in
pretty well earlier, little ones.
But we've crawled back out
of hell to have our revenge!
Now with many times
the power we had before.
You're...
Pitted against the terrifying power-up
afforded Garlic Jr. by the Makyo World,
Piccolo and the others
face their greatest danger!
And will Kami and Popo...
...be able to distribute the Ultra Holy Water
around the world in the time that remains?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Piccolo's body is fading out!
Oh, no! Kami-sama is about to have his spirit
pulled out of him in the Shinsenkai!
That's why Piccolo-san is...!
Between you and Kami,
which of you will be the first to die?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"A Battle of Extreme Measures!!
Kami-sama Breaks the Covenant."
The way things are going,
Garlic is going to get his way!
"Next time"
"A Battle of Extreme Measures!!
Kami-sama Breaks the Covenant"