Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Piccolo is resurrected!
In order to battle Freeza, Piccolo has at
last descended upon his home world of Namek.
Now, speak forth thy third wish!
Make me immortally young!
Do you want to be killed by Freeza?
However, the Grand Elder's
life had reached its end,
and with the third wish unfulfilled,
"Super Shen Long" disappeared.
Moreover, in the worst
of all possible situations...
You have really done it now, gentlemen.
You have done an outstanding job of
shattering my dreams of eternal youth.
"Birth of the Mightiest Warrior?
Nail and Piccolo Merge."
There are no readings
for the Ginyu Special Corps.
Are you the ones who killed them?
It is unfortunate,
that the Dragon Balls have turned to
stone just before I could have used them...
Unfortunate for Vegeta-san, to be
sure, but perhaps more so for myself.
This is the first time anyone has been stupid
enough to make this big a fool out of me.
I did not expect things
to come to such a result.
You're going to pay!
You're going to pay for this, you puny worms!!!
I'm going to kill you all an inch at a time!!
There's no escape for you! Say your prayers!
So you finally show your true nature.
Do your worst!
If you think I'm going to be that
easy to defeat, you're greatly mistaken!
Of all the things you might have said...
Apparently, you have
forgotten how terrifying I really am.
Let me refresh your memory!
Impossible!
I didn't think he'd be this awful!
That enormous ki is getting a lot larger.
This Freeza is about to make
his move against the others.
I feel a faint ki. No, it couldn't be Gohan!
A Namekian, the spitting image of myself.
You're near death.
You must be the... Namekian
the Earthlings spoke of.
So, their wish has been granted. Good.
You seem to have all the facts.
Then you must also know that I'm
rushing to help those brats out right now.
You'll excuse me for leaving you here to die.
Surprising...
I don't know what discipline you've used,
but you've managed to gain incredible power.
And yet, it's such a pity...
If you had returned as a
single, complete Namekian,
you might have been able to beat Freeza.
You're saying that if I had reunited with Kami
and become a single individual again,
only then would I be able
to overcome Freeza's power?
That's right. I may have been
utterly overwhelmed by Freeza,
but I know his powers quite well.
No use arguing over it now.
For that matter, I have no intention
of ever reuniting with that guy.
Unite with me.
I am the... last Warrior-Type
Namekian left on my world.
What? With you?
That's right.
Your current power will be
increased several times over.
Thanks for the offer,
but I'd rather be who I am.
I don't want to combine
my individuality with yours.
Such a proud fellow...
Hurry... There's... no time.
I am about to die.
Quickly, place your hand on my body.
Do not worry.
Your individuality will
be yours. I will be yours.
I offer no more than this opportunity.
You wouldn't lie to me, would you?
If that's what you think,
you can go on ahead and get killed by Freeza.
All right.
Fine, then. I'll try you out.
But if I don't like what
happens, I'll drive you out again.
What a thing to say,
while I'm offering such a wonderful
present to you of my own good will.
I'm in a hurry.
If we're going to do this, let's get it over.
Be sure... you kill... Freeza.
I don't need you to tell me.
If I can, I'll do it for my own sake.
Impossible... How can this be?
What incredible power!
What an unbelievably fearsome power this is!
Is this what uniting with someone is like?!
I will win!
Regardless of the opponent, I cannot lose now!
I have now obtained the ultimate power!
Gohan! At this rate,
Vegeta will be beaten in no time.
We have to act now. It's our only chance!
Right!
Kuririn-san!
Su-Such a ki! There's no way we can win!
Of course not.
Did you think that only three
ants could defeat a whole dinosaur?
We can win!
If the three of us fight together,
we'll find a way to beat you.
What's that? You can beat me?
That's right.
That's the last thing I expected you to say.
Apparently, not even the great
Freeza realizes that these two guy's
battle powers have been rapidly increasing.
Especially the shorter one,
he's sitting on a power reserve
that not even he is fully aware of.
And as for me,
I'm in the process of becoming
the Super Saiyan you've always feared.
You brag quite well, what
with that talk of Super Saiyans.
You irritating rat!
What?!
What's this?
So, apparently you aren't just talk, are you?
He's right...
If the three of us fight together,
there's a definite chance
of us making it through.
He's certainly very powerful,
but our power has risen too.
That's right, ever since Vegeta has come here,
he's managed to keep overcoming
his limits and grow stronger.
So, why is Freeza still so calm?
Transform yourself, Freeza!
–Transform?
He can transform?
Let's get right to it.
Why don't you transform
and show us your true self?
So, you knew about that, did you?
How did you come to find out?
That punk Zarbon let it slip.
What are you talking about?
Among the universe's races,
there is a very small
number that have the odd ability
of changing their forms when needed–
whether for camouflage,
or to conserve energy
consumption when it's unnecessary.
In my case, the reason is different.
I have so much power, it's
difficult for me to control it otherwise.
What was that?
Don't let him scare you.
He's bluffing, he won't change all that much.
Is that so?
Fine, then. If you want to
die that badly, I'll show you.
Watch very carefully.
This is not something you'll see every day.
When I attacked the planet
Vegeta, home to the Saiyans,
you realize there was utterly
no reason for me to transform.
Vegeta-san, your father,
the king of Planet Vegeta,
was none too spectacular a warrior, you know.
Don't flatter yourself too much about that.
I had overcome the king's
power way back when I was still little.
Then the Saiyan's planet was destroyed by him?
Now then, marvel at this!
At last, Freeza begins to change.
However, how much terror will this account for?
And will Piccolo and Goku
arrive in time for this terrific battle?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
What's this? The strength of
Freeza's ki increased many times over.
I'd guess that you never imagined
I could become this powerful.
Now then, which one of
you should I show to Hell first?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"A Nightmare Super-Transformation!!
Freeza's Battle Power of One Million."
Vegeta-san, what happened to those
high spirits you were in a moment ago?
"Next time"
"A Nightmare Super-Transformation!!
Freeza's Battle Power of One Million"