The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
With Videl's help, the Great Saiyaman
rescued a baby monster from Musuka.
Don't worry, Chibi.
Your father is just knocked out.
You can't hide it any longer.
The true identity of the Great Saiyaman...
...is you, Son Gohan-kun!
At last, Videl had seen through to the true
identity of the Great Saiyaman–Gohan!
He was then pressured into
entering the Tenkaichi Tournament.
"Goku Returning to Life!?
Entry into the Tenkaichi Tournament!!"
And so, the airplane that was
experiencing engine trouble
safely landed at Satan Airport.
Today, once again, the Great Saiyaman
has saved many precious lives.
Great Saiyaman, can we have a statement?
–Please!
Saiyaman-san, what do you
think about the fuss being made
about you being the hero
to succeed Mister Satan?
Any thoughts concerning your exploits?
Please, any statement at all!
I guess I have no choice, huh?
From thievery to killing to hijacking,
from small things to big things,
if it is evil, I cannot let it stand!
Knight of love and justice, the Great Saiyaman!
That's who I am!
That's just too nerdy.
You're participating in the
upcoming Tenkaichi Tournament, huh?
Yes.
So, what made you decide to enter?
Well, actually, one of my classmates
is Mister Satan-san's daughter...
Huh? Mister Satan?
Mister Satan is that guy
who was skittering about
during the fight with Cell, right?
The combat sports world champion?
Wow, so his daughter is one of your classmates.
Yeah, but even so, she's a pretty good girl.
Like me, she's the type that
can't leave bad guys alone.
But my transformation was exposed
by her, because of my voice and scars.
And so, she said that if I don't
enter the Tenkaichi Tournament,
she would reveal my true identity.
That really is unsightly, Gohan-san.
You don't need to wear that thing.
You're kind of clumsy when it
comes to that sort of thing, huh?
You may appear to be flying straight,
but you've still got that blood
you've inherited from your father.
So, now what?
Do you want me to refit the
helmet so it changes your voice?
No, it's not that. Apparently,
you can't wear helmets, protectors,
or that sort of equipment
at the Tenkaichi Tournament.
So I was wondering if there was something
that could take the place of this helmet.
So you're saying that you can't wear anything
that would greatly decrease any damage done?
That's no big deal, right?
In short, so long as no one
finds out that it's you, Gohan-kun,
that's all you need, right?
I wonder if she means some new helmet.
Indeed! I just needed to do
something as simple as this!
What do you think,
Trunks-kun? Pretty cool, huh?
No comment.
I'm glad I didn't ask her to make me one.
Then again, no matter how much you hold back,
it's going to be dull, knowing
that you're a shoe-in to win, huh?
I wouldn't be too sure of that.
This whatever-you-called-it
tournament–if you're entering, then I am too.
Back then, there was a huge
difference between our powers.
But what about now?
While you've been
jubilating over your peacetime,
I've been continuing my training.
Yeah. This guy doesn't do a lick of work.
Just like your father.
I wonder, don't Saiyans ever work?
Awesome! Father and
Gohan-san are going to fight?!
I'm entering, too!
Gohan!
F-Father...? That's Father's voice!
Son-kun?
Kakarrot...?
Father! It's you, isn't it?
That's right. It's been a
long time, huh everyone?
Have you been well, Father?
Who is it?
Yeah. Well, if you can call
this doing well, then I guess so.
I am dead, and all.
Really?! You're really going to be able
to come to the Tenkaichi Tournament?!
Yeah! If I ask Uranai Baba,
I can come back for one day.
I'm going to make that day, the
day of the Tenkaichi Tournament.
Gohan and Vegeta, you're entering, right?
I'm entering too!
Hooray! Banzai!
Who is it?
I'll be looking forward to this, Kakarrot.
Come prepared. I've improved considerably.
So have I, Vegeta. Bye now.
I'll see you at the Tenkaichi Tournament.
Great! This is starting to get interesting!
Great news, huh Gohan-kun?
You'll have to hurry and
tell your mother, Goten-kun,
and Kuririn and the others.
Right!
So, who was that?
That's right! Vegeta-san, you'll
have to wear a costume like this,
so your identity doesn't get revealed.
Y-You expect me to wear that?!
I don't particularly care if anyone does find out!
Okay, see you at the Tenkaichi Tournament!
I'm on my way to go tell everyone else!
Tell everyone I said hello!
Bye-bye!
I wonder whose voice that was earlier.
Father is coming back! He's coming back!
I'll be able to see him after all this time!
W-Whuzzat?
Hold it!
Who cares? Let her have it!
Get her! Get her! Get her!
Stop!
Look, Misters, you can't
go around doing bad things.
Yow-ow-ow-ow-ow...
W-Who are you?
Liberator of those who are captive...
helper of the weak and router of evil...
the warrior of justice... Great Saiya–
Yow-ow-ow-ow!
Hey, you! What did you do that for?!
Everything was going so well!
That take was academy award-winning material!
Cut! Cut! Cut!
You there! We can't have you just
jumping in front of the camera like that!
You mean.... me?
Of course I do! Who else could I mean?!
For crying out loud, you're not even a child,
and yet you're running around
pretending to be the Great Saiyaman?!
Pretending?
We've got no choice! Let's take it from the top!
Right.
What if we speed the timing
up just a little bit this time?
W-W-What?
Scene 153! Great Saiyaman's flying action!
Ah, this is a surprise.
I never expected that they'd be
shooting a Great Saiyaman movie.
Ready...!
No!!
I-I can't do this! Let me down!
I'm afraid of heights!
W-What do we do, Director?
W-What do we do?
We're already behind schedule as it is.
We've got to finish shooting
this scene today, no matter what!
What a pathetic Great Saiyaman!
What?
I mean, I was just thinking, if the
real Great Saiyaman were to see this,
that's probably what he'd say.
That's it...!
Director, if we were to use him...
What? Him?
We won't have to go to any trouble
dressing him up, for one thing.
W-Who would have ever thought
things would turn out like this?
Okay then, we're going
with the posturing scene!
Are you ready to pose?!
Y-Yes!
Scene 312, Ready...!
From thievery to killing to hijacking,
if it is evil, I cannot let it stand!
Cut!
No, no, no, no, no, no!
There's no way a hero of justice
would strike such embarrassing poses, is there?!
But...
Let's do this once again!
Warrior of love, justice, and freedom, Great–
Cut!
Once again!
Helper of the weak, router of evil...!
No!
Shrieks call out to me...!
No, no, no!
Officially sanctioned helmet wearer...!
No!
Hater of sins, not of sinners...!
The G in "Great" stands for "Good"...!
Stop it! Stop it! Stop it!
I can't take this anymore! You are
nothing at all like the Great Saiyaman!
B-But this is really how...
Shut up! Criminy, forget
the transformation scene,
get ready to do your flying!
R-Right!
Oh, no! Is it already this late?!
I have to go tell everyone about Father.
All right, pause! Now, fly from there!
What are you so nervous about?!
There's no danger!
Fly yourself all-out from there! Ready?!
Yes!
All right, fly now!
I have to hurry this up a little.
Great, great! That's the way!
All right, cut, cut!
I'm out of time now, so you'll have to excuse me!
Y-You don't suppose that was the real...
...G-Great Saiyaman...?
Goku, too?! Really?!
This is Kuririn-san, who gave up fighting,
and also stopped shaving his head.
It's been a long time
since we've seen Goku, huh?
The Tenkaichi Tournament, eh?
Maybe I'll enter, too.
Let's enter together!
But then, if Goku and Vegeta are
entering, there's no way I can win.
Besides, what would my wife say?
There, there.
You really ought to enter!
I hear that there are prizes
all the way to fifth place!
How much prize money will there be?
Let's see...
first place is 10 million zenie,
2nd place is 5 million,
3rd place is 3 million, 4th place is
2 million, and 5th place is 1 million.
Enter yourself, Kuririn! I'm coming too!
1 million zenie! 1 million zenie!
Right? Enter, Kuririn!
Daddy, enter, enter!
Y-You're right. I guess I will enter!
I wonder if I should.
Hey, don't tell Piccolo.
The chances of me getting as far
as 5th place will be lower if you do.
Oh, I couldn't do that.
By the way, what are you wearing
that ridiculous, geeky outfit for?
What are you saying?! This is cool!
Kuririn-san, your fashion sense has grown dull.
Bye!
Is that so? That does indeed sound interesting.
Doesn't it?
All right, I think I'll enter.
Oh, good luck. Popo cheer for you.
Dende, what about you?
No, I'm not entering.
I'm not the fighting type of Namekian, after all.
By the way, Gohan, what the
hell is with that strange getup?
Not you too, Piccolo-san!
Don't you think this is cool?
I-I can't tell.
Popo either.
I don't know where
Tenshinhan-san and company are...
and I think Bulma-san
will contact Yamucha-san...
All that leaves is Mother and Goten.
I'll bet that Mother will be thrilled
that Father is coming back for one day!
And this will be the first time
Goten ever sees his father, huh?
Still, I wonder if Mother will allow me
to participate in the Tenkaichi Tournament.
For my part, as long as I'm
going to enter, I'd like to win.
For that to happen, I think I'll be in trouble
unless I take a break from school and train hard,
since I've gotten so soft.
Goku-sa's comin' back from the Next
World for the Tenkaichi Tournament?!
Why didn't you tell me this big surprise sooner?!
Terrific!
Goten! You'll be able to see your pa for one day!
This is too much! I'm the
only one who's gotten older.
You don't get any older in the Next World, right?
I should have gone to a beauty salon!
Ah, how many years has
it been? Seven years, is it?
Ah, this is too much!
Really, he's comin' home, huh?
Um, Mother, I wonder if I could
enter as well–the Tenkaichi Tournament?
I'll get myself all gussied up–eh?
I-If I win, we can get 10 million zenie.
5 million for 2nd place.
10-10 million zenie?!
Enter yourself, Gohan-chan!
Together with Goku-sa,
you two could get
15 million zenie in prize money!
N-Not exactly, it's still not
definite that we would win.
No way! It's a sure thing that one of you will win!
B-But for me to do this,
I'd like to take a short
break from school to train...
Who cares?! Train!
You can always make it up later!
Wow, this is a blessin' from heaven!
Pa's fortune is runnin' out,
and I was worryin' about
what we were goin' to do!
Goten, will you help Big Brother
out in his training starting tomorrow?
Uh-huh.
I think for now, I'll turn Super Saiyan.
All right, shall we get started?
Due to unexpected circumstances,
Gohan has come to enter
the Tenkaichi Tournament.
Having established that his
long-time friends will participate as well,
his spirits have been lifted.
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Whoo! Goten, you can turn Super Saiyan?
As small as you are, that's awesome!
Goten, don't go turnin' into
that in front of other people!
They'll think you're a delinquent!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Even Gohan is Surprised!
Goten's Explosion of Power."
Uh-oh! If I just sit around, the
little guys are going to pass me up!
"Next time"
"Even Gohan is Surprised!
Goten's Explosion of Power"