The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
According to Piccolo's strategy,
Majin Boo was sealed up
inside the alternate dimensional
space of the Room of Spirit and Time.
My candy is gone!! I can't stand this!!
I choose choco!
Elsewhere, Gotenks had transformed
into the even fiercer Super Gotenks 3,
and escaped from the Room of Spirit and Time!
Why, you! What have you done
with the group that was here?!
They're right here.
Now I'm completely mad!!
"Going Too Far!? Boo-Boo Volleyball."
You'll pay for this, Majin Boo!
Th-The temple...!
The temple...
You're doing pretty good. I'm glad
I waited. It's fun fighting with you.
Ha! Smart off now, while you still can!
Dammit!
Why, you...!
Go-Go-Go-Go-Go-Go–
Gotenks!
G-Gotenks...
Brain Crush Hammer!!
I did it! I did it!
Finish Flash!!
All right!
Way to go, Gotenks!
Oh, awesome, awesome! The tykes
are sure giving it to him, ain't they?
Whoa, nice one, nice one!
Nice one, little guys! Get him! Get him!
Yeah, way to go, way to go!
F-Father, what's happening on Earth?
It's incredible! Goten and
Trunks have undergone Fusion,
and have become Super Saiyan 3, see?
They've got unbelievable power! Really!
Gohan...
You've just pushed us back a little bit more.
Don't get distracted. The more you get
distracted, the more time this will take.
You can't mean it...!
Drive all idle thoughts out and
concentrate yourself. Concentrate!
This manga is so funny!
It's not fair, just me...!
Oh! Awesome, awesome!
They really do have a gift for this!
In just a short amount of time,
they were able to perform both
Fusion and Super Saiyan 3, after all!
Say, Kaioshin-sama, do you think
there's a chance that they have a chance?
Goku-san! You must not look down on
Majin Boo. This is not the depth of Boo's power!
R-Really? Hang in there, Goten and Trunks!
H-Help...!
Dammit, now you've done it!
All right, watch this!
Super Balloon Bomber!!
Ghosts! Ghosts! How scary, how scary!
The ghosts have powered up as well!
They're good and scary now!
Okay! Go! Go!
That did it!
Nothing to it, Majin Boo!
Now I'm mad!!
Oh! Boo is angry! He's angry!
He's coming, he's coming!
Hey! Over here! Over here!
Not even Boo can keep up with my speed!
Where is he now?
I'm here!
Bye-bye.
Don't! Stop! Come on!
Stop it!!
Th-The temple...!
Th-The temple!
The temple...
You okay, Piccolo-san?
Th-The temple...!
He's here, he's here!
What in the world happened?
Isn't there anyone left on Earth?
Hey, what's the matter?
I-It's a city! Maybe there's someone there!
We'll be able to eat something! Yahoo!
Hey!! Isn't there anyone here?!
Come on out! Mister Satan has come!
Earth's hero, Mister Satan,
is making his entrance!
Hey...!
There's nobody here after all.
Has every human on
Earth been killed by Boo? Why?
He was an unexpectedly good fellow.
Right? He was a good guy, huh?
How come, Boo?
The temple...! The temple...!
Watch this!
What, what? What's he doing?
Huh? He's become round, like a ball!
The temple...!
Whoa! Look out, Piccolo-san!
Here he comes again!
The temple's going to be all gone like this!
I wonder what in the world is happening.
G-Gotenks! Do something!
Hey, leave it to me!
Renzoku Super...
[Renzoku: Consecutive]
–Dammit! Renzoku Super...
–Hey, Gotenks!
Can't you do the technique without that pose?!
I-I can do it, but... well, no matter.
Geez, it looks so cool, too!
Renzoku Super Donuts!!
All right! Tighten around him!
Nice going, Gotenks!
You've sealed up Majin Boo!
No way, no way! Boo could
get out of this in a second!
I'm going to inflict a
whole lot of damage on him!
Er... um... hmm...
What should I do?
I know! Smash him in Ultra Boo-Boo Volleyball!
W-What is that?!
Piccolo-san, don't just stand there,
not paying attention, help me out!
O-Okay!
Here goes, dearie!
That's not right, Piccolo-san!
When I say "Here goes, dearie!"
you have to say "Ha-ai!"
You have to hurry and do it right,
or Majin Boo will come on out!
And I can only stay in this
form a short time, so I'm hurrying!
O-Okay.
Here goes, dearie!
Ha-ai!
T-Toss!
Ultra Boo-Boo Attack!!
Yahoo! I am in perfect form!
H-He would have been all right just
now, even if I hadn't helped out, right?
Yahoo!
Wow!!
It looks just like a meteor
fell here! Ooh! I'm scared!
Piccolo-san!
–Come on, come on, you have to say "Ha-ai!"
–Would you cut that out?!
What happened to Boo?
He's here, he's here!
Yahoo! Nicely done, Goten and Trunks!
I-It's not over yet! Please,
you must be careful to the very end!
Goten-san! Trunks-san!
Yo, yo, yo! Majin Boo! Come on out!
I know you aren't going
to keel over from just this!
Get on with it!
I can only stay this ridiculously
strong for a little while longer, after all!
It will take another hour
before I can become like this again!
Huh? Maybe he really did die.
You've got me there!
I guess that was a little disappointing, huh?
I wonder if I've gotten too strong!
Look out!
Super Gotenks 3 exhibits ferocious strength!
However, What's more fearsome
is Majin Boo's depth of strength!
Who will come out the victor
in this battle of the strongest?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
This is bad. The little guys'
Fusion has powered down.
Old-time Kaioshin-sama,
ain't Gohan's training done yet?
Don't panic. We finished a while ago.
I intentionally didn't say
anything until things got tight.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Truly 'Great'!!
A Reborn Gohan Returns to Earth."
I never knew I had this
kind of power inside me.
"Next time"
"Truly 'Great'!!
A Reborn Gohan Returns to Earth"