Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Out of his hatred for Son Goku,
Doctor Gero devoted himself to creating
the Artificial Humans, Nos. 16, 17 and 18.
A private battle between
Vegeta and No. 18 began.
Are you all right?!
Get this straight.
If it comes down to fighting
alongside Earthlings, or Namekians,
or Kakarrot, for that matter...
...I'd rather fight by myself and die!
I don't think anyone here would interfere
in Vegeta and No. 18's one-on-one fight,
but if you do...
...I will have to join in as well.
Dad!!
"Nobody Is Able to Stop Them...
Is This the End of the Z Warriors!?"
Dad!
Dammit!
No you don't!
O-One blow! And he was even a Super Saiyan!
Damn you!
How incredibly strong!
What's up with him?
Dammit!
Looks like I'd better make sure
you can't use your other arm, either.
His hair color changed back,
and that strange glow is gone too.
Pretty unusual phenomenon, I'd say.
The one over there was the same way.
So what is it about him, then?
I've got no data on this.
Not that it's important.
E-Everyone's been beaten!
Maron-chan, well done, well done–!
Hey, sugar. How are you?
Hi!
Hey, baby, how about
having some fun together?
Come on aboard!
I'll be happy to!
Help!
What a racket...
Maron-chan, are you okay?
Maron thought she was going
to die. Thanks, Turtle-chan.
Hey, baby! How about taking
a ride with us in the boat?
Hi, come on, over here!
Maron will take that ride!
Turtle-chan, what are you doing?
You mustn't, Maron-chan.
You're waiting for Kuririn to return, aren't you?
Oh, that's right.
That's right, I'm waiting for Kurin-chan–
Yo, honey!
Come aboard with us!
Honey, let's go get something to drink! Yeah?
Sure, but...
Then we'll get some cake,
something sweet to eat, right?
How's that sound?
Huh? What's your problem?
Puny turtle, you're going to get hurt
if you try to mess with us human beings.
You rotten punk!
Turtle-chan, you're so strong!
I like my men strong.
Turtle-chan!
You mustn't! You have Kuririn-san!
Kuririn-san! K-Kuririn-san!
Kuririn this, Kuririn that, I'm tired of hearing it!
Kuririn's not the only man out there, you know!
Maron-chan...
Damn, you expect me to be beaten too?
Don't worry. They're all still alive.
Hurry and feed them those senzu whatsits.
They should recover completely.
Tell them that if they manage to toughen up any,
we're willing to take them on again.
See you.
Aren't you going to ask where Son Goku is?
No worry. It'll be more fun
seeking it out for ourselves.
Besides, if we smash things
around enough, he'll come to us.
Bye.
You're so bratty, No. 17.
You think so?
What are you looking at, No. 16?
You guys made all that noise,
so the little birds flew away.
Little birds?
Say, not too many cars pass through here.
Let's fly off to somewhere a little more busy.
Goku-sa seems to be feelin' better.
Come to think of it,
what's Gohan-chan doin' now?
Look! We're almost there!
Hold on a second. Go to my home first.
But there are things
I need to tell Father right away.
You have no idea how it
feels to be a "Young Missus."
You're just like your father in that way.
You're the type who's going to
have a hard time with women later on.
It's a real struggle being a young mother.
There's so much I have to do for Trunks,
like change him and
prepare his milk and so on.
She's right. There'll be
more, better chow there too.
Head to Bulma's home.
W-Well, okay then.
We'll go to Bulma-san's home.
There sure aren't any
cars coming through here.
No choice but to fly
on to somewhere busier.
That's fine with me.
I want to get some new clothes too.
Great. So, let's go find a nearby town.
W-Wait!
What, you have some other errand with us?
What is it you guys are after?
Are you just out to kill Goku?
Or are you just out to
turn the world upside-down?
For now, we're going to defeat Son Goku.
We'll think about what
to do next after we're done.
But why?! Why go after Goku?
You guys killed Doctor Gero,
when he was the one who hated him!
Doctor Gero doesn't figure into this.
This is all just a game.
A game, you say?
That's the only purpose for all this?
I said we didn't need to ask you where
Son Goku was, right? This is the reason.
Looking for him is part of the game.
S-Suppose, then, I were to ask you to stop.
Would it be any use?
It wouldn't be any use.
We were created to kill Son Goku.
Like he said.
You'd better hurry and feed
them those senzu. They'll die soon.
See ya. Bye.
The Artificial Humans are overpoweringly strong!
However, their character is somewhat unexpected.
Will Goku and the others be
able to defend the Earth from them?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
It's no use, they're too strong!
The way things stand, even once I do recover,
I ain't no match for the Artificial Humans!
What's up, Piccolo? Do you
have some kind of strategy? Tell us!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Piccolo's Resolution!!
The Last Measure in His Reserve."
You don't think Piccolo-san means
to merge with Kami-sama, do you?
"Next time"
"Piccolo's Resolution!!
The Last Measure in His Reserve"