Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Namek counts down its last
moments before destruction...
Right in the middle of it all,
the life-and-death battle between Freeza,
the strongest being in the universe,
and Son Goku, who has become a
Super Saiyan, continues to unfold.
There ain't any time!
Let's finish this right now!
How's that?
Those were just my warm-up
exercises for my final attack!
I would suppose so.
At that level, they'd have to be.
The battle continues...
"Shen Long, Run Yourself Through Space!!
The Time of Namek's Destruction Draws Near."
Enough with the false bravado!
The only thing that remains for you is death!
Before you die, there is
one point I will praise you for.
Your superb, incredible
strength, Super Saiyan.
It's certainly the greatest in the universe.
If only I, Freeza, weren't around!
Miserable idiot!
If you had only beaten Freeza
before he attained full power,
this wouldn't be happening.
Kaio-sama? Kaio-sama?
This is the Kami over Earth. Kaio-sama?
I hear you. Something I can do?
I have just received word from Mister Popo.
He has located where the last Dragon Ball is.
Yes, and...?
Ah, right. Very shortly, all
seven will be gathered together,
and so we will be resurrecting
Tenshinhan and Yamucha there with you.
Ah, that's right.
But, as I said earlier,
unfortunately for Chaozu...
Don't worry, Chaozu.
I will remain here too.
We're always together, aren't we?
You can't! Ten-san, that won't do!
If you guys are going to remain here,
then as far as I'm concerned...
What are you saying?!
You have Bulma waiting for you, don't you?
Y-Yeah, but...
Wait a second! Hold on, hold on!
Say, Kami of Earth, can those Dragon
Balls resurrect two people at the same time?
Hm? Er, yes, so long as the
conditions are the same. For example,
as we are to ask this time,
"Please return to life those who
were killed by Vegeta and his group–"
So long as the request
is made in this manner,
it will likely work on any number of people.
Then even with only the one wish,
they surpass Planet Namek's Dragon Balls.
Okay then, can the wish be granted
even on worlds far separated from Earth?
Mm, probably. Why do you ask such a thing?
You can't be thinking of bringing
back to life all the aliens Vegeta
has ever killed in the past, can you?
Naturally, such a thing is possible,
but it would only be effective for
those who had died within one year's time.
There's just one more thing I'd like to ask.
Can those who died having lived the
full measure of their life be resurrected?
Unfortunately, that is impossible.
In the event of a natural death...
But what about the case of someone who met
with evil beings, and even though indirectly,
had their life's measure reduced as a result?
A good question indeed.
This is a first-time case.
But I believe they would be
able to live for the portion of time
that had been shortened from their measure.
I have no proof of such, however.
Kaio-sama, what is it?
All right, it's decided then!
Kami, change that wish for me!
Make it, "Please return to life all
those killed by Freeza and his ring," okay?
Aren't we to Son-kun's spaceship yet?
If we don't get off this dangerous
planet as soon as possible,
we'll never set foot on
the soil of Earth again!
Yes, I know that.
You're really sure about that?
Yet you don't even know how
hard I had to struggle up until now!
But I do know.
It was so awful, after all!
Being chased by dinosaurs,
getting changed into a frog,
almost getting pinched by giant rocks...!
There it is! That's it!
That's Father's spaceship!
Hooray! Now we can return to Earth!
Hey, hold on! Where are
you going on your own?!
The lifespan of this planet is nearly up.
Two or three minutes left at the outside.
You must be getting
anxious, eh Super Saiyan?
So that's it, you're buying time, are you?
Enough for that kid and
the others to leave this planet?
Well, that's okay.
I may let them go now, but
I will make them my next target.
Their deaths will only be slightly delayed.
Buying time, did you say?
I don't have the need to!
You're going to die. Here and now.
That's enough of your big talk!
I'm going to shut you up right now!
What's taking so long for
Gohan and the others? Get moving!
Killed by Freeza and his ring, you say?
Kaio-sama, what is this about?
There isn't any time, so I'll explain this simply.
First, we use the Dragon Balls on Earth
to return to life those killed by Freeza
and his men, meaning the Namekians.
By doing so, it is likely that
the Grand Elder of Planet Namek
will be resurrected, however briefly.
From that point, I'm not too
sure this is going to work myself,
but of the Namekian Dragon Balls'
three wishes, only two have been granted.
Once the Grand Elder is returned to life,
there should be one more wish
to be granted, shouldn't there?
A-And then?
With that one wish,
instantaneously relocate all those on
Planet Namek, with the exception of Freeza,
to someplace like Earth!
I-I see. That is one possible gamble, isn't it?
You guys' resurrections
will be considerably delayed.
Can you put up with that for us?
I can't return to life in the first place, so...
Of course, that will be fine with me!
It's only one year, isn't it?
It is an excellent idea you have, Kaio-sama!
And that's that. Now
pardon me, but you must hurry!
The very planet Namek itself
is just about to be vaporized!
Is that so? Very well, I will tell
this to Mister Popo right away.
Bulma-san, come inside, quick!
What's going on? It's pitch black in here!
What's wrong?
It can't be malfunctioning, can it–?
That's strange. When I was
here earlier, the lights were on.
W-Watch out!
The floor is slanted.
I'm not familiar with this
thing, but I'll try this and that.
Could this be it?
I-Isn't that Piccolo over there?!
Yes, it is.
What's he doing in a place like this?
I don't want to journey through
space together with someone like Piccolo!
Piccolo-san helped save me and Father,
so I am going to be sure
to take him back to Earth!
You know, Gohan-kun,
this is Piccolo's homeland.
I wonder if he wouldn't
rather like to stay here.
O-Okay, already!
Well, what else can I do?
He's unconscious and all, so
there's nothing to worry about, right?
What?!
We've reached the limit!
If we stay here any longer,
we won't be able to take off!
You can't! Father still hasn't come!
Son-kun will be fine!
He's sure to escape somehow or other!
Please, Bulma-san! For Father!
Wait for Father, please!
Just one more minute will be enough!
G-Gohan-kun...
Hold out against this,
Piccolo! If you and I die now,
all hope will disappear as well!
Kami-sama! Kami-sama!
Kami-sama, Dragon Balls gathered.
Can say wish any time.
Very well!
So, speak forth thy wish!
I shall grant thee any one wish!
Um, want to have those killed by
Freeza and his men returned to life.
This on distant planet.
Can you grant this wish?
I know not. However, I shall try.
Not know is trouble. Can only have do.
Request this. Good luck.
Go to hell, Freeza!
What will be the outcome of this,
the greatest conflict in the universe?
And will the wish to Shen Long be granted?
There is no more time remaining!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
There's only three minutes
until the planet explodes!
Shen Long, hurry up and bring the
people on Planet Namek back to life!
This is hopeless now!
Gohan-kun, let's get out
of here as fast as we can!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"I Am Son Goku's Son!!
Gohan Returns to the Battlefield."
Freeza, now you'll have to take me on!
"Next time"
"I Am Son Goku's Son!!
Gohan Returns to the Battlefield"