The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Vegeta, with your great pride, you
allowed yourself to be controlled by that guy
just because you wanted to become stronger?!
I...
I wanted to return to the way I was long ago!
I wanted to return to the brutal,
cold-blooded Saiyan that I was,
so I could fight all-out with
you and not worry about anything!
Vegeta, having returned
to being a wicked warrior,
continues a ferocious battle with Son Goku.
And so, as Majin Boo's ball
received the inflicted damage energy...
He's at full power! Majin Boo is at full power!!
The seal was at last broken.
Will the terrifying monster,
Majin Boo, finally reveal himself?
"I Won't Allow the Revival!!
A Kamehame-Ha of Resistance."
Dabura, he's emerging now!
Majin Boo is emerging!
Y-Yes!
The seal has finally been broken!
We will finally be able to see Majin Boo!
So, come on out!
What sort of incredible guy is
Majin Boo, who my papa created?!
We are indeed certainly looking
forward to this, Babidi-sama!
I've been eagerly awaiting
this day! Hurry and come on out!
F-Father's damage energy–
Having gone beyond Super
Saiyan, Father's damage energy...
Who could have thought it would
have revived Majin Boo so quickly?
It's no longer any use!
Let's run away, Gohan-san!
If we do such a thing, then what?
Is it okay for us to leave it here like this?
If we do that, Majin Boo will be revived!
There is no way we can win
against Majin Boo, Gohan-san!
No matter how strong you
guys may be, it's impossible!
The person who can defeat
Majin Boo does not exist in this world!
If we stay here, make no
mistake, we will be killed!
But Kaioshin-sama...
Hurry, Gohan-san! Let's run away!
Kaioshin-sama!
Hurry!!
As long as he's already at
full power, I can at least...
Gohan-san, what are you...?
W-What is he planning to do?
A good question.
I'll do this much to him!
Gohan-san...
Trunks-kun! Stop! Stop!
What is it, Goten?
Something's been strange for a while now.
There's a big ki in that direction, too!
Yeah, I know. A weird kind
of ki like I've never felt before.
It's pretty big.
Both this way and that way–Aah, this
is getting more and more complicated!
B-Birds!
There's so many of them.
What could be the matter?
What in the world is happening?
Do you think it has anything
to do with Majin Boo?
Who knows?
W-What is it? What's wrong?
Good question.
Mister Satan, please call
on everyone to calm down!
But...
At this rate, it will become a panic,
and we won't be able to conclude!
We still have not handed over the prize
money for your victory, Mister Satan!
Prize money!
That's right! I haven't gotten
my prize money yet, have I?
Quickly, award me my prize money!
That's impossible, under these circumstances!
People! Do not panic!
I, Mister Satan, am always
here together with you, am I not?!
Even in the event that the
end of the world is approaching,
as long as I, Mister Satan, am here,
I will protect you, no matter what!
Oh, it's Mister Satan!
That's right, we still have Mister Satan!
Mister Satan, we're counting on you!
Satan! Satan! Satan!
I nailed it! I nailed that so cool!
Let's get my money quick and go home!
Mm, something is happening.
Something more frightfully
terrible than anything else up to now...
I-It can't be! Goten-chan's
run off somewhere now,
and just when I'm thinkin'
Gohan and Goku-sa have appeared,
they go vanishin' again.
What am I supposed to do?
Why, that lousy– Babidi-sama!
I will go and make him heed us!
I-It's all right! Majin Boo won't
even blink over something like this!
Y-You fool! Doing such a thing is worthless!
All right!
Out he comes! Majin Boo!
Babidi-sama!
It's empty!
N-No! This wasn't supposed to be! It can't be!
Why is this? Why is this so?
Come on out! Come on out, I say!
Majin Boo! Please, come out!
What good fortune!
Tough luck, Babidi!
Majin Boo was exterminated
by that attack just now!
It's probable he shriveled
up over his long sleep,
and no matter how much
energy you poured into him,
he would not be as tough as he was in the past!
And now, the Earth will be saved!
It is well, is it not, Babidi-sama?
Even if we do not have Majin Boo, I am here.
On top of that, there is that guy Vegeta,
who even though incompletely,
is still under your control.
B-But... Majin Boo!
My papa's creation, Majin Boo!
Babidi, at this stage, are
you reduced to whining?
Dabura, having come to this, let's at
least deal with that insolent Kaioshin!
Right!
I will somehow or other pin Babidi down.
Gohan-san, if you will then defeat Dabura,
Babidi's ambitious
schemes will utterly evaporate!
And so, as you were told by Goku-san,
now is just the time for you to become angry!
Become angry, and
show your true power for me!
Gohan-san, peace has nearly come upon us!
Th-Th-That's not true!
A terrible ki... a terrible
ki is swelling up! I-It's...
W-What is it you're saying, Gohan-san?
The smoke! The smoke that
came out of where that ball is!
What? What is he looking at?
That cloud! No, the smoke
from before is gathering!
Y-You don't mean...!
–Not bad, Vegeta!
–I'll show you what I do best!
What a terrible ki!
Hey, up there!
C-Can it be...?
Babidi-sama, is that Majin Boo?
N-Not sure.
I've never seen him before.
The only one who has ever
seen Majin Boo is Kaioshin there.
Er, is that Majin Boo?
Th-That's right! I would never
forget th-that terrifying face!
Oh, that seems to
be Majin Boo, after all!
A-A guy such as this...?!
Hey there, Majin Boo!
He's called a Majin, so I figured he'd be bigger.
It's no use any more! We can't escape!
Are you sure about that?
While he certainly does
possess an extraordinary ki,
it doesn't appear to be so much
that we can do nothing about it.
I-Is that true, Gohan-san?!
Yes! If I can just put forward all of my force...
Majin Boo!
Damn you!
Wait, Vegeta! Wait!
A ki! A fairly enormous ki has appeared!
Majin Boo has emerged after all!
At last, Majin Boo is revived.
However, is he really strong
enough to plunge the Earth into crisis?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Look, Gohan, Majin Boo ain't
an opponent that we can handle.
It's too late! The two of
us will not likely return alive.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"A Straight Line to Despair!?
The Grief of Kaioshin."
Oh, no... To think that I can't even get away!
"Next time"
"A Straight Line to Despair!?
The Grief of Kaioshin"