Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Just as Trunks came from the future to forewarn,
Doctor Gero is killed by the hand
of No. 17, one of his own creations.
Afterward, No. 16, an Artificial Human that
not even Trunks knows about, is re-activated.
Vegeta, having transformed
himself into a Super Saiyan,
challenges the Artificial
Humans to battle all alone.
"Good Looks and Super Power!?
No Blind Spot on No. 18."
You should have kept your place.
Very well. I'll do it.
Let me warn you now,
I won't be pulling any punches
just because you're a woman.
Then again, you're an Artificial Human.
You aren't a woman, are you?
Here!
Surprising.
He's got a much greater strength...
...than in the information
Doctor Gero provided us.
Vegeta, huh?
Not too bad.
Looks like No. 18 is starting to play with him.
Hey, stackin' this way's
awfully rough on me, ain't it?
Please, just hang in there for
a little while longer, Yajirobe-san.
Enough! Can't you do anything but complain?
How can you ask a question like that?
My belly's so empty!
I gotta put away some chow!
Incredible. You have no class.
Yeah, he's such a poor example for you–huh?
Hey! This ain't funny!
Which one of us ain't got class now?
Please, stop shifting around there, Yajirobe-san!
You hush! I'm gettin' off!
Take us down! Take us down!
Whoa!
You're not getting away!
What'm I s'pposed to do now?
I sure hope the Artificial Humans
haven't overtaken Gohan and Bulma-san.
Dad...
What's that?
What's the matter?
Have you stopped running from me?
You guys are just fooling, right?
Huh? What the–?
They've come back.
There's no way I can tell if you
wind-up mannequins suffer damage or not.
As such, I'll just have to blow you to pieces.
Enough so that you'll never smile again.
Hey, you numbskulls!
What do you think you're
doing in the middle of the road?
Blithering halfwits!
If you don't get out of the way,
I'll run right over the top of you!
Just keep smiling, while you're still able.
Hey, didn't you hear me?!
Go ahead, try it.
Hey!
It looks as though you're faster than I thought.
Yoo-hoo!
Hello!
Hey there! Hey there!
So bouncy, bouncy!
So jiggly, jiggly!
Oh, for a camera!
It's been so long!
Hi! Turtle-chan!
Hi!
No, not you, old man!
Turtle-chan! Turtle-chan!
Turtle-chan?
How cute!
Why, you...
You haven't been giving me your all, have you?
Of course not.
If I gave it my all, it would destroy the Earth.
I haven't been giving it my all, either.
Could you tell?
In that case, don't hold back.
You'd better give me your best while you can,
or you'll regret it later.
Well then, I will.
Are you all right, Vegeta-san?!
Vegeta-san!
Unbelievable. You're such a bunch of pests!
You guys think you're any help
against an opponent like this?
My goodness.
Could it be time to lend a hand?
Not even No. 18 would
be able to take them all on.
Nothing left for me but to get in there.
Unless, No. 16, you want to go?
No, I'm not going.
Not going, huh? You really are slipshod.
Just what were you built for, anyhow?
I thought I told you. To kill Son Goku.
My, my, how nice for you to be so carefree.
Hey, No. 17 is headed this way.
Let's get out of here, Vegeta-san.
If you get killed, your
pride won't be worth crap.
P-Please!
You want another beating?
You're in our way! Get lost, now!
If you want to run, you're free to do so.
We don't have any interest in that which flees.
Don't be ridiculous.
Why should I find it necessary to
run when I'm about to obliterate you?
Get this straight.
If it comes down to fighting
alongside Earthlings, or Namekians...
...or Kakarrot, for that matter...
...I'd rather fight by myself and die!
Very nice commentary.
Coupled with your fighting style,
you're every bit worthy
to be prince of the Saiyans.
It's not up to you wind-up dolls to say so.
Particularly a kid like you.
However, in the hopes that each
of you hold the code of Bushido dear,
I'm putting you on notice.
I don't think anyone here...
...would interfere in Vegeta
and No. 18's one-on-one fight,
but if you do, I will have to join in as well.
These guys are cowardly pacifists.
You don't have to trouble
yourself for them to stay out of it.
Fine, then.
Shall we keep going?
Of course we will!
That's my boy!
You're getting me irritated,
pretending like nothing's happened.
You surprise me.
Even being an alien, I didn't
think any man could push me this far.
Is the man Son Goku even stronger?
Don't be absurd.
He may have pulled ahead for a
while, but now, as it should be...
...I'm stronger than he is.
You don't say. Then you're not
all that great, either one of you.
W-What was that?!
This is bad! Go get her!
Incredible. I hadn't realized
that Dad was so incredible.
He's actually holding his own against
one of those terrible Artificial Humans.
He's going to get killed. Vegeta, I mean.
Watch!
It's just a little bit each time,
but the Artificial Human is
starting to get the upper hand.
His opponent hardly loses any power,
but for every move Vegeta makes,
his stamina drops proportionately.
Shoot!
Goku, what should we do?!
Dad!!
No, you fool!
Vegeta is in trouble.
Without thinking, Trunks leaps to his aid.
However, how should they do
battle against the Artificial Humans...
...and their unmeasurable power?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
How can Trunks–as a Super Saiyan–
be completely knocked out with one blow?!
How disappointing. This isn't much of a game.
Is this the extent of what
flesh-and-blood people can do?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Nobody Is Able to Stop Them...
Is This the End of the Z Warriors?"
At this rate, everyone will be killed!
"Next time"
"Nobody Is Able to Stop Them...
Is This the End of the Z Warriors?"