Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
The worst state of affairs could not be avoided.
The Artificial Human No. 18 was
absorbed into the body of the evil Cell.
Has every hope for saving
the Earth evaporated here?
"Battle Power Infinity!!
Birth of the God of Destruction Named Cell."
So, you're finally transforming
into your perfect form?
Don't you disappoint me this time!
What?
I-I'm to blame for all of this.
It's all because I didn't destroy No. 18!
W-Why, you...!
I won't... I won't let you do
with the future as you like!
To think that it could be this bad!
M-Muten Roshi-sama, at this rate,
the house is gonna be washed away!
We need to be runnin' away somewhere!
That's right!
What with Cell and Vegeta and
so on, we're getting caught up in...
...something terrific, aren't we?
It's no use. This situation is
spread out over the entire Earth.
No matter where we go, it would be the same.
The Earth will be wrecked!
Are you finally done?
The trembling of the
atmosphere has finally died down.
We survived then, huh?
No.
This is where it begins.
Muten Roshi-sama...
The real terror, that is.
Cell has become his perfect form.
How is that? Did Kuririn
not use the controller I made?
Kuririn himself stomped the controller.
Why?!
Miserable Vegeta! Take responsibility!
Are you okay, Gohan?
Gohan?
Piccolo-san said long ago that you
would be unsuitable as a teacher, Father!
That you were too gentle, Father!
That you were utterly lacking...
...in the harshness it takes to do this!
That just by seeing how
coddled I was, he could tell!
Gohan!
I finally understand that!
I have always been spoiled
by your gentleness, Father!
Father, please treat this
like you are trying to kill me!
Then, even supposing I really do die,
that will have been all I was capable of!
And if that is my level,
there's no way I could surpass you, Father!
If I won't bring myself to die...
...there's no way I can obtain real strength.
I can't ever become a Super Saiyan!
Ka... me... ha... me...
Ha!!
Damned if I'm running from this!
I-I've been a pampered child...
There was the time...
Gohan! Now! Shoot!
Then there was the time...
It was my fault for being weak.
It was because I depended on everyone else...
You've finally become a Super Saiyan!
Just like that.
Now, you have to control
your excitement in that state.
You did good, Gohan!
Sorry, Father. It's so hard!
Hey, you just have to
take it a little at a time.
Let's take a short break.
Should I cut your hair? It's getting too long!
I knew it. Even if it is his perfect form,
it doesn't appear to be anything special.
He's shrunk, compared to how he was before.
Kuririn-san!
T-This can't be...!
So this is my perfect form?
This is my body, perfect in every way?
Splendid! I've finally obtained it!
Very good! Those are
wonderful attacks, you guys!
Move away, Trunks!
Don't you move, Cell!
Kienzan!!
G-G-Got him!
I-It can't be!
That was the Kienzan that
cut through even Freeza...!
Tremendous power and speed!
Is this the true ability of
the perfected form of Cell?
Kuririn-san!!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Cell has enormous potential power.
Vegeta is in trouble! He's going to be done in!
I have far surpassed Dad.
But I can't let him know
that I have all this power.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Super Vegeta in Peril!!
An Absolutely Perfect Terror Closes In!!"
How can there be this wide a
gap between Vegeta and Cell?!
"Next time"
"Super Vegeta in Peril!!
An Absolutely Perfect Terror Closes In!!"