Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
The mysterious youth who
unexpectedly appeared was a Super Saiyan!
Son Goku-san should be landing any moment.
And, exactly where and
when the young man predicted,
Son Goku returned!
Huh?
Goku!
Father!
So, you really did survive.
What are you guys doing here?
"My Dad is Vegeta...
Admissions of the Mysterious Youth."
Son-kun!
Father!
–Goku!
How did you guys know I was
going to be arriving here now?
This boy here, this boy!
He told us you'd be coming here.
Father, you know this person, right?
Who is he?
You mean you don't
know who he is? Not at all?
No, I don't know him at all.
This boy knew when you
would return here, Son-kun.
Really? That's strange.
After Freeza's spaceship discovered mine,
they must have known when I would arrive.
Speaking of which, who was it
that defeated Freeza and his men?
That was an awesome ki!
Piccolo?
Or maybe Vegeta?
This guy here did Freeza and the others in,
and it only took a split second.
Moreover...
He can become a Super
Saiyan, the same as you.
A Super Saiyan?!
That's incredible, for being so young!
And I didn't even know there were
any other Saiyans besides ourselves.
There aren't! There are
no other Saiyans besides us!
There's no way there could be.
Well, makes no difference.
Anyhow, you're a Saiyan, right?
Of course it makes a difference!
You're taking things as
casually as you always do!
Really?
Son-san...
I need to have a word.
–You mean with me?
–Yes.
Just the two of us.
Gotcha.
What's this? You mean it's a secret from us?
'Scuse us, guys, be back a minute!
This is far enough.
Come to think of it,
I've forgotten my manners.
Sorry for making you knock
off Freeza and them for me.
Guess I really did go too easy on him.
I should have polished him
off for good back on Namek.
Freeza and his men...
...were actually supposed to
have been defeated by yourself,
but some kind of time discrepancy
came up, making that impossible.
And so I had little choice but to step in.
Yeah. Freeza's ship was faster
than mine and they passed me up.
He didn't seem at all
sorry about what he'd done,
so I was going to put him away,
and then you showed up.
There were three hours until you got here,
so of course it was impossible
for you to deal with him.
Oh, not really.
I've gotten myself a new technique.
A new technique?
Yeah. It's what's known as
"Instantaneous Movement."
Instantaneous Movement?
The folks on a planet
called Yardrat taught it to me.
They were some unusual folks.
Not all that powerful,
but they did know all kinds of techniques.
I could have moved myself
from inside the spaceship I was in...
...to wherever Freeza was in an instant.
Is that so?
I wasn't aware that you had
learned such a technique, Son-san.
I was certain there was no
way you could have arrived...
...without your spaceship for that three hours.
I've changed history for no reason.
On top of that, I only meant
to meet with you, Son-san,
but instead I've run
into everyone else as well.
History? What are you talking about?
Before I answer, I have something to ask you.
Son-san can you, of your own accord,
become a Super Saiyan at will?
Yeah. I couldn't at first,
but I struggled with it and
managed to bring it under control.
Then may I ask you to
turn yourself, here and now?
It is my humble request.
What do you suppose
Father and he are talking about?
You got it.
What happened to Son-kun? What's the matter?
He's turned into a Super Saiyan.
That's what a Super Saiyan is?
He's not even fighting, but what a ki!
Is this okay?
Thank you very much.
It's amazing!
You look so much like I do as a Super Saiyan.
Okay, now what?
I will also become a Super Saiyan.
That guy also turned into a Super Saiyan!
What are they planning to do?
Dammit!
We really do look alike.
Please excuse me.
Why is it you did not avoid me?
Your ki was not that of a killer.
I knew you would stop.
I see.
Very well then, this time I will not stop.
Do you understand?
Got it.
Just as I expected. The stories were true.
No, you're even better!
This is the sword I used to slice up Freeza.
You just weren't trying your hardest.
I can put my trust in you.
I will tell you everything.
Did you see that?
They're incredible!
Kakarrot, you rat!
He's gotten even better.
Please lock away what I am about
to tell you within your heart alone.
Okay. Feel at ease to tell me anything.
My lips are sealed.
This may sound unbelievable
to those of you in this era,
but I've traveled back
from nearly twenty years...
...in the future in a time machine.
From the future? Twenty years?
Yes. My name is Trunks.
If you're wondering how
it is I can have Saiyan blood,
the reason is because I am
the son of Vegeta-san over there.
Vegeta's?!
Are you really Vegeta's son?!
Yes.
There's a resemblance!
Now that you say so,
there is a resemblance!
He's you're pop, huh?
Two years from now, I was born.
This is quite a surprise!
However, I didn't travel back in a
time machine just to tell you that.
Son-san, there are important
things I must make you aware of.
In roughly three years from this
time, on May 12, at around 10 a.m.,
on an island located 9 kilometers
southwest of Metro South,
a terrifying pair of villains will appear.
They will be monsters, both
possessing a power so great,
it will be unthinkable
that they are of this world.
Who are they? Aliens?
No. They are born of Earth.
They are Artificial Humans,
sometimes called Cyborgs.
They were created by a maniacal scientist,
formerly of the Red Ribbon Army,
named Doctor Gero.
Red Ribbon Army?!
How long are those two planning on talking?
Red Ribbon Army?
You mean the same
Red Ribbon army I wiped out?
That's right.
The army itself was struck
down many years ago by yourself.
However, Doctor Gero survived,
and continued his research.
What did he do it for?
I mean, was he after world domination?
No one is really sure,
but I think Doctor Gero
was after at least that much.
However, those Artificial Humans,
built to be ultimate killing machines...
...also killed their own creator, Doctor Gero.
In short, all that remained
were the Artificial Humans,
who liked nothing better than
causing death and destruction.
As a Super Saiyan, who took
only a moment to beat Freeza,
for you to describe them as monsters,
must mean they're pretty tough.
Yes.
I've stood up to them, but
there's two of them, after all.
Even one-on-one, it was all
I could do just to escape them.
Hold on, if there's two of them...
Don't you have any allies?
No.
Twenty years from now,
I am the only warrior still alive.
In twenty years, I will be
the only warrior to survive!
In the battle three years from now,
my dad Vegeta, Kuririn-san, Yamucha-san,
Tenshinhan-san, Chaozu-san,
and Piccolo-san, were all killed.
Son Gohan-san was just barely able to escape.
Gohan-san served as my master,
and taught me everything I know,
up until four years ago, when he, too, was...
As you are already aware of, with Piccolo gone,
the Dragon Balls also disappear,
so we were unable to
bring anyone back to life.
As a result of the Artificial Humans...
...taking so many lives to
amuse themselves over the years,
the future that I come from is a living hell.
They're too strong! They're just too strong!
Just a minute. What about me?
What happens to me? Am I killed too?
You won't even fight.
In a short time, you will become very sick.
Soon after, you will pass away.
It will be a viral infection of your heart.
Not even a mighty Super Saiyan
can win against this illness.
Oh no, senzu won't have
any effect on the illness either.
Aw, crud, I'm going to die?
What a rip-off, I wanted to fight them!
Shoot!
You're really that disappointed
at not being able to fight?
Aren't you afraid?
Sure I'm scared, but these
guys are incredibly strong, right?
I sure would like to give them a shot!
You certainly are a true Saiyan warrior.
You're exactly how Mom
and Gohan-san described you.
We can surely count on you. I'm glad I came!
When your symptoms first
appear, please drink this.
What have you got?
It's medicine for you.
There is no treatment in this era,
but twenty years from now, we have a cure.
That medicine will allow
you to make it through alive.
You mean it?! All right!
I wish you'd told me that a lot sooner!
It really isn't good for me
to be doing this sort of thing.
It changes history.
But considering the
history we'll be changing...
I believe that you will definitely
manage to do something about all this.
My mom also hopes so, which
allowed her to struggle through...
...and finally complete her time machine.
Hold on! Your mom knows me?
Yes, quite well.
And she built a time machine?
Don't tell me! Your mom is...
Yes, right over there.
B-Bulma?!
How long are they going
to yap?! This is ticking me off!
Son-kun looks like he was
bowled over by something!
This is the biggest surprise of all!
I thought for sure that Bulma
would take up with Yamucha.
But instead, she goes with Vegeta there!
Yamucha-san was, well...
something of a playboy,
and she got fed up with him
and they split up, I understand.
What's wrong?
When she did, she saw how
alone my dad seemed, and somehow,
before she realized what was happening...
However, they never married.
That's just the way my mom is.
Boy, I don't know.
But when it comes to that
issue, it sounds just like her.
My dad died before
I had any memories of him,
so I was quite moved to
finally meet him a little while ago.
He's looking over here at something.
It looks like he's smiling a little.
Now, please be sure to especially
keep this matter a secret, okay?
If you say anything, and the feelings
between the two of them go bad,
then my very existence will be erased!
Yeah, I got it, I got it!
Well then, I will excuse myself now.
I want to return to the future and
reassure my mom as soon as I can.
Sure. Tell her I said thanks for saving my life.
It'll be nice if we can change the future, huh?
Yes. Knowing your strength,
Goku-san, has raised my hopes.
Will we meet again?
I don't know.
It takes a long time to
gather the energy necessary...
...for the time machine to make a round trip.
If I'm still alive after that time has passed,
I will definitely come to help out!
Three years from now.
Be sure you survive.
You've got yourself a good goal.
I'll be training as much as...
...I can the next three
years for the same reason.
Hey, he took off out of there!
Now what do I do?
How am I supposed to
explain this to everyone?
Father!
Goku! What did he say?
Um, well, it wasn't all that much.
Start talking. This is an
important matter for all of us, too.
Piccolo, you overheard us?
My sense of hearing is a bit
different from the rest of yours.
What does he mean, an important matter?
Tell us!
Um, you see...
If it's too hard for you to
tell them, I'll do it for you.
Yeah, but–
Don't worry.
I won't say anything that
will threaten his existence.
And we can't afford to let ourselves get killed...
...because we didn't put in the due training.
–Ki–
–Killed?!
Piccolo told everyone what was to happen,
while skillfully leaving
Trunks' nature a mystery.
As might be expected, no one
was able to conceal their shock.
Isn't this all a little hard to swallow?
A time machine?
Any of you who don't believe him,
that's fine. Enjoy yourselves.
But I'm going to train,
because I don't want to die.
What's that?!
Dad, you were strong, proud,
stern, and lonesome, just as Mom said.
Please don't die.
Young Mom, you hang in there too.
He vanished!
I'm going to train.
Me too.
I'm in too.
Dammit, three years from
now I am going to survive!
Having delivered the hard truth,
the mysterious young man departed.
Will such a terrible pair
really appear in three years?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
All right, everyone,
let's meet up again in three years.
Those of you who are
sure of yourselves, anyhow.
Artificial Humans are apparently
even worse than anything before.
Before that, Kakarrot, tell us
how you survived on Planet Namek!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Goku's New Finishing Technique!?
Watch My Instantaneous Movement."
H-Huh? Father disappeared!
"Next time"
"Goku's New Finishing Technique!?
Watch My Instantaneous Movement"