Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
At last, the mighty
Saiyans had arrived on Earth.
However, even though Goku,
upon whom everyone was relying,
had been returned to
life with the Dragon Balls,
it would still take him one day to
travel back home along the Serpentine Road.
Will the Earth be safe until Goku returns?
"Unbelievable! Saibaimen, Born of the Soil."
It's a person!
There's–there's a person coming out of it!
W-What do those guys want?!
Who are they?
"Earth," they called it, right?
Not a bad planet, is it?
Shall we say hello to those
annoying, peeping little chicks?
Not too hard, now.
What was that?!
W-What the hell did they do?!
W-What the–?
I-It's unheard-of!
Perhaps that greeting was a bit too polite.
Leave it at that, Nappa.
If we go at it too excessively,
we won't be able to sell
this planet for a high price.
O-Oh, yeah.
Now that you mention it, we were going to
look for those whatever-they're-called balls,
which can grant us any wish, huh?
Dragon Balls.
How about we first find
the one who killed Raditz,
and ask him about the Dragon Balls?
Sure.
Now, supposing that one of those
Dragon Ball things was in the area,
our wish for eternal life
would have been wiped out,
thanks to that senseless "greeting" of yours.
S-Sorry about that.
It completely slipped my mind.
Well, what's done is done.
First thing we need to do
is find the guy who has
the highest battle power.
He'll be the one who killed
Raditz. Either him, or Kakarrot's son.
That's strange. I'm picking up
more than just one or two readings
that have a battle power higher than 1,000.
What are they doing on this planet?
Don't panic. They're still no match for us.
In any case, find the one
who has the highest battle power.
I found him!
There are two fairly
high battle powers together.
All right, Nappa, let's go have some fun.
Currently, the cause of the
large-scale earthquake is a complete mystery.
All communications with Metro East,
which is thought to have been the
epicenter of this earthquake, have been cut off,
and the safety of its residents is in doubt.
T-They're finally here, are they?
Let's go help them out.
With this, I can tell where they are.
I-I'm going over my dead body!
I-I'm going! I'm sure
Yamucha-sama will be going, too!
No, let's not.
There's too great a difference in our levels.
Even if I did go, I'd just be in the way.
All we can do is pray
for their victory from here.
Y-You're probably right.
Right! Right!
Yamucha-sama, don't die!
Son-kun, get here soon!
Get here soon!
Hold out until I get there, everyone!
This is great! This planet
"Earth" here has fairly little gravity,
and we can move with no difficulty at all!
They're moving at incredible speed!
They're heading straight for that
area where those two other large ki are!
Is that where Tenshinhan-san and them are?
Or is it where Piccolo and Goku's son are?
They're coming. They intend to come here.
Right.
Chaozu, you stay here!
No way! I'm coming, too!
I trained hard, and I'm coming!
Together with you, Ten-san!
W-What the hell happened here?!
Er, the scene is more
terrible than you can imagine.
Metro East has been
wiped out without a trace.
What in the world could have happened here?
Chief, how is the investigation coming?
We haven't the faintest idea.
This ain't no ordinary case!
Who is that?
I knew it! So this was the Saiyans' doin'!
Are they tellin' me I gotta
fight someone with this kinda power?!
H-Hey, you!
What are you doing there?!
A-Are you the one who did this?!
You dimwit! There ain't
no way I coulda done this!
If I had this sorta power,
I wouldn't be so scared, y'know?!
You know something, don't you?!
Chief!
Hey!
This was done by aliens,
who're called "Saiyans"!
W-What?! Aliens?!
They're fixin' to exterminate
everyone on Earth! Every last one!
My boys're fightin' 'em right now for
ya, to make sure they don't get their way.
Ya got that?!
Of all things!
Come on, now, it's dangerous
for the general public to be here!
Go home! Go home!
There are guys like this one
running around out there, you know.
True, true...
All right then, you guys! How do
you explain this weird situation?! Eh?!
'sides, look over there at those!
Kind of large for basketballs, aren't they?
You stupid numbskull!
N-Numbskull?!
Those're the spaceships
that the Saiyans came in!
–Spaceships?!
T-They couldn't be!
So check 'em out!
Hey, crime lab!
–Yes?
Examine–examine those things.
–Right!
I'm from AHO TV. C-Come over here a second...
I'd like to hear all the details.
I tell ya, I sure am gettin' hungry, here...
–Y-You want an appearance fee?
–C-Chief!
T-This definitely is not of this earth!
W-What?!
I'll pay you whatever money you ask!
So, where are these Saiyan guys now?
AHO TV-san, you're not
getting the scoop on us!
We'll pay as much as you like, too.
Us, too!
Us, as well!
Me, too!
In that case, to keep ya all
from fightin', I'll tell ya all!
You can stick your wads of bills in here.
How's that?
I got it!
They're that way!
No, this way, this way!
Lessee...
About 6,000 kilometers in that direction.
6,000 kilos?
South, huh?
I won't steer ya wrong, though.
You'd best not get too close to 'em.
These're some pretty horrific guys, after all.
We're going to be the
first ones there, for sure!
No, we are!
We're leaving, too!
We're going to capture the aliens!
Hunh, no hope for 'em.
All right... I'm gonna eat my fill with this!
Could be the last meal
I ever eat in this world...
Prob'ly...
The time was 12:20 p.m. The birds and animals
sensed a presence out of the
ordinary, and had begun leaving the area.
There's nothing to be afraid of.
We've become so strong, it's
incomparable to what we were a year ago.
R-Right!
Something is coming this
way from that direction, too!
And someone is coming from over here, as well!
W-Weren't there only going to be two Saiyans?
A Saiyan?!
Hey, long time no see, Piccolo.
Oh, it's you, huh?
What business do you have here?
Did you come to get in our way?
Don't talk like that.
I've improved a little, myself.
So it appears. Looks like there are
some other fools who mean to come here.
Yeah, I'm sure everyone is coming.
I guess I was just the closest one.
I remember! You're one of the people
that was at the Turtle Hermit-sama's place.
Yeah, Kuririn. You've
beefed up quite a bit, haven't you?
You're just like Goku was, when he was a kid.
You're small, but strong, right?
Father said that about you a lot.
You're going to fight alongside us, right?
He didn't have to include that "small" part.
That jerk– he grows a little
bit taller, and thinks he's so big...
Still, it must have been rough,
having Piccolo train you like this, right?
Mm-hmm. But Piccolo-san is a
much better person than I thought.
Enough chit-chat! They're here!
There they are, there they are!
There's one more of them
now, making three tough guys.
It appears that they know all about us.
T-Those are the Saiyans, huh?
Indeed, I can sense an
incredible ki from them.
D-Danger truly is closing in on us!
It looks as though you've
been waiting anxiously for us.
You've got that right.
Just for the record, let me ask you,
what the hell have you come here for?
That voice...
So, you're the one who defeated Raditz, right?
Voice?
Didn't Raditz tell you?
This acts as a communicator, too.
He's a Namekian!
So it would seem. I guess it's not
that surprising that Raditz was done in.
Namekian?
Piccolo! Y-You're an alien, too?
That would explain...
I-Is that right, Piccolo-san?
I get it. In addition to having
an unusually high battle power,
I've heard that Namekians
have certain remarkable abilities.
I'm a Namekian?
I've also heard that there are some of
them that can perform magician-like feats.
You must be the one who
created these Dragon Ball things.
Y-You even know about the Dragon Balls?!
The Dragon Balls are our first objective.
Hand them over to us
without making any trouble.
Even if you are Namekian, by yourself,
you're no more than a housefly to us.
Thanks. Because of you, I'm more-or-less
starting to understand my heritage.
But, unfortunately for you,
I'm not the one who created the Dragon Balls.
I'm the kind that
specializes in fighting, you see.
Come try me, and we'll see
whether or not I'm a housefly!
Kami-sama...
I-I didn't know. To think that I am an alien...
No wonder I always felt so
different from everyone else.
I am definitely the one who
created the Dragon Balls long ago.
Even though it was the first time I had
ever made any, they seemed strangely familiar.
There was probably someone on Planet Namek
that also created
something like the Dragon Balls.
There were still memories of
my distant ancestors within me.
Pipe down!
It looks like you don't have any
intention of telling us about the Dragon Balls.
Fine with me. You'll talk,
even if I have to force it out of you!
981...
1,220...
1,083...
Miserable fools! You plan on
facing us with that kind of battle power?
Nappa,
take off your Scouter.
What?
These guys can alter their
battle powers in response to the battle.
We can't rely on these values anymore.
Now that you mention it, that's right.
That idiotic wimp Raditz got done in
because he got overconfident
in his Scouter's figures, after all.
"T-That wimp Raditz"?
R-Raditz was that Saiyan
that you and Goku barely
managed to defeat together, right?
Wimp, huh?
I know–what do you say we have
ourselves a look at what they are capable of?
Hey, Nappa, there are still six
Saibaimen left, right? Bring them out.
Vegeta, you sure do like
having a good time, huh?
S-Saibaiman?
W-What's that?
Six of them, all right.
Once you see the Saibaimen,
I imagine you'll want to
tell us about the Dragon Balls.
This soil will grow some fine Saibaimen.
W-What is that?
All right!
T-Those guys are creepy!
T-These guys are pretty good!
So it would appear.
Those three are your targets.
Do them some harm, Saibaimen.
Saibaimen, born of the soil...
Their power is the real deal.
Will Gohan...
...Kuririn...
...and Piccolo be able to hold
out against them until Goku returns?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
You came after all, Yamucha!
Relax. I'll put all of these
Saibaimen away in one shot.
All right, come and get it!
Yamucha! Don't take those guys too lightly!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Yamucha Dies!
The Terror of the Saibaimen."
Father! Come quickly!
"Next time"
"Yamucha Dies!
The Terror of the Saibaimen"