Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Even against Goku and Piccolo,
the strongest combo in the world,
the strength of Raditz was overwhelming!
And so, unable to do anything,
Goku was faced with a crisis.
However, at that moment...
"Goku Dies!
There's Only One Last Chance."
W-What is this?!
I-It's Son Goku's boy...
I-Impossible!
G-Gohan!
R-Run, Gohan!
Run away!
B-Battle power...
O-One thousand...
one thousand three hundred seven?!
Stop picking on...
...my father!
G-Gohan?
Father?
Did you–?
Father...
Y-You little brat!
R-Run!
Gohan, run away!
Run away! Quickly!
N-Now his battle power is a mere one?
It changed suddenly,
along with his emotions.
Father...
Run!
Gohan!
S-Stop! Please stop! He's–
–still just a child? Is that
what you were going to say?
You've got to be joking! That brat has
a battle power far higher than you two!
I'm going to kill him now, while he's
still incapable of adeptly using his power.
Don't worry. You'll see
him again soon enough!
In the Other World, that is.
Wait!
You're the first one who has
inflicted this much damage on me.
But this is the end of the line for you.
W-Why, you!
You still have this much power left?!
Piccolo!
Hurry! Do that technique from earlier!
I've been getting it ready, just in case!
But it's still going to take...
a little bit more time!
Why didn't you grab his tail?!
If he decided to, he could
cut off his tail on his own!
Y-You knew about that?
Piccolo! Hurry!
Hurry it up, please!
Damn! Thanks to the blow that kid
landed on me... my power has dropped!
L-Let me go, Kakarrot! You idiot!
You're going to get it too,
clinging to me like this!
I'm going to die together with you!
Y-You're what?!
Are you out of your mind?!
This is the only way
there is to defeat you!
Son Goku!
I'm not going to hesitate here.
If I can wipe you out as well,
nothing could be better for me!
But then again,
your friends will probably just bring
you back to life with the Dragon Balls.
Piccolo... still not yet?
My ribs are broken!
H-Hurry!
O-One thousand
four hundred eighty-five?!
L-Let me go! I was in the wrong!
I-I'll never come to this planet again!
Y-You think you can fool me again?
It's no lie! Don't you believe the
word of your own older brother?!
Piccolo! Hurry and do it!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Are you ready for this?!
Do it!
W-Wait!
Makankosappo!
Stop!
D-Damn it to hell!
Damn... To think that I...
would be done in... by these guys!
T-Take that!
W-Who would have
thought... that Kakarrot...
...w-would even lay
down... his own life...
You idiot...
Son Goku can come
back to life right away.
W-What?!
We have these nice things called
Dragon Balls here on this planet.
By asking of them, any desire
one may have can become possible.
Bringing the dead
back to life, for example.
Damn it all...
Still, you've told me something good...
The entire situation up until now...
has been communicated to
m-my two pals, deep in space.
What?
They know that I've been done in...
...and they will be sure to come here...
...to handle not only you...
...but to completely mop up...
...e-every last person on this
planet, in the blink of an eye.
And while they're at it...
maybe they'll use those
whatever-you-called-them things...
and have me brought back to life.
T-Those...
...other two...
...when will they get here?
One year... just one year from now...
One year? Two more of
you... who are even stronger?
Your chances of winning will be
absolutely zero that time for sure...
Enjoy yourselves as much
as you can for the next year...
It was a short-lived joy, wasn't it?
You guys are no more
than worms, after all...
Right now, Goku-sa and the others must
be havin' a good time at the Kame House.
I wonder if Gohan is
adjustin' okay to them...
Still, he'll be okay.
That boy's got good manners.
I wish I had gone, too...
Gohan-chan!
Pa!
Chichi, where's Gohan-chan?
Hey, Gohan-chan!
I brung you a whole mess of presents–!
Pa!
I think it was around here somewhere.
You're out of your misery now.
You just had to go and spit out
all of that uncalled-for blather.
Son Goku, he's dead.
There's somebody there!
Some of them are down!
T-The only one standing is...
...Piccolo!
W-What the hell?
At that same time,
a great distance away in space...
That miserable Raditz...
He's dead.
He's pathetic! I mean, really...
...for him to be killed by someone
with a battle power of
just a bit more than a thousand!
What should we do? Put this
planet on hold and go there?
They mentioned something...
interesting, didn't they?
"Dragon... balls," or something.
Yeah. It sounds like
they can grant any wish.
All right then, let's go.
We're going to bring
Raditz back to life, right?
Don't make jokes! We don't need
that good-for-nothing any more.
We won't ever grow any older,
but instead have eternal youth.
How does that sound?
If that were so, we
could enjoy fighting forever!
I get you. That would be great!
That's how it happened.
I-I see...
Goku! Goku, I say!
Hey, Goku! Stay with us!
Gohan-kun is fine.
He's just unconscious.
Thank...
goodness...
He's coming around.
Goku...
Chichi won't... chew me out...
Son-kun...
K– uririn...
...this dying stuff...
it's pretty... n-nasty, ain't it?
Y-You might say that.
W-What are you saying,
Goku?! D-Don't give up!
This isn't like you!
Goku!
T-This time...
it doesn't look... so good for me...
D-Don't worry! We'll bring
you back to life right away!
I'm... counting... on it...
Goku...
Goku!
Everything else aside,
Kakarrot's son's battle power...
...was unusually high,
compared to Saiyan children.
It could have been some
kind of mistake, couldn't it?
No, there's no mistake.
Raditz did actually take a great
deal of damage from that kid's strike.
Apparently, when our blood
is mixed with an Earthling's,
it results in a hybrid with mighty power.
Hmph, a Super Saiyan, you mean?
I get it. If we were to produce
those guys one after another,
then once again, Saiyan
rule will no longer be a dream.
You've got to be kidding.
Just watch those guys grow and gain
even greater power for themselves.
Then it will be our
positions that are in danger.
That would be true.
In any case,
we will exterminate everyone on Earth.
Three days should be enough for that.
Until then, let's have ourselves a good,
long sleep for the first time in a while.
Yeah! I'll look forward
to seeing you in a year!
Goku!
Goku...
Son-kun! I can't stand you dying!
Goku!
He vanished!
I get it. This is Kami's doing.
This is something he would be capable of.
That bastard.
He's thinking of using Son Goku
again for some nonsense or other.
Some nonsense?
How does Kami-sama
intend to use Son Goku?
Now that Goku is no longer here to rely on,
is there any means left
of defending the Earth?
The mighty Saiyans
arrive on Earth in one year!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
I've ended up traveling across the Next World,
to train with someone named Kaio-sama.
What are you talking about?
Your son is just starting a hard
journey down in the Lower Realm.
Yeah, together with Piccolo.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Even Yama-sama is Surprised –
The Fight Continues in the Next World."
Father, I'm scared of Uncle Piccolo!
"Next time"
"Even Yama-sama is Surprised–
The Fight Continues in the Next World"