The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Vegeta, you...
Don't tell me you fell under
Babidi's spell on purpose.
"Tenkaichi Tournament"
If I hadn't done all this,
you wouldn't have fought me!
Babidi! Change us to a place
where no one else is around!
I have decided to fight Vegeta!
Goku, who at last resolves to confront Vegeta,
turns away even Kaioshin
as he steps in to stop them.
Here we go! I'll kill you, Kakarrot!
"Just You Wait, Babidi!!
Your Aspirations Will Not Be Allowed."
Um... Mister Satan, what should
we do about an awards ceremony?
Indeed, with all that commotion,
the spectators have fled,
and there's no television...
Under the circumstances, there
isn't much sense in having one.
Well, we'll just leave it at "See you later."
There's also the matter of the runner-up.
Runner-up?
That would have to be Contestant No. 18,
who remained until the end to go
one-on-one with you, wouldn't it?
N-No. 18?
"Martial"
Th-That's right! She may not have been my
equal, but truthfully, she did do quite well.
Yeah, she really was
something there! Superb, superb!
Vegeta, of all the...!
After wreckin' the grounds like
this, where has he gone off to?!
You don't suppose Goten-chan's been
buried under all that rubble, do you?
Vegeta... what's wrong with you?
What's wrong? I thought you were
going to bring this to an end quickly!
And I will!
K-Kakarrot!
Nice, nice, Vegeta!
That's the way!
Look, look!
Majin Boo's energy is quickly,
quickly being stored up!
All that's left is how we're going
to serve them up, right Dabura?
That is right.
Th-They're here!
Y-You expect to get by us?!
Some of Babidi's warriors?
We don't have time to toy
with these small fry. Let's hurry!
Right!
H-Hey, let's go!
As good as ever!
They sure are confident.
Does this mean they don't feel it
necessary to buy any more time?
Let's go, onto where Majin Boo's ball is!
Right!
Very soon, you will see the death
of Kaioshin before your very eyes!
I'm counting on it, Dabura!
You defy me? You defy me, Kakarrot?!
What are you doing, Goten?!
If we're not quick, we won't
be able to see Majin Boo!
But...
What is it?
I have to go pee!
Go pee? Just hold it in!
I can't! After all, I haven't gone the whole time
since the tournament started!
I'm going to leak out!
I can't do anything with you!
Okay, over there!
Go do it over there!
Hurry!
Yeah!
–Trunks-kun!
–Me too!
Mine's shooting out so far!
Look at mine!
Whee! There it goes! There it goes!
–Ah, that startled me!
–We have to hurry!
Let's fly, Goten!
Yeah!
W-What force! Vegeta's raised
his power quite a bit, huh?
Vegeta...
What's the matter, weren't
you going to end this quickly?
That's what I'm trying to do.
And this is the way?
However, this does not approach
the humiliation I've been subjected to!
Not yet! Even at this, it still falls far, far short!
For myself, the proud Saiyan prince,
to be pitied by a lower-class
warrior, such as yourself...
To have my life saved by you...!
You are to be put to death!
I'll tear you clean apart!
Starting with your arms!
What?!
Where is he?
Here, Kakarrot!
Kamehame...
Take this!
Is that Majin Boo's ball?
Yes. The fearsome Majin Boo,
born of the evil Madoshi Bibidi, is inside there.
Incredible. This is an enormous, evil ki,
the likes of which I've never felt until now.
That is correct.
I welcome you here.
How nice of you to come, Kaioshin.
I have come to defeat you, Babidi.
Rotten enemy of my papa!
I will also terminate the
revival of the Majin Boo.
Unfortunately, I do not think
it will go that smoothly for you.
The demonic king, Dabura, is here as well!
Let's hurry, Gohan-san. Even as
we're here, the damage energy
from Goku-san may be on its way to Majin Boo!
–Right.
–I will fight Babidi.
An unprecedented, fierce conflict between
Goku and Vegeta! Who will be the winner?
Further, will Shin and Gohan be
able to defeat Babidi and Dabura,
and stop Majin Boo from being revived?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Our fighting has allowed
Majin Boo's energy to be filled up.
This is the worst! I've
completely misjudged things!
How has Goku-san's damage
energy filled it up so quickly?!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Seal is Broken!
Out Comes the Vicious Majin Boo!!"
Rats! Isn't there anything we can do now?!
"Next time"
"The Seal is Broken!
Out Comes the Vicious Majin Boo!!"