Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Under Popo's guidance, Bulma
traveled to the ends of the earth,
where she was shown a mysterious object.
When Planet Namek had bad time,
Kami-sama's parents put child
Kami-sama aboard, sent to Earth.
Try saying something
in Namekian. Tell it to fly.
Anywhere is fine!
I know, how about around Jupiter for now?
It's Jupiter! That's incredible!
This is an incredible spaceship! Not
even Planet Namek is too far away like this!
"Blast-off for Planet Namek!
The Terror Awaiting Gohan & Co."
Wow, this truly is amazing.
The universe really is a big place.
To think that there's a genius
even greater than myself out there...
This is no time to be admiring it, Dad.
Check it out as fast as possible, okay?
Okay, okay.
So anyway, this is an incredible spaceship.
It took us to Jupiter, just like that!
Really, it was amazing!
Huh? Sweet olives?
What's wrong with your nose?
No! Jupiter! Jupiter!
Anyhow, once we finish up here,
we're taking off, so get everyone together!
I'm counting on you!
Nah, it's nothin'.
Here.
I've had enough.
No you haven't! You've got to eat,
and recover from your injuries, quick.
Okay.
We've done it, Goku!
Cheer up! Word is, we've found a
spaceship! We can go to Planet Namek!
Piccolo and Tenshinhan and the
others will be coming back to life for sure!
Is that right?
Good work.
I splurged, and bought this many! See?
G-Gohan-chan?
Where did he go?!
What's wrong?
Gohan-chan isn't here.
Huh? He was there reading
his book just a little while ago.
He shouldn't even be
able to walk properly yet...
What if he breaks a bone?!
She's making too much of it.
35...
36...
37...
38...
That was close, that was close...
Gohan-chan!
Where could Gohan-chan have gone?
His legs haven't healed,
so he couldn't be up walkin'...
All righty...
That should be okay.
Gohan-chan! Gohan-chan!
Gohan-chan!
What are you doin' in a place like this?!
Mother... It was such a nice day,
I thought I would read my book outside.
Don't be so rash!
Come on, I'll carry you back to the room.
I-I'm completely okay now...
That carelessness of yours
is dangerous. Come on, get on.
Good grief, you're so
reckless. Who are you takin' after?
What that all means is, the
spaceship is absolutely okay!
In that spaceship, you'll be able to
get to Planet Namek in just one month!
All that's left is to
remodel the interior a little.
I'd say you can leave in five days.
That's right.
To Planet Namek in Kami-sama's
spaceship, huh? Amazing!
That glimmer of light
looks like it's becoming reality.
And so, Popo-san, it's all up to
you to go to Planet Namek for us.
Mister Popo not going.
Mister Popo can't go. Be away from
Kami-sama's palace two months. Can't.
Oh, no! But you're the only one
who knows how to speak Namekian!
You also seem pretty tough.
Popo-san, you have to be the one who goes!
No worry. Teach you Namekian.
Well, Bulma-san, you'll have to go.
If anything were to happen, you're the only
one familiar with the mechanics, Bulma-san.
Fine, then. It doesn't sound all that dangerous.
I'll have to build in a shower room, too...
...and a more comfortable bed, and a stereo...
But there's no way I'm going by
myself, okay? Someone come with me!
I'm tellin' ya right now,
there ain't no way I'm goin'.
Nobody was expecting you to.
Ahem...
Two months round trip, huh? All right,
I guess I've got no choice but to go with you.
That will just add unnecessary danger!
I knew it.
Son-kun is in this state and all...
Kuririn, you'll come with me, right?
M-Me? That's okay and all, but
for two months? I wanted to train...
You never know when that
Saiyan will be coming again.
Nice for you. I wanted to go, too.
I wanted to see what kind of Shen
Long would appear on Planet Namek.
Well, Goku, you stay here and rest up,
and come up with a strategy
against the Saiyan, or something.
Yeah, right. We'll be
counting on the both of you.
U-Um...
What's the matter? Have to go potty?
P-Please take me, too!
G-Gohan-chan! W-What kind of silly joke is that?
It's not a joke! I-I really want to go...
D-Don't be absurd! It'll take two
more months, on top of everythin' else!
I'm sorry. I want to go, no matter what.
I want to be the one who
brings Piccolo-san back to life myself.
So that's it. Well said, Gohan.
What kind of nonsense are you two talkin'?!
There's no reason for
Gohan-chan to be doin' any of this!
What if anythin' were to happen?!
For cryin' out loud, he
hasn't even healed enough!
We'd better stand back.
As far as my body goes, I'm fine.
W-What are you doin'?!
S-Stop that, Gohan-chan!
I beg you, please take me.
I won't stand for this!
I absolutely won't stand for this!
It's two months! On top of the year
of anxiety I've already been through!
What about cram school?
What about your lessons?!
You've already fallen way
behind the other children!
Piccolo's got nothin' to do with anythin'!
You are a little child, and
you should act like a child!
Shut up!
Gohan-chan... you've turned into a delinquent!
M-Mother... right now... right now
really isn't the time to be talking about that.
We all fought desperately
to save everyone on Earth,
and we have to bring
those who died back to life,
to fight against the Saiyan once again!
I can... I can fight, too!
I have to... I have to do something!
Understand, Mother. I'm sorry.
That kid says some pretty
awesome things once in a while.
He's got you beat, Chichi.
Now let Gohan go off into space willingly.
Gohan, nice going.
You really have grown stronger.
It's okay, I tell you. He'll be completely fine.
Let us take care of him.
There won't be anything
dangerous this time around, after all.
Can you learn Namekian in five days?
Right, we'll have to input
it all into a translator device,
so... let's see, we'll need ten days.
All right, let's meet up ten
days from now at Kame House!
Right!
"Good day" is "Pikonatto."
"Pikonatto," huh?
All right, you're fine.
Yow!
You don't need to bother...
Oh, no! If you say that,
girls aren't goin' to like you.
Time for your medicine already.
Oh, water, water...
Hit me.
All right!
Don't hold back! Hit me as hard as you can!
Right.
Good. If you can hit that
hard, you'll be fine, Gohan.
You'll do a great job of standing in for me.
And so, in the blink of
an eye, ten days went by,
and the day of launch had come.
Whoo! Can we really get
to Planet Namek in this thing?
Well, don't you look sharp, Kuririn?
You're not, by any chance,
making light of outer space, are you?
I even cut my hair, because it
would be in the way inside my space suit!
Well? Isn't Gohan-kun here yet?
He'll be coming really soon, from the hospital.
He hadn't been discharged yet?
No. Chichi-san insisted that
he remain up until the last minute.
Good grief, she's so overprotective.
Say, Bulma-san...
Do you think we should take umbrellas?
Planet Namek won't
necessarily have nice weather.
Suit yourself.
Oh, looks like they're here.
Sorry we're a little late.
So this is the spaceship, huh?
It's somethin' else!
Okay, Gohan-chan, make
sure you're careful as you go.
What's the matter? Come on out.
Make sure you brush your teeth after meals.
Is that really you, Gohan?
What happened to your hair?
F-Father laughed at me, too.
Whatever else you might say, this is
the first time man is goin' to outer space.
We don't want to be ill-mannered.
Uh, what is all that?
This is his change of
underwear and study gear...
this is two months' worth
of his medicine and vitamins...
his dryer...
his brush... his bowl and chopsticks... also–
T-That's enough.
Well, shall we get going right away, then?
For some reason, I'm feeling discouraged.
We're depending on you. Make
sure you find the Dragon Balls for us.
Right!
"Piccolo."
Grandpa, Mother, Turtle Hermit-san,
Turtle-san, we're off. Take care.
"Piccolo."
Make sure to eat all your meals!
Send me a letter every day!
Bye!
This is a little exciting, huh?
Say, Bulma-san, where should I put my bag?
You can stick it wherever you need
to, can't you?! Hurry up and sit down!
She's in a bad mood for some reason.
Five seconds to launch!
Destination: Planet Namek!
J-Just a minute!
4...
3...
2...
1...
W-W-We still haven't f-fastened our b-b-belts!
It's too late to stop now, you know!
T-That truly is some tremendous
speed. They're out of sight already.
Gohan-chan! Be sure to rinse, too!
You can move about freely now.
Once we're out of the
atmosphere, everything calms down.
Eh? Already?
I wanted to see Earth.
Huh? What are you doing, Bulma-san?
How nosy! I'm changing my clothes!
You're changing? You mean,
into pajamas? You're going to bed already?
Whoops, come to think of it,
I forgot to bring pajamas myself.
What about you, Gohan?
I made sure I brought some.
I know it's none of my business,
but can't you do anything
about that Shichigosan outfit?
This is just for the first part.
I actually have some clothes that
I made without Mother finding out about it.
Well?
You really do look up to Piccolo, don't you?
Yes. About the same as I do Father.
Huh? T-Those are unusual pajamas, huh?
They look hard to sleep in.
Of course they're not
pajamas! When I saw you guys,
I felt like an idiot for working so
hard getting ready to go into space.
Hey, did we do something wrong?
Search me.
Good luck, Gohan.
The trio had departed for Planet Namek,
carrying the hopes of Goku and the others...
...with no way of knowing the
incredible terror that awaited them.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
It's already been a week since
Gohan and the others left Earth, huh?
Outer space sure is a boring place, huh?
Bulma-san, please, look closely at this.
There's something moving in front of us.
Could they be, by any chance, aliens?!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Friends or Foes? Children of
the Mysterious Giant Spaceship."
Don't kill us! We're not your enemy!
"Next time"
"Friends or Foes? Children of
the Mysterious Giant Spaceship"