Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Burning with vengeance against Son Goku,
Freeza and his father,
Cold the Great, arrived on Earth.
However, a mysterious
young man stood in their way.
Son Goku-san is not the
one and only Super Saiyan...
...meaning there is another one, right here.
Burn in hell!
You did it, Freeza.
Looks as though he was
no match for us after all.
Freeza!
You expect such a low-level attack to...?
"Heya!! It's Been a While...
Son Goku Returns."
Kuririn-san, over there!
There's no mistaking it,
that was Freeza just now!
It took him only a
moment to take Freeza apart!
What are you guys using to see with?
I'm surprised you could make that out at all!
Anyhow, Son-kun must
have really gotten stronger.
He only needed a second
to take care of Freeza, right?
I guess he saved Earth yet again!
That guy isn't Goku.
But he does appear to be a Super Saiyan.
Piccolo-san!
I'm going too!
Me too!
Yeah, I'm going too!
Hold on!
Don't you leave me behind in a place like this!
This feels great!
Not bad, are you?
That was wonderful, Super Saiyan.
Even greater than I had imagined.
To think you were able to eliminate...
...my son Freeza in that brief instant...
How would you like to
take Freeza's place as my son?
Having the greatest strength in the universe
makes you especially qualified to join my clan.
You will be able to do as you
please, not only with this Earth,
but with many other wonderful worlds.
I'm not interested.
I thought it was a good idea.
What a shame.
Now then, that sword you have there,
it's a very nice sword indeed.
It sliced through the tempered body of Freeza...
...without the slightest difficulty, after all.
Would you let me see it for a moment?
What's the matter?
Are you afraid to hand your sword over to me?
I see, it has indeed been ground very well.
Leaving that aside, the reason
you were able to defeat Freeza,
is because you had this sword.
Don't you think so?
What is it you're trying to say?
It's a simple matter, really.
In short, without this sword,
you cannot win against me!
Apparently, it takes more than just the sword.
W-Wait!
He's a... Super Saiyan all right!
Spa-Spare my life!
Please!
Spare my life!
I know, I'll give you one of my worlds!
No, I'll give you all the worlds in this system!
P-Pl-Please!
Who in the world is that guy?!
He not only defeated Freeza,
but that other brute with the huge ki,
without any difficulty at all.
I'm now going to go greet Son Goku-san!
Won't you come with me?!
What?
How come?
How come he knows about Father?
This way.
Shortly, Son Goku-san is
due to arrive in this area.
Just what is the story with this guy?
A Super Saiyan? Him? Don't be ridiculous!
There's no way there
can be any other Saiyans!
Son Goku-san will arrive in three hours.
Please come with me.
I'm–I'm going to go with him!
Now, hold on!
We don't know anything about him.
I'm going too.
He defeated Freeza and his men,
and knows about Son Goku.
I can't imagine he's all that bad.
Besides that, I'm also curious.
I wonder if he's really planning
on greeting Son Goku, like he says.
How do you think he knows? It's strange, huh?
I guess I'll go, and discover
who this guy really is!
Hey, wait a minute!
Point five-seven-three mark
one-eight-two-two-zero.
Well, I guess this is it.
Be careful, everyone!
He's produced a strange object!
There's still some time
before Son Goku-san arrives.
There's plenty here to drink.
If you like, be my guest.
I'll take one.
Me too!
Hey, Gohan!
I'll help myself, thank you. Hmm, which one?
I don't remember us
having this in our product line.
I'll take this one.
Wow, delicious!
Ah, you're right!
Maybe I'll have one too.
–Yum!
–Yeah!
Have we met somewhere?
Uh, no, not exactly.
How is it you know about Father?
I've only heard stories
about him. We've never met.
Well then, how do you know that
Goku will land here in three hours?
That, uh...
Forgive me, I cannot say.
What do you mean you can't say?
Who exactly are you?
How did you come to have such power?
Forgive me. That as well...
Um, when you defeated Freeza,
you were a Super Saiyan, right?
Yes, that's right.
Cut the crap!
Counting me and Kakarrot–or
Son Goku as he's known here on Earth–
and that earthling half-breed kid there,
there aren't any Saiyans left but us three!
Therefore, there's no
way you could be a Saiyan!
But the fact remains, he really
did become a Super Saiyan,
and defeated Freeza.
On top of that, all Saiyans are black-haired.
Huh?
Say, isn't that the trademark of
my family's Capsule Corporation?
How come?
Are you one of our employees?
That's not entirely true.
That's a secret too?
Then are your name and
age also a private matter?
I can't tell you my name,
but I can say I'm 17 years old.
Eh... 17.
Not being able to tell us
his name is a little strange.
Yeah, there's no reason
for him to keep that from us.
He's an odd one.
Hey, let's cut out the questions,
we're making him feel awkward.
After all, this kid saved us,
and the Earth as well.
Right.
Hey, Chichi!
Chichi!
Wh-Whatcha got there?
I bought it from a TV shop-at-home show.
It's the latest in study centers.
This is a Somnioscholastic bed,
which lets you increase
your knowledge while sleepin'.
Besides that, there's this convenient portable
encyclopedia tape that comes with it.
Now, both day and night,
I can make sure Gohan keeps studyin'
and studyin' and studyin' some more.
Gohan! Get home soon!
Um, Piccolo-san?
I've been wanting to ask
you for some time now...
What?
Back a year ago,
when Dende and the other
Namekians moved to their new planet,
why didn't you go along
with them, Piccolo-san?
There's no great reason.
I just wouldn't be able to put up
with their dull, uninspiring lifestyle.
So even now, you're passing
each day with your harsh training?
You might say that.
You know, Vegeta's also gone all day long.
I'm sure he's off somewhere training hard.
Yeah. I guess even now he's
thinking of defeating Goku.
That guy bears an incredibly high level of pride,
since he was the prince of all Saiyans, I hear.
Say, don't you think there's a resemblance?
What do you mean?
Between that unusual boy and Vegeta.
Look, there's something about them.
I don't know, maybe there is
something similar about them.
But I think their dispositions
are completely different.
Why have you been staring
at me so for the last while?
If you really are a Saiyan yourself,
I shouldn't be such a rare sight.
I'm sorry.
Bothersome punk.
I suppose he...
...might be someone Son Goku
knew on some planet out in space.
That's not unthinkable, is it?
But he seems to be right
at home here on Earth.
Well, like he said, if Son Goku
really does show up here,
we should be able to
unravel some of this mystery.
I wonder if Goku really is coming.
S-Sorry!
Three hours have passed.
Son Goku-san should be landing any moment.
Really?
It's true!
I feel it! I can feel his ki!
He's coming!
There's something coming, that's for sure!
Then, you mean what this boy said,
about the time and location, was all accurate?
It's Father! It's Father's ki!
He's here!
Over there!
Wait! Wait for me!
Hold on!
Down there!
Huh?
Welcome home, Father!
Goku!
You really are too much!
How come all you guys are here?
Just as the young man said,
Son Goku has returned home.
However, the mystery surrounding
him has just grown more complex.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Whoa, what a surprise!
Imagine, you being Vegeta's child!
My name is Trunks. I came
from twenty years in the future.
In three years, a terrifying
enemy will appear. I came to tell you.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"My Dad is Vegeta...
Admissions of the Mysterious Youth."
I get it. So that's why
he can turn Super Saiyan.
"Next time"
"My Dad is Vegeta...
Admissions of the Mysterious Youth"