Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Three years from now, on
March 12, at around 10:00 a.m.,
on an island 9 kilometers
southeast of Metro South,
a pair of Artificial Humans will appear,
and plunge the world
into the depths of terror.
So says the mysterious young man Trunks,
before returning into the future.
In preparation for the upcoming conflict,
Goku and the others
begin their intense training.
And then, three years later, the
dreadful day of destiny finally arrives.
What kind of battle awaits Goku and friends?
"Murderers Who Leave No Trace –
Which Ones Are the Artificial Humans!?"
Hey, Gohan!
You don't have to fly yourself all
out like that, we'll get there in time!
You're going to use all your
strength before the fight even starts!
Okay!
Son Goku, how about it?
In your honest opinion,
against these new foes...
Do you think we can win?
There's no way to know
without seeing them first.
I'll tell you once we get started.
How nice for you to be so carefree.
I'm sure I can beat these Artificial Humans...
But I can't shake this terrible
foreboding feeling I have.
Terrible foreboding?
Piccolo, do me a favor, if things
get rough on you, don't overdo it.
After all, if you die, the
Dragon Balls will disappear too.
Father, look! It's Kuririn-san!
Kuririn-san!
Look how big you're getting, Gohan!
Hey!
–Hey...
–What's the matter, Kuririn?
After all this time,
aren't you excited to see us?
We're just about to wage the fight
of our lives against horrible monsters.
How can you expect me to be cheery?
I'm not a Super Saiyan, you know.
About nine kilometers southwest of Metro South...
There it is! That island there!
This is a pretty big island.
Yeah. This is bad.
There's a relatively large city down there.
If we can't lure the Artificial
Humans away from here,
the people down there will
likely become casualties of our fight.
You're right.
I can feel a pair of large
ki over on that mountain.
That's probably Yamucha and the others.
Right, let's go!
It's them, all right, Goku's group!
Hey, there!
Hey!
We've been waiting for you.
You guys are a little late.
Bulma!
Bulma-san!
Yoo-hoo! Wow, look how
tall you are now, Gohan-kun!
I don't believe it! What are you doing here?
Observing, of course!
It'll be all right.
I just want a quick look at the
Artificial Humans, then I'll go back.
Never mind that,
I'm more surprised by what you've
got in your arms there, Bulma-san.
You've gotten married, right?
You and Yamucha-san.
He isn't my kid.
We broke up some time ago.
You'll be shocked when
you hear whose kid that is.
Your daddy is Vegeta, huh, Trunks?
How did you know that?
I wanted to surprise everyone
here, so I didn't contact any of you!
Uh, yeah, I just sort of
had a hunch, you know?
I mean, his face does
kind of look like Vegeta's.
You even guessed his name!
Wow, really? Incredible!
I wonder if I have psychic abilities.
That's really Vegeta's child?
So where is Vegeta, anyhow?
I don't see him around.
Well, I don't know.
We haven't been living together.
He'll probably be here before long, though.
He's apparently gone through a
lot of training to prepare for this day.
Oh, he'll come. He'll come for sure.
As far as Chaozu goes,
I left him behind this time.
Frankly, he's not up to this kind of fight.
So, what time is it now?
Let's see, it's 9:30.
They'll show themselves in
another thirty minutes or so.
You really should go
back now, while you still can.
Especially since you've got that baby with you!
Like I said, once I get a peek at
the Artificial Humans, I'll go back.
So, thirty more minutes.
Hey, Trunks!
Trunks-chan!
I've made you another toy! Huh?
Don't tell me Bulma's taken him to
show off around the neighborhood again?
I swear, there's just no
helping someone like her.
On the other hand,
he's such a cute grandson!
Who can blame her?
Boy, is he going to be
surprised when I show him this!
Googly-googly-goo!
Say, Kuririn-san, you give it a try!
Who, me?
I wonder what kind of face should I pull?
Ahem, I haven't done anything yet.
There's someone headed this way.
They aren't malicious.
Maybe it's Vegeta-san.
Nah, he is malicious.
Ah, there they are, there!
Yajirobe!
I'm glad I got here in time.
Have you come to fight too?
Here. I'm droppin' off these
senzu Karin-sama sent yas.
My hero! You can always count on Karin-sama!
Well, besta luck to yas.
Yajirobe, you're fighting too, ain't you?
See now, I ain't like the resta you idiots,
'cuz I don't wanna die.
Don't tell me ya expected
me to hang around with y'all.
Don't you guys find it a little strange?
It's well past 10 o'clock now,
yet we still haven't felt
any sign of our opponents.
Now that you mention it...
You don't suppose what
he told us isn't true, do you?
I mean, Artificial Humans! Come on!
Well, he did say it was around 10 o'clock.
It's only 10:17 now, so
it's too early to tell for sure.
Yeah, but figure, we're
not sensing any strong ki.
If they're really all that strong,
we should be able to sense
them anywhere on Earth.
What happened?!
It's Yajirobe!
Look! There's someone there!
They attacked him!
They've descended into the city!
Where did they go?!
Did you see them, Goku?
No! I didn't see what they looked like!
How can it be?
I didn't sense any ki at all!
It's because they're Artificial Humans!
They don't have ki!
They what?!
Where are they?! Where did they go?!
Damn.
If we can't sense their ki, we'll
just have to search them out visually.
All right. Let's split up and find them.
Bulma, hang on to these!
Remember now, don't get in over your heads.
Once you find them, let the
rest of us know immediately!
Gohan, you look after Yajirobe.
He should still be alive.
Right!
Let's go!!
Shoot! Where are they?! Where did they go?!
I wish I'd had Trunks show me
a photo of them or something.
Dammit, man. Where are they?!
He-He flew here!
That's not them.
Them either.
–Hey, have you seen anyone
out of the ordinary?
–Y-Yeah!
What?!
You!
Are you okay?
Who were them guys?
Are those guys really here somewhere?
Hey, look at that. It fell into the ocean.
Hey, did you fellas see it too?
A Sky Car just blew up!
Did you see it?
What's the matter?
Hey you, get out of my way!
I said move it!
Stupid clod, what do you think
you're doing in the middle of the stree–?
A scream!
A human with an abnormally
high energy level is approaching.
Could my Search System be malfunctioning?
It is not a malfunction, No. 20.
I am tracking the same energy.
But this reading is far beyond
our data for a normal person.
We've found him already. It is Son Goku.
It came from around here.
Where are they? Where have they gone?
Hey, you there!
You two!
Who was it that killed these people?
Did you see anything?
–Yeah, there were two strange guys.
–Right, they were there just
a second ago, but they disappeared.
They disappeared?
Damn.
In any case, I'd better call everyone.
No, it is not Son Goku.
There is no exact data match.
There is a 96 percent probability
that this is the human Yamucha.
In any event, we can take a
great deal of energy from him.
But without those guys here,
what's the point in calling everyone in?
I don't suppose you guys saw anything?
Like where those two murderers ran off to?
Don't tell me...
We're them.
Everybody!
What's that?!
M-My power...
Finally, the attack of the Artificial Humans,
whose only purpose is that
of mass slaughter, has begun.
What will be the fate of
Yamucha, their first victim?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Hey, you Artificial Humans!
How dare you do that to Yamucha!
Come with me, both
of you! I'll smash you up!
You guys don't understand how
terrible these Artificial Humans are!
Those guys suck the power out of you!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Cold-Blooded No. 20's Hideous Atrocities!!
Goku's Super Transformation of Anger."
Father is strong!
"Next time"
"The Cold-Blooded No. 20's Hideous Atrocities!!
Goku's Super Transformation of Anger"