Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
At last, Cell has achieved his perfect form.
His hidden powers overwhelmed even Super Vegeta.
Trunks! It's now or never!
Now's the time to become
that drastic Super Saiyan!
I will... kill you, Cell!
The time when I will prove the
strength of this perfect form has come.
"A Future of Despair!!
Trunks, the Man Who Lived Through Hell."
That ki is so large it's terrifying...
It's Trunks' ki.
Awesome... And we've
already gotten pretty far away.
Those Saiyans really are frightful!
Now we're havin' an earthquake!
This is awful.
Pardon me a moment...
What are you doin', you nasty old man?!
An incredible ki... I-Is this...?
It's Trunks' ki.
It's more awesome than
Vegeta's. Far more awesome!
He'll be able to defeat Cell like this!
An admirable power.
Certainly one incomparable
to that of your father, Vegeta's.
I will no longer allow you
Artificial Humans to have your own way!
I will not let you create that miserable future,
and allow that hell to be repeated!
It's the Artificial Humans!
The Artificial Humans have come to attack us!
It's No. 17 and No. 18!
Destroying cities sure is fun, huh?
Take this city...
how many hundreds of years
did it take to become like this?
But it only takes a moment to destroy it.
Even so, it's getting a bit dull.
Isn't there anyone with a
little backbone to face us?
The Artificial Humans were strong. Too strong.
The warriors who stood against
them were all killed with ferocious power
Including my father, Vegeta...
Dammit!
Piccolo-san too...
Kuririn-san too...
As well as Tenshinhan-san,
Yamucha-san, Yajirobe-san...
Everyone... Everyone was done in.
Only myself and Gohan-san remained.
Oh? Son Gohan, is it?
You guys aren't going to get your way forever!
Vegeta and Piccolo, who we also defeated,
tried the same kind of posturing, you know.
Trunks, stay back!
Right!
Gohan-san!
How dare you cut my precious hair!
Dammit...!
Die!!
Masenko!!
Dammit! Where are they?!
In that case, we'll have
to comb the area for them!
We'll just destroy one place after another!
Gohan-san...
It's no good.
We're just no match for them!
Sure is aggravating, huh?
If only Father,
who died of that heart disease,
was still alive at times like these...!
Knowing Father,
he would have fought courageously,
without hesitation, at any time!
I want to be strong, like Father!
Gohan-san...
After that, the battle with the
Artificial Humans continued...
And then, in time, Gohan-san was killed.
I became the only warrior remaining.
Because of just two Artificial Humans,
the future had become hell.
I won't let that miserable
future happen again! Cell!
For the future of the Earth, I will kill you!
Good, good! Better and better!
Such marvelous power!
You might have even
surpassed me. I am pleased!
I would bet that even Doctor
Gero-sama is happy because of you.
After all, we have finally come across
an opponent to test my ultimate power.
Cell! I am Doctor Gero.
You are the ultimate artificial human,
cultured by my computer from the cells...
...of martial arts experts that I have gathered.
I look forward to watching
as you become complete–
the ultimate Artificial Human,
with terrible, mind-boggling powers!
Cell, you will absorb the energy
of the living, and continue to grow.
And then, by absorbing No. 17 and No. 18,
two of the Artificial Humans that I have created,
and becoming your perfect form,
you can obtain ultimate power,
and be invincible in this world!
W-What is that monster?!
Get him! Capture him!
Run!
Help me–
Doctor Gero's research was perfect.
I, having been created from the cells
of the best of the martial arts experts,
was unopposed.
However, I did not come across No. 17 or No. 18,
whom I was searching for, anywhere.
When I came forth upon the Earth,
No. 17 and No. 18, whom I was seeking out,
were no longer around.
Apparently, you had defeated them.
However, thanks to your time machine,
I was able to return into the past like this,
meet the No. 17 and No. 18 of this time,
and become my perfect form.
At last, my wish has been granted!
I would like to test the power
of this perfect form right away!
That's just what I was hoping for, Cell!
I will now show you the
true power of the Saiyans.
What?!
W-What are those guys?!
I can't see their movements at all!
I will kill you!
I will not let you Artificial Humans
have your way with the Earth!
Indeed, you certainly do have marvelous power.
You have well surpassed me.
However, you cannot beat me like this.
Absolutely not!
Speak hollow boasts to me, will you?
I see...
The clash between Trunks,
with his absolute self-assuredness,
and Cell, with the tenacity of his perfect form,
has gotten underway.
However, why in the world is it...
...that Cell is poised to the
point of being frightening?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Trunks' ki has grown extremely faint.
And he said he was sure to win, too.
I will give you ten days' time, free of charge.
See that you get good and strong.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Super Trunks Has a Weakness!!
Cell's Shocking Bombshell Declaration."
You say Cell is holding
a martial arts tournament?
"Next time"
"Super Trunks Has a Weakness!!
Cell's Shocking Bombshell Declaration"