Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
The power of the Saiyans who had
landed on Earth was something fearsome.
However, it would still take Son Goku,
on whom everyone was counting,
one day to travel back home
along the Serpentine Road.
Piccolo, Gohan, and Kuririn
were the first to face the Saiyans.
However, the Saiyans
themselves were not going to fight;
instead, they brought forth six strange
creatures, called Saibaimen, out from the dirt.
Those three are your targets.
Do them some harm, Saibaimen.
"Yamucha Dies!
The Terror of the Saibaimen."
Gohan! Don't take your eyes off of theirs!
R-Right!
There's nothing to be afraid of.
Right!
Gohan, don't lose your nerve!
R-Right!
This time, shall we take the fight to them?
Kuririn!
Tenshinhan!
Chaozu, you're here, too?
Mm-hmm!
Weren't there only
supposed to be two Saiyans?
Well, a lot has happened.
It looks like there are more of them.
However many there are, it's all the same.
Is that him? Goku's son?
Yeah. He appears to have
been trained quite a bit by Piccolo.
He's got a fine look to him.
What shrimps...
Saibaimen, make them all suffer!
Just a minute!
Kuririn, sorry I'm late.
Yamucha-san!
I guess we're all here, except for Goku.
Yeah!
1... 2... 3... 4... 5... 6, huh?
Interesting. The exact number
of Saibaimen that we have here.
Yes, it is.
How about you all take turns
fighting each one of our soldiers?
It will be a game.
A game?! Ridiculous!
Stop beating around the bush
and let's settle this right here and now!
Now, now, where's the harm? It works
out better for our side to do it this way.
Goku hasn't arrived yet, after all.
Very well.
I'll lead off. Now, come and get it!
He's going to be bowled over once he
realizes how strong the Saibaimen are!
So, which one of you is going to face me?
You go first. Hammer him
with all you've got. Understood?
T-Ten-san, good luck!
We're going to start reporting
from above the scene now...
Whoa! Those are the Saiyans!
The Saiyans!
Noisy mosquitoes!
Okay, Saibaiman!
Don't hold back! Crush him!
These Saiyans appear to possess
tremendous power. Is everything all right?
You idiot! 'Course everything ain't all right!
L-Like I said, my boys're fightin'
with 'em for your sakes right now!
–Who do you mean when you say "my boys"?
–Won't you be surprised when I tell ya!
The winner of the
Tenkaichi Tournament, Son Goku.
With him're Tenshinhan, and Piccolo, as well.
That is amazing!
So, everything'll be okay.
Prob'ly...
There's a good chance
that this'll be my last meal...
But I can't tell 'em that!
Muten Roshi-sama, are you sure
that Goku has been returned to life?
Gyumao!
He should be heading to where
Piccolo and the others are, right now.
W-Well then...
W-Where is my Gohan?
Muten Roshi-sama, where is my Gohan?
He's still with Piccolo and the others.
Chichi!
I-Incredible!
W-What?!
You did it!
That's Tenshinhan for you!
Incredible!
I-Impossible!
Saibaimen have a battle power of 1,200.
They're on par with
Raditz, as far as power goes!
His battle power must be higher than that.
B-But...
It's simple arithmetic.
That wasn't in our data...
Nappa, it looks like these guys
are going to be somewhat entertaining.
Ten-san! He's getting up!
V-Vegeta! How could you do that?
W-What is this strange uneasiness I'm feeling?
I've got a bad feeling about this.
Piccolo, hang in there somehow
until I get back! I'm counting on you!
W-Why?
Anything more would be a
waste of time. He couldn't win.
That Saibaiman took him
too lightly when he attacked.
I told him to go at it with everything he's got.
H-How could he do that?!
T-That Saiyan blew that
monster to bits in the blink of an eye!
What destructive force!
We'll be okay from here.
This special lens is working out great!
There's so much energy colliding
in the area, we can't get very close.
This is almost as if the end of the world
were approaching, it's such a spectacle.
Now, who's going to be next?
You guys, go all-out from the start this time!
A-All right... I'll face them.
Wait, Kuririn.
Yamucha-san...
Let me do this. I want to show them
that we've had enough of their games.
Yamucha-san, I can do that–
You've already been brought
back to life once by the Dragon Balls.
Supposing that the unthinkable happens,
you couldn't come back to life again.
Let me handle this. I'm going to take
care of the other five all at the same time.
Y-Yamucha-san...
What a beautiful friendship you
must have. All right, you take him on.
All right, come on!
Don't you take us so lightly!
He's getting cocky.
Give us a look...
...at how truly terrifying you Saibaimen are!
T-These are the Saiyans!
These are the Saiyans that have
plunged us into depths of terror!
Oh, that face!
It's one of the regulars
from the Tenkaichi Tournament!
Yamucha!
Yamucha-sama's face is
looking even tougher now, isn't it?
It's not just his face.
His abilities are a lot greater now, too.
Bulma, you're taken with him again, aren't you?
D-Don't be silly!
Once they defeat the Saiyans, you
could get married, couldn't you, Bulma-san?
Y-You don't mean–I mean, marriage!
Oh, that's the face of Piccolo Daimao!
It's Gohan!
G-Gohan-chan!
He's lookin' a lot tougher, huh?
Gohan-chan... Look at how you've become...
G-Gohan-chan is in the same
place as those revoltin' monsters?
Chichi!
W-Why isn't Goku there?
T-They vanished!
You fool! They're moving at high speed!
Try feeling out the movement of their ki.
T-The movement of their ki?
Everyone except for you can see them.
You all can see them? All right, then!
Use your whole body as your eyes.
My whole body as my eyes?
Do you see them?
I see them!
You're not getting away!
You did it!
I-Incredible!
He did it!
Yamucha-sama!
Yamucha did it!
Not again!
Looks like these monsters
aren't as strong as you think they are.
W-What did you say?
Keep your head, Nappa.
I'll take care of the other four by myself, too.
It appears that this time, you're the
ones who took the Saibaimen too lightly.
What?
Oh, crap!
N-No!
Yamucha!
Yes. That will do.
W-What a fiend! He blew himself up!
H-How awful!
H-He's dead...
W-What's wrong with Yamucha?
What happened, Oolong?
I-I'm not sure. I couldn't hear what he said.
Yamucha-sama! Yamucha-sama! Yamucha-sama!
Yamucha-sama!
Bulma...
No!
Y-Yamucha-san must have
had a bad feeling about this.
T-That's why he went in my place. Damn it all!
Damn it all! What do I
tell Pu-erh and Bulma-san?!
What a pathetic Saibaiman–ending in a draw!
What did he think he was
doing, against scum like that?!
Hey, clean that filth up.
He's polluting up the place.
You dirty bastard!
Get back, everyone!
Yamucha-san,
I'll avenge you, no matter what!
Let me show you the results of my training!
Having watched Yamucha die
before his eyes, Kuririn's fury has erupted!
What were the results of his training?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Damn it, right on the heels of
Yamucha, now Chaozu is going to die?
Chaozu has already been brought
back to life by the Dragonballs once.
He can't ever be brought back again!
You're going to pay for this, Saiyan!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Farewell, Ten-san!
Chaozu's Suicide Strategy."
Father! Come quickly!
"Next time"
"Farewell, Ten-san!
Chaozu's Suicide Strategy"