Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Using his finishing move, the Body Change,
Ginyu switched his body with Goku's.
Meanwhile, Gohan and Kuririn had finally
found the Dragon Balls that Freeza had hidden.
Come forth, Shen Long, and grant me my wish!
However, nothing appeared to happen.
And, as Ginyu once again
confronted Gohan and Kuririn...
...he released all of the ki in Goku's body,
to demonstrate how powerful he had become.
"That Ain't Me! Gohan, Don't
Lose Your Nerve, Hit Your Father!!"
Jheese, how high is my battle power now?
Yes, sir...
What's wrong? Jheese, hurry up and tell me!
I-It's 23,000.
What's that? I can't hear you!
23,000!
There, you hear that?!
Just 23,000! That's all!
Why?
W-Why, you ask?
23,000?
You say it's just 23,000?!
That's my body there.
You see, unless your mind and body are united,
you can't put out any great power!
Kuririn, Gohan, you can beat this guy now!
I-Impossible!
T-This is impossible!
I-It's true! We just might
be able to beat him like this!
Let's go, Gohan!
R-Right!
Now, Gohan!
What's the matter, Gohan?!
Father...
Gohan!
What's the matter, Gohan?
I-I'm sorry. For a moment,
he seemed like he really was Father.
I-I know what you mean. I feel the same way.
But that isn't Goku. It's Ginyu!
Got it?
Gohan... Kuririn...
Okay, it won't happen this time.
Here we go!
Jheese!
What are you doing? Why don't you fight?!
Y-Yes, sir!
Whoa!
You're going to face me!
Vegeta!
You mean that lousy Vegeta is still around?
You expect such a wimpy attack to hurt me?
W-Why?! This body is supposed to
have a power greater than 180,000!
Didn't you hear what Goku said before?
You can't use that body very well.
Why don't you just give up now?
G-Give up? You expect me,
Ginyu-sama to give up?!
Don't be ridiculous!
Kuririn... Gohan...
For someone such as yourself to
even consider picking a fight with me...
...takes a lot of guts!
Babble as much as you want!
How did you manage to hide yourself?!
There wasn't any reading on my Scouter!
You guys rely too much on your Scouters!
If you were to fight
against those guys from Earth,
you'd figure it out for yourself!
That is, assuming you don't die here first!
Don't be ridiculous! The Ginyu
Special Corps is made up of only
the most super-elite warriors in the universe!
There's no way a monkey bastard such as you
could ever stand a chance against me!
So you say, but you're actually afraid of
my renewed battle power, aren't you?
W-What?
Take a good, long look,
with your precious Scouter there.
Afraid, you say?
Me? Afraid of a battle
power such as yours, Vegeta?
I-Impossible...
Dammit!
It's broken!
Do you really think it was a malfunction?
W-Why, you!
Every time I recover from
being near death, I grow stronger.
I've also overcome the
limits of ordinary Saiyans,
and I'm still getting stronger!
Actually, I've just now realized something–
This growth in power is not just
due to some kind of gift that I have.
Which means, I must be getting
very close to becoming one myself!
A Super Saiyan!
W-What?
S-Stop talking nonsense!
A Super Saiyan is the mightiest of all warriors,
delighting in death and battle!
Kakarrot may not be
cold-hearted enough to become one,
but I'm different!
I-I-Impossible!
Attaway, attaway!
We're really hitting our stride!
L-Looks like we're going
to beat him, huh, Kuririn-san?
I-Impossible! How can I,
Commander of the Ginyu Special Corps,
be beaten by these guys?
G-Goku,
Sure enough, it was useless trying to stop you,
and now you've become tangled
up in things better left untouched.
Goku, soon you will realize the
hidden terror possessed by Freeza.
It's not too late, even now.
Depart from that planet as quickly as you can!
I-If Dende... can just
make it to where they are...
You Namekians really are very stubborn.
You have absolutely no chance of winning.
I do not want to use my energy needlessly.
Dende...
I wonder how much longer I will
be able to view Namek's scenery.
I hope it is until Dende reaches the Earthlings.
W-When Grand Elder-sama dies,
the Dragon Balls will also disappear.
Before that happens, I have to
hurry and meet up with those people.
Oh, no!
Gohan!
This is strange.
It's like suddenly, it seems
like he's gotten much stronger.
Watch yourself, Gohan!
R-Right!
Impressive.
Looks like he's starting
to get used to my body.
This ain't good.
From here on out,
I'm not going to be pushed
around by rubbish like you guys!
Here it comes! The Ginyu Special Corps'...
I haven't done this by myself very much,
but there's got to be something
good for me to say here...
Oh well, maybe I'll just skip it
this time and leap right into battle.
I-I-I wasn't finished yet!
I won't be beaten by that flimsy blast!
This one will be even harder!
Gohan! Get out of the way!
Goku!
F-Father...
Yow-ow-ow!
H-How did you manage that in your condition?!
I-It's just like you're doing.
I'm starting to get used to this body.
I'm going to fight, too!
Y-You may have become partially used to it,
but you still can't generate its full power.
We've got to eliminate him,
before he completely masters my body.
With the three of us, we can beat him!
Kuririn! Gohan!
Right, Father!
Y-Yeah!
There's something strange about this, huh?
I-I feel the same way.
I-It's a little odd to think that
I'm about to attack my own body like this.
Vegeta! There's no way we're going to
be beaten by a monkey bastard like you!
Babble on all you like!
It does not change the fact that you
are no longer a match for Vegeta-sama!
Now then, how about
I show you my true power?
S-S-Spare me–
Vegeta! You didn't have to go that far!
You just keep on spouting that
soft-hearted nonsense of yours, Kakarrot!
You'll never become a Super Saiyan!
I'm the only one who has that capacity!
What? You, a Super Saiyan?
Haven't you taken care of Ginyu yet?
All right then, I'll dispose of him for you!
Move it!
I-Incredible!
Now, to finish you off!
Why, you...
T-That's enough! Don't kill him, Vegeta!
Die!!
You fool!
I-It can't be!
Change!!
What?
Once again, Ginyu's signature
technique, the Body Change, bursts forth.
What is Ginyu's target?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
I did it! I'm finally back in my original body!
I have to say, you've really
beaten my body up good, Vegeta.
Hmph! Never mind that, tell me
exactly what happened to Ginyu!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Whoops!! Ginyu Has Turned Into a Frog."
When you think about
Ginyu-san's life from now on,
"Next time"
"Whoops!! Ginyu Has Turned Into a Frog"
you have to feel bad for him, huh?