The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Madoshi Babidi's strategy to
call out Piccolo, Trunks and Goten,
who have concealed themselves in
Kami's palace, has finally commenced.
Okay, begin, Majin Boo!
Okay!
You turn into hard candy!
All the people on this
planet will end up like this!
"Gohan Revived –
Kaioshin's Secret Weapon!?"
If those three don't come forward,
everyone is going to be eaten up!
And now, there's no reason to have this
city here with no people left in it, right?
I have no choice but to sweep it up
for you! Okay, Majin Boo, make it clean!
Not too hard, though, or the
whole Earth will be wiped out!
Okay! Okay!
That guy's getting cocky now!
My, my, my, looks like
he messed it up instead!
I'll say it one more time.
Him,
and him,
and him.
Tell me where they are,
unless you'd rather be turned
into candy and eaten by Majin Boo!
Let's see, it will take about five days
to exterminate every Earthling.
And so, I think it would
be best if you tell me soon.
Piccolo, Shen Long will do anything for us.
Right, right! I almost
forgot something important!
How are you supposed to contact me?
Call to me inside your head.
You just have to think out a little bit,
and then you can talk to me.
Of course, contact from those
people themselves is most welcome!
I'm sure those three were...
Hey! If he doesn't find them fast,
we're all going to be
turned to candy and eaten!
Doesn't anyone know them?!
I don't know who you are,
but where are you hiding?!
Come out now!
We're going to be turned into
candy and eaten because of you!
If I am turned into
candy here and eaten now,
then all the studying I've done for
my entrance exams will have meant...
...that I did it all for nothing, you stupid jerks!!
We were to have our wedding tomorrow.
We've done everything we
could to save up for our marriage.
What have you done with my life?!
It isn't my fault!!
Oh? Looks like I'm being contacted right away!
Um, I am the one who was in charge of the
Tenkaichi Tournament that was held today.
Mm hmm, and...?
Those three were entered
into today's tournament.
Oh? So, who are they?
Um, his name is Ma Junior, and
the children are... Trunks and Goten.
Their names don't matter,
I want you to tell me where they live!
Uh, n-no, I do not have their addresses...
Just names? Those don't mean anything!
His head...!
I must turn down trivial
information and prank calls.
You don't want to die
like he did just now, right?
How awful!
I'm quite busy.
After all, I have to go all over now and
wipe out the people and cities of Earth!
Majin Boo, let's go!
Well, next might be your location!
And let me say now,
that there's no use in hiding.
After five days, I plan on blowing
every last bit of the Earth to bits!
Well, I'll be waiting for that information!
D-Damn... That bastard!
What kind of guys are these?
Popo head hurts.
Th-They... are the ones who
killed Vegeta and Gohan-kun, right?
Yeah. Some awful guys
sure have come around.
In five days, they really could
blow the Earth to smithereens.
There's no reason to watch as those
people are sacrificed. I'm going out.
What sort of foolishness
are you saying, Piccolo?!
If you die, who will there be to teach
Fusion to Trunks and Goten in place of me?!
If they can't perform Fusion,
Majin Boo cannot be beaten!
In any event, they are going
to destroy Earth. That's for sure!
Until they master Fusion,
a considerable number of people
will become casualties of Majin Boo.
We'll just have to endure it–it
was you that said so, ain't it?
Everyone who's dead, and everything
on the ground that's been destroyed
can be brought back with the Dragon Balls.
So don't worry about it!
What he says is right!
That's right!
Now is the time for patience, right?
Understood...
Where is this?
I don't know this place!
Hey, Goten!
Wake up! Hey, Goten, I say!
Yeesh, can't do anything with you!
I know! Goten! Time to eat!
Food?!
Where? Where? Where? Where's the food?!
Ow, ow, ow! Of all the...!
You are such a glutton!
Trunks-kun, where is this?
I don't know! This is my first time!
This is the first time for me too. Wow!
What an expensive-looking dish!
Never mind that, what are we doing here?
W-Where's Papa?!
That's right! We were...
And then Papa...
Yeah.
Take care, Trunks.
T-Trunks-kun!
Why?! Why did you hit
Trunks-kun! That's awful!
How come?!
Trunks-kun, where's Uncle?
Goten, let's figure out where this is!
What is this place?
There's nothing here, huh?
Where those two go?
Okay, Kibit, restore Gohan-san's power.
Right.
H-Huh?
Kaioshin-sama...
Where is this...?
The Kaioshin Realm, or if you like, my world.
Kaioshin-sama's...?
S-So that's it. I've died after all, haven't I?
Huh? I don't have a halo like Dad does...
No, you're okay. It was
close, but you are alive.
Then, why am I in a place like this?
What do you mean by calling the
Kaioshin Realm "a place like this?!"
From the beginning, the
Kaioshin Realm was a holy place,
where not even Kami or Kaio
could come, let alone humans.
Surely, you're supposed to be dead!
Can you come back to life?
N-No, I cannot. I don't understand
myself, but for some reason,
I have come back to life.
A strange thing has happened.
Ah, really? Um, why
have you brought me here?
I was wanting to ask that as well!
Kaioshin-sama, why have you
brought a human to this sacred place?
We're going to use the
Z-Sword to defeat Majin Boo!
Knowing Gohan-san, he's
sure to be able to use that blade.
Th-The Z-Sword?!
A-Are you in your right mind, Kaioshin-sama?
There is no way any human
should be able to use the Z-Sword!
Not that legendary blade,
which so many Kaioshin-sama before
could do nothing with, let alone myself!
Kibit, you were dead, so you do not know
of Gohan-san's unbelievable, amazing power.
Z-Sword?
B-B-But no matter how strong he is...
In any case, let us go try it.
Son Gohan-san, come with us.
Entrusting the Z-Sword to a human...
Kaioshin-sama, what in the world...?!
Yummy, huh Trunks-kun?
Say, where do you think this is?
Where did Uncle and
Piccolo-san and the others go?
Goten! Talking should not
be done in the middle of a meal!
You've got a few bad manners.
No matter what happens, you
should be quiet during meals.
Sorry, Trunks-kun.
Just so you know.
Found you!
Plenty appetite! No worries!
W-What are you doing?!
We were wrong to eat without
asking first, but there's so much here,
you won't miss a little bit, stingy!
Damn! Why, you son of a... Hey, Goten!
Do something here! This is no
time to be just casually eating!
Trunks-kun, it's bad manners
to speak in such a loud voice.
You idiot!
You're the one who said meals
should be spent quietly, Trunks-kun.
I was a fool for counting on you!
Incredible power, greater
than Son Goku when child!
Goten, let's get out of here!
Yeah!
Wait!
–Get him!
–Yeah!
Goten, get out of here now!
Yeah!
Nice going, Goten!
Both of you, stay there!
Father!
Uncle...
Goku, both full of spirit.
Yeah, we'll have to have
them work hard for us.
These children could be awesome if do Fusion.
This sure is a nice place here.
It's a lot like the place where I live.
Those clothes are unworthy of this holy region.
It suits you well, Gohan-san!
Y-You think so?
Over there, Gohan-san.
This blade is the Z-Sword.
Please pull it out.
As far as I know, there has not been
anyone capable of pulling this blade out.
Pull it out?
Seems like there was something
like this in ancient folklore...
Y-You're lying! Papa beaten by that guy?!
It's a lie! A lie! A lie!
Big Brother is dead!
Stop crying! There ain't any time for it!
If you don't like it, then hurry
and learn this new technique
and avenge them! Got it?!
I know it seems harsh,
but Babidi might find out
about this place sometime.
We start training immediately!
Are you using the Room of Spirit and Time?
No. You can only use that room for
two days during your lifetime, right?
There might be a time
afterward that they need it.
It's okay. Knowing these two,
they'll make Fusion their own
in a considerably short time.
Let's begin!
Piccolo, you be sure to learn this well yourself.
Trunks, Goten, hang in there!
You two, stop your endless sobbing!
You guys are going to defeat Majin Boo!
Trunks and Goten are about
to be taught Fusion from Goku.
Gohan is about to dare to
pull out the Z-Sword as well.
Will this be the ultimate
weapon to defeat Majin Boo?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Hey, Gohan, unless you turn
Super Saiyan, you ain't gonna be able
to pull out that whatever-it's-called sword.
Oh?! Impossible! How can
a human pull that sword out?!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"It Came Ou~t!!
The Legendary Z-Sword."
Goten, Trunks, good luck to you guys, too.
"Next time"
"It Came Ou~t!!
The Legendary Z-Sword"