Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Goku had come to participate
in the Anoyoichi Tournament
that was being held on Grand Kaio's World.
The champion was to be
awarded... of all things...
personal training by the Grand Kaio himself,
the strongest man in the Next World.
Goku's fighting spirit was fired up...
K-Kaio of the South, if I could ask,
when will Contestant
Caterpi hatch from his chrysalis?
In about 1200 years, I would say.
I-I can't wait, either. Son Goku wins this match!
Goku had safely made
his way past the first round.
W-What just happened?
"Grand Kaio's World Gone Wild!!
Goku Kicks Up a Whirlwind."
And so, we have safely
concluded the preliminary tournament,
and the Best Eight have been decided!
The eight martial artists who will
compete in the final tournament are...
From the South Galaxy,
Contestant Furog and Contestant Tolbee!
From the East Galaxy, Contestant Aqua!
From the North Galaxy,
Contestant Olivue and Contestant Son Goku!
From the West Galaxy, Contestant Malaiko,
Contestant Tapica, and Contestant Paikuhan.
Go, go, West! Go, go, Paikuhan!
That's what you'd expect
from the folks from our Galaxy!
They're still in this!
Don't go bragging just because
you've got one more than the rest of us,
Kaio of the West!
W-What?!
What?
Now, now, you two, you go saying that,
and you have to feel sorry
for Kaio of the East, don't you?
She only has one person left, after all.
Who asked you?
It's not who has the most
people remaining that's important!
Even with only one person,
I can still advance my way up!
And so, we now begin the first match!
The South Galaxy's Contestant Tolbee versus...
The West Galaxy's Contestant Tapica!
Tolbee! Give that little
guy a nice, gentle pounding!
Underestimate Tapica, and you'll be sorry!
–What?
–Tapica, show them a little something!
H-He sure is fast! I wouldn't be
able to dodge him at that speed!
H-He's good.
Okay then, please begin!
I give up.
I'm exhausted.
That ring must have been
exceedingly large for Tapica's little body.
Don't offer your commentary so seriously!
Okay then, we'll now begin the second match!
Did you get him?
All right! At this point, that
move is the only thing I can do!
I take on big guys with a bigger body!
The South Galaxy's Contestant
Furog is swelling up larger and larger!
What in the world could he be planning to do?!
He's huge. There's all sorts of folks
with different techniques here, huh?
The Next World is a big place, all right.
Damn! Why, you...!
Keep at it! This is what happens!
I'll swell up more and more,
and push you right out of the ring!
W-What's this? Contestant
Furog's aim in growing so large
is to push Contestant Malaiko out of the ring!
I'm not about to lose!
Incredible!
"West"
The West Galaxy's Contestant Malaiko wins!
Contestant Malaiko proceeds to the semifinals!
Damn!
All right! Next comes my turn.
Let's do this!
Moving on,
the third match will be a fight between
the East Galaxy's Contestant Aqua,
and the North Galaxy's Contestant Son Goku!
Goku, stick it to him!
What are you talking about?!
Aqua is the one who'll be doing the sticking!
Okay then, please begin!
What are you waiting for?!
Don't just stand there!
Go on! Get going! Aqua!
Huh? Could it be that
he's an awfully weak guy?
I've gone and done something terrible.
Aqua! Now! Use that technique of yours!
Wha–?
W-What the...?
Aqua, whose specialty is underwater combat,
has the ability to turn anyplace into water!
That's cheating!
Nope! There's no rule against
turning the ring to water, after all.
That may be so, but...
I can'd mobe bery well underwader!
All righd...!
Taiyo-ken!!
Ka... me...
ha... me...
Ha!
R-Ringout!
Contestant Son Goku wins!
Goku, you did it!
Geez! You've smeared mud on my face!
All of you, 10,000 laps
around Grand Kaio's World!
Don't you "oh-oh" me!
You sure are strong, huh?
If you'd put me in the water
once again, I might have lost.
I'll win next time.
You bet. Let's do that again.
What are you doing?! Get going right now!
And now, the last match of
the Best Eight is coming up!
The North Galaxy's Contestant Olivue,
and the West Galaxy's Contestant Paikuhan!
Olivue-chan! Paikuhan-chan!
Good luck to both of you!
The West Galaxy's Contestant Paikuhan,
who is highly favored to be the champion,
and the North Galaxy's Contestant Olivue!
Both competitors in this battle are veterans!
It looks like we can
count on a magnificent fight!
Olivue! Olivue!
Paikuhan! Paikuhan!
Olivue! Give it your all!
Ha! You fool! There's
nobody that can beat Paikuhan!
It's useless to even cheer him on!
What?! You don't know that about Paikuhan!
How about you wait to say that
until after you've seen them fight?!
Ah! I'll say it as much as I want!
So much so that after Paikuhan has won,
you'll have calluses on your ears!
Why, you...
N-Not even I can see them! Awesome!
They're awesome!
Both Paikuhan and Olivue!
So this is the power the martial
artists have in the Next World, is it?
R-Ring–
Since I was out of the ring,
there's no need for me to say this...
but I still wanted to say it. I am defeated.
You've beaten me decisively.
C-Contestant Paikuhan wins!
Well, Goku-chan, what do you think?
A-Awesome...! My body is shaking...!
Are you afraid? Well,
you're a newcomer, after all.
You probably can't help but feel that way.
That ain't it. I'm all excited!
What?! Excited, you say?!
That's great, Goku-chan!
T-To think that I could fight
against someone that strong...!
The martial artists of the Next
World possess techniques and power
beyond imagination.
A stormy semifinal round awaits Goku!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
The Anoyoichi Tournament
is at last reaching its finale.
I'll finally be able to fight Paikuhan!
You have a lot more
power than when we first met.
Nice work, Son Goku.
I look forward to our match.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Final Round of Flame!!
Goku or Paikuhan!?"
Father, if you've made it this far,
you definitely have to win!
"Next time"
"Final Round of Flame!!
Goku or Paikuhan!?"