Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
The terrifying monster Cell
has at length absorbed No. 17.
Even I myself am surprised
by my magnificent speed.
Of course, this is due to absorbing No. 17.
I wonder how my power is.
He closed in, in an effort to absorb No. 18 as well.
However, just then, it was
Tenshinhan who stood forward!
Shin-Kikoho!!
"Tomorrow, I Am Going to Pulverize You!!
Goku's Challenge."
What are you doing?!
Run away!
Run away from here!
Come on! Now, while we can, No. 16!
R-Right...
Let's go, No. 16!
D-Damned if I'm letting you get away!
Why, you...!
R-Rotten monster!
T-Tenshinhan-san is hanging in there.
But his ki is dropping rapidly!
Tenshinhan's Shin-Kikoho...
Uses considerable energy.
Even so, everything he
can do, stop Cell from moving.
If keeps this up...
S-Stop it, Tenshinhan!
Don't use your Kikoho any more!
I said stop it, and I mean stop it!
S-Still, the only one who can
keep Cell in check right now is me...
A-As long as my energy holds out...
S-Such an enormous ki!
H-How will this turn out?
C-Chaozu...
T-Ten-san's g-going to die...!
S-Sorry, Chaozu.
There isn't anything we
can do. He's just too strong!
What are you sayin'?!
Goku-sa's still around, isn't he?!
Gohan-chan's gettin' stronger!
On top of that, Goku-sa's about
to go and take care of that monster!
It's no good! Tenshinhan's
ki has dropped substantially!
If things keep going like this, Tenshinhan will be...
Ten-san...
Chaozu, let's go!
Right!
H-Hold on!
Even if you do go, there isn't
anything any more that you can do!
Not only that, but you will
just add to our casualties!
–But...!
–It's just as Chichi said.
All we can do is wait for Goku to come!
I hate it myself, the same as you.
You've got to understand!
Damn...!
T-Ten-san...
Goku-sa...
T-Ten-san!
Damn. They've escaped, have they?
Can't you move?!
To think that I could possibly have
been hindered by the likes of you!
H-He'll be killed!
T-Tenshinhan-san!
Damn...
You look like you'll die even if I leave you be...
...but I'll eradicate you anyway!
F-Father!
W-What?!
Son Goku?
So you're Cell?
H-How did he just appear?
It looks as though you're one fantastic monster.
I'd like to settle everything right here,
but no matter how you shake it up,
there ain't no way I can win the way I am now.
However, just you wait one more day,
and I'll be sure to thoroughly
defeat you, you'll see!
Of all the things I would
have expected you to say!
After one day, you're going to
show me that you can defeat me?!
That's right!
In just one day, what is it
you're saying you can do, huh?
It's Piccolo's ki! Piccolo is still alive!
What?
Tenshinhan, don't you leave me!
There he is!
Hey, Piccolo! Stay with us!
H-How did those guys move...
...in that one instant?
Piccolo, Tenshinhan, both of
you are going to be all right now!
Once we get back to Kami-sama's palace,
the senzu we got from Karin-sama will be there!
You're planning to run away?
That will not do, Son Goku!
They vanished!
That's a peculiar technique.
Son Goku, when did you
come up with that technique?
Well, right now that doesn't matter.
I have to catch No. 18.
Lousy gal, she couldn't have gotten too far away
together with the broken-down No. 16!
P-Piccolo-san!
Thank goodness you're alive!
Gohan, give them both a senzu!
Right!
It's Bulma-san!
What's the matter, Trunks?
Kuririn?! Where? Say, where is he?
You were right! Well done, Trunks!
Way to find him!
You really are gifted!
Just what you'd expect from any child of mine!
Bulma-san!
Bulma-san, please give me
the controller to shut down
the Artificial Humans right away!
I know!
Here it is!
This is the controller, huh?
However, you must get within ten
meters of them, or it will have no effect.
Don't forget that when you use it, okay?
T-Ten meters?
T-That's pretty close, huh?
Even so, I had to work very hard to make that!
I-I understand.
I'll be careful when using it.
And, besides that...
I had battle suits made for everyone,
the same as the kind Vegeta requested.
Will you take these
while you're at it?
They're light, but pretty tough!
It's Goku and the others that need those!
They should be at Kami-sama's palace,
so Bulma-san, could
you take them there for us?
Kami-sama's palace?
As I remember, that's way
above Karin-To Tower, right?
That's right!
Sure thing!
I'll take them there for you!
In return, Kuririn, you hang in there
and destroy the Artificial Humans, okay?
R-Right!
Well, let's fly on over to Kami-sama's palace!
Damn. Where did that
miserable No. 18 disappear to?
Are you really all right,
Piccolo-san, Tenshinhan-san?
Yeah! The senzu truly do work well!
Anyhow, Tenshinhan, you really were reckless, huh?
Really! I was worried too!
But thanks to you,
Tenshinhan-san, we got away...
...without No. 18 being
absorbed by Cell, and that's great!
Still, that monster Cell has an abnormal strength.
Frankly, no one is able to beat him.
Not even Vegeta. Not
even Goku. That's what I think.
Hey!
Goku! Vegeta and Trunks
about to come out of room!
Really?
Vegeta and Trunks finally emerge.
Were they indeed able to surpass Super Saiyan?
Can they stop Cell's ambitions
to become his perfect form?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Wow, I'm blown away! Trunks,
you've really gotten all strong, huh?
I do indeed sense a different
sort of ki coming from them.
Does this mean that they have
gained a power greater than Cell has?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"I Will Dispose of Everything!!
A Reborn Vegeta, Father and Son, Sally Forth."
Ha, now it's our turn, right, Father?
"Next time"
"I Will Dispose of Everything!!
A Reborn Vegeta, Father and Son, Sally Forth"