Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Gohan and the others,
seeking a new set of Dragon Balls,
had at last arrived on Planet Namek.
However, Vegeta had also come to
Planet Namek to look for the Dragon Balls.
Further, the evil wire-puller
Freeza and his men were also there.
There is a reading of around
ten Namekians in that direction.
Very well.
It would be nice if they
had the fifth Dragon Ball.
Let us be going.
The circumstances surrounding the
Dragon Balls had taken a sudden turn.
Will Gohan and the others be
able to get hold of the Dragon Balls?
"Goku's Power Unleashed!!
Six Days to the Far End of the Galaxy."
A ki! There's another unknown
ki coming this way from over there!
Hide! Gohan! Bulma-san!
W-What, now?
Come on, hurry!
What in the world is it?
I'm always impressed by
how you guys know these things.
Shh! Keep quiet. It's coming this way.
Could we have been discovered?
I don't know.
They're here!
T-They're gone.
Thank goodness. It looks like those
people weren't coming after us, huh?
B-But, what exactly was that about just now?
What's the matter with you guys?
B-Bulma-san, could you check
something with the Dragon Radar?
W-What?
W-When you examined it before, there
were four Dragon Balls together, right?
What are they doing now?
All right, I'll check.
All four of them are moving. Which means...
R-Right, no doubt about it. Those guys
just now had the four Dragon Balls with them.
I-I knew it.
You don't say.
Gohan!
Yes?
Gohan, did you see him? The weird
one, flying second from the front?
Yes. I sensed an incredible power from him.
The moment I saw him, I froze.
That guy might be even more
ridiculously powerful than Vegeta.
I-It looked like there were
some other amazing guys in there,
but that guy was in a whole different league.
Stronger than Vegeta?
It couldn't be! Just who is he?
I-I don't know, but
I think he's one of Vegeta's pals.
They were all wearing the same kind of outfits.
Dammit! How are we supposed to get
the Dragon Balls away from those guys?!
H-Hey, look at this.
That group just now is
heading toward another Dragon Ball.
What's going on? Do they have radar, too?
What's the location?
About fourteen kilometers in that direction.
That's where we sensed that ki
Kuririn-san said could be Namekians!
I'm going to go over
there and see what's going on.
I'm going with you!
J-Just a minute, now!
Are you planning on
leaving me here all by myself?!
It's a lot safer staying here
than moving around carelessly.
W-When you put it that way, you're right.
Okay then, I'll put up a house with my
Capsules inside this cave and wait for you.
Okay, please do.
Come back soon, okay?
Remember, Gohan, keep your ki
as suppressed as you can, but hurry.
You can do that, right?
Yes.
All right!
They're gone. I wonder
if they'll really be okay.
Oh, that's right! I need to contact Earth!
Oh, okay, okay, okay...
Hello? Oh, Bulma... Yeah,
I was just heading to the hospital...
What?
Doctor, can't I have
your permission to train yet?
Are you still goin' on about that?!
I told you, bed rest is the
best thing for you right now.
If I don't start training soon,
my body is going to go soft.
How are you doing, Goku?
Old Timer!
Oh, Doctor, hello there.
Uh, is Chichi around, too?
Does me bein' here make
things inconvenient for you?
Oh, no, no, no, I wouldn't say that...
I'm goin' to go do some laundry.
Ah, thank goodness.
As it happens, I just received a
message from Bulma and the others.
Not again!
Oh, my, no, what a
naughty hand! Sorry 'bout that.
So, are Gohan and them okay?
Ah, they did indeed arrive on
Planet Namek safely. However,
Gohan and the others weren't the
only ones who went to Planet Namek.
That Saiyan, Vegeta, has gone there, too.
Vegeta?! He's there?!
That's not all. In addition to Vegeta,
there are dozens of his
buddies there on Planet Namek.
Those guys wrecked the
spaceship they went there in,
so they can't get back to Earth.
W-What?!
What's more, at least one of them
has a ki that's even greater than Vegeta's.
That can't be... Someone with
a ki even greater than Vegeta?
Hey, you still alive?
What's this? After I went to
all the trouble of comin' here,
ya don't look to happy to see me.
The senzu beans're finally ready.
There's just a few of 'em, though.
But Karin-sama said to take all seven of 'em.
Wow, all right! That's what you call
good timing! Hurry and let me have one!
N-Now look, you, you can't go
giving strange foods to patients!
Here ya go.
I've been waiting for this moment!
Here it is, here it is. Kaio-sama
sent this new gi to me for just this day.
All right! I'm off to Planet Namek!
Oh, thanks. I'm taking
the rest of the senzu with me.
H-How are you planning to get to Planet Namek?
When Bulma's daddy
came to visit me here earlier,
I asked him to make me
a spaceship, just in case.
A spaceship? You mean like Kami-sama's?
That one was made from
stuff that ain't found on Earth,
so even Bulma's daddy
said he couldn't do that.
Well, then–?
When I thought hard about it,
I realized there were still two
Saiyan spaceships here on Earth.
The spaceship that my brother came here in,
and the spaceship that
I myself came to Earth in as a kid.
T-That's right!
I had Bulma's daddy go looking for
them, and while my brother's was blown up,
mine was from long ago,
so it was still all right.
I'm having him repair and rebuild it.
Kinto Un!
Okay, I'll be back later.
Um...
I'm off to Bulma's house!
Ah! Goku-sa!
Hey! Where are you goin'?!
Goku-sa!
So, where's he going?
Hmm, well, as it turns out...
With things's bad as you're saying
they are, what's that guy so happy for?
I guess it has to be his Saiyan blood.
Of course, he wants to save everyone,
but more than anything, he seems
thrilled to be able to fight someone so strong.
That guy sure ain't normal,
all right. I can't take being around him.
Idiot. It's obvious he's
got zero chance of winning.
I can't believe it. How could there be
anyone even more incredible than Vegeta?
Gohan, your ki is a little too
strong. Suppress it a little more.
Right.
Huh?
Goku-chan!
Ah, Bulma's mommy.
Oh, my, are you all better now?
As fit as you see me.
By the way, is the reconstruction on
the spaceship that I asked for finished?
Well, I'm not sure. It looked like
he was still working on something.
He ain't done yet? That's a problem...
It's in the inner yard. Let's go there.
You know, I never thought that little
Goku-chan would grow up to be so handsome.
Say, let's date sometime, okay, okay?
I-I have to beat that
Saiyan before I can do that...
You're so busy, aren't you?
Oh, right, I discovered this
terribly delicious cake shop not long ago,
and it's all thanks to you, Goku-chan.
If the Earth had been lost, I wouldn't have been
able to eat any of it. Thank goodness for that.
I guess so.
Dear, Goku-chan is here!
I-Is this...
...my spaceship?
It's huge!
Oh, Goku, you're better already?
Yeah, thanks to a senzu. This is mine, right?
Is it true it ain't finished yet?
Yeah, there's still a little bit
left on it. Well, come on in and see.
Okay, I'll go get us something to drink.
Thanks.
This is incredible! I'm surprised
that teeny spaceship has become this.
Nothing to it. Everything is as you ordered.
I can train just fine like this.
I took great pains. It was
hard to find your spaceship.
It was broken into little pieces, you know.
Still, lucky for us,
the important parts were left
intact, but I had to rebuild most of it.
My spaceship was in pieces?!
That's strange. I wonder if
I busted it when I was a kid.
You know, this Saiyan
science is absolutely amazing.
Huh? Um, where is the
artificial gravity device thing?
Oh, this is it over here.
Wow, this thing, huh?
Let's see, this is the switch.
This is the controller.
As you ordered, it can generate
at most 100 Gs worth of gravity,
but even for you, isn't that a bit reckless?
At 100 Gs, after all, if you weigh
60 kilos, that will become 6,000 kilos.
That's six tons.
Ordinarily, that would kill you.
That's okay. If I don't
train someplace like that,
I won't be able to beat that Saiyan.
So, can't this thing fly yet?
It can fly anywhere you want to.
Even to the ends of the universe.
Huh? Then...
Uh, the bathroom, kitchen and
bedroom are down that ladder...
Say, then what still ain't done yet?
I can't quite settle on the
placement for the stereo speakers.
As long as you're listening to it,
you want it to sound good, don't you?
T-That's all?! When you say it
ain't finished, is that all you mean?!
"Is that all?"
When you consider reverberations
and everything, it's quite difficult.
I-I don't care where the stereo is placed!
I'm in a hurry here! I'll leave right now!
What are you in such a rush for?
We got a message from Bulma,
and anyhow, I just have to hurry!
Tell me how to make this thing fly, quickly!
All right. Now, you're sure
about the placement of the stereo?
Uh-huh!
The data has all been input. All you
have to do is give the switch a little boi-oing,
and six days later, you
will arrive on Planet Namek.
Six days? I can get there in
just six days? That's awesome!
Is it true that Goku is here?!
Yes. He's looking at the
spaceship in the inner yard right now.
Huh?
Let's see... after that
comes this button, right?
Ho, for as hurriedly as I put that together...
...it actually flew.
Huh? Where's Goku?
He left in a hurry.
I wonder if he's really okay with the stereo...
Close... we're close. Cut your
ki completely. Let's walk our way in.
Right.
They're on the other side of that bluff.
What an incredible ki!
This is bad! We've come
up right in front of them!
Let's move around to the other side.
Right.
Those houses are just like the
spaceship that we came here in.
What are they doing? Those other guys aside,
those three–especially the one in
the middle, riding in that round vehicle–
each have a terrifyingly strong ki.
I can tell.
Look at what the two guys on
either side have in their hands!
They're Dragon Balls!
H-Huge Dragon Balls...
Is something the matter, Dodoria-san?
No, there was just a slight
power reading coming from that cliff.
It is gone now, though. It must
have been a small animal or insect.
Y-Yikes, yikes! They very nearly spotted us!
Freeza-sama, we have only found five of them.
The remaining others
appear to be out at the moment.
Get out here, now, unless you want to die!
He looks just like Piccolo-san!
T-They're Namekians!
Wow, this certainly is fast.
Outer space sure is dark, huh? Or maybe
it's just nighttime out here right now.
Well, never mind. I've got
to start training right away.
I'm glad it's only going
to take six days to get there,
but I've got to surpass that
Vegeta guy before then, too.
Let's see, as I remember,
Kaio-sama said that his world
had ten-times gravity, didn't he?
For the time being, I guess I
should get used to around twenty-times.
It's working, all right!
At last, Goku had blasted off into space.
However, the Dragon Balls were falling
into Freeza's hands, one after the next.
Is Goku's power about to be unleashed?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Father, come quickly!
The Namekians are in trouble!
My wish is to obtain eternal
life with the Dragon Balls.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Surprise Attack!!
The Elder's Target Was the Scouters."
Freeza, you are such a terrible person!
"Next time"
"Surprise Attack!!
The Elder's Target Was the Scouters"