Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
The trio of Gohan, Kuririn and Bulma
had at last arrived on Planet Namek,
and set out at once to
search for the Dragon Balls.
And already, they had
gotten three of the Dragon Balls.
"Planet Freeza No. 79
Vegeta Recovers!!"
Kakarrot...
Yow-ow-ow-ow!
Okay, let's find the remaining
Dragon Balls quickly, and go back to Earth!
Saying "do it quickly" is one thing,
but as spread-out as this place is...
We'll find them for sure, you'll see.
Thank you very much, Zarkuro-san.
Come to mention it,
where is Lychee-san today?
He said he was staying home
because he had some work to do.
That's strange. One of the
Dragon Balls is moving toward us rapidly.
What is that?
What are you doing?!
The Dragon Ball is inside that thing!
Hurry up and go get the Dragon Ball!
Y-You can't mean that. Let's
just wait until the tornado disperses.
That tornado isn't going to disperse.
On this planet, tornados
roam around the desert forever.
Snap to it. I'm going
to be taking shelter, okay?
What are you doing?!
Hurry up!
A-All right.
Gohan, we're going to
release our ki toward that thing.
Right.
All right...
Kienzan!
Masenko!
Stop that! If you do that, you're
going to destroy the Dragon Ball!
B-But...
What are you doing?! Clumsy, clumsy, clumsy!
Stay away! Stay away! Stay away!
This is why I said I didn't
want to come to Planet Namek!
Bulma-san!
This is why I said I couldn't
go from the start, you know!
There's no way a delicate young lady
like myself can go looking for Dragon Balls!
You're not serious!
Without that Dragon Ball,
Piccolo-san won't be coming back to life.
There it is!
I did it!
All right...
Masenko!
Gohan!
Gohan-kun!
I got it out.
You did it!
Yahoo! That makes four of them! You did it!
Sure enough, this is the best outfit for me!
This one is that way, no doubt about it.
It sure is dark. I can't see a thing.
Shall I make us a torch?
W-What was that just now?
This isn't a forest, it's a bird!
Aah! Help!
Look at that incredible castle!
We've got no choice but to jump off!
It does look like that's
the only thing we can do.
Y-You're kidding, right?!
If we don't act fast, we're
going to become bird food.
All right! All right, already. But you
guys are responsible for catching me!
We know.
Remember this well, you trash...
There aren't going to be any more miracles...
Be sure to enjoy yourselves until then...
I can't beat that Saiyan like this.
Say, the Dragon Ball is right nearby.
Okay, Bulma-san, you
keep a lookout, if you please.
I-It'll be okay, right?
He's sound asleep, after all.
Kuririn-san, have you found it?
No, not yet. What about you, Zarkuro-san?
I haven't found it.
Geez, where exactly have you hidden it?
There it is!
Here goes.
Ready, set...
Safe!
Okay, let's get back, quickly.
I've looked everywhere I can think of,
but I have absolutely no idea where he went.
Good grief! My darlin' Gohan-chan
is off strugglin' hard on a distant planet,
and what is his father, Goku-sa, doin'?!
He never does anythin' a parent should!
N-Now, now, Chichi, you
don't need to get so worked up...
Goku must have felt terrible that he
couldn't do anything, all here on his own.
No, he's not gettin' away with it!
Makin' others worry about him like this...
If he doesn't get back here soon,
I'm goin' to turn this sweater into hankies!
You won't get away from me!
Bulma-san, are you sure this toy can fly?
You just hush! If I say
it will fly, then it will fly!
I told you, we should
have run away down the stairs.
Stop all of your complaining and
do something about that guy, now!
I guess we've got no choice.
–All right, Gohan, let's go!
–Right!
Hold it, hold it, hold it!
Oh, man! Enough, already!
I did it! I really am a
mechanical genius! Amazing!
Kienzan!
Masenko!
We got him!
We're saved!
For goodness' sake, you guys
are nothing but trouble for me!
If I weren't around, we wouldn't have
gotten a single Dragon Ball. You're hopeless.
You don't say...
Now there's only two left.
At this rate, we should be able
to go back to Earth soon, huh?
That would be nice...
Huh?!
It's almost time...
All right.
You are now healed. You may open your eyes.
Unfortunately, we were not
able to regenerate your tail.
No matter. It will grow back in time.
Vegeta has recovered at last. The
fearsome battle is about to begin again.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Oh yeah, you've finally
found the last Dragon Ball?
Way to go, everyone!
Whew, we're just about
ready to come back to Earth!
Then I can put some makeup on,
and go back to being the
usual beauty that I am, can't I?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Dragon Balls are All Found!
Piccolo-san Will Also Come Back to Life."
Say, Bulma-san, don't you
think this world is a little strange?
"Next time"
"The Dragon Balls are All Found!
Piccolo-san Will Also Come Back to Life"