Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
At last, Super Shen Long appears!
However, burning with rage, Freeza
bares his fangs as he draws ever closer!
Hurry up, Kuririn and Gohan!
"Kami-sama Also Returns to Life!
Piccolo Is Resurrected by Super Shen Long."
He-He's huge!
His form is different
than the one on Earth as well.
Thi-This is Shen... Long?
Thou who hast gathered the
Dragon Balls, now speak forth thy wish.
I shall grant thee any three wishes,
whichsoever art within mine ability.
Awesome! He really does grant three wishes!
We should have expected as
much from the home soil's Shen Long!
It sure is generous of him!
What should we do? We have three wishes.
Your wishes, quickly! Don't
forget about Freeza and Vegeta!
Oh yeah.
First, ask him to please bring back to
life everyone the Saiyans killed on Earth.
All right, I got it!
That wish cannot be granted.
Restoring the dead to life canst only
be accomplished one individual at a time.
Oh no!
Apparently, he can only
bring back one person at a time.
Only one at a time?!
If they only have three wishes,
and there's me, Yamucha, Chaozu, and Piccolo...
All right! I'll have
myself restored to life first.
What was that?
Well, Kaio-sama, I'll go first–
Wait! Don't be so selfish, I'm going first!
What are you saying?!
I was the first one of us to die!
Therefore, I will be the first brought back!
That's choplogic!
Everyone! Let's draw straws!
No way! You'll use your
telekinesis to cheat on us!
How awful! I wouldn't do that!
Let me...
Let me talk with Gohan!
–What?
–Please!
What keeps thee? Speak forth thy wish.
I shall grant thee any three wishes,
whichsoever art within my ability.
Within his ability, he says.
Quickly! If we're found out by
Freeza or Vegeta, we're finished!
What do we do? Only one
person can be brought back per wish!
This is quite a fix. Who do we choose?
Shoot! For the home soil's Shen Long,
he's not that generous after all!
You say you want to speak with Goku's son?
What are you planning to do, Piccolo?
Why you! What are you thinking of doing?!
You're not thinking of having
just yourself brought back, are you?!
What?! Is that right?
Piccolo, that's not fair!
You're not the only one
who's been training here!
We've also powered up several
levels, you know. What's more–
Hurry and let me speak, please!
All right, then. Place your hand on
my shoulder, and then you can speak.
Gohan! Can you hear me?! It's me! It's Piccolo!
Gohan!
Answer me, Gohan! It's me! Piccolo!
Piccolo? It can't be!
Where are you, Piccolo-san?
I'm using Kaio to speak
directly into your hearts.
I won't have you dishonor my name.
Kaio-sama is how I am addressed, Kaio-sama.
Into... our hearts?
We know that you have three wishes,
but that only one person can
be brought back to life per wish.
Now listen closely!
With the first wish, bring me back to life!
Wait!
We won't let you get away with this, Piccolo!
You shut up!
Don't forget, if I am returned
to life, Kami will be also.
When that happens, the Dragon Balls
on Earth will also be restored,
and the rest of us here
can then be brought back.
Hey, yeah! We can do it that way!
Understood, Piccolo-san.
I get it now. So that's what you were after.
–Nice thinking!
–Piccolo is great!
Now, I'll tell you the second wish...
Once I... Once I'm brought back to life,
bring me to Planet Namek,
where you guys are!
I... I want to fight.
I want to fight that rotten
Freeza, who's killed my people,
in the homeland from which I was born.
What are you saying, Piccolo?!
I've gained great power since I've been here.
I'll defeat him for you for sure!
Send me there to that
planet you're on. Got it?
Understood, Piccolo-san!
I'm counting on you. Do whatever
you want with the third wish.
Right! I'll be so happy once you get here!
Hey, Piccolo!
Have you forgotten the
promise you made to me?
That you would never fight against Freeza?
I must have. I don't remember
making such a promise.
What's that?
Unfortunately, my memory isn't that great.
–Why you!
–Hold it now...
–Kaio-sama!
–Just take it easy!
Let go of me! How dare you do this to me!
I don't know what kind of punk you are,
but I, Piccolo-sama, will be sure to defeat you!
You guys! You have no
idea how terrible Freeza is!
Let go of me! I can't talk to you like this!
Okay!
Before we do anything else,
let's get those two wishes granted!
–Right!
–Dende!
Yes?
Ask that Piccolo, the Namekian who
was on Earth, be brought back to life!
Piccolo-san, you say? Got it.
Any second now, Piccolo-san...
What's this? Something's headed this way!
It's an incredible battle power!
F-Freeza!
It will still take several more
minutes for Kakarrot to fully recover.
It's still a bad time for Freeza to appear.
Ah, crap. I got a bad feeling about this.
What?
What is going on here? It's night!
Why?
There's not supposed to
be any night on this planet.
Why is the sky so dark?
This has to mean...
No, it couldn't be...
It couldn't be... It couldn't be!
It couldn't be!!
Understood. I shall grant thy first wish.
No!!
The Dragon Balls are gone!
Shoot! Kakarrot's son is also missing.
Why you dirty rotten little brat!
What's that monster over there?
Is that the dragon they said
would appear out of the Dragon Balls?
Dammit, those rotten kids
have gotten the jump on me!
You'll pay for this!!
This is bad! Freeza is almost on top of us!
I'm reading four life signs.
At last I've found you!
Just you wait for what you've got
coming, you crummy lower life forms!
It vanished!
All right.
I'm alive again! Now, for the next wish!
I'm counting on you, Gohan!
I won't be responsible for this!
It's out of my hands now!
Wait... Wait! Wait!
Kami-sama!
Piccolo, you rascal.
That was some smart thinking.
Popo, you've taken good
care of the place in my absence.
Great!
Kami-sama is back alive! So happy!
I have granted thine first wish.
Now, speak forth thy second wish!
The second wish is to have Piccolo,
who was just restored to life,
"warped" here to Planet Namek.
Right!
Dende, make it fast! Vegeta's found us out!
Okay!
That is a simple matter.
I shall grant thine second wish.
Such a fool!
I have granted thy second wish.
Thou mayest now speak thy final wish.
He said it's granted?
But Piccolo isn't here yet.
Where are you, Piccolo-san?
You just said to have him brought to
this planet, so he could be anywhere.
Did you mean you wanted him brought here?
Oh, no!
What should we do?
We could use the third wish to bring him–Aaah!
Vegeta!
I knew it! I knew it was something like this!
How dare you... How dare you try
to trick me, Vegeta-sama, you punks!?!
You'll pay for this!
You simple fools!
You've taken the only chance we
had to defeat Freeza and wasted it!
The only way we can
win is if I am made immortal.
You dirty, stinking brats!
Wait! We've only had two wishes granted so far,
there's still one wish
that remains to be granted.
Idiot! Keep your mouth shut!
I'm quite relieved to hear this.
What is that column of light there?
That's where the life sign readings are...
No, they couldn't be using
the Dragon Balls to get their wish!
What is thine third wish?
Now then, make me eternally young! Do it now!
Lousy brat!
Don't you know what "Do it now" means?!
Dende!
You have to do it now!
Freeza is nearly upon us!
If that wish gets granted...
But we don't have any choice!
Father's injuries won't
heal for some time still...
So this is my homeland?
Planet Namek.
Then it's no wonder I feel such
an odd nostalgia for this place.
The Namekian blood that flows
within me must be responsible.
Hold on, this is no time
to be waxing sentimental.
I'd better locate Gohan and the others.
Shoot, where are they?
They aren't around here anywhere close.
Wh-What's that?!
I can feel a tremendous ki off in the distance.
Can that be the monster, Freeza?
There are three other ki
near them. Gohan and the others.
All right. Hold on, Gohan!
I still await thy final wish.
Thou mayest speak it now.
What are you waiting for?! Tell him now!
Make me immortally young!
Do you want to be killed by Freeza?
Kuririn-san, Freeza is almost here!
Our situation is desperate.
Dende! Let him have his wish!
Vegeta may also be incredibly bad,
but at least he's better than Freeza.
I hate to have to do this,
but right now, there's no other
way to get us out of this pinch.
Very well.
All right, that's better.
So, do it now.
Okay.
Stop messing around!
This is good! This will fix it so
that Freeza will not be able to kill me.
I just have to keep after him,
and even if I can't do it now,
eventually, I will defeat him!
Very soon now, the time will come when I,
Vegeta-sama, will rule the universe!
What?
What's happened?
Why did the dragon disappear,
and the sky become light again?
Why have the Dragon
Balls turned into those stones?
The Grand Elder-sama has...
Dende...
...passed away.
Are you sure?
The life of the Grand Elder-sama,
who created these Dragon Balls,
has come to an end.
What do you mean, you little snot?!
What about my... what am
I supposed to do about my eternal youth?!
What do you want me to say?
You rotten punks!
If you hadn't double-crossed me,
none of this would have happened!
You're going to pay! You dirty, rotten fools!
Freeza!
You have really done it now,
have you not, gentlemen?
You have done an outstanding job of
shattering my dreams of eternal youth.
I certainly trust that you fools
are now prepared to pay the price.
It's the worst possible situation–
Freeza has at last arrived!
Freeza is burning with anger.
In this great crisis,
what will happen with Piccolo?
What will happen with Goku?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Crap, I didn't know he was this strong.
Freeza has shown his true nature, huh?
Piccolo! Hurry, there's no time!
You say that by merging with Nail,
my power will increase many times over?
If I don't like what happens,
I'll drive you right back out again.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Birth of the Mightiest Warrior?
Nail and Piccolo Merge."
That's surprising! Who knew
that Freeza could transform?
"Next time"
"Birth of the Mightiest Warrior?
Nail and Piccolo Merge"