Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Trunks, the youth who traveled back 20
years from the future in a time machine,
delivers some frightening news.
In three years from this time,
on an island about nine
kilometers from Metro South,
a terrifying pair of villains will appear.
Who are they? Are they aliens?
They are monsters, both
possessing a power so great,
it's unthinkable that they are of this world.
Dad, please don't die.
Young mom, you hang in there too.
And so, Trunks returned home.
Son Goku and the others
have resolved to defy history,
and prepare themselves for battle.
"Goku's New Finishing Technique!?
Watch My Instantaneous Movement."
Kakarrot, tell us!
How did you survive Planet Namek?!
Hey, that's right!
Freeza's spaceship was all busted up, wasn't it?
Even Kaio-sama said there
was no way you could survive.
I thought it was hopeless myself...
Move it! Move it!
It's exploding! Namek is exploding!
Dammit... dammit!
I thought I was really
gonna buy the dust there.
But lucky for me, there were
those ball-like spaceships nearby.
So that's it! The ships that
the Ginyu Special Corps came in!
Anyhow, I got into one of them,
and started flipping every switch I could find.
Crap! Crap! Crap!
Gohan!
Looks like I came down pretty hard.
I guess this isn't Heaven, is it?
The Ginyu Corps were set to invade Yardrat.
The ships were input with
instructions to land there.
That explains it.
That outfit must be
from the people of Yardrat.
Yeah. I made friends with
them, and they gave it to me.
These clothes looks a little
funny, but mine were all torn up.
I know you well enough!
You wouldn't go to Yardrat
and come back empty-handed.
Those guys may not have much power,
but they do employ some odd techniques!
You learned them, didn't you?!
Bingo!
So that's it!
No wonder you didn't
return to Earth for so long.
So, tell us, what kind of
techniques did you learn?
I didn't have much time,
so I only learned one technique.
Even so, I had to work
really hard to get it down.
I can now perform "Instantaneous Movement."
Instantaneous Movement?!
Really, Son? Show us!
You want to see? Okay.
To do this, you have to bring to
mind a person, rather than a place.
More precisely, you have
to feel out that person's ki.
That means you can't go someplace
where there aren't any people.
So then, where should I go...?
Got it!
Bye-bye!
He disappeared!
So where's the "Instantaneous Movement"?
You're just trying to fool us
by moving at super speeds.
Ta-da! What are these here?
Aren't those Muten Roshi-sama's sunglasses?!
He's right!
They're gone, gone!
My sunglasses are gone!
But we're over 10,000 kilometers
from the Kame House! Incredible!
Must be the real thing then, huh?
Kuririn, give these back to
the old man when you see him.
You got it.
You can do anything now, can't you?
That's not true.
All right. Well everyone,
let's meet up again in three years
where this is supposed to happen.
When and where should we go in three years?
Oh, that's right, he mentioned that.
I've already forgotten.
Three years from now,
on May 12, around 10 a.m.,
on an island nine kilometers
southwest of Metro South.
We can get together at that
island at 9 a.m., an hour earlier.
Thank goodness!
Boy, it's a good thing Piccolo overheard you!
Let me say now, that if any of you
are unsure of yourselves, stay away.
Our opponents this time are
even more terrible than any before.
We won't be any match for them...
...if we have one of our own slowing us down.
That's right. Stay away!
Don't make me laugh.
Aren't you the least sure
of yourself of anyone here?
What was that? Should we find out?!
Easy, easy.
Hey, know what? I was just thinking.
What if we get rid of this Doctor Gero,
the one who creates the
Artificial Humans, right now?
Even if we don't know where he is,
we could use the Dragon
Balls and ask Shen Long.
He'll be sure to tell us where he is.
If we do that,
then we won't have to bother going
through all that agony in three years.
Hey, yeah! That's right, Bulma-san.
If we do so, we sure won't have to fight later!
Great! Way to go, Bulma-san!
If you pull an uncalled-for stunt like that,
I'll kill you! You got that?!
What do you mean uncalled-for?
This isn't a game you know!
The fate of the Earth is in the balance!
Bulma-san! Bulma-san!
Son-kun, you agree with me, don't you?
Sorry. To be honest, I want to fight them.
Besides that, this scientist
hasn't even built anything yet,
how can we take him out?
The rest of you!
We don't have to go along with these Saiyans!
They're just a race of fighting maniacs!
If you die this time, there's
no bringing you back to life!
I'm going to fight too.
I want to see what I'm capable of.
If I die, then I'll concede
that that's all I could do.
Well, I never!
Bulma-san, this is the way I see it.
Everyone here used to be enemies in the past.
For my part, I hated Goku at first.
But when a terrible opponent appears,
there's no choice but
for everyone to join forces.
As a result, without us realizing it,
we've also become friends.
Ordinarily, this type of
thing wouldn't happen.
Not with everyone as
frighteningly powerful as they are.
What are you trying to say?
Without the target
provided by a common enemy,
even allowing that
Piccolo wouldn't make trouble,
we can pretty well guess that
Vegeta is going to lord it over us.
Kuririn-san, you had such a
good speech going there for a while.
You be quiet. I don't need any sass.
What I'm saying is the truth.
Fine, I understand you.
You can all do what you want.
Those city people caught in
the crossfire will pay the price,
being as fragile as I am.
Let's take back a peaceful future!
You're just like some kind of crazy dictator!
This time you're absolutely
mistaken! It's abnormal!
There's nothing I can do about it,
so I'll keep associating with you for now.
Well then, three years from now–
um, May 12, 10 a.m. at that island.
We won't mind if you don't feel you're up to it.
Kakarrot!
Just because you can become a Super Saiyan,
don't get too full of yourself!
I'm still going to beat the
crap out of you some time.
Don't you forget that I am
still the Number One Saiyan!
Right.
We're leaving too. See you in three years.
Bye-bye.
Chaozu, show up really strong now!
Tenshinhan-san, come up with
some incredible new techniques!
Piccolo...
Why don't you come train with me and Gohan?
I want to spar and stuff.
Sounds good, I was hoping to myself.
Kuririn and Yamucha, care to join us?
I'm fine. I'll be training at my
own pace with Muten Roshi-sama.
I'll decline too.
Quite honestly, I don't think
I could keep up with your training.
Okay then.
That's right! Bulma!
Have yourself a healthy baby!
Baby? Bulma-san, are you pregnant?
No, I'm not. What could
he be jibbering about?
See, in other words–
He's saying why don't we finally get married,
settle down and raise a happy family?
Now even he's starting to say so!
And so, to prepare for the appearance
of their fearsome foes in three years,
everyone departed for their
respective training grounds.
Muten Roshi-sama!
Kuririn, there was a ghost!
Earlier, Goku's ghost appeared
and made off with my glasses!
Huh? What are you doing with my glasses?
I wish to once again further my training...
Now I can look without being worried.
Um, I was thinking of restarting
my training, you see... Uh...
Muten Roshi-sama, my training!
Build you a 300G gravity room, you say?
That's right!
I heard Kakarrot trained
under the force of 100G.
So I'm going to undergo triple that!
That's unheard of!
Vegeta-kun, assuming you weigh 60 kilos now,
you'd end up weighing 18 tons!
I'm afraid it's out of the question.
Build it! Just build it for me!
I have had enough!!
You gotta be kiddin'!
Goku-sa, how long are you
gonna stand in Gohan-chan's way
before you're satisfied?!
I wanted to get
Gohan-chan to study even more,
so I bought that Academic Dresser Center,
and the Somnioscholastic Bed!
And now you want to take him
trainin' with you to strengthen him up?!
You just butt out!
Goku-sa, you can just
train with Piccolo by yourself!
But I already told you, we're
going to need Gohan's power too.
I understand about
studying, but in three years,
Earth itself is going to be in great danger.
You talk so big! Goku-sa,
you never do any work, you
can't take care of Gohan-chan!
Have you ever earned even a penny,
in all the time we've been married?
When you say it that way,
I'm sorry, but this isn't the time for that.
Gohan's already made
up his mind to fight with us.
No way! No way! Nothin'
you say will change my mind!
Then, you think Gohan's studying...
...is more important than
the future of the world?
That's right! Of course it is!
It doesn't matter whatever else may happen!
Gohan-chan's studyin' is
more important than anythin'!
You're such a kidder!
Sorry, Chichi!
I've gotten too strong,
and meant to just tap you!
I really am sorry.
I can't believe I let this happen.
It's all right! The woman
always backs down eventually.
But three years from now, I'm going
to be putting an end to his kung fu.
Three more years, that's it!
So, even Super Saiyans have weaknesses.
And so, the harsh training begins all around...
Ten-san...
Ten-san, nicely done.
Oh, this is great!
Hey, Kuririn! These are great!
Hey, Kuririn, why don't
you come check this out?
Let's go, Gohan!
Right!
Too soft!
Should we call it a day?
Yeah.
Pl-Please, let me try a little longer.
I want to become stronger.
Just like you two, Father and Piccolo-san.
You there, stop looking
elsewhere and start using the machine.
Oh, right.
I guess using these
machines won't serve as training.
I will surpass them!
I will surpass even the Super Saiyans!
The harsh training continues.
Three years from now, who will
defy their destiny and remain alive?
Come on!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
It's been a while since we parted
ways. Is everyone doing all right?
I hope you haven't gotten too
fired up, and hurt yourselves.
Hey, Vegeta! Enough of your recklessness!
What are we going to
do if you wreck the house?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"I Will Overcome Goku!!
The King of the Saiyan Warrior Race."
I want to get stronger, too!
"Next time"
"I Will Overcome Goku!!
The King of the Saiyan Warrior Race"