The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Several years had passed
since the battle against Cell.
Thanks to the actions of Son Goku and his son,
the Earth had been rescued from
falling into Cell's devilish hands,
and its people were able to take back
their peaceful existence once again.
However, once they become
accustomed to that peace,
foolish people begin to proliferate immediately.
That's just the way people are.
In the countryside where Son
Gohan lives, there weren't any schools,
and up to now, he had gotten
along at home through self-study
and correspondence courses,
but his mother, Chichi, was concerned
that that was not enough by itself,
and so it was decided that
he would attend high school.
There's the edge of town.
I suppose it's about time I landed.
Bye-bye, Kinto Un! I'll need
you to take me home, too!
Father, Mister Satan is believed
to be the hero who saved the Earth.
And because this is the
city where Mister Satan lives,
its name has even been changed to Satan City.
"7 Years Since Then!
Starting Today, I'm a High School Student."
Come on, come on! Make with the money, quick!
You want to die?!
Don't make any trouble!
Get it in there, fast!
Hey, this looks like all there is.
All right, let's beat it!
Once we've used up the money
we've taken, we'll be back again!
Yahoo!
Huh? Maybe I dawdled too much on the way.
All right...!
Go on, go on! Fire!
Not again. There's just no helping this city.
I'll have to transform again,
so nobody can tell who I really am.
Hey, hey! Come and get us!
What?!
W-Who are you?!
H-He's a monster!
G-Get out of here!
Y-Yow-ow-ow-ow...
Incredible!
W-What happened?
Say...
Who was it that did this?
Don't tell me it was the police.
Gee, I didn't see.
And after I flew all the way here...
I wonder who on Earth it was.
Ah, Videl-sama, I saw him.
It was that Golden Warrior.
The Golden Warrior? Again?
Yeah. He had incredible strength and speed.
He even turned over the criminal's
car from a distance as it was escaping,
with what looked like some kind of Kiai shout.
Oh, yeah. I think he might have been a student
at Orange Star High School, just like you.
He was wearing that same school badge there.
A-A student at my high school?
Is there anyone there like that?
With golden-colored hair...?
Say, Shapner, you're not him,
are you? The Golden Warrior?
Sorry to disappoint you.
I was doing early-morning training in my club.
I don't have the time to be
carrying on such nonsense.
Say, Videl, could this guy be
even stronger than your Papa?
Don't be ridiculous. Videl's Papa is
Mister Satan, the guy who saved the Earth.
Could there be anyone in
this world stronger than him?
Good morning, people.
Let me introduce to you a new student
who is transferring in and will
be in your class starting today.
You can come in.
G-Good day.
I'm Son. Son Gohan. Nice to meet you.
Oh, my, he's pretty cute,
isn't he? He's just my type!
"Gohan," he said. That's a strange name.
It seems like I've seen him somewhere...
He looks completely like a
quiet little bookworm, huh?
Son-kun here is an excellent student,
who got perfect scores in
math, chemistry, physics,
history, language, and foreign
languages on his admissions test.
Quiet! I would very much like for
his motivation to rub off on you, too.
Son-kun, go ahead and
sit down in an empty seat.
Right.
Let's see...
Over here!
Here, here!
Th-Thanks.
I'm Eraza. Nice to meet you.
And while we're at it, this girl is Videl.
Okay then, today, we're starting on page 24.
Gohan-kun, you'll be surprised
to hear this! Videl's Papa, you see,
is Mister Satan, of all people!
M-Mister Satan?
See? You're surprised!
Then, you're Mister Satan's daughter?
That's right. You've got to be grateful to them.
It's because of this girl's
Papa that we're all alive now.
That's it! You were...
You were that person
I talked to this morning
at the scene where those
bank robbers were arrested.
Yeah.
Ah, the one where they say
the Golden Warrior appeared?
The Golden Warrior? Who is that?
You just got here, so you wouldn't know, huh?
He's a warrior for justice, who has
appeared three times in the last ten days.
He's supposed to be this incredibly strong boy,
with gold-colored hair that stands on end.
He's famous around this city.
Ulp! Th-They mean me!
Those two times from when I was arranging
to attend this school, plus this morning...
"I just wanted to say with
you when she said to me that..."
"But I wanna make her feel so
good. Nothing I can do to you..."
"And..."
You know...
according to an eyewitness,
the Golden Warrior was
wearing a badge from this school.
He was said to be wearing a whitish
shirt, with a black vest, and brown pants.
It may be a coincidence, but that's you to a T.
Oh, my, it's true!
No, i-it's just...
You there, be quiet!
Right, right.
Okay then, moving along...
"Two weeks are passed and at last..."
Look at who you're talking about.
Is that the body of a warrior?
Since long ago, the general rule is
that anyone who was good at studying
was hopeless when it comes to athletics.
And he's not even blond to begin with.
Yeah, you're right.
You look altogether weak,
if you don't mind me saying.
That's true, huh?
Naturally, I don't believe it's him,
but on the video where
Papa was fighting Cell long ago,
there was a strange group whose
hair did turn golden, wasn't there?
Papa said it was just a worthless trick, though.
Say, Gohan-kun, are you commuting from home?
Or are you renting an apartment in town?
Oh, I'm commuting from home.
Where is it? Where is your home?
Um, Eastern Zone 439. It's in a small village.
Eh?! Eastern Zone 439?! You're kidding, right?!
That's a thousand kilometers from here, isn't it?!
Geez, that's enough already!
Can't you keep quiet?!
How on earth do you get here?
It would take a jet flyer
five hours to travel that far!
W-Well, you can see how hard
it is, with all the time it takes.
Whoops...
"He is the greatest man..."
Okay, why don't we have
someone translate up to that point?
Let's see, who should I pick?
Mister Satan even shows up in the textbooks!
I guess that's Satan City for you.
Hey, you!
Go on and translate by way of
introducing yourself, "Mountain Boy."
Go on, Gohan-kun!
Right, you're the transfer student, aren't you?
Let's see, your name was...
Son Gohan, of the perfect admissions test!
That's right, isn't it?
Okay, Son-kun, try translating this.
Right. Let's see...
Er, what page are we on again?
We're starting on page 24.
Ah, right. "Mister Satan came
to live in what is now Satan City,
"and at the time was Orange Star City,
"following his victory at
the 24th Tenkaichi Tournament.
"Even after becoming the world
champion, he never misses his training,
"and his running through town every
morning has become a feature of the city."
Someone must be talking about me again.
It's tough being a hero. Am I right, you guys?
For today's phys ed,
we'll continue what we were doing
last time by having a baseball game.
Hey, you know what baseball is?
Yes. I've never played it,
but I do at least know the rules.
You've never played?
That's just great. You must have
done nothing but study, right?
Videl, you can have him on your team.
I don't want him!
Why not? His brain is first rate,
so maybe he can come up with some strategy.
That's true. All right.
You cover right. Do you know what "right" is?
Yes. It's "migi," isn't it?
Migi?!
Well, you're not wrong...
I wonder if Gohan is gettin' along okay.
This is his first time goin' to school, after all.
I sure hope he's gettin' accustomed to it.
Both Mom and Bulma-san said
that if people knew who I really was,
there would be a big commotion,
and it would make a mess.
I'll have to make sure I play suitably sloppily.
It sure is hard being out in the world.
Let 'er rip, Shapner!
I'm not letting you hit this, Shapner!
Damn!
He did it! A home run!
The runner on third has gone.
As I recall, if I throw it to
third in this case, they'll be out.
All right, gently, gently...
about this hard, maybe?
O-Out!
I did it! Three outs, change sides!
Th-This is bad. Even at just
that, I must have overdone it.
Th-That was incredible of you.
You just jumped about eight meters, didn't you?
No, it was just a fluke! A fluke!
O-Oh, a fluke, huh?
B-But still, is that
something you can call a fluke?
Hey, who's the next batter?
Number 8 leads off, right? Isn't that you?
Right, right! Right!
Sorry!
I wonder what will happen with his batting.
L-Let's watch him!
You bat left-handed, do you?
Is that wrong?
No, it's fine with me,
but, er, your grip is backwards.
Backwards?
Uh, just do it however you like.
How dare you deny me my home run earlier!
Maybe I ought to drop you...
This is bad. If I draw any more
attention than this, it will really be bad.
I can't hit it.
Here goes! If you don't duck this, you'll die!
Look out!
Y-You idiot! W-Why didn't you avoid that?!
Um, this is what's called a "dead ball," right?
M-Mm-hmm...
Lucky! Lucky! I got on
base without having to hit!
I'm not drawing attention,
I'm not drawing attention!
W-What's the deal with that guy?
That's suspicious...
Hey, you! Which clubs have you decided on?
Er, well, I haven't decided on any.
In that case, join the boxing club.
You're tougher than I thought.
You could do pretty well.
Um, I don't plan on joining any clubs. You see...
Right, right! Gohan-kun's
house is terribly far away.
He doesn't have time to get
involved in any club activities.
Th-That's right.
Say, Gohan-kun, let's go home together.
Take me as far as my house?
Um, sorry, but my car only has room for one.
You could move to Satan City, couldn't you?
Well, no, you see, about that...
This is suspicious, all right!
If his home is so far away, why
isn't he going by car or jet flyer?
Huh?
The city sure does wear you out, huh?
And now, there's the Golden Warrior, huh?
I'll need some kind of clothing
so that people won't know it's me.
I think I'll discuss it with Bulma-san.
The first day of high school was over.
Gohan thought that this
was the first time in his life
that he'd had a day that was this tiring.
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Gohan, that's a funny outfit
you've got on. What's going on?
Looks like he really likes
that transformation device
that conceals his identity.
He's transformed over
and over again for no reason,
and seems tickled.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"For Love and Justice –
Enter the Great Saiyaman."
I am he who does not abide evil!
"Next time"
"For Love and Justice–
Enter the Great Saiyaman"