The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
In order to upset Madoshi Babidi's
plot to revive the sealed-up Majin Boo,
Goku and the others
have infiltrated his spaceship
and have arrived at Stage 3.
To defeat Goku and the others, a powered-up
Dabura, King of the Demon Realm of Darkness,
at length commences his
attack in the third Stage.
Elsewhere, at the Tenkaichi Tournament,
an intense battle between No. 18
and Mighty Mask was unfolding.
However, it was revealed that Mighty Mask's
true identity was that of Trunks and Goten,
and they were disqualified.
Finally, all that remained
were No. 18 and Mister Satan.
"Confrontation with the Demon King!
It's Your Turn, Gohan!!"
So, will it be Mister Satan that
triumphs over the Tenkaichi Tournament?
Or will it be Contestant No. 18?!
After seeing her astounding manner of fighting,
there are suddenly many
cheers for Contestant No. 18!
Who will it be that obtains the
10 million Zeni in prize money?
There's no way I can win against that!
Satan! Go, Satan!
Satan! Satan!
Well, come at me any way you want!
Isn't that nice for your mommy?
10 million Zeni, he said!
She'll take it, she'll take it!
This is no time to be
laughing, Muten Roshi-sama!
What on earth could be
happening to Goku and the others?
Hmm, you're right. Where on
earth could they have gone to?
Well, come on!
"Tenkaichi Tournament"
P-Please, don't kill me! I'll do anything!
Shut up! Stop blubbering!
Be quiet, or I really will kill you!
Oh! Contestant No. 18 has
connected with a headlock!
Listen, speak softly. Do you want to win?
N-No, enough! I've had enough,
please don't do anything terrible...
What's wrong, Satan! Get her!
If so, I don't mind letting you win...
That's ticklish... Hmm?
W-What did you just...?
I said I was going to let you win!
In exchange, you will hand
over to me 20 million Zeni.
I will lose to you. Not a bad deal, right?
That's all it will cost you to keep your fame.
What can this be? Mister
Satan is not moving at all!
Can it be that even Mister Satan
is not up to this opponent?
2-20 million Zeni?
When you win, you'll get
10 million Zeni in prize money.
You just have to shoulder
the other 10 million Zeni.
–Cheap, don't you think?
–B-But...
Hey, I don't care. I could
just knock you out right here
and make due with 10 million Zeni...
Kn-Knockout...?
You jerk! Worthless idiot!
You damned fool, Satan!
Don't ever come back!
Die, Satan!
Hmph, I hate you, Papa!
How about it?
I-I'll pay it! O-Of course I will let you have it!!
Well then, that's settled.
Pleasure doing business.
Oh! Mister Satan has flicked
Contestant No. 18 off of him!
D-Damn!
Hurry and come at me!
I have now seen through all your tricks!
I hate to say it, but you are no match for me!
–Oh, really?
–Incredible, Mister Satan!
I will admit that you have considerable skill.
However, your opponent is too much for you!
You've fought well, but
after all, I am the champion!
Wow, cool!
Fine, just go already, moron!
Ah, r-right...
Oh, now comes Mister Satan's counterattack!
Incredible! Incredible! A storm of punches!
Contestant No. 18 is being pummeled!
D-Didn't we have an agreement?
I just said I'd let you win,
I didn't say I wouldn't hit back.
If only I get beaten up, it
would look suspicious, right?
B-But that's all I can take...
All right! Then grab hold and throw me!
Then use your finishing
technique for the big finish.
–Got that?
–Y-Yes!
Oh! Mister Satan has thrown Contestant No. 18!
Here goes! This will put an end to it all!
Go, Satan!
Take this!
Satan Miracle Special
Ultra Super Megaton Punch!!
S-She took that head-on!
Um...
This is your finishing technique?
Y-Yes. For the time being...
Did you see that?!
Uh, at first glance, it may have
looked like an ordinary blow,
but after a few seconds, it
strikes with an explosive shock!
That was the Satan Miracle...
um... Beautiful Super Bari-bari Punch!
Mister Satan is victorious!
Number One!
Whoa! You really are awesome, Mister Satan!
He's every bit our protector of the Earth!
Contestant No. 18 showed
us marvelous strength indeed,
but before Mister Satan,
she was all-too-easily defeated.
Mister Satan defends his championship!
What the hell is happenin'?
G-Good question...
I'll come to your house
tomorrow to get the money.
If you don't pay me, I'll kill you!
Y-Yes, I understand.
Satan! Satan! Satan!
Damn...
I wonder what gave us away.
No. 18-san is certain to win now.
Nothing is ever certain... Hmm?
Isn't that...?
Ah, it's Videl-san!
Hey!
Videl-san!
Goten-kun!
Ah, wait up, Goten!
They're late.
They're too late!
I wonder what kind of guy is coming out.
I wish they'd come soon.
What could they be doing?
I'm looking forward to seeing
how strong you've become.
Gohan, have you been training
regularly while I've been gone?
Ah, no, you see...
Hmph! Unfortunately,
it seems he's used peacetime as an
excuse not to do all that much training.
Nowadays, we're the
ones with the higher powers.
Of course, in his case, we
never know what might happen
if he launches into a rage, do we?
No wonder these three are so composed!
If it comes to it, they can
release incredible power,
like Goku-san momentarily displayed before.
Th-The truth is so utterly hard to believe...
To think, that the Kaioshin could be
flustered by people from the lower realm...
I-It can't be...!
D-Dabura!!
I-It can't be! I wasn't expecting
them to send out Dabura so soon!
It's really quite something for you humans
to have beaten Yakon and come to Stage 3.
You might even call it miraculous.
I will give you credit for that.
However, this is as far as it goes.
I will be your opponent now.
Hmph! For you, his number one,
to be making an appearance already,
it must mean that Babidi is
getting considerably anxious.
Enough of your idle chit-chat!
Let's go, right now, all of you!
No way, no way!
It's my turn to be the one that beats you!
What did you say?!
Never mind that, let's
fight in a different location,
like when Father and Vegeta did,
not this cramped place!
Oh, but that dark place would be a problem.
W-Why you...!
That's enough mocking out of you!
Just a minute, Dabura!
Any shock received by the
spaceship will not be good
towards completely reviving Majin Boo.
If you can, why don't you
fight in a different place?
Ah, certainly.
Where would be good?
Wherever allows them the best handicap.
A world with an environment similar to Earth's.
You're sure self-possessed. Little wonder.
Nobody can stand up to you, after all.
Well, here goes.
Papparapa!
W-What's this?
How's this? You should
have no quarrel with this place.
Okay! Well, here goes!
Don't get careless, Gohan!
That's about it. And that's
why everyone's gone there.
Madoshi...?!
Majin...?!
Y-Yeah...
D-Did you hear that, Goten?
Y-Yeah!
Sounds like fun! Yeah? Yeah? Yeah?
That way, right?
That's right, that's right! I can feel our Papas' ki!
J-Just a second, you guys! Don't
tell me you're thinking of going there?
Hurry! If we don't get there fast,
our Papas will have already beaten their foes!
No, no! I wanna see, I wanna see!
I want to see this Majin Boo guy!
Go!!
Yahoo!
You've got to be kidding!
You fool!
What?
Gohan's power is at full throttle!
The real fight begins now!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Dabura pulled out.
I don't think he's running away.
What is he thinking?
Babidi-sama, there is one among them
with strong enough wickedness in his heart,
that we can draw him over to our side.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"A Wicked Heart Discovered!!
Dabura's Great Idea."
They're going after Vegeta-san!
"Next time"
"A Wicked Heart Discovered!!
Dabura's Great Idea"