The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
The ultra-power of Super Gotenks
had finally cornered Majin Boo.
However, at the moment when
he was about to finish him off,
his Fusion dissolved, and
Gotenks returned to Trunks and Goten.
Huh?! This is bad!
Our Fusion has come undone!
Elsewhere, in the Kaioshin Realm,
Gohan finally completed his power-up.
I ain't gonna see you again.
Not until you come to
the Other World, that is...
Good luck! Go blow Majin Boo away!
Fine!
All right! let's go!
"Boo Overwhelmed!!
Gohan's Miracle Power."
For them to run out of time...!
You rotten guys! This is all because
you didn't finish him off right away!
Now we've had it! Our Fusion has ended too!
You don't suppose we're
going to get killed now?
There's no supposing about it! We are
definitely going to be killed like this!
I-It can't be so...!
Say, shall we run away?
Do you think we could get away?
It would be impossible, wouldn't it?
We're going to get killed, are we?
Damn, and we're still so young!
I don't want to be!
Piccolo-san!
I don't think it will be
much help, but I'll fight too.
I'll do everything I can, and if it's
not enough, I'll die alongside you.
Do everything you can?!
You've got to be kidding!
Piccolo-san, you know darn well
this is the guy not even
Fusion could stand up to!
Right! Right! Piccolo-san, you're
an adult, so maybe you're fine with it,
but we're still children,
and we'd definitely hate to die!
What should we do, Trunks-kun?
Okay, then...!
Having come to this...
Having come to this...?
Let's sincerely apologize!
He's pretty simple, so if we give him
one of his favorite candies and apologize,
he might unexpectedly forgive us!
That's it! Maybe he will forgive us!
If he does, ha ha, we can buy
enough time for our next Fusion!
N-Now, come on...
All right, Goten! Let's get
some candy ready right now!
But there aren't any
stores anywhere around.
It's possible that we could look
throughout the entire world and there
wouldn't be any candy stores left.
I don't think there's anyone
around who makes candy, either.
Maybe this won't work after all...
Hey! Cut it out already!
What?!
W-What's the matter with Majin Boo?
B-Beats me...
I-I hear something!
Huh? Is that... could it be... snoring?
H-He's asleep. He fell asleep! How come?
W-What does this mean?!
Is he just toying around with us?
Or is he instead...?
We're going to go have a look!
W-Wait! Don't do anything uncalled-for!
He has to be sleeping
after all, here, doesn't he?
I'm not sure. Maybe he's just trying to trick us.
I know! Let's tug on this and see!
If he's playing possum on us, he's
sure to be surprised and open his eyes!
Here goes!
A little farther...
What?!
Y-You idiots! Goten! Trunks!
W-What are you guys trying to do,
intentionally wake him up now
that he's so kindly gone to sleep?!
I don't know what he's planning,
but right now it doesn't matter!
In any case, we have to do
whatever it takes to buy some time,
and get ready for your next Fusion!
That's the only way we can defeat him! Got it?
Okay...
What?!
W-What ki is this?!
Someone's coming!
Who is it?!
Th-They're strong! This is a fantastic ki!
I-I don't know it! Who can it be?!
Is it a new enemy? Or is it instead...?
I-It's Goku!!
No it isn't! It's Big Brother! Big Brother!
Gohan-san?!
W-What?
It couldn't be!
Thank goodness I'm in time!
–Gohan-san...
–Big Brother! Thank goodness!
You weren't dead, huh?
Nah. It was a close one, but
I was saved by Kaioshin-sama.
Up to now, I've been at Kaioshin-sama's place.
I-Is that Gohan? No.
There's something different!
The look on his face is a little different,
and he has a different
sort of ki than before, too.
On top of that, his meekness has disappeared.
That's why I couldn't tell it was him.
What about everyone else?
They were killed by Majin Boo!
What?! Including Mom
and Dende and the others?
That's right! Everyone except for us!
That's done it! To think that
even Dende had been killed!
How can this be?! The Dragon Balls, upon
which everything depends, have vanished!
They were delicious!
I ate them, after I turned them into choco!
No, that's not true! I can feel it! A faint ki...
Hey, don't tell me you intend to fight me!
No. I intend to kill you!
Okay, Gohan! Show him your power,
now that you've undergone that power-up!
Still, Kaioshin-sama, when you first said
you were going to bring Gohan-san
to this holy region, the Kaioshin Realm,
I was thinking, "What could come from this?"
Kibit, I was right in my judgment, wasn't I?
Yes. Not only did he pull
out the legendary Z-Sword,
which even successive generations
of Kaioshin-sama were unable to do,
but he also released the Grand
Kaioshin-sama that was sealed within it!
Indeed. To think that in fourteen generations,
and with fourteen other Kaioshin,
not one was able to break my seal...
P-Please, forgive us!
Even so, I think that
effectively, this is for the best.
After all, the human realm should be defended
by the hands of humans themselves.
I think so too.
After all, the future ain't something
to be handed to us by someone.
Which is why...
People must always continue to work for it,
and it's precisely because
we have a future we believe in
that people can hold life precious.
Now that I think about it,
I'm dead, huh? Oh, well...
Still, Goku-san, what you say is correct.
Hmph! I knew that without
having to be lectured by you fellas!
After all, how many years
do you think I've been alive?!
Everyone together
making a fool of the old guy...!
That's not how it is!
Hang in there, Gohan! The future
of Earth rests on your shoulders!
I remember! You're the guy I blew away earlier!
You're going to kill me?
Looks like you want to get
blown away by me once again!
I-It's hopeless! Judging from
his ki, Gohan has powered up,
but no matter how much, there's no
way he can win by fighting him head-on!
I-It's too dangerous! We have to use
Fusion and fight together with him!
We can't! We can't do that
until an hour has gone by!
I know! But let's at least try to do what we can!
After all, at this rate, Big Brother will be...!
Goten...
All right! Let's try to fight
together, even if it is hopeless!
All right!
N-Now you've done it!
B-Big Brother...!
A-Awesome!
Way to go, Gohan-san!
What's the matter? Weren't
you going to blow me away?
I will blow you away! I will blow you away!
I will blow you away!!
Unbelievable! What the
hell has happened to him?
It's hard to believe he's the same Gohan!
And he's not even
Super Saiyan, but that power...!
Way to go, Big Brother!
That level of attack couldn't
have had any effect on you.
It's useless for you to try to trick me.
Damn! It hasn't affected him at all!
What's the matter? Aren't you
going to come? In that case, I'll go!
He's coming! He's coming! He's coming!
W-What's this?!
Over here.
You retard.
With his ultimate power,
Gohan tosses Majin Boo around!
The light of hope for the
Earth has begun to shine!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
It looks like you're stunned by
Gohan's power, huh, Majin Boo?
I will not stand for any
power stronger than mine!
Absolutely not, absolutely not!
I won't stand for you!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Has He Done It!?
Majin Boo's Great Explosion."
What does this mean? What is
he planning by blowing himself up?
"Next time"
"Has He Done It!?
Majin Boo's Great Explosion"