The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Majin Boo is dramatically
stronger than any previous foe.
Has every last means of
defeating him been lost?
V-Vegeta, what are you doing?
It's still too soon to be using the Dragon Balls.
Kakarrot, how many times have
you saved the Earth up to now?
What's this, all of a sudden?
It's time to let the guys on Earth
take responsibility for a change.
And with that, Vegeta then suddenly
used the Dragon Balls of Planet Namek
to bring back the Earth and the Earthlings.
Vegeta's idea was to...
We're starting! Get ready!
Ready? For what?
Get ready to make a Genki Dama!
A-A Genki Dama? A Genki Dama, you say?!
"A Last Hope!!
We'll Make a Huge Genki Dama."
We didn't die!
We're saved!
Huh? Did I come back to life?
Thank goodness, Mother! Thank goodness!
What on earth is going on?
What the hell happened?
Never mind us, even the cities have
been returned to the way they were.
Good question. I don't have any idea.
Say, where did that Majin Boo guy go?
Satan isn't here, either.
Don't tell me Satan managed to...?!
I guess there's no way he could have, huh?
Thank goodness!
We were training at Kaio-sama's place.
So that's why you weren't in Heaven, huh?
I was thinkin' that you'd gone to Hell.
That's awful!
–We wouldn't go!
–Papa!
Papa!
Papa! I missed you!
H-Hey, cut it out! This is
embarrassing, in front of everyone!
How nice for you, everyone!
To be able to return to life!
I committed too many sins, so I couldn't,
but I will pray for everyone's
peace from Heaven here!
Hey, Vegeta, your idea
was to use a Genki Dama?
That's right.
So that's it! You've thought
this out, huh Vegeta?
Surely, with a Genki Dama,
we might be able to defeat Boo!
Hang in there, Boo! That's it!
To the body! Hook! Uppercut!
What's the matter, Boo?
If this is my dream, you should
definitely be winning! My Boo!
Y-You turn into candy!
B-Boo!
Shake it off, Boo!
Say, it's impossible,
ain't it? With a Genki Dama?
Even if I were to gather a
little bit of ki from everyone...
I told you, didn't I?
Let the folks on Earth take
responsibility for a change.
Besides, you're not going
to get a little from everyone.
You're going to push
everyone right to their limit!
Right to their limit?
Vegeta-san!
Polunga is telling us to say the third wish!
The third one doesn't matter!
Do whatever you want!
You can't mean... for me to
do whatever I want would be...
Never mind, listen!
Is Kaioshin listening?
Y-Yes!
I want to talk to all the people
on Earth! Do something about it!
B-By that, do you mean like the way
Madoshi Babidi used magic to do so?
That's not something I can do!
Th-That will be impossible, I'm afraid.
W-What?!
Leave that to me!
Who's that?!
Th-That voice! It's Kaio-sama, right?
You guessed it!
Vegeta, for you to choose my Genki Dama
as your finishing technique was nice!
Okay, talk! Never mind Earth,
you can talk to the whole universe!
That will help a lot!
Do you hear me, people of the world?!
I am speaking to you from some other place.
I believe you already know, but
most of you were killed by Majin Boo.
However, through a mysterious power,
I had you brought back to life.
Your cities and houses and such should
also be returned to just the way they were.
However, this is by no means a dream!
N-Not a dream?
H-Hey, what's he talking about?
He's talking to everyone on Earth.
I-I knew this was a dream!
H-Hey, you guys! If you've got
time for this worthless spacing off,
then help Boo out, would you?
We know! Just hold on a moment!
Right now, in a certain location,
there is a warrior who is
fighting Majin Boo in your place!
However, to be honest, you could
say that our odds are pretty bad.
I-It's Vegeta! It's Vegeta's voice!
Majin Boo's strength far exceeds even Cell's!
Vegeta...!
And so, we want to make use of your power!
Raise your hands to the sky!
Gather your energy together and defeat Boo!
It will wear you out
considerably, but don't worry!
It will be just like after
you run as hard as you can!
Now, do it! Raise your hands!
What a lousy approach towards
making requests this guy has!
For crying out loud...
All right, Kakarrot! Get started!
Right!
Not bad, Vegeta! I've got
to give you more credit!
Everyone! Share your Genki with me! Please!
That's it! A Genki Dama!
You got it, Papa!
Hmph! Vegeta! This stunt isn't like you!
Here it comes, here it comes, here it comes!
It's so huge all of a sudden!
This is from Gohan and the others!
Ha! This is awesome, all right!
With just the ki from them,
it's already gotten this huge!
That's it! Great! More! More!
Come on! More of you, raise your hands!
Understood, Vegeta! Here!
L-Like this?
–Here!
Yahoo!
This time it's Kuririn and
Bulma and those guys' ki!
Way to go, Vegeta!
It's working! It's working!
They've done it!
Goku-san! Quickly now, finish Boo off!
Incredible! To think that a
method such as this still remained!
Really, what incredible people they are!
Yay!
This is strange!
If they're getting power
from all of the folks on Earth,
then that Super Genki Dama has
no business being only that large!
From here on... from here on,
it will get larger! I'm sure it will!
Y-Yeah...
Polunga, you're certain that everyone who
was wished for has come back to life, right?
Of course, I am certain.
More importantly, do you
not have a third wish yet?
Th-The Kaioshin Realm!
Dammit, no!
Didn't we make it in time?
Damn it all! We were so close!
Hey! Look–look over there!
Boo hasn't had it yet!
Geez, don't scare me like that!
Vegeta!
It hasn't gotten the
slightest bit bigger since then!
This much probably still
ain't enough to defeat Boo yet!
Strange... it should have
long since been completed!
W-Why isn't it?
Hey, he said to raise our hands!
What good will it do to do that?
W-W-What's that?
Why am I hearing those voices?
Who the hell was that?
That was some dubious voice!
W-What did you say?!
Something I don't trust about this, you know?
Yeah. Who do they think is
going to raise their hands?
That was kind of creepy, huh?
Let's go, let's go!
Hey, now, I'm hungry!
Oh? I suppose so. How about
we go get something to eat?
–Don't fall for it!
–It doesn't have anything to do with us!
W-What was that?!
L-Look here! Shh! Be quiet!
Don't fall for it, you say?!
It has nothing to do with us, you say?!
Damn it to hell!! What sort of
rubbish are you talking about?!
It's your Earth!!
How long are you going to act so
spoiled before you're finally satisfied?!
What's the matter with everyone on Earth?
This Genki Dama isn't getting
even the least bit more Genki!
Oh, my! Boo!
Boo!
B-Boo!!
I-It's no use any more! Please! Help Boo out!
Dammit! I won't ask any more!
Hey! Out of my way!
Wait! Don't be hasty, Vegeta!
You fool! How can you ask like that?!
Don't give up, you've got to keep
on persuading everyone on Earth!
There's no other way for
the universe to be saved!
Listen, Earthlings!
I'm saying this one more time!
Stop your whining! All you
have to do is raise your hands!
This isn't going to work.
Too bad, Vegeta. It was a good idea, though.
You understand, don't you, that
Earthlings are this level of race, after all?
W-What are you doing, Vegeta?!
Aside from our friends, just about
nobody is giving up any ki, you know!
I know!
But nobody there believes
a damn thing I'm saying!
Damn!
Hey! Earthlings! Cooperate, right now!
Do you want to get killed by Majin Boo again?!
This is not a dream, or anything! I am serious!
Why don't you... why don't you
lend us your power for a change?!
Again and again, the Earthlings utterly
refuse to listen to what Vegeta tells them.
The Super Genki Dama is the only
thing that can dispatch Majin Boo now!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
With the universe in this much trouble,
why won't everybody cooperate?!
You people! Don't you hear
the request of Mister Satan?!
I need to defeat Boo, so hurry
up and lend me your strength!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Ultra-Impressive!! The Genki Dama
From Everyone is Finished."
There it is! The extra-large
Genki Dama is finished!
"Next time"
"Ultra-Impressive!! The Genki Dama
From Everyone is Finished"