Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
K-Kami-sama! Don't die...
I am neither Kami nor Piccolo any longer.
I'm a Namekian who has long
since forgotten his real name.
The mysterious monster finally reveals himself.
And yet, he bears even
greater, more startling secrets...
"Kamehame-Ha!?
The Monster Who Possesses Goku's Ki."
So, you've shown yourself, you beast.
Save me!
W-What's this?
What sort of ki am I sensing from him?
I-Impossible!
H-How can it be?!
Mister Popo scared.
Kami-sama and Piccolo united, got strong.
But still feel he not able defeat monster.
Kami-sama...
Help me!
I am the wealthiest man around here!
I'll give you whatever money you want, save me!
Hey! How about it, you?!
I don't expect you can understand
what I'm saying, but release him.
Even a life such as his is still a life.
S-Save me...
My... mon... ey...
The next one to end up like this will be you,
Piccolo Daimao!
W-What?! What's this?!
What's the matter, Gohan?
I can feel Piccolo-san's ki, but twice over!
Eh? Piccolo's?
What's this?
W-Who are you?!
Why do you know the name Piccolo?
I am your brother.
What?!
Hey, what's going on?! This ki...
It's Freeza's, and his father's ki as well!
I can feel others.
Piccolo-san, Freeza and his father, and now Dad!
So many ki, all gathered in one spot.
What's going on here?
This is impossible!
We're feeling them, all right.
But this cannot be happening.
Freeza and his father are supposed to be dead.
This direction...
It's coming from the direction of Gingertown,
where those incidents were reported!
That's impossible!
Now there's even Goku's ki...
Father is definitely sleeping up here.
Sector 1051 West.
Right near where that egg
and carapace were located.
There's no doubt about it now.
Now then, what exactly are you?
Tell me! Let's have it all.
That won't be necessary.
See, you are about to become my meal.
So, you don't intend to tell me, then.
In that event, I'll just have
to squeeze the life out of you
not knowing any more than I already do.
Does Piccolo Daimao plan on killing me, then?
For whatever reason, you
apparently know who Piccolo is.
However...
However, unfortunately for you...
You're mistaking me for him.
What?!
I'm mistaking you for him, you say?
Are you saying you are not Piccolo Daimao?
That's what I am saying.
Thank goodness, I made it.
You may be everything you are,
but this unknown monster may
be too dangerous for even you.
There's another incredibly powerful ki.
Someone else has appeared.
Yeah, just now.
Just what exactly is going on?
That has to be Piccolo!
But isn't this ki too far
different from Piccolo-san's ki?
Awesome, man! He really has united!
United? With Kami-sama, like you were saying?
They're back together now,
after having been apart?
Right.
And since Piccolo was so incredibly
strong to begin with and all...
This is the ki of a Super Namekian!
T-This is amazing.
He was able to power up that much?
Your having extinguished all the people
of this city actually works in my favor.
What's that?
What do you mean by that?
It means I can go all-out.
What?!
That shockwave just now...
Over there. It's started.
There was a definite atmospheric
vibration a moment ago.
Could you tell?
Yeah.
I wonder if a volcano just
exploded somewhere. Or perhaps...
At any rate, it's far from here.
The suburbs of Metro West.
No. 16!
There are two giant powers
there, likely battling each other.
You've got power radar installed?
How come you haven't said
anything about it until now?
You didn't ask.
I suppose not.
So then, can we have you
tell us who is fighting whom?
I don't know.
I have no data on either one.
However, one of the powers is
large enough it even rivals your levels.
What?!
Chalk up yet another "miss" to Doctor Gero.
That radar of yours is malfunctioning.
There's no one in this world
who has the power to rival mine.
Utterly ludicrous.
Let's go, No. 16.
T-That was...
So that's what you've got, is it?
I had you sized up as
quite an abominable monster,
and it looks like I was right.
You do pretty well yourself.
No matter that I have not
achieved my perfect form yet...
P-Perfect form?
You don't mean...
So that's why you've been
preying on these people?!
I take them as the energy of life for myself.
Answer this!
Who was it that sent you to
this era in that time machine?!
Some ally of yours?
I was the one who sent me.
That time machine was too
small for this body, you see.
I had to revert myself back
to my egg form in order to fit.
In any case, it surprises
me that you would even know
about me and the time machine.
But...
I doubt you already knew about this...
No way, this can't be right!
It's Goku-san's ki again!
Ka...
me...
ha...
Impossible!
F-Father...
W-What is this?
Can this monster even
perform a Kamehame-Ha?!
How can this be?!
Ha!!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
He can even perform a Kamehame-Ha!
This guy is outrageous!
The ultimate creature,
created by Doctor Gero's computer–
that's what I am!
Piccolo, I'm going to help
myself to your life's essence.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"A Life Form of Evil and Destruction!!
His Name Is Artificial Human Cell."
Don't let him beat you, Piccolo-san!
"Next time"
"A Life Form of Evil and Destruction!!
His Name Is Artificial Human Cell"