Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
May I take care of all three of them?
Feel free.
No! He was targeting the Scouters!
Scouters?
Those devices that can tell your
opponent's strength and location!
So that's it! Then they can't tell
precisely where the Dragon Balls are, after all!
Using those Scouter things,
they just searched out Namekians,
then forced them out of them!
That old man knew that, so that's
why he destroyed all of their Scouters!
The Elder launched a surprise attack.
However, this has immediately set
fire to Freeza and company's ferocity.
I'll kill you all!
I'll kill each and every one of you!
"Gohan in Peril!
A Pursuing Dodoria Summons Death."
Elder!
Dodoria-san! Wait!
Begin by killing these three younger ones!
Dammit!
I'll dispose of all three
of you within ten seconds.
Don't be ridiculous! You think
you're a match for all three of us?!
Huh? Do I think I'm a match
for you? What an amusing joke.
What?!
Come on!
It's hopeless! He can't defeat
that guy with that kind of attack!
You now understand that it is
useless to try to defy us or run away, I trust.
In any case, come back down here, please.
So you have finally grown
cooperative, I see. That will do.
You have destroyed my precious Scouters.
May I have you produce your
Dragon Ball, by way of apology?
I have no choice. But
promise me that no matter what,
you will not lay a hand on the children!
Yes, yes, we ought to have done
it this way right from the beginning.
W-What monsters these guys are! How awful!
Why, those–!
H-Hey, Gohan! Don't go getting any funny ideas.
T-There's simply no way we
can stand up to those guys, okay?
Yow-ow-ow... With twenty times the
gravity, you get twenty times the pain!
Now, take this, and get out of here at once.
Well done.
While I am at it, let me also
have you tell me the locations
of the two remaining Dragon Balls.
Don't be ridiculous!
We Namekians don't sell each
other out, even if it means our own lives!
Now, we had an agreement! Leave here at once!
Oh dear, not you, too.
There is absolutely no one on this
planet who will speak about their friends.
I guess I will have to have
you die... along with the children!
W-What did you say?! Why, you–!
Elder! Elder!
This isn't what we agreed to!
You promised you wouldn't do anything
else if I handed over the Dragon Ball!
But unless I have all seven
Dragon Balls, it is meaningless, correct?
You have destroyed our Scouters,
so we will need to have you tell us
where the remaining two are.
I told you, I'll tell you about
the others over my dead body!
Is that how badly you want to die?
In that case, I will do as you wish.
What?!
Freeza-sama, will we possibly be able to
search for the Dragon Balls without Scouters?
Kill all three of them.
Yes, sir.
T-That's dirty!
You guys run! Run away!
Right!
I'll show you the pride of the Namekian people!
C-Cargot!
Control yourself, Gohan!
Control yourself.
There's nothing we can do! Hey!
Cargot! Cargot! Cargot!
You didn't even have a chance to
show us this "pride" of yours, huh?
It won't even be any fun
to smash a little kid like this.
Well, all the same, die!
Stop!
Gohan!
What? Your buddies? Where?
Does that teach you?
W-Who the hell are you?!
That idiot!
I am going to take you down!
What did you say?
Kuririn-san!
You dumbass! Run! Hurry!
Hurry!
Right!
They do not appear to be Namekians, do they?
No, sir.
Damn it!
After them! Dodoria-san, catch them!
Gohan, fly as fast as you can!
If he catches us, we're finished!
Right!
Fools! Do you think you can escape?
It's no good! He's faster
than us! He'll overtake us!
They are quite fast, aren't they, Freeza-sama?
They also seem to have more
battle power than the Namekians.
Who in the world could they be?
In the way, to be sure.
That mountain is in the way, you see?
Now our visibility has
become much clearer, has it not?
Huh?
Gohan!
Oh, crap!
Damn!
Dammit, let go of me! Let go of me, you!
I'm not going to make it in time!
Gohan! Get out of here! Hurry! He's coming!
Damn, these sure are nimble little guys!
Kuririn-san, let's land and fight him!
We can't! He isn't the sort of foe we
can do anything against by fighting!
Just fly as hard as you can!
Damn, if this keeps up, we've
had it! I've got to do something!
That's it! Gohan!
Gohan, from here on, don't look
in my direction! Close your eyes!
I have an idea. Got that?!
Right!
Take this!
Taiyo-ken!
My eyes! My eyes!
My eyes!
I did it! It worked!
Why, you–! My eyes!
Gohan! Hide now, while we can!
Right!
W-Why, you rotten–!
W-Where did you go, dammit?!
Where are you?! Where the hell did you go?!
Come on out, dammit!
W-What did you do, Kuririn-san?
Oh, I just blinded him a little bit.
It's okay. He doesn't have
his Scouter anymore, after all.
However, will they indeed be able to
escape the hands of this brutal pursuer?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Saiyans increase their strength
the stronger their opponents are.
I'm sure that goes for Vegeta, too.
What? A Saiyan like you?! You've
got some nerve saying that, don't you?!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Dodoria Dies by Explosion!
Vegeta's Fearsome Shockwave."
Father, that Dodoria guy is scared.
"Next time"
"Dodoria Dies by Explosion!
Vegeta's Fearsome Shockwave"