Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
The Dragon Balls were falling into
the brutal hands of Freeza and his men.
Instinctively jumping into the fray,
Gohan rescued the Namekian child.
Gohan was in jeopardy as
Dodoria followed in hot pursuit.
However, Vegeta then appeared before him.
We Saiyans grow stronger every time we fight.
And Goku continued his
intensive training inside his spaceship
as it headed toward Planet Namek.
"Escape From a Burning Planet!!
A Life-or-Death Kamehame-Ha."
I shot down Dodoria!
I easily beat Dodoria,
who took such pride in his own power!
Even I'm surprised by how much I've improved.
It truly seems that my
battle on Earth was not in vain.
Be that as it may, Dodoria
did say something curious...
I see now. Those runts I was chasing
earlier were Earthlings, weren't they?!
I do indeed sense two large
powers getting farther away.
Of course they couldn't be
Earthlings, but it's still disturbing.
Maybe I should go look into it, just to see.
Whatever the case, I have to get rid of
even the small fries that stand in my way.
The cave that Bulma-san
is hiding in is right over there.
For this being a planet you've never been to
before, I'm surprised you remember so well.
What's that?! Something is
coming! It's incredibly fast!
Hide! Quickly!
Right!
We'll be found if we stay here, won't we?
Never mind, just hurry up and suppress your ki!
All we can do now is
leave our fate up to heaven.
Will it be someone like
that monster from earlier?
Dammit, how did they know where we were?
Both of the power readings
have disappeared. What's going on?
Over in that area, all of a sudden...
K-Kuririn-san! O-Over there!
V-Vegeta! T-Then he
is on this planet, after all!
How can he be here?! This is the
absolute worst thing that could happen!
He's still looking.
He wasn't wearing one of those Scouter devices.
And yet, how is it that
he can tell where we are?
D-Don't tell me he has the ability to sense ki!
If that's the case, then this is bad.
We might be able to extinguish
our ki, but this kid still has a faint one.
Damn. Was I mistaken?
Is it because I'm not yet used to
using this power sensing technique?
Maybe I shouldn't have destroyed that Scouter.
I'm sensing a small power.
It's no mistake this time. Let's check it out.
He's coming this way!
It's hopeless! He's going to find us!
It's near that rock over there.
At this point, all we can do is fight.
Even though we know we'll get killed.
Let's go!
Right!
Now!
Tch! It was a fish?
Oh, well. Right now, the first
order of business is to get the two–
no, even just one of
the remaining Dragon Balls.
Once I've hidden it,
Freeza and the others will no
longer be able to get all seven together.
Then I'll find the chance to take the five
that Freeza and company have away from them.
Their having lost their Scouters means
that luck has shifted in Vegeta-sama's favor!
W-We're saved!
I thought it was completely hopeless there.
Lucky for us, huh? We have
that guy in the water to thank.
Anyhow, let's get back to where Bulma-san is,
while keeping our
presence as masked as we can.
You said it was right close by, right?
Yes.
We didn't even fight, and I'm already
exhausted. I'd like to get some rest.
I, uh...
To be honest, I'm starting to think
we shouldn't have come to this planet.
It might not be fair to the
late Yamucha-san and the others,
but far from bringing everyone back to life,
it looks like we're just going
to be adding to the deceased.
You mean, us?
Look! Kuririn-san, over there!
Yeah, right, right.
Bulma-san!
Huh? She's not here.
I'm sure she's hiding deeper inside the cave.
Bulma-san!
It's us! Where are you?! Bulma-san!
A Capsule house!
What were you guys taking it so easy for?!
While leaving a young girl
like me alone in a place like this?!
Taking it easy, she says...
W-What's with the small-size
Piccolo-looking kid there?
By any chance, is that a Namekian?
It's okay.
Has something happened?
For now, just let us in, please.
We'll fill you in on the details.
Oh, right!
I just got some delightful news from my dad!
He said that Son-kun had
blasted off for Planet Namek here!
And that he would arrive in just six days!
You see, apparently, my dad
rebuilt the Saiyan spaceship
that Son-kun came in as a baby!
What's more, he said that Son-kun was
doing some incredible training inside it
along the way.
F-Father?
Yahoo!
Yay! Hooray! Hooray!
Incredible training along the way?
All right! All right! We've found some hope!
Next up, I'll do this for thirty minutes!
Huh? Is it already time for
the next item on the schedule?
That's strange...
What's going on here?
W-What's that?
Goku, can you hear me?
Ah, it's Bulma's daddy!
What on earth is going on?
Part of the exterior of the
spaceship has been damaged.
A meteor or something must have hit it.
If you keep going like this,
you'll slip off course.
W-What's going to happen?!
You won't be able to go to Planet Namek.
You'll become lost in space.
I can't have that!
Go outside and repair it.
Repair it?!
Mm-hmm, it will be easy.
Inside the repair box, there should be
some material and a powerful adhesive.
Wow, so this is space, huh?
Goku, don't panic.
You've got a lifeline, don't you?
That's right. I just
have to reel myself in, huh?
You know, this speed is amazing.
Yikes, I'd better hurry.
Oh, that gave me a start.
Goku, the soles of your boots are magnets,
so you can stand up and walk around.
Oh, yeah?
Ha-ha, it's true!
This is terrific!
Oh, that must be it.
All right, there it is.
Let's see... This is the glue, huh?
Let's see, the course
deviation caused by that damage is...
Oh, what's this?!
All right, that does it.
It was easier than I thought.
Goku, this is bad! You have to
make a course correction right now!
Goku, your position right
now is at SU-83 by 643-XY.
If you keep going the way you are,
you're going to collide
with the star Alpha HZ at 653-XY.
I can't understand anything as
complicated as that! What should I do?!
Oh, just do as I instruct
you to, and it will be easy.
Hurry and get back inside the spaceship.
All right, you got it.
Huh?
I'm stuck here. Come on, now!
This is bad. I can't get loose.
All right, one more time...
Goku, what are you doing? There's no time!
That's easy for you to say,
but my feet got stuck with
the glue, and I can't get free!
What did you say?!
What do I do?!
Tell me!
G-Goku!
Goku-san!
I don't want to die out here!
All right, all I can do now is count on this...
Ka... me...
ha... me...
Ha!
Whew! This is incredible power!
I get it, this is the
result of the twenty G training!
He did it! He did it!
I-It's no use!
Goku-san!
All right, I'm sure of myself now.
This time, full power!
Ka... me...
ha... me...
Ha!
He did it! He did it! He did it!
That much force from twenty Gs.
If I raise the Gs even more,
I'll become even stronger!
I feel it! Larger-size powers!
They number about twenty.
No question about it, it's a Namekian village.
They probably have one of the Dragon Balls.
Freeza and his men don't have Scouters!
No matter what action I may
take now, they won't know about it!
Sure enough. And since
the villagers are still alive,
that proves that Freeza and
the others haven't been here yet!
W-What's this?
It's an alien!
Is the one called Elder here? I've come
to take your Dragon Ball off your hands.
W-What?
I am the Elder. Would you tell
me why you want the Dragon Balls?
Never mind, just hand it over
quickly. You have it, don't you?
Leave us. I cannot allow you
to have it. I can sense evil in you.
Then die.
Bang!
Elder!
Planet Namek was in the worst of circumstances.
At length, Vegeta had also set
out in search of the Dragon Balls.
Is their only hope to await the arrival of Goku?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
This is awesome! Everyone has
arrived at your place, Kaio-sama?
Yamucha, Piccolo, Tenshinhan, and Chaozu.
They all want even tougher
training than what you went through.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Courage Times One Hundred!
The Warriors Gathered Under Kaio."
I Io-Io-Io-love Piccolo-san!
"Next time"
"Courage Times One Hundred!
The Warriors Gathered Under Kaio"