Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
As if the fight with Garlic Jr. had been
just a dream from a scene of a TV drama,
peaceful days had once
again returned to Earth.
"You're My Guy... Kuririn –
A 101st Proposal."
Kurin-chan, hurry!
Right, right, right!
Of all the... why does shopping
with women have to be this tough?
So, what do you think
you're doing, Kurin-chan?!
S-Sorry, Maron-chan...
How annoying! I'm picking up, already!
Yes, hello?
Hmm?
Oh, Bulma, is that you?
T-There's an emergency situation!
Come to the Kame House right away!
All right, let's see you
knock out a home run this time!
Yamucha-san, you have a telephone call.
A phone call? For me?
Hello?
M-Muten Roshi-sama!
I wonder how Maron-chan feels about me.
Maybe she'd be happier if
she were seeing a rich man,
like that one earlier...
What a pretty dress!
Kurin-chan, I want to try this dress on!
Maron-chan, I didn't realize
you were considering this...
Congratulations, Kuririn!
Lucky you, Kuririn!
That car is so nice! I want to ride in it!
Which...?
That house is so cute! I want to live there!
Where, where, where?
Okay, Maron-chan.
I have to act like a man!
I'm going to start thinking seriously too!
What is this?!
Y-You don't have to get so angry.
How can I not be angry about this?!
Really, this ain't funny!
We pulled Gohan-chan away
from studyin' to fly here, you know!
How can you do this to us?
What part of Umigame's birthday are
you calling the emergency situation?!
W-Well, given he's turning
1,000, we can't just let it go.
And well, I forgot all
about it until this morning,
so getting ready for it has been a real struggle.
Oh, everyone,
I'm so touched that you
would trouble yourselves...
...to gather together here today on my behalf...
...I am so truly blessed
to have such good friends!
Cheers!
This is a bit hot, isn't it?
Thank you very much!
Umigame-san, congratulations
on your 1,000th birthday!
Congratulations!
Oh, Kuririn!
Hi, everybody! Hi, Yamucha!
H-Hi...!
Why, you...
Why are you all here?
What a big cake!
Oh, no! It's still much too
early to be giving us cake!
And how did you know?
You don't mean, you
two are... getting married?
Nah, we haven't formalized anything yet,
but Maron-chan keeps saying these things...
Way to go, Kuririn!
How nice for you!
Well, didn't we do nicely for ourselves?
I hope you turn out as
good a bride as I have.
This won't do, Kuririn!
As your master, I have
not yet given my permission!
Y-You mean...
I see no other choice.
If you want my permission...
I'll need one round of
pafu-pafu with Maron-chan!
Turtle-chan, how cute!
Maron-chan, I wonder,
can I make you truly happy?
Why don't you give her the
Mermaid's Tear as a present?
For some reason, I couldn't sleep.
Please forgive me,
I didn't mean to eavesdrop.
No, it's okay. So, what's this
Mermaid's Tear you mentioned?
It's a legendary giant pearl, said to
be at the bottom of the sea around here.
Legend has it that whoever is given this pearl,
by one who loves them, is sure to be happy.
Sure to be happy, huh?
All right!
I will find this Mermaid's Tear,
and present it to Maron-chan!
By doing so, I'm sure I'll be
able to propose to her properly!
"Legend has it that whoever is given this pearl,
by one who loves them, is sure to be happy."
Maron-chan, I vow to give you
the Mermaid's Tear. And then...
Oh, they sure are fine, those lively young girls!
Muten Roshi-sama, they're your favorites,
same as they've always been, huh?
Pa! Don't you go pullin' any lecherous faces!
Say, how come Kurin-chan
isn't here? I'm bored.
Hey, Yamucha, take me to
the city for some shopping?
Well, you see...
Hold on, now, are you sure
you're serious about Kuririn?
Maron doesn't know.
You don't know? Of all the...
She's right!
To get married, you
have to have what it takes...
...for keepin' house and
raisin' children, like I do!
You can't be gettin' married
with half-hearted feelin's.
Oh, my! You're such a couple of Auntie-san s!
–A-Auntie...
–...san s?
She might be one, but not me...
What did you say?!
I'm younger than you are!
I'm not the one who looks house-worn!
I do not look like I'm house-worn!
I am a lovely, lovely housewife!
This is a fright...
I can do whatever I want.
Maron will go to a nearby beach now.
Kuririn-san, we should search
the ocean floor around here, right?
Yeah. Thanks for helping me out on this.
What's the matter with the fish-san s?
It's the Mermaid's Tear!
I-I've finally found it!
Kuririn-san, watch out!
Kuririn-san!
The Mermaid's Tear!
Kuririn-san, watch out!
I see. This pearl is the treasure of the fish-san s.
Treasure?
Yeah.
They're guarding it with everything they have.
Kuririn-san, is it out of the question
to give Maron-san a different present?
Do we have to take this pearl
back with us, no matter what?
I'm sorry, Maron-chan. I...
Gohan, let's go home.
Kuririn-san...
Maron-chan...
Kurin-chan!
What's wrong, Kurin-chan?
I hate a gloomy person.
Y-Yeah.
You see... Maron-chan...
What?
I'll be frank. I'm not sure I have what
it takes to make you happy. And so...
Farewell.
Kurin-chan...
Say, hold on a minute! How come?
Don't you like me any more?
S-Sure I do...
Then why?
You know, for you, Kurin-chan,
I wouldn't mind being a bride...
Maron-chan, see, you can't... huh?
Bride?
M-Maron-chan!
Maron-chan!
Maron-chan!!
Yo.
Say there, honey, how about
going for a drive with me?
How far?
Metro West.
Lucky lucky! I'll go, I'll go!
I'm back!
Hmm? Where's Maron-chan?
Yeah, well, she wasn't the kind
of girl who would settle down,
so "bang," I broke up with her!
You did what?!
What a waste!
Are you sure about that? She didn't dump you?
Oolong!
Way to go, Kuririn!
I gotta give you more credit.
That's right! I can say this now,
but I was against it from the start!
So was I. There's somethin' about that li'l lady...
...she lacked any kind of discretion!
Didn't she though?
Kuririn-san...
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Freeza is still alive?!
Judging by the way he's heading for Earth,
he's about to cause more trouble, huh?
It's not just one!
There's another gut with
impossibly large ki coming this way!
How can this be?!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"That There is Earth, Papa...
The Counter-Attack of Freeza, Father and Son."
Oh, no! I can't just sit here studying!
"Next time"
"That There is Earth, Papa...
The Counter-Attack of Freeza, Father and Son"