Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
What's up with Father, anyhow?
It's been a year now.
Maybe he doesn't want to come back to Earth.
"That There is Earth, Papa...
The Counter-Attack of Freeza, Father and Son."
Ka... me...
ha... me...
Ha!!
Shoot!
It's no use. At my level...
...I don't even hold a candle to Goku.
The time when I, Muten Roshi,
could be hailed as the greatest
under the sun is now a thing of the past.
Yeah, and now you're no more
than a simple, dirty old man.
Goku must be off in space
somewhere, continuing his training.
Roughly one year's time has passed since
Son Goku, having become a Super Saiyan,
and waging the most difficult of battles,
had managed to defeat Freeza in
an incredible display of strength.
However, Son Goku had
still not returned to Earth.
Gohan-chan, are ya studyin'?
Mother!
Gohan-chan, what are ya doin'?
Gohan-chan, this is Shu Saiaku-sensei,
a private tutor who startin'
today'll be helpin' with your studyin'.
Private tutor?
Lately, you've been goofin' off too much,
an' you've gotten too
far behind in your studyin'.
Startin' today, I'm havin' the Sensei
here strictly oversee your learnin'.
Mother, I can do this on my own!
No way! Soon you'd be off
playin' with Haiya Dragon!
With Goku-sa not coming home in all this time,
an' with my good looks an'
youth, to feel like a thermos...
I mean, a widow...
...is a terrible thing.
I don't have anyone I can
count on except you, Gohan-chan.
I want you to do everythin' the Sensei tells you.
Sensei-sama, please accept our request.
I am the strictest, most
superior private tutor in the world.
By obediently doing exactly as I say,
even the most stupid pupil can succeed.
Gohan-chan ain't stupid.
If you want to get into a good
school, you will submit to me!
Now then, we will begin with a test.
It sure is nice to be at peace.
I've been wondering, where do
you suppose Vegeta went off to?
Most likely he's flying around in
space, trying to catch up with Goku.
The guy is obsessed.
Just looking at him
makes chills go down my back!
If you look closer, you'll see he's a good guy.
Where do you see that? He's a spaceship thief!
To go through all that just to pursue
Goku, you have to admire his guts.
Hey, Bulma, are you...?
Yamucha, don't be jealous, don't be jealous!
Makes no difference to me.
From what Papa tells me,
he should be out of fuel soon.
I wonder if he found Son-kun or not.
Let's see, this is...
Can't you solve a problem as easy as this?
It's only a first year high school level problem!
Yeah, well I haven't learned this yet.
Don't talk back to me!
What kind of attitude is that?
I will not tolerate any
rebelliousness toward me!
Do you really want to
deny your mother her wishes?
Aw, crap...
Now Gohan-chan will be all right.
We're lucky to have found a good Sensei.
I'll cook them somethin' yummy.
Such a low level of intelligence!
Don't give me that impudent look!
You brat! Don't mess around with me.
Unbelievable.
I'd like to see the face of the
father that ran out on you two.
Haiya Dragon!
Haiya Dragon, we can't let
Mother or the private tutor find out.
Haiya Dragon, wait!
Hey, Gohan. How've you been?
Father!
Goku-sa!
Chichi! I just got back.
Chichi, I'm hungry.
Let me have something to eat.
Goku-sa, it's bad manners
to go in through a window.
What'll we do if Gohan starts doin' it too?
Chichi, less formality, more food!
Okay, then!
I'll put all my skill into makin' you somethin'!
Father, tell me a story about
how you fought with Freeza!
What have you been
doing up until now? Hm? Hm?
How did you get back? Hm?
Tell me?
Father, tell me!
Let go of me, kid!
Let go! Owww, let go, kid!
Hey, kid! Let go! Let go of me!
Let go of my hand now!
You nasty brute!
If you've got that much
power, you don't need to nap,
you should be applying
that power to your studies!
Oh, it was a dream?
Well, I guess I should have expected as much
from the son of a man who is so inhuman,
someone who directs all his attention to
his own physical strengths, isn't that right?
Well, you lousy dropout?
What are you looking at me like that for?!
I thought I told you to submit to me!
Stop talking badly about my father!
Stop talking badly... about him.
Stop this.
I won't let you talk badly about Father!
Stop this! I am your private tutor!
Ma'am! Gohan-kun is having a tantrum!
Gohan, what are you doin' to the Sensei?
Mother!
What kind of parenting are you
doing to be raising a child like this?
Indeed! Such a rebellious nature
as this is out of the ordinary.
How dare you look at me like that?
Gohan...
This is all your father's fault,
him not coming home.
Goku-sa's fault?!
That's right! It's his father's fault!
This has nothing to do with Father!
You be quiet!
This is the second year now that
you haven't heard from him, isn't it?
How incredibly thoughtless of him!
Stop talking badly about Father!
But, since this is my job, if you
were to ask me to teach a pig...
or for that matter,
a monkey, I would teach them.
You'll have to provide five times
my usual tutoring fee, though.
Gohan-kun is even harder to
teach than a monkey, you see.
And he has no real potential...
You've had your say,
now get the hell outta here!
Mother!
Gohan...
The blame for that brat's poor
upbringing lies not only with his father,
but even more so with his mother!
You shut up!
Oh, dear! The spaceship thief has returned!
Vegeta! What do you want?!
Oh, dear! Oh, dear! Oh, dear!
I see Kakarrot hasn't returned yet.
You mean you didn't meet
up with Goku out in space?
I don't have any compelling need to answer you.
Hey, hey, that's enough talk, you two.
Why don't we let him take a shower?
See? You're so dirty, aren't you?
So, it's this way.
Well, hurry up! You're being
impolite in front of a Lady.
What?!
What's this?
Vegeta is at her mercy.
So, anyone for tea?
I've left you something to change into here.
Kakarrot, hurry up and get back here.
Show me the power of a Super Saiyan.
Oh, so it was Vegeta, was it?
And here I came over,
certain that it was Goku instead.
Even now, the only thing Vegeta
seems to have on his mind is Goku.
I don't suppose he's ever
worn our kind of clothes, huh?
There's no way to know.
Hey, woman!
Uh...
Woman!
Hey!
Can't you hear me, Earth woman?
Now listen here! My name is "Bulma"!
Call me by my name, you boor.
What have you done with my clothes?
They were dirty, so I put them in the wash.
You did what?!
You've got a change
of clothes there, right?
You presume to make me,
the prince of the warrior Saiyan race,
wear something like this?!
Well then, how about going naked?
Man, what a vulgar woman!
Why, you...
Oh, my, it suits you better than I thought!
Don't laugh!
If you value your lives, don't laugh!
Until Son-kun gets back,
how about staying here?
That's a brave front, but I bet
you don't have any money, do you?
And if you stay here, you'll know
right away when Son-kun comes back.
It's your own fault for
hirin' that private tutor, Chichi!
An' on the other hand, I bet
the tutor sure was surprised, huh?
Gohan-chan's studyin'.
Oh, that's right! But I still bet that
private tutor was really surprisified!
Pa! Can'tcha be more quiet?
Can you feel it, Gohan? That incredible ki?
Yes.
This... isn't a very good ki, is it?
It's awful! And it's approaching fast.
You must also be vaguely sensing this–
This ki, it belongs to Freeza, doesn't it?
It couldn't be.
And yet, it certainly does...
Impossible! I'm certain
that Goku took care of Freeza!
It's not just one... there's
another... impossibly large ki.
How can this be?
Kakarrot, you scum!
You didn't finish him off!
This ki, are you sure it's Freeza?
You think I could be mistaken about this?
Under what stupid reasoning?
What did you say?!
Vegeta! This isn't stupid
reasoning, it's Yakiniku seasoning!
I have a feeling that even if the
Earth were gone, Bulma would survive.
How can this be?
That there is Earth, Papa.
It looks as though we've arrived here...
...before the Super Saiyan
that did all this to me has.
It's a small planet.
We could blow it away
with one blast if we wanted.
If we did that, I wouldn't be satisfied.
I want to teach him a lesson.
Now that I'm powered up like this.
You mean this "Super Saiyan" guy?
I can tell by the radar here,
that you're also on a course towards Earth.
I'll make you understand soon enough.
Just who the strongest
being in the universe really is!
This is terrible. This is terrible. This is terrible.
This is terrible. This is terrible.
Gohan-chan!
Hold on, Gohan-chan, where are ya going?!
Today I'm having a new
private tutor come over.
Freeza was supposed to be dead, but
instead he's returned in a powered-up form!
Once again, with Goku still away,
the Earth stands in the shadow
of an approaching great evil.
Goku, hurry back home!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Looks like that Freeza jerk is
completely unrepentant, huh?
But be careful, guys.
If Freeza wanted to, he
could blow the whole earth up!
D-Damn. I've just been brought back to life,
and now I have to die again?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"I Will Defeat Freeza...
The Mysterious Youth Awaiting Goku."
That man reminds me of someone.
"Next time"
"I Will Defeat Freeza...
The Mysterious Youth Awaiting Goku"