Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Do it!
Makankosappo!
Sacrificing his own life, Goku saved
the Earth and his own son from Raditz.
However, the death of Raditz
has caused the two strongest
Saiyans to head for Earth.
One year remains before they arrive.
This dying stuff...
it's pretty nasty... ain't it?
Don't worry, Goku! We'll
bring you back to life right away!
I'm... counting... on it...
Goku...
Goku!
He vanished!
"Even Yama-sama is Surprised –
The Fight Continues in the Next World."
He vanished?
This is Kami's doing, I'll bet.
This is something he would be capable of.
I wonder what he
intends to do with him.
Nevertheless, if it is
Kami-sama, then we can relax.
In any case, we need to hurry
and gather the other six balls,
and bring Goku back to life.
Good grief!
At a critical time like this,
I wonder where Yamucha
and the others have gone off to!
You were the one who
chased him away, weren't you?
But then again, how did Son-kun's
brother know where he was so easily?
It's that strange device
he has attached to his face.
It seems to be able to tell an
opponent's strength and location.
Kuririn?
Right.
Here.
That thing, huh?
Kuririn, remove it, would you?
S-Sure. H-He's not about to
come back to life or anything, right?
So this here does that...
This is an incredible mechanism!
It's a little bit damaged, but
I think I can do something with it.
You sure are incredible, Bulma-san.
Once I take this back, study it,
and make some alterations,
we just might be able to find out
where Yamucha and
Tenshinhan and the others are.
Whatever we do, let's go back to
the Kame House for the time being.
Right. There's nothing
more we can do here, huh?
Okay then, right after that,
I'll go looking for the Dragon Balls.
Piccolo, what do you plan to–
Just like a lizard's tail!
You guys search for the Dragon Balls.
Kami doesn't have the kind
of power it takes to restore life.
However, I'm going to be taking
charge of Son Goku's son there.
What?
You're kidding, right?!
What do you plan to do with him?!
I know what it is!
You're planning to eat him, huh?!
Eat him?!
W-What are you going to do?
This Gohan kid should give us
some powerful fighting potential,
depending on the training he gets.
For us to confront the two Saiyans
who are to arrive here in another year,
we're going to need his power.
To that end, I'm going
to have to train him.
Y-You can't seriously be saying that...
I'm not sure if that's going
to be agreeable, you know?
We'll first have to take it up with
Goku, as well as his mother, Chichi...
We don't have the
time to spare for that!
Keep up that bickering, and I'll take him
away, even if it means killing you to do so!
After a year has passed, I'll be coming
to your house, together with this kid.
When Son Goku comes back to life,
tell him he can wait
in expectation until then.
I don't know...
I don't know about this...
He's going to die! Even if he's lucky,
he's still going to become a delinquent!
Goku and Chichi-san
are going to be upset.
And so, about that same
time, in the Other World...
Okay, okay, all of you spirits,
please remain orderly in line!
Okay, you there! Do not form two lines!
Be sure to maintain
one orderly line, please!
...and that is why I have brought
him here as flesh and blood,
to ask that he be allowed to train.
If you please, Great King Yama-sama,
allow him to call on Kaio-sama.
Son Goku, huh? Indeed, his
achievements have been outstanding.
So you're asking that someone
who could go to heaven be
allowed to put himself at risk of danger,
travel the Serpentine Road,
and meet with Kaio-sama, then?
Yes.
Say, does everyone
come here when they die?
That's right.
Even aliens?
Mm-hmm. All who die have
judgment passed upon them here,
to determine whether they
are to go to heaven or hell.
Hey! Just a little bit before me,
did a guy named Raditz wash up here?
N-Now look here! You need
to say "did he come through?"
He was here, all right.
He was your brother, huh?
He's now hell-bound, of course.
Didn't he raise a commotion?
He did, he did! He did raise a
commotion, but I put him down!
You sure are strong, huh? You
took care of somebody that awesome?
Maybe I should get Pops here to train me!
Shh! Your voice is too loud!
You shouldn't be addressing
Yama-sama in that tone!
But...
Keep quiet! Kaio-sama is even stronger.
I heard that, Kami of Earth!
When you die, maybe
I ought to send you to hell.
P-Please forgive me! Surely, I never
thought that would reach your ears!
I should have expected as much of
someone who has "the devil's own ears."
Just kidding!
You've got no sense of humor, huh?
Nope.
Very well. If you wish to go that badly,
you may go to where Kaio-sama is.
T-Thank you very much.
I'll call a guide over for you.
Leave through there and wait for him.
Okay!
However... I can't be responsible for
you if you fall from the Serpentine Road.
All right then, good luck. This
whole year will be a challenge, after all.
Right! I ain't sure what's going on,
but anyhow, I'll go see this Kaio-sama guy.
Thanks! Say hi to Mister Popo for me!
Then again, our Earth has drawn the
attention of some rather egregious folks.
We might indeed be in for
some real trouble this time.
Even if we were to petition
Shen Long to dispose of them,
he probably wouldn't be able to win out
against the incredible power of the Saiyans.
Even if Son Goku does
get trained by Kaio-sama,
just how much will he improve?
Our one and only salvation is Goku's son.
How is Piccolo going to raise Son Gohan?
And in this limited time, how will–
Shut up!
You're disturbing me!
Would you go home already?!
Hey, what's taking so long?
E-Excuse me! Please excuse me!
Thank you for your patience.
I will now guide you to
where the Head of the Serpent is.
The Serpentine Road is very long!
Are you in healthy shape?
Nope. I'm dead, so I ain't in
very healthy shape at all, am I?
Say, what kind of person is Kaio-sama?
Ah yes, Kaio-sama is the gentleman
that stands above all the
Kami-sama throughout the universe.
I'm sure he must be strong, then!
We can't very well not say
anything about this to Chichi.
Kuririn, go on over there and
explain the situation to her for us.
M-Me?!
She appears to be an education-minded-mama,
so you're going to get killed for sure.
Hello? Hello?
Aloha! Turtle-chan is currently not at home.
If there's something I can do for you,
please wait until the sound of the beep–
Well, I never!
Where have they gone off to?!
And here I've come all
this way to see my grandson...
Knowin' Goku-sa and those others,
they're teachin' Gohan how to do
somethin' dangerous, I'm sure of it!
Well, that's okay, ain't it?
Children should be a li'l bit naughty.
Nothin' doin'!
If they're up to that and his mind goes
numb on him, then what are we goin' to do?!
Don't be silly!
No, if he goes learnin' the martial arts,
before long, he'll get kicked
in the chin or somethin',
and he'll get himself
thrown into the ocean!
And then, and then, a man-eater
will catch his scent, or perhaps,
he'll drift ashore to
some uninhabited island!
He'll get hungry, and as he's
tryin' to grab some bananas,
he'll get bitten by a snake,
and the poison will circulate
to his brain, and then... and then...
after his mind has gone
numb, what will we do?!
Okay, we're here.
This is the Serpentine Road, then?
Yes.
What do I do from here?
Earnestly press on as you travel
along this serpent, if you please.
It leads to where Kaio-sama is. Yes indeed.
It sure looks long.
Yes. According to legend, it's
approximately one million kilometers long.
A million kilometers?! Has
anyone ever reached the end?
As I recall, in the last billion years,
Great King Yama has
been the only one, yes indeed.
That older guy, huh?
Well, even so, as long as there's
someone who has reached the end,
I might be able to manage something too.
Please be absolutely careful
not to fall off into the clouds.
After all, beneath the clouds is where
hell is, and you will never return again.
Oh, really?
Rats, I should have brought
a bento lunch or something.
That's all right, sir.
You are already dead,
so I doubt there's any chance of
you starving to death. Yes indeed.
Oh, yeah!
Okay, then...
Oh, that's right!
I have a favor I'd like to ask!
Do you know Uranai Baba?
Yes. She comes by once in a while.
Thank goodness!
The next time she comes, right?
Ask her to tell Old Timer Turtle Hermit not
to bring me back to life for one year for me.
Understood. Let's see, one year...
the Turtle Hermit-sama, right?
Okay, guess I'll go now.
So in short, all I have to do
is not fall off the snake, right?
Yes, be sure not to.
Bukujutsu!
That's cheating...
Wake up already, son of Son Goku!
We need to talk.
Come up out of the water!
Who are you? Father?
Father! Where are you?!
Save me! Father! Father!
Father! I'm scared! I'm scared!
Sheesh, you dirty brat!
Don't give me any trouble!
Stop your bawling! If you don't
get quiet, I'm going to snap your neck!
Ready? Listen close to what I have to say.
First, your father has died.
You remember a little bit of that,
right? In order to defeat that man,
he sacrificed himself.
R-Run away, Gohan!
Run away!
Father...
Whoa, now, don't you cry!
I really will snap your neck!
You've heard about the
Dragon Balls from your father, right?
Goku's friends should be
gathering them to bring him back to life.
However, that's not what the problem is.
We managed to deal with
the guy who kidnapped you,
but in a year from now,
it seems that some even more
terrible friends of his will be coming.
Once they do, then even with
having Son Goku returned to life,
there's absolutely no chance of
us winning with just him and myself.
We need your power too. Train
yourself to learn the tactics of fighting,
and defend the Earth!
Me? You can't mean it!
I can't fight at all!
Apparently, you still
haven't realized it yourself.
The power that you have
locked within you is something else.
That's why we're going to
draw out that power through training,
until you can use it effectively.
It can't be... I don't
have any power like that.
You want to see some proof?
W-What are you doing?!
Ow! That hurts!
That hurts! Stop it! That hurts!
That hurts! Stop it!
It hurts! It hurts! It hurts!
Here you go!
Come on! Show me that
power you have locked away!
W-What the–?
W-What a surprise!
This is more than I imagined!
I've got mixed feelings about this.
Here I am about to raise someone
who could turn out to be my
most fearsome opponent in the future.
That's... what I did?
That's right. Looks like you've
more or less realized it now.
When your emotions
become considerably raised,
the natural power that you have
locked up inside you is exhibited.
However, it only lasts for an instant.
We can't beat them like that!
I'm going to drill into you the way to fight,
and turn you into the greatest
warrior ever. You got that?
But I don't want to
learn to be a martial artist.
I want to be a great scholar.
So become one. Just do it after
we've defeated the two Saiyans
who will be coming in a year.
They're planning to
exterminate every person on Earth.
If they do that, your future's
not going to be worth crap, is it?
But I'm scared...
Stop your griping!
You want to get killed right now?!
We don't have time!
We're going to begin right now!
Take off your tunic immediately!
Once Father comes back to life,
I want to be taught by Father.
That's too bad. He certainly is strong,
but he's not at all cut out to be a teacher.
He doesn't have any of the
firmness it takes to handle others.
You can easily tell that just by
looking at how spoiled you are!
Huh?
Uh oh, I've used up too much
strength, and now I can't fly any more.
His own son's grief aside,
Goku presses on in earnest along the long
road in search of Kaio-sama's guidance.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Whoa, how long does this road
go on? I can't see where the end is!
Father!
Don't act so spoiled! You hold
the fate of the earth in your hands!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Survival with Dinosaurs!
Gohan's Harsh Training"
Father, I'm scared of Uncle Piccolo!
"Next time"
"Survival with Dinosaurs!
Gohan's Harsh Training"