Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Vegeta, with his gift for fighting,
easily defeats No. 1 9. But then...
Looks like he's gotten too
used to using an opponent's ki...
...to follow their moves.
If I drain all of their energy,
and add it to my own, then I can beat Vegeta!
"A Reality More Terrifying than the Future!?
Trunks' Suspicions."
Oh. Don't scare me like that!
Shoot. Not being able to
see your foe like this is eerie.
Damn. Really, where did
he disappear to, anyhow?
If this is the way it's going to be,
I wish I'd done like Vegeta said
and went home to have some milk!
So then, whose energy should I take first?
It has to be Piccolo, the most
powerful one next to Vegeta!
With what I can get from Piccolo,
anything becomes possible!
You just wait until I come for you, Vegeta!
Damn.
He might already have gotten away.
No one will find us!
I know exactly where everyone else is!
Now then, to take your energy...
G-Gohan, come here! Now!
T-The Artificial Human's got me...
Piccolo-san!
Which way?
A faint ki disruption. This way!
Only a small amount of
your energy still remains.
All that's left is for you to die–
Y-You saved me, Gohan.
B-But how?!
There wasn't any way he could have found me!
Kuririn-san! Let Piccolo-san have a senzu!
Yeah!
I still can't beat Vegeta,
not even with this level of energy.
You flea-market doll...
I'll have to take energy from the others as well.
Piccolo-san!
Let me handle this, Vegeta!
Stay out of this, no matter what!
If you're wanting to die, that's up to you...
but won't you just be providing
him with more energy unnecessarily?
"Stay out of this"?
This is perfect!
I'll just absorb his energy once again!
And once I do...
Vegeta won't pose any...
That shouldn't have happened!
I must have let my guard down, that's all.
I-Impossible!
There's no reason I shouldn't
be able to defeat him!
After all, it was his energy
I took and added to my own!
At the least, the power I have acquired
should be more than equal to his!
I-I was afraid of this. I'm too late.
Both Goku-san's team...
...and the Artificial Humans are no longer here.
The island is all blown apart, but
just what exactly happened here?
I'd like to take the time machine
a little further back in time,
but I've just barely got enough
energy to get back home.
On top of that, the machine
doesn't exactly work perfectly.
I might miss my intended time again.
Ki! I sense fighting ki!
So that's it! They're fighting in a different place!
Piccolo-san! Incredible!
Such strength!
What kind of training could Piccolo have done?
He's not even a Super Saiyan!
Why, you...!
Hang in there, Goku!
Get better quickly, so we can
go back and beat those guys!
I'm positive! They must be
where that explosion just was!
There's no reason fer us to go there, right?
Let's jes' go back home.
We'll be better off lettin'
Goku an' them take care of this.
'Sides, we got this tyke.
Did you see that just now?
That was the boy from the future!
Hey, lookit! You raised
yer voice and woke 'im up!
That boy is on his way to fight!
I knew this is the right direction!
All right, Let's go!!
Down there.
Behind you!
Piccolo-san!
Make a note of this.
As we fight, we can take
our energy, as you call it,
amplify it, then release
it in one explosive burst.
This is why the energy
you took from me earlier...
...made so little difference.
We've won!
Looks like what that young man
from the future said was wrong!
What kind of Artificial Human is this?
What is everyone else fighting against?
This isn't right. What's going on?
The fight is still going on!
That one... was different from
the Artificial Humans I know of.
How can that be?
Are there three Artificial Humans?
Curse you, Piccolo!
To think even you raised
your power by so much...
According to the original order of history,
you two Artificial Humans...
...were supposed to have killed
just about every single one of us.
But it looks as though that future
is going to change, doesn't it?
Does that mean you guys weren't
as strong as you were supposed to be?
Or maybe...
...we just became too strong for you?
Hey, we did it!
We're going to win this
time even without Goku!
Right!
I'm not all that happy with the
unusual increase in power both Piccolo...
...and Vegeta have undergone, but
for now, at least I'm relieved about this.
Piccolo! Hurry up and put him away!
That is, unless you'd like me to do it?
Thanks anyway,
but I am the embodiment of
evil cast off by Kami, after all.
I'm not all mushy about this the way Goku is.
Who's that?!
I-It's...
Trunks?!
What?
Trunks?
Trunks, did you say?!
But that's the same name as my kid!
The same name!
He came from the future–
So that's it!
H-He's different too!
A-Another new guy just arrived!
Who is this one?
I-I have no data on him at all.
Regardless, this was all a terrible
miscalculation, especially for me.
All that remains is for me to go back...
...to the laboratory.
W-Who is that guy down there?
He is who you were fighting with, isn't he?
What?
Who is he? Isn't he one of the
Artificial Humans you told us about?
What does this mean?
Y-You mean he isn't?!
W-What's this? You're saying he isn't?
It can't be!
Trunks' unexpected statement...
Can this mean there are other Artificial Humans,
in addition to No. 1 9 and No. 20?
Further, what is the nature of No. 20,
whom everyone has been fighting?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Are you sure, Bulma? No. 20 is Doctor Gero?
I wasn't lying when I said
there's no way you could win!
No. 17 and No. 18 will be
coming soon to kill you all!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Give Chase!! The Search for
Doctor Gero's Mysterious Laboratory."
The real Artificial Humans
are at Gero's laboratory.
"Next time"
"Give Chase!! The Search for
Doctor Gero's Mysterious Laboratory"