Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Change!!
H-How come... I'm... over... there?
I've made an exchange, your body for mine.
You did what?
W-What's this? Goku and
Ginyu have switched bodies!
And now, Vegeta...
...Gohan, Kuririn...
...Ginyu, Jheese...
and Goku are all racing toward
Freeza's spaceship, to get the Dragon Balls!
"Come Forth, Super Shen Long!!
Grant Me My Wish."
Looks like Freeza is out and about, all right.
And so then, right there, I told him...
Wait, hold on now...
What's this?
–What was that?!
–What's going on?!
W-What was that explosion just now?!
V-V-V–
Vegeta!
Damn!
Hey!
Where are the Dragon Balls?
Look at all of you, lined up so loyally!
If you don't want to tell me...
...then you don't have to tell me.
Lousy small fry.
You can swear your allegiance
to Freeza from the Other Side now.
Damn it all, Freeza...
Seeing as how Ginyu stayed behind,
the Dragon Balls must
be around here somewhere.
In any event, those Earth punks can locate them
with that strange device of theirs.
They should be here very shortly now.
Until then, I'll see about
changing into some new battle wear.
So, this is what it's like to have
a body with a power of 180,000?
However, I think my previous face
was more handsome. Right, Jheese?
Absolutely!
I-I've got to go faster, or
Kuririn and Gohan will get killed!
That way? No, this way!
Ribbit... ribbit... ribbit...
Damn it, I can't keep my
balance very well in this body.
You know, there's something very unusual
about the medicine Kakarrot was using.
Not only does it heal injuries,
but it completely
restores one's strength as well.
The only ones in my size
are the older models, huh?
We're almost there, Kuririn-san!
Kuririn-san, there it is!
G-Got it! So that's their spaceship, huh?
So, you've arrived, Earthlings.
It's no good if they realize I'm here.
I have to suppress my
battle power, the way they do.
Let's hurry and find them!
No one else seems to be here.
Kuririn-san, wait!
According to the readings on the Radar,
the Dragon Balls aren't
inside the ship, but away from it.
Where are they, Gohan?
Let's see... this way.
Right over here.
Here they are, Kuririn-san, here!
Yeah, looks like something
was buried here, all right.
Why would they put them here?
Okay, let's dig them out!
Right!
Here's one! I found one!
There's another one over here!
Hooray! Here's another!
Looks like all seven are here after all!
So that's where they hid them, huh?
We've got them all! We've got them all!
Good. Now just summon that Shen Long thing.
I'll put you two away,
and then have my wish of
eternal life and youth given to me!
We did it!
Hey, Gohan, what's that on your face?
Well, what about you, Kuririn-san?
Hurry up and summon it, would you?!
We sure worked hard for this, huh?
Yes. Now Piccolo-san and everyone
else can finally be brought back to life.
Do it already! Summon it!
Okay, here goes. We've come
such a long way for this moment.
Let's have ourselves a look at
what the original Shen Long looks like!
Right.
Come forth, Shen Long, and grant me my wish!
The incantation is as simple as that?
W-What's wrong? Isn't
something supposed to happen?
What is this Shen Long?
H-H-He's not coming out...
Shen Long isn't coming out. Why not?
Why isn't Shen Long blasting out of there?
Maybe the incantation is a little different.
–Shen Long, come forth!
–Those dirty punks! What are they doing?
–Please grant us our wish!
Maybe his name isn't Shen Long.
That's strange.
Kuririn-san, someone is coming this way!
Hey, I can feel two ki!
Is it those two Ginyu guys?
If so, does that mean that Father was beaten?
Things are turning for the worse again!
They're evil ki! There's no mistake,
it has to be those two from before!
W-What happened to Goku, then?
We've got to suppress our
own ki and take cover, Gohan!
Right!
The Dragon Balls have been dug up!
What's going on?
How did anyone know where they were buried?
Goku!
It's me, it's me! You sure surprised me!
I thought, "Ginyu! It must
be that Ginyu guy coming!"
I didn't know you had beat him,
and convinced his pal
to come over to our side.
Are you the one that
found the Dragon Balls here?
How did you know where they were?
What are you talking about, Goku?
I used the Dragon Radar to find them, of course.
Radar, did he say? Damn,
they've got something like that?
So, have you gotten your wish granted then?
That's the funny thing. It didn't work.
Shen Long won't appear. I can't figure out why.
The password may be
different from what we use on Earth.
So, it didn't work, huh?
Goku, is something wrong
with you? Something about you...
It just doesn't seem right.
And how come you're wearing
that Scouter, or whatever it's called?
You really want to know?
Kuririn-san! That isn't Father!
Kuririn-san, run!
So, there's another one of you, huh?
I didn't get any reading on my Scouter.
Apparently you can control your
battle power all the way down to zero.
What do you think you're doing, Goku?!
It's not Father! That isn't Father there!
I-If that isn't Goku, then what's going on?
He looks just like him!
I don't know, but I can just tell.
I've switched bodies. This one
was so much stronger, you see.
What?!
H-He's switched bodies?
That's right.
Red Magma of the Ginyu Special Corps, Jheese!
And I am... Commander of the
Ginyu Special Corps... Ginyu-sama!
D-Damn... This unfamiliar body
makes it hard to read ki, as well.
"Unfamiliar body?"That's right!
If I ain't used to this body, he
shouldn't be used to my body, either!
You've switched bodies? That's impossible!
I think I'll test it out right now.
The incredible power of a
better-than-180,000 battle power!
D-Don't do it, Goku!
You're being controlled somehow!
You've been hypnotized or something!
Whether he's actually switched
bodies, or has just been hypnotized,
Kakarrot's strength would still be the same.
Things are getting worse and worse!
I'm going to keep increasing
my power even higher and higher!
I hope you're ready!
Commander Ginyu! That
other bastard followed us here.
What?
I've found you!
You've done well to make it this far.
I should have made the wound more severe.
K-Kuririn, Gohan, listen up!
That ain't me! He's taken over my body!
You mean, it's true?
I-I-It can't be!
That's Father?
Yahoo!
Yum, yum!
I couldn't stand that!
That guy is Ginyu!
Don't hesitate to take him down!
There's no way he can
defeat you at your present levels!
Go on, start beating on him!
S-Start beating on him, you say?
Fool! You think I cannot defeat
them? This was originally your body!
It's battle power is over 180,000.
There's no reason why
that would have changed!
You'll see, once you give it
a try. That's my body there.
How do you even expect to
use its ki well, let alone Kaio-ken?
If body and mind ain't completely
united, you won't get any great power!
Your lies won't work on Ginyu-sama.
I'll show you what my
battle power is right now!
Jheese...
Yes, sir!
Jheese! How high is my battle power?
Just how high a battle power does Ginyu
have, now that he has stolen Goku's body?
Moreover, will Goku be
able to get his own body back?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
I'm going to fight alongside you.
Although, it feels kind of weird,
attacking my own body.
G-Goku! It seems like he
suddenly got a lot stronger!
Could he be getting used to your body?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"That Ain't Me! Gohan, Don't
Lose Your Nerve, Hit Your Father!!"
I won't be beaten by you,
even if you do look like Father!
"Next time"
"That Ain't Me! Gohan, Don't
Lose Your Nerve, Hit Your Father!!"