Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
A Genki Dama, filled
with the Earth's hopes...
However, not even that
was enough to finish Vegeta off.
The terrible Vegeta was the
mightiest of Saiyan warriors. But just then...
T-This brat has... re-grown his tail!
"Cause a Miracle!
Son Gohan, the Super Saiyan."
Which way?
The left. A little more to the left.
Ah, I see it! That's the island!
That island is where Goku
and the others are fighting.
What about Gohan?! Gohan-chan
really is still alive, right?! Really?!
P-Probably...
What do you mean, "probably"?!
"Probably" isn't good enough!
I told you we shouldn't have brought her.
Still, I'm worried about
the four– no, five of them.
I can barely sense any ki from any of them.
H-His tail? That's right... In the past,
Goku's tail suddenly grew back, too...
If he were to transform,
that would be a problem!
What?!
I got him! I got him!
T-Take that, you jackass! Ha-ha-ha on you!
How'dya like that?! Ain't no way
yer a match for Yajirobe-sama! Nyaah!
W-Why, you!
You filthy bastard!
S-S-Sorry 'bout that! Did it hurt?
I was just jokin' around. Did I cut ya?
That's right! I got lotsa
respect for ya! Lemme be your friend–
Y-Yajirobe...
Nobody inflicts a wound on
my body and gets away with it!
There's no way you're getting away with that!
Dammit!
G-Gohan... Gohan!
Gohan!
T-That's Father's voice...
Gohan, hear my voice...
Look at the ball of light in the sky...
B-Ball of light? Ball of light?
O-Oh, hell!
You think I'm going to allow that?!
Die!
Oh, no!
You brat! I'm not about to let you grow huge!
I-If I don't kill him right now–!
Gohan! It's up to you!
G-Gohan is becoming a Great Ape...
I-It's an all-or-nothing gamble...
T-That's right! His tail! In my panic,
I forgot the most important thing!
If I can just cut off his tail!
G-Gohan...
B-But when Goku turned Great Ape,
he lost virtually all of his rationality!
What about Gohan?
Gohan is the same! T-That makes sense.
It's not so much that Goku
and Gohan lose their rationality,
as it is that when they become Great Apes,
they revert to being ferocious Saiyans!
Hey! Stay back!
Gohan!
G-Gohan!
W-What happened to him?
G-Gohan...
The Saiyan!
Get the Saiyan!
You idiot! Don't provoke him!
W-Why, you!
Gohan!
T-The look in his eye is different.
Gohan! Get the Saiyan!
Great! There's still a little bit of
Gohan's mind left in there. S-Sure...
He's half earthling!
T-The moon I created
won't go out for another hour...
I'll just have to cut off his tail!
What a freak. And after
he's taken all that damage, too.
Is this guy immortal?
D-Damn! My power!
Dammit!
I-I can't move!
W-What happened?
D-Did he get him?
Is he still alive?
What a monster!
T-The only things left in the city
appear to be these two strange spheres.
Does that mean that these
are the Saiyans' spaceships?
What's that?
I-It's flying!
W-What's that?
I-It's here...
T-To think that I would have to withdraw...
D-Damn...
Me, Vegeta-sama, known as the
mightiest warrior in the universe...
How disgraceful...
T-That's his spaceship...
Y-You're not about to get away...
Kuririn! Use my katana!
W-We've come this far...
I'm going to finish him off...
Hold it!
T-This is for everyone that you killed...
Say your prayers!
Dammit! M-My body won't respond!
You did well to come this far.
I wasn't sure how this would turn out.
It's wrong for me to play favorites,
but that Saiyan is a villain that has
plunged the whole universe into terror.
I can't help it.
Although, this will not
completely weed out the root of evil.
No, not the root of evil...
Die!
Wait!
G-Goku?
Goku, was that you
who just spoke into my mind?
Yeah, it was...
I can't talk very loud, and all...
K-Kuririn, forgive me, but let him get away...
Let him what? A-Are you crazy?
P-Please... T-This is the only
thing I'll ever ask for myself...
But Goku, this is the
guy that killed our friends,
and tried to kill everyone else in the world!
If we let him go now, he's certain to
recover his strength, and come back here!
Y-You're probably right...
If you're thinking that maybe he'll
have a change of heart, the way Piccolo did,
then you're greatly mistaken!
He's not that kind of guy!
I know that... and I know that
Vegeta there has incredible strength...
S-Still... I ain't able to say this too well...
but when I saw him nearly
dead there, I thought to myself...
"What a waste."
What a waste?
After training at Kaio-sama's place,
I thought I had reached my pinnacle...
But that Vegeta guy there
has done far better than I have...
It surprised me...
To be honest, I was overwhelmed...
But somewhere within my heart,
I was happy, and excited...
That must be because I'm a Saiyan too...
Whenever I see an amazing
guy like that, my heart leaps...
I want to train even
more, and fight him again...
This is the guy who killed
Yamucha-san, Tenshinhan, and Chaozu!
I know it's not the right thing to do...
but please... grant me my selfish request...
Let me have... another chance to fight him!
All right. You've got the right
to ask for something for yourself.
It's thanks to you that we even
have the Earth at all now, Goku.
But remember, Goku...
Next time, you take him
down with devastating power!
Yeah, I sure will...
R-Remember this well, you trash...
There aren't going to be any more miracles...
Next time we meet, you're all dead!
Be sure to enjoy yourselves
to the fullest until then...
For now, the danger of the
Earth's extinction has passed.
Or has it? And what is this
"root of evil" that Kaio spoke of?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Kuririn, thanks to you guys,
I somehow managed to survive.
But the other guys and the
Dragon Balls are gone now.
If we're able to go to
this Planet Namek place,
we might be able to come by some Dragon Balls!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"We're Off Into Space! The Star
of Hope is Piccolo's Homeland."
Piccolo-san will come back to life!
"Next time"
"We're Off Into Space! The Star
of Hope is Piccolo's Homeland"