Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Son Gohan versus Cell!
The battle over the fate of the Earth
has begun with Cell's one-sided offensive!
Goku! You're responsible for this!
You've completely underestimated the situation!
Everyone warned you about this!
Take it easy, Piccolo.
Gohan's ki ain't dropped in the least, has it?
What?
When I fly off the handle,
I seem to go beyond my own will,
and start fighting
hysterically with amazing power.
If it comes to that, I'm sure I will kill you.
Did you think I would be
scared off by hearing that story?
You really are a brat.
On the contrary, now I want to
make you angry, no matter what.
I want to have a look at this
so-called hidden power you have!
Son Gohan, no matter what it takes,
I'm going to make you angry.
"Teeny Menaces!!
Attack of the Cell Juniors."
Gohan, get angry! Get angry!
By doing so, you'll be able
to draw out your true power!
W-What's going to happen, Mister Satan?
It's irresponsible!
Having a child fight like this, it's crazy!
If nobody defeats Cell in these Cell Games,
every person on Earth is going to be killed.
And yet, is that young boy the only
one who will fight the ferocious Cell?
Isn't there anybody else?!
Mister Satan, is your
stomachache still bothering you?
It's still stinging!
Our star of hope, Mister Satan,
is still suffering from his stomachache!
Is there no savior who
can reclaim our future for us?
Son Gohan, you will show
me your so-called hidden power.
That's the technique that Freeza used!
Gohan, don't let him get you!
Well, what's the matter?
This hurts, right? Get angry!
You don't want to die like this, do you?
D-Dammit...! G-Gohan!
Well, what's wrong?
Why do you hesitate?
Your bones are going to break!
You couldn't dislike fighting so
much that you would rather endure this.
The young boy is being tormented!
What monstrous power! Will the child give up?
What will become of the Earth's future?
What is to be our fate?!
Dammit, I can't take this any more!
Goku! I don't care what you say,
I'm going to go help Gohan!
Wait, Piccolo!
Frankly, he ain't the sort
of opponent you can handle!
Just a little longer... wait just a little bit longer.
Wait, you say?! What do you mean?
Are you saying that I should
wait while he gets killed like this?!
Wait for Gohan to get angry.
He will most likely release
his true power through his anger,
and show us some
terrifying strength all at once!
There's only one way to defeat Cell.
We have to rely on Gohan and his power!
What? That kid has that kind of power?
Get angry. This isn't enough? It must hurt, right?
Your anger has to be welling up!
Goku, you're mistaken!
Gohan doesn't like to fight the way you do!
Does Gohan know about your strategy?!
Did you make sure to discuss it with him?!
Do you know what Gohan is thinking right now?
It's not about anger!
"Why won't Father help me,
when I'm suffering like this?"
"Is having a fair, manly fight more
important than my life?" and so on!
Don't forget!
Even supposing his powers
have made him number one,
he is still a child!
I don't care if he does
let me have it! I'm going in!
Kuririn! Let me have a senzu!
O-Okay!
You're a stubborn one!
It would appear that your own pain alone
will not bring your anger to a boil...
Okay then, how about we
take it up with your friends?
Stop!
Cell is flying!
There are senzu in here, right?
They must be cumbersome, so I'll take them.
O-Oh, no!
D-Damn!
It's not even worth my trouble
to take on the likes of them.
W-What are you planning to do?!
Whatever I want to!
If that's what it takes to make you angry
enough to exhibit your so-called true power.
You have a peculiar way of enduring pain,
so now your friends are going to get hurt.
D-Don't do it, please!
I can't control it under
my own power! That's why...
That's why I'm going to hurt your friends,
in order to draw your power out!
Watch out! He's about to do something!
Damn...
I should have taken a senzu before!
Damn you!
If you're going to get angry,
then get full-on angry!
N-No. 16!
Oh, my! Another man has come forward!
Will he be the savior of the Earth?!
No. 16!
He's a robot, so he doesn't
have any presence to detect!
No. 16 intends to defeat Cell!
N-No matter how strong
he is, he can't do it alone!
Let's get in there too!
W-Wait! Stay back!
I'm going to blow myself up, together with Cell!
You're going to what?!
I've got a powerful self-destruct
device equipped within my body.
It is my final, hidden power.
Forgive me for forcing the rest
of you to get caught up with this
and become casualties!
Cell! No matter how powerful you might be,
at this close range, you'll be blown to bits!
This is where it ends, Cell!
Both you and I are going
to be blown to smithereens!
This is where the schemes of Doctor Gero,
who created us Artificial Humans,
and planned to conquer the world, all fall apart!
N-No. 16!
Here goes!
You guys, protect me!
Now, hold on...!
I am your master! Protect me!
Mama!
W-What's the matter?
W-Why? Why don't I explode?
N-No. 16!
Y-You... can't self-destruct!
I heard it from Bulma-san...
The doc... the doc removed the bomb
that was concealed within your body!
What?!
Is that right, Bulma?
It was then...
Oh? Is that...?
Bulma, would you do a magnification scan
on this area around the heart for me?
Sure thing!
Apparently, it's a self-destruct device.
And it's no ordinary bomb, at that.
It might just blow the whole earth up.
So, Doctor Gero installed one of
these inside No. 16's body, did he?
It was probably to defeat Son-kun with, after all.
It surely must have been a final measure.
It's not safe. Let's take it out.
That's right...
Papa removed it from him back then.
No. 16! You can't self-destruct!
Too bad about that, huh No. 16?
Although, I doubt I would have
died from your bomb anyhow.
No. 16!
No. 16, it would appear that
you were one of Doctor Gero's
failed models after all.
Satan-sama, not in front of the others!
Oh, dear, Satan-sama...!
Caroni, go put that thing someplace else, quickly.
Right.
Get out of here...!
Well now, is there no one
who will come after me next?!
D-Dirty rotten scumbag...!
Son Gohan, apparently you
still haven't come around, huh?
But you watch, I will make
you angry, no matter what!
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven...
Seven altogether, huh? All right...!
W-What is he planning to do this time?!
W-What are they?!
Once again, something strange has come forth.
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7...
There are seven of them in all!
What on earth are these
seven mysterious beasts
that have sprung out of Cell's back?!
What are they?
What in the world are those weird things?
Now then, my Cell Juniors,
your opponents are those seven
who are on that rock over there.
Do them harm.
If you like, you can kill them. I don't mind.
Go!
Watch yourselves!
These guys are terrifyingly strong!
These runts?!
It's useless. There's absolutely
no way you will beat them.
They may be small,
but they are still my children.
Cell's terror knows no bounds.
How much power is
possessed by these Cell Juniors,
the small monsters whom Cell has produced?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Sorry, everybody. You're
all in danger because of me.
Son Gohan, it is no sin
to fight for what is right.
You don't have to take it
any longer. Release your anger.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Tragic No. 16!! An Enraged
Super Gohan Begins Taking Action."
Cell, I'll see that you pay for this!
"Next time"
"The Tragic No. 16!! An Enraged
Super Gohan Begins Taking Action"