Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
At last, Goku and Freeza clash.
Freeza's power slices the
air and rends the ground!
However, Goku has not fallen behind!
You're an impudent one!
Son! Behind you!
I'm not going to keep falling
into the same trap like that!
"The Two Superpowers Collide!
A Fistfight Where Both Turn Serious!!!"
Sit tight, Gohan!
Your Ma is comin' to save you right now!
Say there, Chichi-san,
won't you please re-think this?
Planet Namek will be dangerous for you.
He's right! Let's leave
all of this up to Son-in-law!
My Bulma-chan is there with him.
It will be fine!
No! I'm goin'!
After all, you can bet Goku-sa ain't makin'
Gohan-chan do his homework properly!
Yajirobe!
I've brung a message from Karin-sama.
'Parently Piccolo got to Namek all right.
Piccolo?!
If he hangs around with the likes of him,
Gohan-chan will become a delinquent!
I can't dawdle around any longer!
Let go of me! Let me go!
The repairs to the spaceship
aren't likely finished yet!
That kinda thing takes a lotta time!
That's right!
Ah, here, everyone's all together!
The third time around, I could handle
it without even looking at the blueprints.
Well, Chichi-san, the repairs
on the spaceship are finished.
I can have you take off any time.
I-Is there something...?
There's no other way, is there?
We can't very well let Chichi-san go alone.
At this point, we all go together...
Listen here! If we all put our efforts together,
we just may be of help
to Goku and the others!
Why'd ya need me too?!
You seem to be much stronger than I thought.
I'm a little surprised.
To think that there
was someone in the world
who could reach even
higher than Commander Ginyu...
But you are still no match for me.
Maybe not.
But we just don't know!
I know!
Right back at you!
He's escaped from my Kiai-Ho!
Damn!
Hurry and come back up!
It'll take more than that to beat you.
That rat has incredible speed as well.
So, now what do I do?
He can't find his opponent by just
feeling out their ki, the way we can.
He's always used his eyes to locate me.
All right, let's make use of that!
W-What's wrong? Goku still hasn't come up!
It's okay! Father's ki
hasn't diminished one bit!
You know, it's been a
while since I've done this.
I wonder if Old Man Turtle Hermit is doing okay.
Ka... me... ha... me...
Ha!
Okay, just like that, just like that!
What's the matter? Not ready yet?
And here I was about to deliver a final blow...
I guess we're just about ready.
All right, here goes!
Off you go!
Here he comes!
That's not him!
And the other!
This way?
No!
Father!
A great success!
Huh? He ain't the least bit affected?
To think that you could do this much.
You're the first one aside from my
father who I've had to dust off after.
This might be the first time
I've ever been this excited.
How shall I dish this out?
You got me!
I thought that would have at
least had some effect on you.
I think I'll torment him a little...
That bastard! This is telekinesis!
Dammit!
Okay, if that's how it is...
You are impudent!
What is this?!
I-It's like a whole island!
An island is floating there!
Goku!
This is the end for sure.
You've fallen for it!
Oh, hell!
I... can't... move...!
This serves you right!
When I miss, you're finished!
If I don't somehow find my way out of this...!
We're just about at Game Set!
Are you getting tired of this?
What?!
You might die this time, huh?
Gohan!
Ah, Piccolo-san!
Goku...
Father...
What kind of guys are these?!
Freeza's just playing around!
If he felt like it, he's got the
power to destroy this whole planet.
And yet, seeing as how
we're all still alive here...
It means he really is just playing around, huh?
What a punk he is!
Piccolo-san, what about Father...?
There's no use worrying!
That jerk hasn't gotten serious yet either!
Look over there!
Father!
That was a little too close.
I'll have to be on guard against that attack.
Didn't I tell you earlier?
Don't bust other people's planets up so much!
Goku... But how?
At the moment of the explosion,
he escaped from being
bound up in there at super-speed.
He did something that
incredible? In that instant?
They're freaks! Both of them, dammit!
You're a persistent one!
Even I am starting to get annoyed.
So am I.
I think I'll put an end to all this warming up,
and finally get serious about this.
Me too.
A clash of technique against technique!
Explosive power versus power!
However, to Goku and Freeza,
is this no more than simple warming up?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
You're going to let us fight on
the ground, where I'm better at it?
You're pretty confident, huh, Freeza?
When you look at me this way,
I'm very kind. As an added bonus,
I'll send you to hell
without even using my hands.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Freeza's Terrible Declaration!
I Will Defeat You Without Using My Hands."
You look down on Father,
and you're going to get hurt!
"Next time"
"Freeza's Terrible Declaration!
I Will Defeat You Without Using My Hands"