Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
What's this? Goku and
Chichi had a child! His name...
My name is Son Gohan.
However, there was an alien warrior
who was attempting to bring about
a new shock to these peaceful days.
What was his objective?
This is ridiculous! I-I was
shaking so much, I couldn't move!
"The Mightiest Warrior in All of
History is Goku's Older Brother!"
Have you lost sight
of your pride as a Saiyan,
the mightiest warriors
in the universe, Kakarrot?!
Kakarrot?!
Good afternoon!
It's been so long!
Bulma-san!
You said to come visit you, so I came.
Wow, it really has been a long time!
This house hasn't changed
at all in the meantime, huh?
You sure have been cold to us, huh?
Unless someone tells you to
come over, you never come, after all.
Here!
I brought some manju buns as a present.
You didn't need to go to that trouble.
If you'd just let me touch
your boobs a little bit, I'd–
You just don't appreciate
my gags, the same as always!
You're just a lecherous jerk,
the same as always!
By the way, Bulma-san, what's
happening with Yamucha-san?
Yamucha? That idiot?
How should I know about
that guy? I'm so mad at him,
I didn't tell him that everyone
was getting together here today!
Let's have ourselves a
blast without him being here!
You guys sure do fight a lot.
They sure do.
So then, where's Lunch-san?
She went out somewhere, chasing
after Tenshinhan-san, five years ago.
The position of this power is
moving at considerable speed.
There! That's Muten Roshi-sama's house!
Miserable Kakarrot!
You're not getting away from me!
Yoo-hoo!
It's stopped!
–Son-kun!
–Goku!
Huh? What's up with the boy?
Have you taken up a
job baby-sitting, Goku?
He's my boy!
Y-Yours, Goku?!
Yeah, that's right.
Go on, say hello.
Good afternoon.
–Yes, good afternoon.
His name is Son Gohan.
Son Gohan? So, you've given
him the name of your late grandpa?
Yeah.
Still, this is a surprise!
To think that Goku
would bring a child along!
Gohan-kun, how old might you be?
I'm four years old.
Wow. He's got good manners,
considering he's your boy, Son-kun.
Chichi is fussy about that.
Say, Gohan-kun, what are you
going to be when you grow up?
A great scholar.
S-Scholar?
A tail?
Yeah. Just like I had before, right?
You're right!
S-Say, does anything happen to
your boy that's strange in particular?
Strange?
F-For example, does he undergo any
changes on nights when the moon is full?
Nights when the moon is full?
Well, we all go to sleep early and all...
How come?
It's nothing, it's nothing!
In that case, it's all right!
S-Say, Goku, is your boy strong, like you?
About that...
I think he has quite a bit of power,
but Chichi gets mad
when I try to train Gohan.
Rock scissors paper!
How come? That's such a waste, isn't it?
Ain't it, though?
She says the world is at peace now,
so we don't need martial arts anymore,
and that from now on, it's time for studying.
So that tomboy of a girl turned out to
be an education-minded-mama-san, huh?
Say, is that thing on top
of Gohan-kun's hat a Dragon Ball?
Yeah. It's Si Xing Qiu, the Four-Star-Ball.
It's a keepsake from my grandpa, you know?
I searched it out and stuck it on there.
I also found San Xing Qiu and Liu Xing Qiu
while I was at it. I keep them at home.
That sure takes me back. Dragon Balls, huh?
Are you going to gather the Dragon Balls
together and wish for something else?
I ain't got anything
special that I want to wish for.
And here I thought that now that Goku has
a family, his power might have diminished...
You've got incredible power,
the same as ever, huh?
W-What is that?!
What's wrong?
S-Something's coming this way!
Something's coming?
I wonder if it's Yamucha.
A-Awesome! I feel an
awesome power! What is it?!
It's here!
Here it comes!
W-What is that?!
Who is it?
What kind of ferocious bloodlust is this?
So, we finally meet.
You've grown, huh?
But I still recognized you
at first glance, Kakarrot.
Kakarrot?
You look just like Father.
What does that mean?
What is this? What is this guy saying?
Kakarrot! What is with
the condition of this planet?!
You were supposed to have been
under orders to dispose of humanity!
What the hell have you
been goofing around for?
Now look here, you. I don't know
who you are or where you're from,
but go on back, go on back!
Shoo, shoo! You know,
it won't do for you to be out
drunk this early in the afternoon.
Go on back, go on back.
Kuririn! Don't get close to him!
Kuririn!
Why, you-!
A-A tail! This guy has a tail!
Looks like you've finally learned my identity.
Your identity?
What do you mean?!
Over here!
Kakarrot!
Have you even forgotten about that?!
My name ain't that funny
Kaka-whatever nonsense! It's Son Goku!
How can this be?
Hey, go on, now!
Hey, have you ever taken any
strong shocks to the head in the past?
What?
Back when you were a child or sometime,
did you ever hit your head hard?!
Answer my question!
I did!
I don't remember it, but when I
was good and little, I hit my head!
W-What?!
I still have the scar, even now.
So that's it after all, huh?
But what does that
have to do with anything?!
Goku!
Long ago, your grandfather,
Son Gohan, told me something.
One day, deep in a valley, he found something
unusual, like it had fallen from the sky.
When he got closer and looked at it,
there was a round capsule,
and inside it was a baby that had a tail.
He took him home, and tried to raise him...
...but he had a violent
disposition, and never took to him,
and he was utterly at his wit's end over him.
But then, one day, he fell
into a ravine by accident...
...and hit his head hard,
nearly dying. However,
having an unbelievable life force,
the baby apparently survived.
What's more, afterward,
his violent nature disappeared,
and he became a good little boy.
T-That was me?
Mm-hmm.
S-So then, what does that mean?
Does this guy and Son-kun
have some kind of connection?
Hey, who the hell are you?!
Tell me who you are!
You're being one difficult bastard,
forgetting everything like this!
Fine. I'll remind you, then.
From here on, I'll have a lot of
work for you to do for me, after all...
Are you okay, Kuririn?
Be careful, Goku!
That's no ordinary guy!
Mm-hmm, so it would appear.
To be honest,
just us standing here looking at
each other like this has got me scared!
This has never happened to me before!
I'll tell you, then. You are
not a human from this planet.
You were born on Planet Vegeta.
You are a proud Saiyan, the
mightiest warrior race in the universe!
The universe?
Warriors?
Saiyan?
And I am your older brother, Raditz!
G-Goku's older brother?!
B-Brothers?! You're kidding!
Stop talking nonsense!
R-Right! If Goku is from outer space,
then what is he doing on Earth?!
The answer is simple.
Kakarrot, you were sent here
to exterminate the bothersome
humans that live on this planet!
I was what?!
We Saiyans are a renowned warrior race!
Our task is to go through space,
searching for planets
with good environments,
and once we've exterminated
those who already live there,
we sell them for a high price to aliens
who are looking for a suitable planet.
Adult warriors embark directly upon planets
where those with a higher battle power live.
But to planets like this one,
which have a lower level,
we send babies like you.
I-If that's the truth,
then you guys are awful!
That's crazy! You even
make Piccolo look lovable!
How can you send babies off on their own?!
Kakarrot,
given several years,
you should have had plenty of time
to purge these nuisances all by yourself!
If only you had
remembered your orders, that is.
Luckily, this planet has a moon, as well.
Hey, why is it so lucky
that there's a moon here?
Don't play stupid! It is
when the moon is at its fullest
that we Saiyans are at our best, you know!
What are you talking about?
I don't understand what you mean at all!
What?
I-It can't be... Where's your tail?
What happened to your tail?!
It got cut off and disappeared long ago!
H-How can this be? You miserable fool!
It's no wonder you were able to get
along with the beings on this planet!
Enough!
It doesn't matter if I am
some whatever-you-call-it guy
from another planet,
or if you are my big brother!
Kuririn is right!
Anyone like that is a lowlife!
I am Son Goku, and I was raised here!
Now get out of here right now!
Right! Right!
Like he said!
Whatever his past may be,
right now, Son Goku is a fine Earthling,
more so than anyone else!
Goku has even saved the world!
Get lost! Get lost!
Even so, I cannot allow this to be.
The Saiyans have always
been a race few in numbers,
but now, after colliding with a giant meteor,
the planet Vegeta has blown up.
Just about all of the Saiyans
were vaporized into space dust.
Our father and mother included!
Including you, there are
only four remaining Saiyans.
Me and one of the others were spared
because we were off assaulting another planet.
And as for the other one, he was lucky
enough to be sent off to another planet,
just like you were.
Earlier, we inadvertently found a nice planet
that we ought to be able to
sell for an extremely high price.
We'd like to go attack it,
but it looks like we'd have a hard
time of it with just the three of us.
That's when I remembered
about you, Kakarrot.
Your battle power is still incomplete,
but if you were to join up with the
three of us, you could still manage.
Stay away!
Open your eyes, Kakarrot!
It will be fun! Is your
Saiyan blood not stirred?
I'm scared!
Don't be ridiculous!
I'd die before lending my hand to you!
So that's how it is, huh?
For a while now, I've been wondering,
that boy behind you is your son, isn't he?
N-No!
It's no use trying to fool me!
That tail is proof that he
carries Saiyan blood, isn't it?
So... what if he is?!
Since you, his father,
won't listen to reason,
I guess I'll have to borrow
your son for a little while.
Keep back!
Just try to come any closer!
I'll knock you flying!
Father!
–Father!
–You mustn't go!
Gohan-kun!
Whoa, there!
Kakarrot, I'll be taking the child.
If you want him returned alive,
you'll listen to what
your brother tells you to do!
D-Dammit!
G-Goku went down with only one blow!
Kakarrot, I'm giving you
only one day, so think about it.
You'll probably have to
get your friends to help, too.
Still, you'll have to show me some proof.
Ah, but that's a simple matter.
By this time tomorrow,
you'll kill a hundred of this
planet's humans, at least for now,
and pile their bodies up here!
What?!
You heard me, right? I'll be
looking forward to tomorrow.
He is my brother's son, after all.
If possible, I don't
want to have to kill him.
Father!
I'm scared!
G-Gohan!
Exceedingly strong,
and exceedingly cold-blooded,
he's Goku's brother, Raditz!
Will Goku be able to
save his son, Son Gohan?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Wah! Father!
No fair, Raditz! Give me back my child, Gohan!
S-Son-kun! N-Now Piccolo is here! We've had it!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"All Right! This is the
Strongest Combo in the World!"
Father, do you really think
I can become a great scholar?
"Next time"
"All Right! This is the
Strongest Combo in the World!"