Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
I-I beg you...! Freeza... defeat Freeza...!
Please... by your Saiyan hand...
Vegeta dies.
For you to beg of me, must
have been awfully difficult, I bet.
I understand.
It wasn't that your fellow Saiyans
had been killed that was rough on you...
I hated you so much...
...but you had your Saiyan pride.
And now I too will share in
some of that pride of yours.
I am a Saiyan raised on Earth!
"The Curtain Rises over the Ultimate
Battle!! I Am Going to Defeat You."
For all the Saiyans who were killed by you...
...as well as for the Namekians here...
I am going to beat you!
Such drivel.
It utterly sickens me how you worms can
share this consciousness among yourselves.
A worm is a worm.
Your legend will not be fulfilled.
I don't have anything to do
with this Super Saiyan stuff. Still...
I am going to defeat you!
How is the situation on Namek?
Vegeta has died.
W-What's that?!
Vegeta, did you say?
That's right. He was killed
by Freeza, and easily so.
Even though he served as Freeza's
hands and feet, working exactly as ordered,
in the end he was betrayed
and killed by him. What a shame!
It was his pride as a Saiyan, I suppose.
So that's how terrifying
a guy this Freeza is, then?
They touched that
which must not be touched.
That which must not be touched!
Damn it all! Not even Goku
is a match for a rat like that!
So, what about Goku?
He intends to fight.
It seems that, no matter what,
he's determined to defeat Freeza.
Goku!
G-Goku...
He's got such power under wraps.
Goku, when did you find all that power?
I implore you, Son Goku, defeat him,
and give me another chance to challenge you!
You guys, get away from this
place! We're in the way here!
Gohan! Hurry up!
Gohan!
Father!
Father, don't die! Let Freeza have it!
So fast!
Father...
I get it. He can't sense ki!
Father!
Gohan!
It's incredible! It's too incredible!
That got him for sure.
T-This is a Saiyan?
So many of these insects have
overestimated their own power,
and defied me up until now.
I've never seen a Saiyan
able to take things this far!
Over there!
H-Has something happened?
D-Don't tell us Son has...?
He's putting up a good fight.
These Saiyan characters are strange ones.
Or perhaps this is limited to Goku,
but there's no upper limit to his strength.
It's like he's a different
person from when he trained here.
He really is impossible
to understand, indeed.
Such an unusual guy...
Such an unusual guy!
Ah, that was good!
But it's no use. I can't walk any more!
I'm going to die here.
Without ever getting back to Earth...
...without anyone to
watch over me... quietly...
It's true what they say,
beautiful women do die young.
That's enough!
Who would ever expect me to
die here among all these frogs?!
Oooh, yow.
Now, then...
He's not that bad...
You're an impudent one!
What's this?
I-It's an eruption! What's it doing there?
Father!
Gohan!
If you go, you'll just
get in the way. Have faith!
Goku isn't as green as all that!
Father...
Son...
That's far enough.
I wonder if he's burned up.
What a disappointing
way to end the scene.
Goku!
Oh dear, you didn't have to come all this way.
I would have come to you.
I'll kill you quickly.
That was close, that was close!
If I'd fallen in there, I would've died!
Here goes.
Son!
Son! Behind you!
I'm not going to keep falling
into the same trap like that!
Don't go messing up other
people's planets so much!
What will you do once you break it?!
Frightening powers tear
the land and rend the sky.
However, Goku and Freeza display
nothing but confidence on their faces.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Kamehame-Ha! It sure
has been a long time, huh?
You seem to be much stronger
than I thought. I'm a little surprised.
But you are still no match for me.
Maybe not. But we just don't know!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Two Superpowers Collide!
A Fistfight Where Both Turn Serious!!!"
I've never been this excited in my whole life!
"Next time"
"The Two Superpowers Collide!
A Fistfight Where Both Turn Serious!!!"