Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Just as Kaio had figured,
the power of Earth's
Shen Long returns everyone
who had been killed by Freeza to life,
and together with the
return of the Grand Elder
came the return of Planet Namek's Shen Long.
Elsewhere, the great conflict
between Goku and Freeza continues,
even as the time of Planet Namek's
explosion draws ever closer!
There are now under two minutes remaining
before the explosion of Planet Namek.
Is there any way Goku can win?
"I'm Staying on This Planet!!
A Final Wish Towards Victory."
You're sure an obstinate one!
All you had to do was watch
silently from the edge of death,
and you wouldn't have
had to taste of its horror,
as you met your fate
together with the planet's.
Those of you that have come
from Earth are far too moronic!
So much so that you forget who
you are by challenging me to battle!
You have also forgotten
yourself in your own conceit!
What?!
Fine, then.
I'll crush you into tiny pieces.
The way I did that Earthling.
The way you did that Earthling?
You mean Kuririn?!
Hmph. Unfeeling Saiyans? What a joke!
Grand Elder of Planet Namek,
Namek is very likely to vanish very soon!
The Dragon Balls there
should have one wish remaining.
Yes, Kaio-sama.
Please ask the following
of Shen Long immediately:
"Send everyone there
except for Freeza to Earth."
I understand, Kaio-sama.
I am most grateful for your efforts.
However, the wish must
be told directly to Shen Long.
I will contact whoever is closest
and immediately relay the wish.
You can't! Not like that!
Change that wish for me!
Goku, you heard that?
What is this?
Don't make it everyone except Freeza,
change it to everyone
except for Freeza and me!
Goku, I know how you feel, but
for the time being, return to Earth!
If you don't let me settle
this here and now with Freeza,
I will resent you the rest of my life!
Goku!
I'm begging you, Kaio-sama.
Kaio-sama, what is the matter?
What is Goku saying?
Kaio-sama!
Kaio-sama... Kaio-sama!
See here, can't you be quiet?!
But Goku...
Quickly, now!
We ain't got any time!
You've got it, Goku, I won't say anything else.
If that's how badly you want this.
Shen Long is over there!
I'm supposed to have been
killed by Freeza. Why am I...?
The one most near is Dende.
Dende, this is the Grand Elder.
G-Grand Elder-sama!
Then you are all right!
But how in the world–?
I will answer your questions later.
Right now there is
something I would like you to do.
R-Right!
Shen Long should be waiting
for a final wish near where you are.
Yes!
As I recall, only two
wishes have been granted so far.
I want you to go right now
and speak the third wish for me.
Right! But what shall I...?
The third wish is...
Excepting Freeza and the
Saiyan named Son Goku,
I want all beings relocated to Earth.
Right!
Kaio-sama, thanks a lot!
Freeza! Let's fight!
You pathetic fool.
There is absolutely no chance that you'll win.
The end of this battle is already in sight!
But for Gohan-kun, our
takeoff preparations are all okay.
I wonder if he's really
serious about fighting Freeza!
I wish you would just
bring Son-kun back with you!
Then we could take off right away.
I told him there wasn't any time!
It's working perfectly, Gohan-kun!
Hurry and bring Son-kun with you!
I'm not too wild about going
paired with only Piccolo, after all.
Father...
Where is this place?
Is it getting ready for its destruction?
I'm supposed to have died.
I was killed by Freeza...
I don't know why, but I'm alive!
Where's Freeza? Where's Kakarrot?
Over there, dammit!
Freeza, you bastard!
Be sure you return home alive, Goku!
Yeah! And that was sure some
idea you came up with, Kaio-sama!
What's that?!
So that's the Shen Long of Namek, huh?
Now I can fight without
worrying about anything else.
–Come on, Freeza!!
–What?!
It's the Dragon Balls!
B-But I thought the Dragon Balls
were supposed to have become stones.
This is it!
Wait!
Stay out of my way!
Is that...?!
Dende, it's up to you!
Please, let him be in time!
Polunga!
What keepest thou?
Have you no more wishes?
I do!
Then thou must speak with haste!
Then, the third–final wish!
Make me, Freeza, undyingly young!
F-Freeza!
Oh, hell!
Make me, Freeza, undyingly young!
Very well. Understood.
I shall then leave these two here,
and move everyone else to Earth.
You rotten brat!
Freeza!!
Vegeta!
Kakarrot, you've become
a Super Saiyan after all!
E-Even you! Why?!
Why are you alive?!
Take this!
Farewell!
W-Wait!
Looks as though unless
you speak the language here,
you can't get your wish granted, huh?
You even made me shiver there.
Wasn't that the kid I killed before?
The Dragon Balls on Earth were used
to bring everyone that
you guys killed back to life!
What?!
And with the Dragon Balls here...
What wish did that brat get himself granted?!
Except for you and me, the whole
group of people that were on this planet
were moved to Earth!
Kaio-sama, what has happened?
It has turned out just as I figured.
–All right!
–That's great, huh Yamucha?
It's too early to celebrate.
Why is that?
Because Goku has remained
on Planet Namek with Freeza.
T-That can't be!
Bulma-san!
G-Gohan-kun!
Gohan-kun!
How could you leave me
all alone like that again?!
I apologize.
Where in the world is this?
It doesn't appear to be
Planet Namek, does it?
I was on the spaceship.
I don't see the spaceship around here.
Y-You're...
Where are we?
A planet named Earth.
What?! Where's Freeza?!
Son!!
Piccolo-san!
Gohan!
Piccolo-san! Ah, Dende!
I-Is this a dream?
Ow! It's not a dream!
It looks as though I've returned to life!
And Kuririn-san too?
I don't know.
Yeah, I suppose so.
G-Grand Elder-sama!
Grand Elder-sama?!
All of you, this is the planet called Earth.
–Earth?!
–I-It can't be... How?
What has been going on here?
The time when my measure of life runs out
and I am called away is
once again near at hand.
However, before I die, I wish to
relate to you what has taken place.
Where did Kakarrot
and Freeza vanish away to?
There's nothing left to do but pray.
Goku should not have any time remaining.
The planet has started to contract.
There are probably no more than
two minutes before it explodes.
Will you be killed by me first?
Or will the planet explode first?
Either way, death is all that remains for you,
since you cannot survive
in the vacuum of space.
Even in the miraculously improbable
event that you were to beat me!
Maybe so. But I've been
waiting for this moment–
the moment when, with just the two of
us, I could fight you as hard as I want to!
Hmph, even at the risk of death, huh?
It seems you want to settle
things with me, Freeza, at any price.
A body-blow battle? Very well.
If that's how badly you want to mix it up.
Remaining on Namek as it is
about to become a planet of death,
the utmost brawl is about to unfold between
the only two who remain, Goku and Freeza!
Will a decision be reached
before Planet Namek explodes?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Before Planet Namek explodes,
I swear, I will defeat
Freeza with my own hands!
Son, is this the path you've chosen,
in exchange for your own life?
I don't understand it.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Let's Get It On!!
Two Remain on a Vanishing Planet."
There's only a minute left
before Planet Namek is destroyed!
"Next time"
"Let's Get It On!!
Two Remain on a Vanishing Planet"