Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Disappear, together with the whole planet!
I'll blow you away!
Namek's core is destroyed
by Freeza's tremendous power!
In five more minutes, this
planet will vanish into space dust!
Five minutes is plenty.
I will defeat you, and take off
with my friends in my spaceship!
Unfortunately for you,
I am the one with the better hope.
I'll show you my 100 percent, full power!
I can't allow you to stall for time!
I'm bringing this to a conclusion!
"I Will Be the One Who Wins...
Risking Survival, a Final Attack."
What's wrong?!
Are you so afraid you'll wear yourself
out, you can't put out your full power?!
Don't get...
Don't get so...
...carried away!!
You underestimated me, didn't you?
Let me tell you that this
is still not my full power!
That was only about 70 percent.
And, starting now...
...your long-awaited 100 percent!
I'll settle this with my full power
in one minute–no, thirty seconds!
It's no good! I can't find Bulma-san's ki at all!
And you know, something is
beginning to happen to this planet!
Something beyond hope!
Besides which, Freeza's ki
seems to again be getting greater!
What can it mean?
W-Whatever happens, you
just watch me live through this!
Somebody, hurry and come save me!
Please!
Incredible! His ki is
billowing up and filling him out!
So this is finally the realization
of his 100 percent power, is it?
What are you doing, Goku?!
Goku, can you hear me?! Hey!
Now! Now is your chance!
Now, while Freeza concentrates
his power, is your chance to attack!
Hey, Goku! Do you not hear my voice?!
That can't be possible!
Goku, now is your only–
I do hear you, Kaio-sama.
There's no doubt, I probably ain't
going to get a second chance at this.
That chance to see with my own eyes
the strongest scumbag in the universe
at his full power, that is.
W-What did you say?!
Goku, are you even
aware of what you are saying?
...seventy-eight... seventy-nine...
...eighty...
...eighty-one...
Hey! What the hell is the matter with you?!
I... I want to fight Freeza.
...eighty-four... eighty-five...
And...
win!
Such foolishness! This isn't a game, Goku!
I am going to avenge
Kuririn! He has died twice!
He cannot return to life,
even with the Dragon Balls!
Kuririn was a good guy!
A really good guy.
My very best friend!
And he blew him to bits...
But there's no reason to
wait for him to reach full power!
Besides, what about Gohan and the others?
It's all right.
Gohan and the others will be saved.
Where are you? Where are you, Bulma-san?!
N-No way! I don't want
to die in a place like this!
Gohan-kun!
What have you all been up to?!
I was nearly worried out of my mind!
What exactly is up with this planet?!
Leaving me behind by
myself in such a dangerous place!
What is going on with Kuririn and Son-kun?!
I'll explain what's happening later.
Right now, we have to hurry!
Hurry? To where?
I know, the spaceship
Son-kun came in, right?!
We can go home now, right?!
Yeah.
Hooray!
Where's Gohan-chan?!
What's happenin' to Gohan-chan?!
There's only two reasons
this high-performance monitor
would stop sending images.
The first case is the
spaceship has been vaporized.
The second case...
is that something irregular is
affecting Planet Namek's axis,
causing fluctuations in its magnetic field,
thus causing electromagnetic
waves to become unstable.
What kind of conditions are those?
Uh, you might call it a portent
of the destruction of Planet Namek.
In any case, Goku and
Gohan-kun... and even Bulma...
...ninety-three percent...
ninety-four percent... almost there!
Freeza, the reason I'm waiting for
you to reach your full power like this,
is because I want to demolish
you when you're at your best!
That's so I won't have
any regrets as a warrior.
As for you, you must have come to
want to try out your full power, right?
Otherwise, you would have blasted
the planet again and finished it off.
K-Kaio-sama?
That guy is no longer Son Goku.
He is now a warrior of fury, a Super Saiyan.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
This is the full power you wanted.
There ain't time. Let's settle this quickly!
Contemptible fool!
W-What?!
I-Impossible! That I should
lose sight of them–what speed!
Too slow!
He vanished!
Behind you!
How about that?
That was just me warming
up for my final attack!
I'd hope so...
At such a level, I was just
about to become disappointed.
The time limit is up shortly.
Can Goku settle his fight
with Freeza at his full power?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Gohan, what are you dawdling around for?!
Hurry up and get out of here!
Kami of Earth, make your
wish to the Dragon Balls be,
"Bring back to life those who
were killed by Freeza and his men."
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Shen Long, Run Yourself Through Space!!
The Time of Namek's Destruction Draws Near."
Please, Kami-sama!
"Next time"
"Shen Long, Run Yourself Through Space!!
The Time of Namek's Destruction Draws Near"