The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
From the depths of space come Madoshi
Babidi and Dabura, King of the Demon Realm.
Their goal is to gather the greatest energy in
the world, and revive the sealed-up Majin Boo.
In order to return Kuririn and Piccolo,
who had been turned
to stone, back to normal,
Goku and the others made
their way inside Babidi's spaceship.
Within the spaceship
Babidi's henchmen assault
Goku and the others one after another!
At Stage 1, Vegeta overwhelmed Puiupi.
At Stage 2, Goku rips through Maju Yakon!
Impossible!
These aren't your ordinary guys after all!
I will go to Stage 3 for you!
Come three thousand kili,
come four thousand kili,
there does not exist a man in all
the world with greater power than I!
"A Great Miscalculation!!
Satan vs. Three Super-Warriors!?"
I wonder just what kind of
guy is going to come out next.
Gohan, it's your turn now.
Goku-san, this is not a game.
Babidi only selects the very strongest
henchmen from the far corners of the universe!
It is fine that we have
won up until now and all,
but from now on, how
about we all fight together?
Ah, don't worry about it, Kaioshin-sama.
Besides, it wouldn't be fair, would it?
Unfair?
Yeah! If only me and Vegeta get to fight alone,
while Gohan has to fight with everyone else...
He's right! Kaioshin-sama,
please, leave this up to me.
Okay, Dabura. Go!
They will surely fall at my hand!
Oh? Dabura-sama, where are you going?
The lift to the Stages is this way.
He's all right how he is.
Th-The meditation chamber?
I get it. Dabura-sama is going
to heighten his ki before fighting.
We absolutely must not open
that door until Dabura says it's okay.
Right!
He's sure set his mind to it!
If he goes all out, it will be a simple
matter for him to beat all three of them.
It's taking too long. How long
are they going to make me wait?
Don't be so impatient.
They're surely getting a
first-rate warrior ready for you.
By the way, I wonder what's
happening at the Tenkaichi Tournament.
Good question.
All of us pulled out of there together.
Hmph, rather than going
up against the trivial scum
that pass for opponents in a place like this,
I wanted to fight you in
the Tenkaichi Tournament!
I was looking forward to
fighting against Father myself.
Same goes for me.
I wonder if No. 18-san is doing well.
These people... revel in battle...
The Saiyans really do love to fight.
Hey! What's going on?!
–How long are you going to make us wait?!
–Hurry and start the fights again!
Oh, what's goin' on?
Are they fixin' to start again?
Not yet. It doesn't look like
Goku and the others are back yet.
Really, where has Goku-sa gone off to?
Hmm, it appears as though
something is happening.
There are large ki
gathered in a distant location.
They haven't come back now in nearly
in hour, surely they must be disqualified.
But with only five others remaining...
This is a problem, all right.
"Martial"
What, everyone's together already?
It's a good thing we got back in time.
Hmph, those guys who left
have done so in fear of Satan.
In that sense,
it's fair to say that you who
have remained have true courage.
W-We are greatly honored, Mister Satan!
Speak for yourself.
Oh, I know!
–Oh, it's Mister Satan!
–Mister Satan!
Satan! Satan! Satan!
Don't worry, ladies and gentlemen!
There can be no problem as
long as I remain here! Mister Satan!
Didn't you come here to see my strength?!
That's right, Mister Satan!
Way to go! You said it!
Show us your elegant techniques!
Pops is at it again.
Really. He never learns.
What do you think, guys?
I, Mister Satan, have a good idea.
Oh, what is it, Mister Satan?
A Battle Royale.
Battle Royale?!
Yeah. Disqualify those spineless
guys who have run off right now,
so the courageous five of us who
remain can all fight together in the ring.
No one will get excited over a
tournament with only five of us, right?
Having a Battle Royale
will be a smash! A smash!!
I-I see!
Clever as always, Mister
Satan! That's a great idea!
However...
Mister Satan, in a Battle Royale...
W-What is it?
Do you have some kind of objection
to an idea from Mister Satan?
N-No, it's...
Fine. If that's the case,
I'll just head on home.
N-No, not at all. It is a fantastic idea.
Good, it's settled. Make the announcement.
Right!
Ladies and gentlemen, we
are terribly sorry for the delay.
It has just been decided,
at Mister Satan's proposal,
to hold a Battle Royale with
the remaining five contestants!
All five will fight within the ring,
and whoever remains at
the end will be the victor.
Way to go! That's our Mister Satan!
You said it!
Wow, a Battle Royale. As might
be expected of Mister Satan.
I greatly admire you making
such a courageous statement.
Hm? Courageous?
That's right, Mister Satan!
After all, as the anticipated
winner, in a Battle Royale,
the other four will first come at you en masse.
If I were to be worried over such a thing,
I would not be able to
call myself a true Champion.
Indeed! Mister Satan, you
truly are a great Champion!
Right, everyone?
Oh, hell...
Battle Royale, he says.
I wonder if it'll be startin' before
Goku-sa and Gohan-chan come back.
Hmm, we won't be able to help it if it does.
In that case, we won't be
earnin' any prize money at all!
Our family budget! We're broke!
So then, let us now
introduce the five contestants
who will be appearing in the Battle Royale!
First, as you all know,
the Champion Mister Satan!
I'm going to artfully score this one!
Satan! Satan! Satan!
To continue, the only
female contestant this time,
the oddly-named Contestant No. 18!
Oh, you cute chick, hang in there!
No. 18!
Good luck!
Win, Mommy!
And, defeated during the first
round in the last tournament,
Contestant Mighty Mask!
Oh, that's us. All right,
let's make this look smooth!
Yeah!
Don't overdo it, Mighty Mask!
Further, defeated in the second
round in the last tournament,
Contestant Killa!
Killa, get out of there!
Finally, he's quite popular with the ladies...
unfortunately defeated last tournament by
Mister Satan in the final round,
Contestant Jewel!
You're so handsome, Jewel!
That's it! These five contestants
will compete in the Battle Royale!
Well, here we go!
Let's win the Adult Division as well, Trunks-kun!
Yeah!
Who among these five contestants
will it be that attains victory?!
Hey, why don't we both send
Mister Satan-sama to a ringout loss first, eh?
Don't bother me. That guy doesn't matter.
The only real threat is No. 18-san, yeah?
Yeah.
W-What the... He's got a
strange way of speaking.
Bonjour, my lovely princess.
I cannot bear that a lady such
as yourself should have to fight.
What do you say?
After the match, just the two of
us could get something to eat, or...
Get lost, you eyesore!
W-What did you say?!
So then, the final round
will have no time limit!
Let us have this five-man
Battle Royale begin at once!
I-If you're coming, then come on!
I'll take you! Well, bring it on!
That woman! How dare she
refuse my explicit invitation!
Rotten Mighty Mask!
When did you start having
such a sassy mouth? Damn you!
Begin the match!
Oh, what is this?
Very early into the match,
Contestant Jewel and Contestant
Killa have both dropped out!
That lady has a cute face, and she's incredible!
Contestant Mighty Mask is pretty good too!
Yea! Mommy, nice going!
Stick it to 'em, No. 18! Attaway!
Mommy, nice work!
H-How lucky!
I don't know how, but two of
those dismal characters are out of it!
All that's left are those two lowlifes!
V-Victory is mine!
That strange long-torsoed
creep... he's no slouch!
Those short arms have greater
punching power than I would have thought.
Stay sharp, Goten.
They say Kuririn-san's wife
used to be stronger than our
papas were a long time ago.
Yeah, got it!
Come on, both of you!
I'll take you both out at once!
Just ignore him.
Yeah.
And so, three contestants remain!
Contestant Mighty Mask!
Contestant No. 18!
And the Champion, Contestant Mister Satan!
Who among these three
will remain and be victorious?!
My victory is all but assured!
All I have to do is settle it all
while looking cool! That's it!
First, I'll defeat that masked goon with moves
far more flamboyant than they need to be!
Then, as that cute girl cowers at my strength,
I'll tenderly escort her like a
gentleman to a ringout loss!
Both the cute girl and the
spectators will be captivated by it all!
Oh, Mister Satan!
He is already proclaiming victory!
Magnificent! That was absolutely magnificent!
What is he, stupid?
Just let him be!
Okay, then! You, masked goon!
You will be the first to fall!
Forgive me, but there is no
sentiment in the world of fighting!
All right, our opponent is
No. 18-san! Got that, Goten?
Okay!
She's strong, all right.
Fight back!
I know! Here goes!
They're good!
Incredible!
If Goku-sa isn't fightin',
we'll cheer for No. 18 instead.
Hang in there, No. 18-san!
Mommy, hang tough!
Hmm?
Mm? Can it be?
Idiot, not that way! Right! Right!
Easy for you to say!
Oh no!
We're going to lose!
Okay, then!
They're flying!
The two of them are flying through the air!
Just what is going on here?
That does it, let's break through here!
You must not do such a thing!
We can't just wait here forever!
B-But you can't just break it!
If we irritate them for no reason,
it is instead likely to place us in danger!
They're getting impatient!
Is Dabura ready yet?
Sir, he's still in the meditation chamber.
Good, good! Dabura, raise
that ki even higher! More, more!
Dabura, king of the Demon Realm,
has entered the meditation chamber
to heighten his ki before doing battle.
Gohan eagerly looks forward to his attack!
This is hard to fight in!
Elsewhere, who will it be that dominates
the Tenkaichi Tournament's Battle Royale?
No. 18? Mighty Mask?
Or for that matter, Mister Satan?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Hey, now Goten and Trunks,
are you sure it's all right
to be fighting No. 18 in that strange outfit?
This is no laughing matter.
Those kids have incredible attack power!
This is bad. I have to finish this fight now!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Such Strong Kids!! No. 18's Close Fight!?"
Wow, way to go! Amazing, both of you!
"Next time"
"Such Strong Kids!! No. 18's Close Fight!?"