The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
The final, decisive clash between
Goku and Majin Boo has become fierce.
Goku boldly challenged Boo, with
strength that taxes the imagination, to battle.
Seeing this, Vegeta learned
of Goku's true greatness.
Hang in there, Kakarrot!
You are Number One!
"Pull Through, Vegeta!!
One Life-Threatening Minute."
Th-This is a considerably powerful dream!
Not again!
Ka... me...
ha... me...
Ha!!
Stupid punk! That was
a genuine Kamehame-Ha.
Th-The Kaioshin Realm...!
That holy region of the gods...!
Hey! Don't get so upset! This is a
crisis for the whole universe, you know!
At a time like this, can't you
overlook such a small thing?
You might call it a small thing...
Hang in there, Goku-san!
You truly are strong!
Even greater than I imagined.
Gonna kill you!
If I had known it was
going to turn out like this...
I should have finished you off for
good when I had become Vegetto.
But no matter what, I can't afford to lose!
Damn! My attacks ain't having
any effect on him at all any more!
What the hell's the matter?!
Th-This is bad!
As a result of the fight being drawn out,
Goku is just about out of stamina!
How do you like this?!
Even with me repeatedly
attacking him at that level,
that bastard ain't lost any of his resilience!
He just immediately goes
back to being good as new!
Kakarrot!
What is it, Vegeta? You want to switch
in again? Let me go a little bit longer!
You've got no intention of switching
out again, so quit being so transparent!
You must know as well as I do
that even if I were to fight him again,
then never mind me not having any
chance of winning, I'd be killed in a second!
Er, no, that's not...
Hmph, don't bother trying to be gracious.
It's certainly the truth.
I learned well once I tried to fight him.
Boo there is strong–even more than I am.
And you, Kakarrot, are too!
Vegeta...
Don't hold back for me, finish him off!
With your Super Saiyan 3 there,
if you gather as much ki as you can,
you should be able to
completely obliterate Boo!
Yeah... I've been thinking
of doing so for a while now,
but I just ain't had the chance.
Here I'm wanting to obliterate him, but I
have to gather ki for about a whole minute.
One minute?
Maybe I've been trying too much to look cool!
I thought things would go better than this!
Y-You were concerned over me?
That bastard... He could
return to normal in an instant,
but he's dragging it out on
purpose just for the fun of it!
Of all the... How infuriating!
One minute is enough, then?
If you have one minute, you can
gather enough ki to annihilate him, right?
Y-Yeah... If I had a minute, that is...
All right!
I'll keep him in check somehow for one minute.
You start gathering ki immediately!
V-Vegeta...!
You're going to keep him in check, you say?
That's crazy! I told you that
it would take a whole minute
in order to gather enough
ki to wipe him out, right?!
Is there any other way, Kakarrot?
Any other way to beat him?
W-Well...
In that case, stop your useless
worrying and hurry up and gather that ki!
I'll buy you that one minute.
I'll stake my pride on it.
Understood. I'm counting on you, Vegeta!
Listen, Vegeta, in your state,
you're already once dead.
Do you know what happens to
that kind of guy if he dies again?
They vanish.
In both this world, and the
Other World, you will no longer exist.
Don't you die, Vegeta.
Hmph. Mind your own business.
All right, here I go.
You piece of crap!!
Take this!
D-Do you hear something strange?
Not again!
That's great! If we're lucky, he just
might keep up like this for one minute!
Damn!
Hang in there, Vegeta!
One minute... If I can hold out for one minute...
Vegeta!
Bastard...!
Hey... Where do you think you're going...?
Vegeta!
We're... not finished... yet!
Are you thinking of running away?
You miserable coward!
Hurry up and come at me!
Come on, what's the matter?!
You're the mighty Majin Boo, right?
Or are you afraid of me?
Big Bang...
...Attack!!
What?!
A little longer... Just a
little longer! Hang on, Vegeta!
What's so funny...?
Y-You can't kill me...
with a wimpy attack like that...!
I'm not lying...
After all, I'm already dead once!
Damned if I'm going to be
done away with by the likes of you!
I am the warrior Saiyan
people's prince... Vegeta!!
This is bad! Vegeta really is
going to get killed for sure this time!
Dammit, what are you doing, Goku?!
One minute has already gone by, hasn't it?
How can this be? It's been one minute...
I can't wipe out Boo with only this much ki!
Die!
Die, die, die, die!
D-Damn it all!
I haven't gathered any ki at all!
What's going on?!
What in the world is the matter, Goku?
The only one who can save Vegeta now,
as well as the whole universe, is you!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Stop, Satan! Don't get involved!
There ain't no way you can stand up to him!
Oh, I'm sorry! I didn't mean any harm!
I just wanted to show off a little!
Please, just spare my life!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Don't You Pick On Satan!!
The Original Boo is Revived."
Surprisingly enough, an
encouraging ally has just appeared.
"Next time"
"Don't You Pick On Satan!!
The Original Boo is Revived"