Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Dammit, three years from
now I am going to survive!
In three years' time, a pair of incredibly
terrifying, murderous machines will appear.
The warriors each resolve
to train themselves anew
on the word of the young
man who came from the future.
"I Will Overcome Goku!!
The King of the Saiyan Warrior Race."
Keep it up, Yamucha-sama!
How can Vegeta suddenly start
training himself under 300-times gravity?
This is pretty severe.
At this very moment,
those terrible monsters
might be being born somewhere.
Just the thought of it
is keeping me on edge.
Bulma-chan! Bulma-chan!
I've discovered a new cake store.
Look! Aren't they pretty?
Well? Don't they look yummy?
How nice for you, Mama,
not to have any worries.
Bulma-chan,
lately you've been upset because
Yamucha-chan and Vegeta-chan...
...are too occupied with their training...
...to be able to pay you any attention, huh?
Of course not! Don't make me laugh.
Boy, that Vegeta is one guy
who sure likes to do crazy things.
Not only is he crazy to be
training under 300g of gravity,
but he keeps ordering
new gadgets to train with,
and then breaks them right away.
He's got an aberrant fanaticism for battle.
Dear, no! Vegeta-chan is quite sharp!
Mama!
You've said before you liked Son-kun,
but now you're saying Vegeta?
My, my, Goku-chan is sharp too!
But Vegeta-chan has this well-moderated,
stoic sense about him that I can't pass up.
Not to mention that wide forehead
of his is so individualistic and cute!
I know! Some time your Mama
will have to take him out on a date!
It's no wonder this would happen,
not with his dangerous mode of training.
Vegeta?
He couldn't have...
You're alive?
Of course I am!
What do you think you were doing?!
You came this close to wrecking my house!
Vegeta!
Y-You mind your own business,
bothersome human slave!
How is this training?
You can't do anything
in the shape you're in!
Injuries such as these are nothing!
I'm the number one Saiyan in the universe.
Y-You'll see how I overcome Kakarrot in no time!
Right, right.
Vegetables, carrots,
whatever, it doesn't matter.
Just do what I tell you now.
Don't you tell me what to...
Vegeta!
Masenko!
Father...
There!
What's wrong, Gohan?
Your motions are too slow!
To get off like he did
after such a major accident?
I'd have to say it's a miracle.
These Saiyans really are something!
Poor Vegeta-chan!
Kakarrot...
I-I will surpass you...
I will surpass you! Count on it!
Kakarrot!
Y-You're...
Why?
Why? Why is it I can't reach them?!
Why?!
Why is it?
You are to become the king of the Saiyans,
the greatest fighting race in the universe.
As soon as we Saiyans are born,
our abilities as warriors are investigated.
The ones with the lower readings
are sent off to planets where
they will not face great opponents.
Those good-for-nothings!
But you, Prince, your abilities
were the highest of anyone's,
that of a super-elite Saiyan!
You are certain to become the
greatest Saiyan in the universe!
In fact, you may even become
a legendary Super Saiyan!
He's right. I am super-elite.
There's no reason I should be beneath
lower class warriors like Kakarrot!
I am the greatest Saiyan in the universe!
Pu-erh, we're going on a training journey.
Okay!
Hold on, Vegeta!
Do you think you're in any
shape to be over-exerting yourself?!
You keep that up, and those
injuries we're treating will never heal!
Carping vermin. You really are a vulgar woman.
Oh, look at that.
I'll tell you flat-out, you're not
the type who's going to live that long.
You can't refute that, can you?
I don't suppose you can,
since what I'm saying is the truth.
Do you want to die in three years?
O-Of course I'd rather live.
After all, I'm still a well-built,
young, beautiful lady, you know.
In that case, shut up!
Three years remain until the
fearsome Artificial Humans...
...who would plunge the Earth into
the depths of terror are to appear.
What kind of battle awaits
Goku and the others in the future?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Wow, driving a car is hard!
It doesn't do what I want it to,
and breaks down easily! What's the deal?
Son, driving is not going to
help us defeat the Artificial Humans.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"License Mastery?
Goku's Newest Trial."
Father, is it true you're going
shopping with Mother by car?
"Next time"
"License Mastery?
Goku's Newest Trial"