Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Uniting with Nail,
Piccolo obtains ultimate power.
Elsewhere, as Goku's recovery continues,
the confrontation at last begins
between Freeza, Vegeta, Kuririn, and Gohan.
However, Freeza was still
hiding the true depth of his power!
Watch very carefully.
This is not something you will see every day!
When I attacked the planet
Vegeta, home to the Saiyans,
you realize there was utterly
no reason for me to transform.
So, the Saiyan's home
planet was destroyed by him?
Now then, marvel at this!
"A Nightmare Super-Transformation!!
Freeza's Battle Power of One Million."
What kind of transformation is this?
You're making us laugh!
To think that taking that off to become
more nimble is your idea of transforming...
Vegeta-san, I am so disappointed in you.
And after I looked after you the way I did.
If only you had peaceably submitted to me,
you would not have to
experience this horror now.
What are you babbling about?
I never submitted myself to you!
I was just pretending to submit,
all the while waiting for the right
moment to come along, so I could defeat you!
Yes, that is one of the
poor habits you Saiyans had.
Take your own father...
The king of Planet Vegeta was the same way.
What's this? You say the occupation
of Planet Tapp is still not complete?
Yes, sir. The Tappan's resistance is
proving tougher than we anticipated.
They say it will take another
three days to complete the occupation.
Three more days?!
Yes, sir. My humblest apologies.
Why, you! Have you forgotten that we promised
Freeza-sama the planet by tomorrow?!
No, I would never do such a thing!
However, the full moon on Tapp
will not appear for three more days.
Be gone.
Be gone! And let nothing remain!
As barbaric as always, I see.
I did not mind if it took another three days.
You've done something unfortunate here.
Nonetheless, I came to speak about your son.
When do you intend to bring him to me?
Well, that is...
I know! You will please
bring him in three day's time,
along with your announcement of
the successful occupation of Planet Tapp.
You need not worry that I will not pamper him.
King Vegeta, are you really going
to deliver the prince to Freeza-sama?
Yeah.
But won't you be risking the prince's life?
I'm not concerned about
things such as my son's life!
What I find unbearable is his attitude!
He has the mistaken idea that we
Saiyans are his slaves or something!
King Vegeta!
Curse you, Freeza!
Someday, we'll teach you a lesson!
You really do resemble
your dearly departed father,
both in your appearance and in your foolishness.
Foolish, you say?
That is right. If your father
had not tried such a foolish stunt,
the Saiyans would have gotten
off without being exterminated.
Listen up, you guys.
Freeza is afraid of us Saiyans
ganging up in large groups.
If you elite warriors combine your
powers as one, we are certain to defeat him!
Let's show him just how strong we Saiyans are!
Freeza-sama,
some Saiyans, including the Royal family,
have just arrived and are
requesting an audience with you.
Freeza-sama?
Lately, there have been some disquieting
tendencies among the Saiyans, yes?
Yes, sir.
They are indeed becoming quite an eyesore.
They are fools.
Quickly, men! Freeza is in here!
Take this!
Zarbon-san, open the door.
You will show the Saiyans in.
Yes, sir.
A little exercise may be good for me.
Where is Freeza?!
I'll kill you, and rule the universe myself!
Are you sure it will be as simple as that?
Are your men not trembling with fear even now?
Aw, crap.
King Vegeta!
Your king has just been defeated,
do you sirs not wish to avenge him?
Was that the best that even Saiyans could do?
Freeza-sama, are you uninjured?
I did not even need to transform myself.
Now then, shall we be off?
We are going to go watch
the fireworks of Planet Vegeta.
How wonderful!
Watch this, Zarbon-san, Dodoria-san!
Watch these beautiful fireworks!
I wanted to show it to you, too.
The fireworks of Planet Vegeta.
What a load of bull! If you
were really afraid of us Saiyans,
simply blowing up Planet Vegeta
would be a completely fruitless measure.
I'm right, aren't I? I mean,
you let me survive, after all!
Not to mention Kakarrot...
That's enough talk out of you.
So then, shall I begin the next part?
Your dearly departed father never saw this form.
What?!
What's this? What does he think he's doing?
Why me? Why am I the only
one that has to go through this?
This isn't funny, for crying out loud.
What's this? What's going on?
Help me!
What–what's going on here?
What?!
Impossible! This can't be!
We'll be killed!
It's a... nightmare!
Watch out, now! In this form,
I won't be as gentle as I was before.
What a ki!
What's this? The strength of Freeza's
ki has just increased several times over!
Oh, no!
Gohan!
Vegeta, what happened to those
high spirits you were in a moment ago?
You were spouting off all
sorts of demands, weren't you?
Well, I really can't blame you.
Not after having been
shown my overwhelming power.
Th-This guy's incredible!
Like I said, watch out!
You see, I have a lot more power now,
and I might just overdo things a little.
Incidentally, my battle power
is now probably over 1,000,000.
Wh-What?!
Unbelievable!
Not even you could reach that high!
If you think I'm lying, I'll show you!
Dende!
No!
What's this?!
Freeza, you low-life, what have you done?!
What is the deal with this planet?!
Kuririn-san?
What happened to Kuririn-san?
Right here!
You– you're bleeding!
It's nothing. I just got
clipped by a flying rock fragment.
You all fled from that more
quickly than might be expected.
You have my praise.
However, that was just my way of saying hello.
Even a Saiyan could have done that.
Why, you!
That's such a pitiful
face you're wearing, Vegeta.
I'd guess that you never imagined
I could become this powerful.
Now then, which one of
you should I show to Hell first?
I've decided!
Kuririn-san!
So... fast!
All too soon, Kuririn is run through by Freeza.
Is this the strength of Freeza?
Kuririn-san!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Damn. First Kuririn was done in, and now Gohan!
It doesn't matter if you're a
Namekian, a Saiyan, or an Earthling,
it won't change the fact
that you're going to die.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Is This the End!? A Brutally
Transcendent Power Attacks Gohan."
I wanted to get married once, too.
"Next time"
"Is This the End!? A Brutally
Transcendent Power Attacks Gohan"