The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
At last! The fight between Goku and Majin Boo,
with the entire universe at stake, has begun!
Majin Boo, you are one dense guy,
but your power, speed, and
powers of recovery are all incredible!
You're on a whole different
level from all the Boos up to now!
You're ridiculously strong!
Finally, Goku has become Super Saiyan 3!
Will it be Majin Boo that wins?
Or will it be Son Goku?
"Vegeta Takes Off His Hat!!
Goku, You Are No. 1."
Damn you, Majin Boo!
Hang in there, blond big brother!
Don't be in such a hurry.
The fight is just getting started.
Th-This is a fierce fight, huh?
E-Even more than fierce...!
Hang in there, Goku!
W-What an awesome fight oni!
If I missed this, I'd regret
it the rest of my life oni!
That blond guy looks like that guy who
fell from the Serpentine Road before oni.
You're right oni! As I remember,
he was named Son Goku oni!
I hate him! Shatter my cherished
dream of ruling the universe, will you?
Lose! Get yourself beaten!
You know, this is surprising.
To think that there is someone
who could put on so much
more incredible a fight than I!
Who is the other one oni?
I've never seen him oni.
He was, you see, my subordinate, Majin Boo!
Ahem... Boo adored me
like I was his older brother,
and anywhere I went, he came with me.
I gave him his first lessons for
those techniques he's fighting with now.
However, he's kind of slow on the uptake,
and I couldn't do much with him, really.
Babidi-san, you're some
incredible guy, huh oni?
Well... you might say so.
And, if you see Boo the
way I do, he's still just a child.
Damn! Boo, make a fool of me, will you?
Lose! Lose! Get beaten to a pulp!
Goku, hang in there! Hang in there!
The Kaioshin Realm is being destroyed!
Hey, it will still be fine after
just this! Hang in there, Goku!
Get him! Get him some more!
Go! That's it! Give it to him!
There, there, don't worry.
Even if we are in the middle of a
dream, I'll be sure to protect you!
I am the hero of Earth, Mister Satan!
W-Where are you, Boo?
Hold on...!
Watch out!
Where the hell is he going to come out from?
Where are you?
So, it was there, huh?
Dammit! Not even at Super Saiyan 3
can I keep up with his movements!
He's able to read every
movement I'm going to make!
That miserable Majin Boo!
He has terrifying strength...
It's all or nothing! This ain't the time to
be thinking about exhausting my power!
Ka... me...
ha... me...
Ha!!
Goku!
W-W-W-What's this?! Huh?
Does Majin Boo have that many children?!
Kakarrot!
Oh, no...
Switch out, Kakarrot!
You rest for a little bit!
V-Vegeta... he has... ridiculous
strength... You need to be prepared!
I know.
Vegeta!
Damn! What quick, heavy attacks these are!
Kakarrot was fighting an opponent like this?!
How can this be? How can Vegeta
there be absolutely no match for him?
This is bad!
D-Dammit, he's toying with me!
I am the warrior Saiyan
people's prince, Vegeta-sama!
Bastard! This is having no effect at all!
Vegeta-san!
I-I'm no match for him...
I'm simply no match for him...!
I-I'll be killed...!
Kakarrot!
Switch out, Vegeta. Majin Boo is strong.
Stronger than anyone
else I've ever fought before!
But I ain't lost yet!
Kakarrot!
Kakarrot, you are one incredible guy...
I was absolutely no match against Majin Boo.
You're the only one who can fight with him.
Kakarrot... the first time I met you
was when I came to Earth as I was
conquering planets on the frontier.
So, you've shown up?
What have you come
all this way for, Kakarrot?
Don't tell me you've come to
say you're going to defeat me,
or some other absurd joke, have you?
D-Damned if I'm about to
let something like this happen!
I-I am the Saiyan prince! I am ultra-elite!
There's no way I can be beaten
by a lower-class warrior like him!
I am the greatest in the universe!
Ever since then, I lived with the
goal of surpassing you, Kakarrot.
It's said that the legendary Super Saiyan
can only appear in one out of a thousand...
Even if the legend were true,
the capacity to become a
Super Saiyan lies within me alone!
There's no way that
lower-class warrior Kakarrot
could become a legendary Super Saiyan!
H-He's clearly surpassed
the Saiyan fighting level.
I-Is the legend really true?
Is he... really a Super Saiyan?!
From my own self-anger, suddenly
I was awakened... to being a Super Saiyan!
I was trembling with the joy of it!
Finally, finally, the time
when I had surpassed Kakarrot
and returned as the Saiyan prince had come!
However, in the end,
I was unable to surpass you.
At first, I thought it was because
you had something to protect–
that having a strong mind
towards defending something
gave rise to some mysterious power...
That certainly may be true, but if that were it,
then it would have been the same for me, now.
It was to have my own way,
it was for my own enjoyment,
it was to kill my enemies,
and it was for my own
pride that I had fought...
But, Kakarrot, you were different.
You don't fight in order to win,
you fight in order to be certain you do not lose,
and in order to keep reaching your limits.
That's why you don't worry
about taking your opponent's life.
In the end, you never did kill me.
It's as if you knew that I would now
come to have the slightest bit of a heart.
It's so maddening! That there should
be a Saiyan who loves to fight, yet is kind!
Hang in there, Kakarrot!
You are Number One!
Please, anything but that!!
A-Awesome oni!
Even the highly proud Vegeta
has at last taken off his hat!
The battle between Son Goku
and Majin Boo continues.
Goku, hang in there!
Protect the universe's tomorrows!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Damn it, Boo's strength
ain't being diminished at all
by these minor attacks.
Kakarrot! I'll keep him
contained somehow for one minute!
You store up enough ki
to wipe him out in that time!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Pull Through, Vegeta!!
One Life-Threatening Minute."
Vegeta-san, hang in there!
"Next time"
"Pull Through, Vegeta!!
One Life-Threatening Minute"