Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
The terrifying Artificial Humans
continue to slowly close in.
Their only target is Son Goku.
Elsewhere, Piccolo has come to the
heavenly plane to merge with Kami-sama,
in an effort to stand against them.
And, in order to escape the Artificial Humans,
Kuririn and the others
take the still-sleeping Goku,
and begin ferrying him to the Kame House.
"An Ominous Foreboding!
Bulma Unveils a Mystery."
Yum!
This ramen definitely makes
the cut. Chaozu, you do good work.
Is that so?
The soup is delicious, nice and full-bodied.
You could get by as a cook with food like this.
Compared to the stuff Kuririn
always makes us, yours is fantastic!
How is it you can make it so well?
I'm always the one who fixed Ten-san's meals.
And so, little by little...
How about it, Chaozu?
Why don't you continue
staying here with us some?
B-But...
It won't be so bad here, training at your leisure.
Isn't that just what he wants to hear?
You really just want Chaozu
to keep on cooking for you!
R-Rubbish! I wasn't
thinking anything of the sort!
Sure you weren't.
No, really...
Ten-san!
Tenshinhan...
Chaozu, let's go.
We have training to do.
Hold on there, Tenshinhan!
What about the Artificial Humans?
Did you guys defeat the Artificial Humans?
What's that?
You don't mean...? In that case...
Is everyone okay?
It's all right. Nobody has died yet.
Very soon, Kuririn and the
others will be bringing Goku here.
Please have them fill you in.
W-What?
Wait for me, Ten-san!
So what could have possibly happened?
...so, to them it's like a game,
but in any case, they intended to come kill Goku.
A-Are they really all that strong?
Yep.
You can even think of them as stronger
than what Trunks warned us about.
This is terrible!
All this time's been gettin'
away while we've been sittin' here.
What a waste!
What's the matter, Mother?
Well, get to it!
At a time like this?
No matter what time it is, studyin' is important!
You really are something else, Chichi-san.
So what do we do now?
Not that I would know... What should we do?
H-How does this sound?
What if I took the time
machine back further into the past,
and destroy them before they're activated?
I know the location of
Doctor Gero's laboratory and all...
I get you. That's a good idea, isn't it?
Hold on. I thought your time machine
didn't quite work perfectly, did it?
And from what Goku said,
it takes an awfully long time to store
enough energy to make a round trip, right?
If you go further into the past, are
you sure you can return to your future?
Not exactly...
You know, I was thinking,
if Trunks-san goes back a little further in time,
and even if you're able to
destroy the Artificial Humans there,
what will happen to the
Artificial Humans that are here now?
Will they suddenly disappear?
Gohan, you should just
be studyin' like a good boy.
T-That's right! I'd forgotten!
Undoubtedly, if I were to go back to
the past and destroy the Artificial Humans,
the future of that world
of that time would be saved.
But in this world, where the
Artificial Humans are already activated,
nothing would be changed.
How does that follow?
Let's see... For example,
Goku-san managed to hold on to
his life with the heart medicine...
...I brought him from the future.
However, in my future,
Goku remains long dead from his heart disease.
In other words, while there may
be a future where Goku-san survives,
there's still another one where he died.
From very minor events,
many different futures are created.
Just a minute, Trunks...
You mean, even supposing that...
...Goku is capable of
defeating the Artificial Humans,
In your future, won't they
still exist there, same as ever?
That's right.
In that case, Trunks, what
did you even come here for?
After all, your world won't be changed.
Mom...
Mom was so ticked off by us always
being clobbered by the Artificial Humans,
she thought it would be nice
if there was a peaceful future...
...where they had been beaten.
But her primary goal was to have me
fight with Goku against the Artificial Humans,
to find a weakness in them.
If that didn't work,
I would have had Goku come to
our future to defeat them there,
or something like that.
What will become of us?
I don't know.
Even more important
than what will become of us,
What are we to do?
Forgive me.
Anyhow, it appears I've come to a
different past than the one I knew of.
The timing of Goku-san's
heart disease was off, for one.
For another, there are
now three Artificial Humans...
Everything we can do.
Their strength so much greater...
What will become of us?
But why is it that so
many things are differen–?
I don't know. Why is it this bad?
I-Is it because of me coming
back in the time machine?
There's nothin' for you to be frettin' about.
If you hadn't come,
Goku would've died from his sickness.
I'm terribly grateful to you.
That's the right idea.
Something's going to turn up.
Y-Yeah, absolutely right!
We've been through so much before.
Something's bound to
come up this time too! Isn't it?
Incidentally, do you even know where he is?
This Son Goku?
We'll come across that information before long.
You mean you don't know?
My, my, I suppose it's just a matter of time.
There is a mountain
village in eastern sector 439...
...where Son Goku's house is located.
You're quite the know-it-all.
Did you learn that from Doctor Gero?
That's right.
If we flew, we could be
there in a matter of minutes.
Isn't that the truth! You say all the right things.
Yet you still want to take
the trouble to drive there.
What's the point?
Stop saying that.
The point is to have fun, isn't it?
So this is where you are, Son Goku?
We've been looking for you, really.
Are you guys Artificial Humans?
Yeah. We're the ones who killed Doctor Gero.
Now it's your turn to die.
Dammit!
Stop!
If you take one more step towards
my father, you'll answer to me!
Gohan! Kuririn!
Do you expect to stand in our way?
Apparently, they want to die.
Stop!
W-Why, you...
That's better.
Otherwise, this wouldn't be as fun.
Stop! Don't you do it!
Chichi!
Out of the way!
I said move it!
Stop!
Chichi!
Trunks...
Are you here for another beating?
Trunks, stop!
Damn you!
Now, then...
Stop!
Stop!!
Father!
Snap out of it, Goku!
Let me through!
Goku-san is even fighting in his dreams.
Yeah, really.
That sounds like Goku.
Is the man Son Goku even stronger?
No kidding? Neither one of
you is all that great, are you?
Wasn't the Super Saiyan supposed
to be invincible throughout the land?!
So what happened?!
How did it come to
that–that debacle I suffered?
I-I am the super-elite prince of the Saiyans!
And then, by becoming a Super Saiyan,
I should have been greatest in the universe!
Is it because my opponents
were Artificial Humans?
Is this the most I will ever be?
No!
There's still more to be had! I am Vegeta!
No matter how strong my
enemy is, I will surpass them!
I will surpass them!
Count on it!
And Kakarrot, after I beat the
Artificial Humans, you're next!
We'll be at Muten Roshi-sama's
island pretty soon.
Say, Kuririn, shouldn't you let
Bulma know what's been going on?
Yes, you're right.
But you want me to contact her? Aw, man...
You're the one who knows
the situation best. Please?
All right.
Your mother sure has a sharp tongue.
She's no different in the future.
Er, this is Kuririn calling, is Bulma-san there?
Ah, yes, Mistress Bulma. One moment please.
Kuririn! What, you mean you're okay?
Where are you calling from?
I thought Gohan-kun
should have been back by now,
but when I called his house, no one was there.
Wait, never mind that, is the future
grown-up son of mine, Trunks there?
Yes, he's right here.
He's there?
Great! Would you let me speak to him?
You can go ahead and talk now,
he can hear you over the speaker.
Okay. Well, the company here got an inquiry...
...from some folks in a rural area to the west.
They came across a strange abandoned vehicle,
and they wanted to keep it for themselves.
However, they couldn't figure
out for the world how to start it up,
and they were asking if we could tell them.
Right.
So we asked them over the
phone what model vehicle it was,
but they didn't know.
We asked them if they were sure it
was one of our products, and they said,
"It says right here on the
body, 'Capsule Corporation'."
We told them, in that case,
please send us a photo, and they did.
I was so surprised when I saw the photo!
It was the time machine
Trunks rode in, but it's damaged!
That can't be right...
No, it's right here.
I turned it into a capsule and took it with me.
He says it's right here with him.
I see, naturally...
So this isn't the one he came in.
There's some moss or something
stuck to it, making it seem pretty old,
so I thought it was kind of strange.
Say, how many time machines
did my future self build?
How many? It was all she
could manage to make just one.
That's strange.
This is definitely a time machine.
I saw the one you were in
before, so I couldn't mistake it.
Hey, do you have a fax there?
Take a look at this photo!
Trunks, here.
Unmistakable. This is the same
time machine I rode back in.
What does this mean?
What's this? A time machine, identical to Trunks'.
A cold shiver is followed
by an ominous foreboding.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
You found a strange egg inside
the older-looking time machine?
I've got a bad feeling about this.
It arrived here four whole years ago.
Could history have changed
so much because of this?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Discovery of an Evil Egg!!
A Terrified Trunks."
Trunks-san, there's a large shell over here.
"Next time"
"The Discovery of an Evil Egg!!
A Terrified Trunks"