The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
The fourth match of the Tenkaichi Tournament,
between the Great Saiyaman and Kibit,
was finally getting underway. However...
Turn yourself into this
Super Saiyan business!
I want to test you, to see
if you will be of help to us!
Further, Shin, who is the Kaioshin,
said to Goku and the others...
You must allow us to make use of
Gohan-san. My humble apologies.
And now, no matter what may happen,
I would ask that you
please not move from here.
If you would be so kind...
And now, finally, Gohan commits to
turning himself into a Super Saiyan!
What exactly is going on behind the
scenes at the Tenkaichi Tournament?
"A Slithering Conspiracy!!
Gohan's Power is Stolen."
As you wish, I will become a Super Saiyan.
I'm not sure exactly why, though.
When Gohan becomes a Super Saiyan,
then what is going to happen?
Quite probably,
I believe Gohan-san will be assaulted by
those two from earlier, Spopovitch and Yamu.
However, as I said a moment ago,
please do not take any action against this.
Sure we won't take action!
Gohan can easily defeat those two!
I'm not so sure.
Kaioshin-sama, you think
Gohan will be beaten by them?
It is all right.
I do not think they will
take his life from him.
It is more likely those two
are only after strong energy.
Energy?
Shall I turn all the way into a
Super Saiyan that has further overcome
the Super Saiyan wall?
What?! "Further overcome
the Super Saiyan wall"?!
Hey, look at this!
Terrific energy! It's him!
It can't be! He's transformed!
Gohan-kun has...
It can't be! It can't be!
W-Who would have thought that
Gohan was the Golden Warrior?!
Th-That is the Golden Warrior, isn't it?
I-Impossible! Him?
How 'bout that?!
Just like I said! Right?!
Somethin' even more incredible's
gonna happen, so watch closely!
As you wished, I have
become a Super Saiyan for you.
Now what do we do? Can I fight this way?
Wh-What incredible power this is!
I can hardly believe he is of the Lower Realm.
Hmph. That lowlife!
When he finished off Cell, he
had a lot more on him than this!
He's gotten soft during this peace,
and has neglected his training!
Even so, he has wonderful
power, greater than I imagined.
As to whether or not
I can contain that power...
Contain it?
Piccolo?
"Tenkaichi Tournament"
What's the matter, come at me!
H-Hey, when Mister Satan was fighting Cell,
there were some guys like that
there, huh? A handful of them.
You're right. They were there
all right. He looks the same.
All right. Let's take that energy from him!
Be sure you hold him tight, Spopovitch!
Yeah!
They're here!
What?! You!
Wh-What are you doing?!
Wh-Why?!
Please trust me.
Why you rotten...!
Let me go, Piccolo!
I told you, take no action!
I'll kill anyone who does
anything funny! Got that?!
Please have patience...
O-Outta my way!
Wh-What are you doin' to my Gohan?!
Goku-sa, what are you lookin' at?!
What are you doing to Gohan-kun?!
Let me go! Gohan-kun will be killed!
Gohan ain't going to die that easily.
Why? Tell me why?!
Well?
Be silent and look on.
Why?
Big Brother's going to get killed!
Why don't our Papas go help him?!
I have to save him!
Spopovitch! That's enough!
We've absorbed a full portion of energy!
That was easier than I thought!
Not yet!
Do not do anything yet!
It's okay. Kibit will soon restore
Son Gohan-san back to normal.
What exactly is this all about?
I will now follow after those two
such that they do not notice me.
After them?
If it is all right with you, you
may all please come with me.
You will be of great help.
Just what is going on?
What's happening down there?
G-G-Gohan-chan...
Wh-What should we do, Goku?
I'm going with him! Kaioshin-sama
said that Gohan will live, after all.
Plus, I just gotta know what's happening here!
Gohan-kun! Are you okay? Shake it off!
Hurry and get a stretcher ready!
S-Say, isn't that Videl? It is, right?
It couldn't be!
I wonder if I'm just having a bad dream...
Ow!
You're going, Goku? W-Well, maybe I'll go too.
I'm a little uneasy about it, though.
Kuririn, what are you gonna do?
Go on ahead first, I'll come
as soon as I let my wife know.
Right!
Don't jerk me around, Kakarrot!
What happened to our battle?!
It comes the match after next!
Vegeta, this ain't the time for that, is it?
Don't you cheat me!
I don't know from this Kaioshin, or whatever.
His business doesn't matter!
All I want is to settle
everything with you, one-on-one!
That's the whole reason I came
to this ridiculous Tournament!
Okay, okay. I know how you must feel.
We'll fight later for sure, even if
it ain't at the Tenkaichi Tournament.
Okay? Is that fine with you, Vegeta?
Damn it all!
You can only be in this
world for one day, right?
So then you'll come with me.
We'll do it over there!
Now that's settled, let's go.
Piccolo!
You can assure me that it's okay
if I leave Gohan in your hands?
It's all right. Once I revive
Son Gohan, I will go as well.
I believe Son Gohan will be going too.
Dammit!
You are really getting on my nerves.
Sorry, but that's the way it is.
I'm not going. There's no money in it, right?
Yeah. Well, make sure you
don't kill anyone in your matches!
See ya!
If things get nasty, you get out of there!
Right!
Wh-Where is everyone going?
You'll find out when you go too.
Okay, please move aside.
We need to carry him off!
Just be quiet and watch.
B-But this man has collapsed!
W-We'll leave it to you!
His full power has not returned
even yet! His power knows no end!
You know, I cannot believe
there are those among mankind
under the power of such
great, such pure energy!
It's no wonder they were after it.
What?! What's going on?!
Goten, did your brother just lose?
I hope Big Brother is okay.
Where did our Papas fly off to?
That's enough, Son Gohan.
Gohan-kun! You're okay, aren't you?
It's like I have more power than before!
Wh-Who are you?
Come with me. I will tell you everything.
Hey, have you seen Videl?
Ah, the young lady is over there.
She's with that kid again!
Dammit! I don't care if he did heal
Videl's injuries with that mysterious bean,
I absolutely forbid them to associate!
Say, can I come along with you?
There are lots of things...
I want to know. Please?
No, you'd better not.
There's going to be some danger for sure.
I know that much, more or less.
I won't get in the way,
I just want to come along.
I'm coming, even if you say no.
Videl?!
Can you promise me that
when things get dangerous,
you'll be sure to run away?
Okay. Let's go.
Thanks!
She's f-f-f-flying...
V-Videl's flying through the air!
Starting a few moments ago,
everyone has been flying.
V-Videl, I...
...should have grounded you.
Wow! That joke sure is an old one!
I got a bad feelin' about this.
Wh-What about the Tenkaichi Tournament?!
With this, the Majin-sama can return to life!
Babidi-sama will be so pleased!
"Tenkaichi Tournament"
What do you suppose happened
to the Tenkaichi Tournament?
The broadcast relay has stopped,
and there's nothing but
Mister Satan's face now!
Hey!
So, you have come after all.
This will be most helpful.
If I cannot borrow your
powers, we will not likely win...
Not win? You mean against those two?
No. Those two are merely
being used by an extremely clever
"Madoshi," or a warlock.
A Madoshi?
Yes.
Long ago, around the
time when mankind on Earth
was just starting to walk on two legs...
...deep in space, there was
an evil Madoshi named Bibidi.
One day, this Bibidi accidentally
conjured up an extraordinary monster.
This incredibly fearsome Majin was named Boo.
Boo? He sounds like a fart...
Majin Boo had no reason or feeling,
and did nothing but perform
destruction and savagery over and over.
He was a monster born only
to raise terror in living things.
In only a few years,
he had turned many hundreds
of planets into worlds of death.
Something along those
lines sounds like us Saiyans...
No, Vegeta-san.
At the time, there were five Kaioshin.
Each of us were such that we could have
defeated the likes of Freeza in one blow.
Among the Kaioshin, four
of us were killed by Majin Boo.
Incredible!
That punk! He can read minds too, can he?
Majin Boo's ferocity was more than
even his creator Bibidi could handle.
In any case, time came
when he needed to rest,
so he temporarily sealed Majin Boo
inside a ball so he could not move.
Bibidi brought the sealed
Majin Boo to this Earth.
The Earth was supposed
to have been his next target.
Th-That's unbelievable!
It was our chance.
Kaioshin-sama was able to kill
Bibidi before he could break the seal.
However, Majin Boo's
sealed ball was left as it was.
But why? You could have
destroyed it way back then!
It was thought best not to
stimulate it any more than necessary.
Besides, Madoshi Bibidi was
supposed to have been the only one
who could break the seal.
Supposed to have been?
Quite recently, we
discovered something terrible.
Madoshi Bibidi had a child!
He was another Madoshi, who had
the same heart of evil as his father.
The child's name was Babidi.
Madoshi Babidi?
It seems that Babidi is nearly
ready to break Majin Boo's seal.
The identity of those squirming
around behind the scenes
at the Tenkaichi Tournament becomes clear.
Kaioshin Shin and the others' goal is to
stop the actions of the Madoshi Babidi.
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
It sounds like our foe this time
is someone out of this world, huh?
Oh, Babidi has come out of the
spaceship. Ah, and what's worse,
that's Dabura, King of the
Demon Realm, beside him!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Man Behind the Curtains Appears!!
The Evil Madoshi Babidi."
Whoever you are, you're going to pay.
I am not about to let you
do evil things with my energy!
"Next time"
"The Man Behind the Curtains Appears!!
The Evil Madoshi Babidi"