The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
The Adult Division matches for the
Tenkaichi Tournament have finally begun!
First, Kuririn showed off
his overpowering strength!
However...
J-Just who is this guy? What is it about him?
You will know soon enough.
E-Excuse me.
I withdraw.
Withdraw?!
Inconceivably, Piccolo resigns
himself to forfeiting without fighting!
Can this mysterious young
man Shin really be that strong?
And so, contributing even
more to this sense of confusion,
the third match, between Videl
and Spopovitch, is about to begin!
"Undyingly Unpleasant!?
The Mystery of Spopovitch."
Videl! Videl! Videl!
How gross!
That guy's really occupied with something...
Videl! Good luck!
Hey, Videl will have an
easy victory against that rat.
Fight! Fight! Lovely Videl!
Whaddya know? Gohan's
girlfriend is unusually popular.
So it seems.
That kid is Gohan's...? How about that?
Gohan must know a thing or two about girls.
Yeah! And besides, I've been
hearin' she's a girl from a rich family,
and Gohan's so good to his Ma.
But she is the only daughter of Mister Satan.
Something like that doesn't matter.
After all, that's a matter
between the two of them.
And so, the third match,
between Contestant Videl
and Contestant Spopovitch!
Please begin!
What is it?
Perhaps I'm mistaken, but m-might you be...
Yes?
...m-might you be the Grand Kaio-sama?
No. I am not.
He isn't the Grand Kaio.
This is Kaioshin-sama.
K-Kaioshin...?!
Whoa!
Contestant Videl makes a lead-off attack!
Such ferocity! She gives him
absolutely no chance to hit back!
Please keep this to yourself, for now.
I do not wish anyone to know just yet.
K-Kaioshin-sama...
Above the four Kaio-sama
stands the Grand Kaio-sama...
I had heard stories that higher still,
there was a Kami that stood
over the Kaio-sama, but...
No wonder he should have a
dimension so different than ours.
What's the matter, Piccolo?
Did he say something inappropriate to you?
If he did, want me to go over and snap at him?
After all, Piccolo, you did
use to be Kami over the Earth!
S-Stop! Don't say a thing!
Please! Don't say anything! Got it?!
That young man is K-Kaioshin-sama?!
I've never even had
the honor of meeting him.
Why would such a figure
go somewhere like Earth?
Oh!
Contestant Spopovitch is down already!
I will begin the count!
Contestant Spopovitch
has gotten to his feet!
Looks like he still has plenty
of get-up-and-go left in him!
Spopovitch there sure does
take a blow a lot stronger now.
I guess more than just his
outward appearance has changed.
Yeah.
When I first saw him, I didn't realize it was him.
Contestant Videl lands a terrific attack!
However, Contestant Spopovitch
seems to be bearing it well.
Contestant Spopovitch
is down... no! He's back up!
He's gotten up!
How's that girl doing?
She can go!
Yeah, she has ability completely over his!
Her techniques are landing one after the other.
Hmph, what a low level of fighting...
She's connected once again!
She certainly is a gifted young
lady when it comes to hand-to-hand!
The great man Spopovitch is no match for her!
Nice!
Way to go, Videl!
She's doin' pretty good, huh, that girl?
She sure is fit to be Gohan's girlfriend, huh?
You really think so! I do!
We gotta get those two
married now, no matter what!
You gotta be kidding.
That's really Mister Satan's daughter?
So? She's pretty good, isn't she?
No way!
Whoa! Contestant Spopovitch once
again rises as if nothing has happened!
What toughness he is displaying!
This proves to be an unexpected development.
Contestant Videl's ferocious
attack does not seem to be registering
any damage on Contestant Spopovitch!
You sure are stubborn!
All right! It's over!
It's decided!
Contestant Videl lands
continuous, terrible attacks!
Not even Contestant
Spopovitch can possibly, possib–
H-He's up.
I-Impossible!
She's better off withdrawing from this match.
There's something weird about him.
Withdraw? But Videl's leading him!
That's right!
Aah! Videl!
Heh, relax! Videl's just playing around with him.
Snap out of it!
I can't very well let you
become Gohan's bride like that!
Looks as though Chichi-san is about
to become the fussy mother-in-law!
Yeah.
Aa! She'll fall!
Oh, no!
She's... stopped.
How's this? Contestant Videl is flying in mid-air!
She has not yet fallen!
W-What?!
What's going on?
Nice going! Nice going!
I taught her how to do that,
the Bukujutsu technique!
She may have been
better off falling out just now.
There's something strange
about that Spopovitch guy.
He should have taken all
that damage up until now,
yet he ain't bothered by it, and
I can't feel any life's ki in him as such.
"Life's ki as such?"What do you mean?
Well, I don't know what it means.
What? Videl is about to
get beaten by Spopovitch?!
Y-Yes.
There's some kind of mistake.
Spopovitch was defeated by me in
the first round of the last Tournament!
Videl has much greater strength than he does!
Well, you see, it appears he has
gotten much better since last time...
She's acting, she's acting! Videl, you rascal,
you've learned from me, trying to
stir up this Tournament, aren't you?!
Are you sure that's it?
That has to be it!
Contestant Spopovitch's neck has been broken!
She's done him in!
Whoa! She killed him!
You mustn't look!
L-Ladies and gentlemen,
this is a most tragic conclusion.
According to the rules of this Tournament,
as Contestant Videl has killed her opponent,
she is disqualif–
W-W-W–
What's this?!
His neck has returned to normal!
How can this possibly be?!
W-What is this?
Goku is right. She'd better concede!
There's definitely something
irregular about that punk!
Oh! Contestant Videl is flying again!
Yeah! That's good!
Escape up into the air for a bit
to recover some of your energy!
H-He's flying!
It can't be!
Spopovitch can fly through the air too?
What is the secret of this man's strength?
Moreover, how will the
now-cornered Videl fight against him?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
That Spopovitch guy is brutal.
He's a real monster, going
that far against a female opponent.
H-Hey, Gohan! What are
you turning Super Saiyan for?!
Don't tell me you're going
to go save her in that getup!
That's a bad idea!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"A Tragic Videl!!
Are You Coming Out, Angry Super Gohan?"
You'll pay for this, Spopovitch!
"Next time"
"A Tragic Videl!!
Are You Coming Out, Angry Super Gohan?"