Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Ka...
me...
ha...
Take this! A full-power Kamehame-Ha!
Ha!!
Ka...
me...
ha...
Ha!!
Cell's ultra-huge Kamehame-Ha
was blown away by Gohan
with an even bigger, ultra-huge Kamehame-Ha!
N-Not by you...!
There's no way my perfect form
can be beaten by the likes of you!
At this point, Gohan's
victory is evident. However...
"Bye-Bye, Everyone!!
Goku's Last Instantaneous Movement."
–No. 18!
–Wait!
What's this?! Under the
bento salesboy's ferocious attack,
Cell's condition has started to change!
This was unexpected!
Will the bento salesboy end up
being the victor of these Cell Games?!
Th-The sound from the mike is broken, too.
Th-That's right...
Your courageous announcer's
voice rings out to no avail.
What's this? What's happening?
C-Cell's body has changed back!
He's no longer in his perfect form!
Gohan has won.
Cell is no longer any match for Gohan.
Dammit!
That's it, Gohan!
Now! Attack him once and for all!
What's the matter?! Get up here!
Damn you!
Tch! This is getting dull. You're through, now.
Gohan! Don't play around!
Hurry up and defeat Cell!
Y-You won't get away with this!
I won't let you get away with this!
W-What could be happening?
Cell is rapidly changing his shape!
Th-This time, he's swelling up like a balloon!
What is this? What is he planning to do?
This is bad!
You guys are finished now!
I-I'm going to blow myself up momentarily.
I may die, but all the rest of you will die, too!
Th-The whole Earth will be caught in the blast!
–What?!
–Wha– He's going to blow himself up?!
S-Sure enough, given his power, the
whole Earth probably would be blown away!
I won't let you do that!
Whoa! You'd better not attack me.
If you apply any shock to me now,
I will explode at that instant!
It would just mean your deaths
will come a little sooner.
O-One more minute! Not even I can stop it now!
This can't be...!
What do we do?
Unless we do something...
I-It's no use!
There's nothing we can do now!
45 more seconds!
Gohan! You're the only one who
can finish Cell off! Do it quickly!
Don't push him any more!
There's no telling what he'll do!
H-How could things have turned
out like this? Father was right...
Damn...
It's my fault.
If only I had finished him off earlier...!
A-Another 30 seconds...!
Th-The Earth will be lost! Damn it all!
W-What is it, Goku?
Sure enough, no matter how I think it through,
I can't come up with any
other way to save the Earth...
What do you mean, Goku?
Goku-san...!
Bye-bye, everyone.
–What?!
–Goku! Don't tell me you're...!
Ten more seconds!
Looks like this fight ended in a draw, huh?
Damn...
Goku!!
You did fine up to this point, Gohan.
F-Father...?
Tell your mom that I'm sorry.
I always selfishly did whatever I wanted.
Goodbye, Gohan.
Goku!
Father!!
Goku!!
Y-Y-You idiot!
Don't you bring that thing here!
Sorry about this, Kaio-sama!
This was the only place!
How can you say that...?!
Damn!
I-It's gone... Goku's ki...
Goku!
Father!!
What's wrong?
I can't sense Goku's ki. Cell's ki either.
You're not telling me Son-kun is dead, are you?
W-What in the world just happened?
C-Cell is not here.
Cell and that young man
just suddenly disappeared.
I'm talking again...
M-Mister Satan, what exactly...?
It's over, Gohan. You and Goku put an end to it.
I-It's my fault...!
If only I'd killed Cell at that
time, like Father told me to...!
But I got too carried away...
Gohan, don't blame yourself too much.
Without your power, the
Earth could not have been saved.
Isn't that so?
Goku died with a contented look on his face.
I'm sure he was happy
about how much you've grown.
Come on, get up.
Let's go home.
No. 18!
Father...
Sorry, Bubbles and Gregory, for getting
you guys caught in the middle of this.
I absolutely cannot believe what you did.
I am Kaio! I'm the most
important person in this world!
I'm higher than even Kami-sama!
And yet... and yet... for the sake of Earth,
a single planet, you used me like this!
I've apologized over and over again, ain't I?
Kaio-sama, you sure are on my back, huh?
There wasn't any other way that I could think of!
Goku! Mind your language!
How dare you say I'm on your back!
Right...!
But you know something, Kaio-sama?
Cell's spirit ain't around, huh?
Could he have gone
straight to Hell or something?
N-Now that you mention it...
Ah! He's gone! He's nowhere!
N-No matter who they are,
whenever anyone dies,
they go to Yama's place first.
What does this mean?
Cell hasn't died yet. He's still alive!
W-What?!
Kuririn! What are you planning
to do with that Artificial Human?
If she's still alive, hurry and kill her!
Y-You can't mean that. She's–No. 18
here wasn't all that bad a person.
Hmph! I wouldn't be too sure.
You guys are as naive as ever!
What?!
Th-That–That ki...!
I-It couldn't be...!
I-It can't be...!
Who was it that I hit? Trunks, was it?
What's this? Cell did not die.
This time, Earth is in a great pinch for sure!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
What do you mean, Cell is still alive?
I was sure he'd blown himself up!
I've returned from the brink of death,
and I've greatly powered up.
All thanks to Son Goku.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"A Nightmare in Broad Daylight!!
The Terror Becomes Even More Perfect."
This time, I have to make
sure I avenge Father for good!
"Next time"
"A Nightmare in Broad Daylight!!
The Terror Becomes Even More Perfect"