The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
It was the long-awaited day
of the Tenkaichi Tournament.
As promised,
Son Goku appeared from the Other
World before Gohan and the others.
Yoo-hoo!
–Goku!
–Father!
Goku-sa! I've been waitin' for you!
I've missed you, too.
Father...?
Father!
You sure are spirited!
You look strong, just like me!
Goku...
I'll remind you one more time,
you've only got 24 hours. Got it?
Yeah, understood.
The Tenkaichi Tournament is about to begin.
"Watch Out, Saiyaman!
Beware Of Snapshooters!?"
Let's shoot over there!
Hi! Where are you from?
I'm from Satan City.
Despite how I might look,
I work out at Satan Dojo.
I wonder if Gohan-kun is here yet.
Videl!
Shapner...
Videl, I'm celebrating
your victory in advance.
You don't say...
I'm going to take some great
shots of you looking cool today, Videl.
Oh yeah?
V-Videl, did you cut your hair?
You can tell just by looking, can't you?
You know, there's a shop near here
that serves a delicious tropical juice.
After the tournament is over,
would you go there with me?
V-Videl!
Goten, your dead pop is
the spitting image of you, huh?
You think so?
He was amazing, right?
Uh-huh.
He doesn't look all that great
to me. My dad seems stronger.
But Big Brother said that Father is
the strongest in the universe, didn't he?
So you do have hair, huh?
I told you a long time ago
that I was shaving it, didn't I?
Why did you grow it out?
I think you looked better without hair.
Well, you see, a lot has happened.
Huh? No. 18! That's No. 18, ain't it?
You just now realized? Idiot.
What's No. 18 doing here?!
We're living together at Muten Roshi's place.
Kuririn, does that mean you and No. 18 are...?
We also have a child. You
saw her earlier, right? The girl?
What a surprise!
Idiot.
You had a child, even though she's a robot?
She's not either a robot!
No. 18 was human to begin with.
She just got a little bit modified.
Oh, is that right? Kuririn, congratulations.
Yeah, thanks.
Gohan-kun, that's you, right?
Videl-san...
I knew it! Gohan-kun,
why are you wearing that outfit?
Shh!
I'm the Great Saiyaman.
Oh, so that's it.
So, Videl-san, have you
gotten so you can fly really well?
Of course I have. Watch.
Listen, Gohan-kun, I'm not
going to hold back, understand?
Aren't you the formidable opponent?
Videl...
I-I'll just be going...
Hold on! Who are you?!
He's the Great Saiyaman.
Him? You seem to be on
awfully familiar terms, huh?
That's just because he's an ally
in my cooperation with the police
in the fight against evildoers.
Right, Great Saiyaman?
Y-Yes, that's right.
Who the hell are you?!
His true identity is unknown.
Not even I know who he is.
Right, Great Saiyaman?
R-Right.
"Right, Great Saiyaman" is it?
Goodness! Shapner, you
wouldn't be jealous, would you?
D-Don't be ridiculous!
Contestants participating
in the Tenkaichi Tournament,
please hurry, as the preliminary is beginning.
Contestants participating
in the Tenkaichi Tournament,
please hurry, as the preliminary is beginning.
Great Saiyaman, we have to hurry!
Videl-san...!
H-Hold on, this is awkward...! Please, let go...!
Dammit!
That miserable Great Saiyaman!
Just who is that guy?!
Thank you very much!
It appears that this bunch
are the last contestants to enter.
Let's shoot them quick, and then
move to the preliminary grounds.
Right, right.
Hi! Where are you from?
Say, haven't we seen
those two someplace before?
You think so?
I'm sure I've seen them somewhere...
I still like the way your head looked before...
Hi! Where did you come from?
Where? I... I came from the Next World.
What a kidder!
I ain't kidding you.
Um, that ring over your head is just
an accessory you're wearing, right?
Ah, this? This ain't for
decoration. See, when you die...
Piccolo hasn't changed at all, huh?
Where do you get off breaking the camera?!
Everything we've shot up
to now is ruined, you know!
How could this be? It's strange,
this has never happened before.
Those of you who have to change,
please use this dressing room.
There isn't much time, so please hurry, okay?
Aw... I sure would have
liked to fight with the adults.
You know what, though,
with us entering, you have
to feel sorry for everyone else.
The only ones who look like they'll
be able to stand up to us are each other.
–He's so handsome!
–So handsome!
Let me have your autograph next!
U-Um, you seem a little pale.
Are you all right?
Leave me alone! My face
is supposed to be this color.
W-We beg your pardon!
D-Dammit, what's so
great about Great Saiyaman?
Thanks for waiting!
Sorry to keep you hanging.
Okay, let's go.
Dammit, I'm going to make sure I find
an opening and reveal his true identity!
This place is packed!
Amazing, isn't it?
Nothing but small-timers.
Oh...?
Oh...! It's you guys!
Yo!
What a wonderful day this is!
I didn't think I'd be seeing you again.
Wow, how this takes me back!
I've been waiting so long for
you guys to participate again.
It wasn't Mister Satan that
defeated Cell, it was you guys, right?
I knew as much.
To be honest with you,
a Tenkaichi Tournament that doesn't
have you folks participating in it
is the very definition of boring.
The level drops so low, so low...
Is everyone else here friends of yours?
I suppose so.
Wow, that's great, that's great.
You there, please don't destroy
the arena like you did before, okay?
We'll see.
This is getting exciting!
This Tenkaichi Tournament
is going to be incredible!
Incidentally, this has been
bothering me for a little while now,
but what is that ring over your head?
Oh, I died. It happened
during the fight with Cell.
I've come here specially from
the Next World just for today.
Okay, okay!
That is strange, but with
you guys, anything is possible.
Whether you're dead or whether
you're alive, it's fine with me.
So there are people who
know how great Father was!
Knowing you guys, you'll smash your
way through the preliminary round for sure!
Okay, I'll see you in the ring!
I'm counting on you for some good matches!
Any of you kids who want
my autograph, line up, line up!
The first fifty of you who get here will
get them for free, as my present to you!
Ah, it's Satan!
Satan! Satan! Satan!
They say that death is the only cure for idiocy,
but he'll probably be the
same even after he dies, huh?
If I can get his sunglasses off,
I can find out his true identity...!
Come on, let's go.
Damn... And I was so close, too...
To those of you who are assembled,
we will now begin the preliminary
round for the Tenkaichi Tournament.
The total number of entrants in this tournament
is 194, not including the Junior Division.
Of those, only the 16 contestants that
win their way through the preliminary round
will be able to participate.
However, the champion, Mister Satan,
will be allowed to participate unconditionally,
so we will now select the
remaining 15 contestants.
What are we doing?
In order for the preliminary
round to be conducted fairly,
it will be held using a Punch Machine.
Those 15 who have the
highest Punch Machine scores
will pass the preliminary.
Punch Machine? What's that?
You're all mine!
Damn! And I was so close, too!
Now then, we will have
the champion, Mister Satan,
hit the Punch Machine to serve as reference,
and see what kind of value it returns.
And now, the champion,
Mister Satan, if you please!
Who among you will surpass me?!
There's plenty of guys here that surpass you.
Over here!
Big Brother...
Pick me up.
This time, for sure...
I did it! I may not have been
able to tell with my naked eyes,
but the camera is sure to
have captured his uncovered face!
I, Shapner-sama, will reveal the
true identity of the Great Saiyaman!
Come on, don't be shy! Take all
the pictures you want, I don't mind!
How long is he going to act so cocky?
M-My camera! And after
I managed to shoot him, too!
Piccolo-san...
I've destroyed all the cameras,
including the ones the spectators have.
Now, even if your disguise
does come off by some chance,
you won't be found out
by anyone at your school.
You can fight without
having to worry about that.
Thanks, Piccolo-san.
What's this? What's going on?
I guess I've got no choice
but to do this without any press.
Th-There it is! 137! 137 points!
That's my Papa!
Okay, everyone, good luck!
I'll be waiting for a
contestant that I can take seriously!
All right then, will all contestants
please take a numbered ticket
and line up in front of the Punch Machine.
Also, all of the kids who will be participating
in the Junior Division, please gather over here.
Well, well, at that rate, Satan
is going to win again this time.
Good luck, kids.
I wonder if Tenshinhan and them are coming.
Probably not.
He did say that it's unlikely
we'd ever see each other again.
Number 6, 97 points.
Number 16, 77 points.
Videl, good luck.
Videl, make sure you win.
Whoa, there's an amazing score!
Number 86, 112 points!
Sheesh, this is nonsense.
Okay, next is number 84.
Hey, look, it's a woman!
And she's a fine woman, isn't she?
Whew, I'd sure like to fight her!
Hey, don't put too much power into it, now.
You'll break the machine.
I know!
S-S-Seven hundred seventy-four?!
I'm sorry, but there appears
to have been a malfunction.
Please wait a moment.
This is why I told you not to overdo it!
Hush, would you? It's hard to hold back!
I-It appears to be fixed now, so once again...
203 points...
Number 85, 192 points...
Number 86, 186 points...
Number 87, 210 points.
Th-This thing appears to be
completely busted, all right.
Let's get a new Punch Machine ready.
Right.
Get back.
You're kidding...!
Ah, there's just no helping him.
Vegeta doesn't know how to hold back.
Even Videl is left speechless
by such overwhelming power.
Goku and the others have all
passed the preliminary round easily.
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
The kids' matches have begun.
Aw, geez, ignorance can be scary!
Trunks' opponent has
started to give him a hard time.
This guy is being so lame.
He's such an annoying dweeb.
Maybe, just for a little bit,
I won't hold back on him.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"No Small Matter!! Little Trunks."
No, no, don't draw any attention, Trunks!
"Next time"
"No Small Matter!! Little Trunks"