Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
In order to rescue Gohan,
who had been kidnapped by Raditz,
Goku and Piccolo took off after them together.
However, in the face of the
overwhelming power of Raditz,
Goku and Piccolo had to take on a
battle more difficult than any other before.
Why don't I let you in on
something good before you die?
The other two Saiyans have a
battle power even higher than mine!
"Piccolo's Trump Card!
Gohan, the Crybaby-kun."
D-Dammit! You say the other
two Saiyans are even stronger?!
W-What's going on here?
It's too late for you now, even if you
do realize how terrible we Saiyans are!
You've got us there.
I wish we hadn't heard that.
There's only one thing that fools,
who defy me without heeding the
warnings I so graciously offered, get...
...and that's death.
You must be pretty excited, huh, Son Goku?
Sorry, but this time, I ain't all that excited.
I'm so scared, I'm trembling!
Of course you are! However, that
terror will turn to hopelessness very soon.
Never mind me, where is my son?!
Where have you hidden him?!
I haven't hidden him. I just locked him
up because he was bawling so loudly.
There's a hole behind
you, right? He's in there.
In there, huh?
Gohan...
Father! Save me, Father!
Hold on, Gohan! Daddy's going
to come rescue you right away!
Don't be ridiculous!
There's no way you can save him!
Not if you guys die first!
All right, let's do it!
That's all we can do!
Behind me!
Yikes!
Where did you go?!
I'm right here.
Even with both of you coming at me,
this isn't even worth wasting my breath on!
Damn... Are you okay, Piccolo?
R-Relax. I can still manage
to fight with o-only one arm.
It looks like your deaths
are finally drawing near, huh?!
I-I wonder if Goku is doing okay.
For some reason, I have this
strange, uneasy feeling in my chest.
I've never felt anything like this before.
I hope nothing bad is happening.
Listen, teamed up with Piccolo,
he's not going to be done in so easily.
That's all the more reason to be concerned!
What if Piccolo double-crosses Goku,
and teams up with that Raditz guy?
If those two are done in, then
there's nothing left that we can do.
It will be the end of everything!
Goku...
What's the matter?
Are you finished already?
Where did all that gusto you had earlier go?
Hey, Son Goku, do you have
any new reserve techniques?
Sorry, can't say I do.
Sheesh, ease up, will you?
And here I've been training
seriously, developing something new.
What are you two whispering about?
Whatever strategy you devise, it won't work!
It'd be easier on you if
you'd just keel over right away.
Are you for real? You've got
yourself a new technique up your sleeve?
Yeah.
Can you do it with only one arm?
Yeah, that part's okay.
But this technique takes quite a bit
of time in order to build up enough ki.
While I'm doing that, you fight him
by yourself, and draw his attention.
Got it! Will this technique work against him?
Probably. If this doesn't work,
then there's no other way to defeat him.
I was saving this in order to kill you.
And instead, you might
end up saving me with it, huh?
If I am able to defeat him
with this, then your turn is next.
Is that right?
This is no time to be laughing, you know.
They're laughing... So they're
changing their posture, are they?
All right, I'm looking forward to this!
Now then, let's see
about keeping him in check!
Hang in there as best you can!
Makankosappo!
So, you've finally resigned yourself?
You're a persistent one!
Ka...
me...
I-Impossible!
His battle power is rising!
Battle power 924... 925!
ha...
He's able to concentrate his battle
power into one point and raise it up?!
me...
T-This one's battle power
is now 1,020! U-Unbelievable!
It's still going up!
Ha!
You've got a lot of nerve!
He caught it!
W-What kind of guy is this?
This time, I'll present you with one!
Die!
You're going to be the one who dies!
Battle power 1,330?!
A-All of his battle power is
gathered into just his fingertip!
Dammit! These guys can
manipulate their powers at will!
Try taking this on! Makankosappo!
H-He avoided it! W-What kind
of bastard is he, with such speed?
You pierced through this armor quite easily.
That's quite a technique.
If I had taken that head-on,
I would have been out!
That doesn't mean anything if I don't hit you!
To think that you would inflict injury upon me!
You're going to pay for this!
I'm through playing around!
W-We've had it now!
I'll obliterate you in an instant!
Rot in hell!
You got careless, didn't you?!
I've got your tail!
Why, you... when did you get behind me?!
Piccolo! Now! Do that thing one more time!
Y-You got it!
Nicely done, Goku!
Keep a firm grip on that tail!
I'm limited to only being able
to use this technique one more time.
K-Kakarrot! Are you planning
to kill your one and only brother?!
Shut up! I told you, any guy as cruel
as you are ain't any brother of mine!
As someone who was going to kill my son,
don't you go saying that self-serving junk!
I-I'll stop! I've had a change of heart!
I'll leave this planet without
making any more trouble!
Don't be fooled, Son Goku!
There's no truth in what he's saying!
There's no way he would do that!
P-Please! Believe me, my younger brother!
Truly, I have done
some cruel things up to now!
To you, as well... But I will
keep my promise, no matter what!
Y-You really mean it?
I-I really do!
N-No! Don't let go of
his tail! That's his tactic!
I'm begging you, Kakarrot! B-Believe me!
Son Goku!
Y-You miserable idiot!
Indeed! Fools such as
yourself are quite uncommon!
To think that you would
be so completely taken in!
Just as I thought, there's no
way that you could be a warrior!
T-That was dirty!
But I'm not like you.
I'm a first-rate warrior!
I have absolutely no hesitations about
killing you, even if you are my brother!
Shall I provide you with a sample?
Father...
There you go, there you go!
Suffer even more! Your death is near!
What's the matter?
Aren't you going to come at me?
Try doing that thing you did earlier!
H-He'll just dodge it again like this!
Father...
That Gohan! I told him that
once he gets his tests back,
he should show them to me.
Still, you've done very well, Gohan.
Sure enough, it's worth it for him to
be studyin' every day for eight hours.
Once I show this to Goku,
I'm sure he'll say the same thing.
I sure wish Goku and Gohan
would both get back soon.
Scream some more! Cry out!
Your turn comes next!
Get yourself ready!
Well now, shall I finally
put you out of your misery?
Die, Kakarrot!
W-What?
What?!
With his father in a great pinch,
Son Gohan instinctively springs forth!
Though his body may be small,
his anger is something fierce!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Gohan, don't go near him!
I'll hit him with my Makankosappo again!
Kuririn, this dying
stuff is pretty nasty, ain't it?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Goku Dies!
There's Only One Last Chance."
Stop picking on my father!
"Next time"
"Goku Dies!
There's Only One Last Chance"