The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
The long-awaited Tenkaichi
Tournament has begun.
The Dragon Warriors easily made
their way through the preliminaries.
And, in the Junior Division,
Trunks eventually took the stage.
Bring it on, you little turd! Come on!
You talk too much. I don't
need you to tell me what to do.
Hmph. Maybe I got a little too serious there.
Guess I'm still a kid, too.
He's unconscious!
Trunks-kun wins!
Trunks easily wins and moves on.
Next is Goten's turn.
"It's My Turn!
Goten's Anxious First Fight."
The battle amongst the youngsters
showing off their skills continues.
So then, let's continue!
We have come to the 16th round.
Ikose-kun, age 14, versus Son Goten-kun, age 7.
"Martial"
This little kid?
Goten's making his entrance.
Can't wait to see what kind of match he has.
Ikose-chan, don't drop your
guard like your brother did!
Goten-chan! Be sure you go rough on him!
Another brat from the vulgar brigade?
To think another one of you
against my genteel, other son.
Intolerable! Intolerable, I say!
Oh, my! Here I was thinking,
there's another idiot-faced
hillbilly making an appearance,
and it turns out to be his brother?
Indeed!
There isn't going to be
a second miracle here today!
I hope your little brat meets a horrible fate!
Wow! So many people here to watch!
He's overcome by how many
spectators are watching him.
Hmm? That face... "Son Goten"...
I-I won, man!
I see. It's Son Goku's son!
Unmistakable! He's identical
to him when he was little.
Now then, begin the match!
Hang in there, Goten! Just take it easy!
Ikose-chan, boom boom,
knock him down! Boom boom!
Sounds like Goten-kun's match has started!
Yeah, so it seems.
If we don't finish up our preliminary
soon, we won't be able to see him.
Ready yet?
Sorry, the new Punch
Machine still needs tuning...
Hey, kid! Your friend's match is beginning!
Aren't you going to watch?
I don't have to watch to know what will happen.
Oh?
Hey, let's go watch!
A little kid like you
shouldn't have come out here!
Take this! Assassin Punch!
Hey, do it for real. As hard as you can.
So, seems you are somewhat capable.
Ikose-chan is really into it at last!
But how many seconds will that hillbilly kid last?
Ikose-chan! Win! Puh-leeze!
Smash that little brat for your Mama's sake!
That's all, huh?
Fair enough.
Incredible! He knocked him out in one punch!
He did it! He did it!
Of course he did.
H-Hey! Ikose-kun! Ikose-kun!
He's unconscious... Son Goten-kun wins!
I won't allow this any longer!
There, things've quieted down now.
Awesome! Your friend beat him with one punch!
Didn't I say? I knew what
would happen without watching.
Y-Yeah.
Hey, looks like the seven-year-old kid won!
Sounds like Goten-kun won!
That's amazing, right, against a 14-year-old?
Yeah.
It's only natural.
What, aren't you happy?
Eh? Sure I'm happy. Yeah, he won!
The matches continued...
Goten-kun wins!
He did it! He did it!
Now!
Trunks-kun wins!
He did it!
Goten and Trunks quickly
advance, until as expected,
they face each other in the final round.
And so, it's nearly time for the final round!
Our contestants for the final are...
Trunks-kun, age 8, and Goten-kun, age 7.
This fight is mine!
You expect me to lose?
And so, it's nearly time for
the Junior Division final round!
Will the victor be Trunks-kun?
Or will it be Son Goten-kun?
Good luck, Trunks!
Goten-chan! Win and get
us a big wad of prize money!
Don't either one of ya lose, now!
Finally, we'll get to see an entertaining match!
Yeah.
Both contestants have fought their
way here with overpowering strength!
And what's more, both of them are good friends!
The final round is about to begin!
Um, is it ready? We're in a hurry here!
Oh, we've just now got it working!
Really? Well then, if I may...
No taking cuts!
–Wait your turn!
–Yeah!
Uh, but I...
No way! Return to your place in line!
Uh, now, hold on...
We're in a hurry!
No, ma'am. It's the rules.
The match is going to be over!
Hang tough, little guy!
Give us a good fight!
Fight! Fight!
Mister Satan! Mister Satan!
Oh, were you resting?
N-No, no.
I was unifying myself mentally before the match.
One of the harder things to do,
once you become the champion,
is to keep yourself in
tip-top condition at all times,
as is expected of you during the match!
The Junior Division final
is about to get underway,
and there are two very
strong children competing.
Would the champion care to watch the match?
I think it will be a very entertaining bout.
Very well, what else can I do?
I'll watch their match for a bit.
After all, I have to take on
whichever one of these youngsters wins.
We apologize for the delay.
We would now like to present the
Tenkaichi Tournament Junior Division Final!
I'm telling you now,
I won't be pulling any punches, Goten.
Yeah, me neither!
Those two?
Yes, that's correct. They say they're 7 and 8.
Those kids did well to get this far.
That kid–I have this feeling like
we've met, but we haven't met...
Hmm, I can't quite place it.
Goten!
Trunks!
Keep your composure, Trunks! Goten!
Oh, incredible!
They've started!
Wait, Gohan-kun!
Whew, sorry to keep you waiting!
We finally finished our preliminary!
You're awful late.
We thought that maybe
you two were off on a date!
That's not true! It wasn't like that!
It's okay, it's okay!
Thank goodness you made
it in time. This is a good part.
Nice going, both of you!
That's cold!
That's the way! Goten! Trunks!
Goten-chan!
Goten! Go!
–Trunks! What are you doing?!
–Hang in there!
All right! All right! Goten-chan!
Trunks!
Go! Go! Trunks!
Goten!
W-What is the story with them?
This is a fight between an
eight-year-old and a seven-year-old?
Lil' Trunks and Goten are both
pretty good at this, ain't they?
Aren't they, though?
Way to go, way to go, Trunks, Goten!
A-Awesome!
The fight between the
promising Trunks and Goten...
Which will be the one decorated as victor of
the Tenkaichi Tournament Junior Division?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Goten, Trunks, not bad, both of you!
Just what you'd expect from Saiyan kids.
Goten, I think it's about time
to end this. Brace yourself.
I am going to be victorious.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Happiness Times A Million!
The Junior Champion is Decided!!"
Aw, I told you both, don't turn Super Saiyan!
"Next time"
"Happiness Times A Million!
The Junior Champion is Decided!!"