Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Priding himself on his overwhelming strength,
Freeza fights toe-to-toe against Piccolo.
Following Freeza's momentary advance,
Piccolo takes the offensive,
and lands some well-placed punches.
Why, you...
"Attack, Goku!! An Enraged
Freeza's Second Transformation."
Incredible! He's holding his own against Freeza!
No, he's doing better!
You really are incredible, Piccolo-san!
Just what the hell has happened?
It hasn't been that long
since he was defeated on Earth!
We might actually be able to get
out of this without dying, Gohan!
Right!
Beat that Freeza, who killed so many of us,
using the power of Nail-san!
What kind of training has Piccolo undergone?
That's the way, stick
with him until I get better!
Kaio-sama, with Piccolo
powered-up as much as he is,
can he defeat Freeza?
If he doesn't beat him for us, we're screwed!
So fast! And I should
have the advantage of speed!
Kuririn-san...
How can this be?
You mean, he hasn't been
taking this seriously up until now?
What's the best step for me to take now?
What should I do?
Damn you for making us rejoice prematurely!
Nail-san...
Piccolo! What kind of guy is this Freeza?!
Piccolo...
Kaio-sama?
I told you, they have touched
that which should not be touched...
–Piccolo...
Sorry about that just now.
I didn't give you enough credit.
But you are capable of more than I imagined.
I decided to show you some true power.
Which is to say, my true power.
There's no end to his power!
Was I really planning to fight against him?
So will I. Let's make this genuine.
What's that?
You're saying you haven't
been serious up until now?
I didn't realize that
Namekians told fish stories.
You'll find out very soon.
You worthless fool!
To have to resort to bluffing at this stage...
I-I get it!
Piccolo's been fighting with that
heavy turban and mantle on all this time?
Now realize the fury of all the
Namekians who were killed by you!!
Piccolo's ki is getting stronger again.
This strength is the real thing!
He can win! Piccolo-san can win!
Piccolo! We're counting on you!
The situation has changed again!
You've removed those heavy
garments and made yourself lighter...
which is supposed to mean your
speed has become even more polished?
We'll have to see.
It will take more than this to
satisfy the fury of the Namekians!
He did it!
Gohan!
Kuririn-san!
Nail-san!
Nice going, Piccolo-san!
That's the way!
At this rate, Kakarrot may still be in time.
In which case, I may get out of this alive!
And now to finish you off!
Has Freeza?
You don't suppose?
Look there!
As tenacious as I expected.
You seem to be laboring under some
false impression concerning my true power.
What?!
Did you really think that what
I just showed you was serious?
You couldn't have known I'd
transformed myself, could you?
Transformed, you say?
I will allow you the same thing
I gave to Vegeta and the others–
A feeling of absolute terror towards me.
All right, first I will
instill a sense of hopelessness.
A hopelessness from knowing that
nothing you can possibly do will help!!
Every time I, Freeza, transform
myself, my power substantially grows!
And I still have two more
transformations remaining!
Do you know what that means?
What's this?
Impossible!
Gohan, what did he just say?
Freeza can transform two more times.
Now getting married is completely out.
So then, let me show it to you.
You guys should feel honored.
You're the first ones I've ever
shown this transformation to!
Watch carefully now!
Here comes Freeza-sama's
second-stage transformation!
I apologize for the delay.
Now then, shall we begin the battle once again?
Y-You monster!
H-He hasn't changed all that much, has he?
Idiot! Try probing what his latent power is!
It's completely different from a moment ago!
Yet he's settled down again, and
he's regained his presence of mind!
He's also lost the damage that
Piccolo-san had inflicted on him!
Damn it all! What's going on out there?
That ki of Freeza's has gotten stronger again!
At this point, even once I completely recover,
I might not be able to beat him. Now what?
Freeza is a super-monster beyond imagination!
You had such confidence in
your speed earlier, did you not?
So then, shall we have another look at it?
You bastard! If you've got
the power, I've got the speed!
You won't catch up to me in this lifetime!
I-It can't be!
My goodness, it has been
too long, my little toddler.
Piccolo-san has lost his
speed advantage over Freeza!
Does that mean Freeza's
power has gone up that much?
Don't lose, Nail-san!
Thank goodness, you aren't dead!
I'll heal you right away!
That's right!
There's still that trick!
It's all over now, isn't it?
Piccolo...
Shall we put an end to this play, then?
D-Damn...
You have realized that, unfortunately
enough, the speed you took such pride in
is of utterly no use
against me now, have you not?
I would have you give up now!
S-So fast!
Piccolo-san!
They're impossibly fast!
There's no way he can dodge them!
Piccolo-san...
Piccolo!
Stop it!
Gohan!
Gohan! Dammit!
Wait!
What are you doing, Vegeta?!
There's no sense for you to go!
B-But if I don't...
Listen here, at this rate, we're
all going to be killed by Freeza!
Never mind him, you blast me half-to-death!
Do it now!
Once I get that kid to heal me,
and rise from a near-death state one more time,
I'm certain to be able to become a Super Saiyan!
Having transformed a second time,
Freeza has become even more powered-up.
Piccolo faces a great pinch, as Gohan
leaps to his aid. How will this turn out?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Regardless of how strong Gohan
has become, it's no use against Freeza!
When we Saiyans recover after
coming one step away from death,
our strength increases! Now, hurry!
Before Freeza makes his final transformation,
you must render me half-dead!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Fear Me!! Freeza Does Battle
with a Third Transformation."
I've had it. And I hit him
with all the power I had, too.
"Next time"
"Fear Me!! Freeza Does Battle
with a Third Transformation"