Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Following a difficult battle,
Goku advanced his way into the
semifinals of the Anoyoichi Tournament,
where he took in the spectacular
battle between Paikuhan and Olivue,
which stoked his fighting spirit even higher.
C-Contestant Paikuhan wins!
T-To think that I could fight
against someone that strong...!
"Final Round of Flame!!
Goku or Paikuhan!?"
Go get him, Goku! Shock
him with a good hard slam!
Malaiko! No need to hold back!
With your power, that
guy will be a piece of cake!
Ah, that newcomer even
made it into the semifinals!
Yeah. But it could be too
much for even him this time.
Nah, you never know.
He could just be the first
person from the North Galaxy
to receive training from Grand Kaio-sama.
You can't mean that.
We will now begin the first
match of the semifinal round
of the Kaio of the North Dying
Commemorative Anoyoichi Tournament!
Contestant Malaiko,
Contestant Goku, please begin!
He's dodging everything
by just a hairsbreadth.
Oh, dear! Contestant Goku has
been knocked high into the air!
After being sent flying
like this... Ah, watch out!
...can he still be all right?!
All right! This is how I'll finish the match!
W-What?!
Malaiko!
Goku!
Here it goes!
Take this!
Where could Contestant Malaiko have gone?!
There you are!
C-Contestant Malaiko is out of bounds!
Contestant Son Goku
advances to the final round!
Goku! Well done! That was great!
That kid definitely has a lot
more power than when we first met.
Don't tell me he's advanced
that much in this short a time...
Thank you!
I look forward to this.
S-So, Goku has advanced to the final round.
The victory is well within his reach now.
You fool!
What?!
Get yourself all worked up now, while you can,
you hardheaded old dimwit.
W-What?!
Listen, your kid might have
been lucky enough to win this time,
but in the final round, he's going to
have to fight against my galaxy's Paikuhan!
There's no way he can win!
That's not so. It's only
natural that Goku is going to win.
I know well just how strong he is.
What are you talking about?!
The winner is going to be Paikuhan!
Goku!
Paikuhan!
–Goku! Goku! Goku!
–Paikuhan! Paikuhan! Paikuhan!
If you're willing to go
that far, shall we bet on it?
Bet on it?
If, by some slim chance that Paikuhan loses,
I will give you my West Kaio's World.
What? Your Kaio's World?
Yeah. And, if Goku loses,
what will you do? Hmm?
A-All right, I'll give you
my North Kaio's World...
Huh? It's not there anymore, is it?
W-What will you do?
W-Well, that is, I...
So that's it, you don't have
enough confidence, do you?
T-That's ridiculous!
A-All right, if Goku loses, I'll become
your servant, or whatever you want.
That's rich! All right, if Goku
loses, then for as long as you live...
...but then again, you've already died...
but anyhow, you'll be my servant. Okay?
Of course! A Kaio doesn't go back on his word!
That was a good match!
Thank you. But you know...
But? But what?
What was that just now?!
That was the sound of my stomach.
Terrific! That's just like you, Goku-chan!
I just asked to have a big
spread be put together over there.
All right! I'm saved!
Grand Kaio-sama!
Just a minute!
What is it, Kaio of the North?
This is no time to be eating.
Are you sure you don't want
to watch Paikuhan's next match?
Moving on to the next match...
Contestant Tolbee versus...
Contestant Paikuhan!
It's okay, it's okay.
Okay...? You mean it?
What an insolent kid!
After all, I already know who's going to win.
You say you already know?
How in the world...?
Never mind that, let's eat! Let's eat!
Wow! I'll help myself!
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
Come on! What's with this shoddy running?!
For crying out loud, not one of
you made it through to the semifinals!
Now I've got mud smeared on my face!
If you keep running this lethargically,
I'll increase your
punishment a hundredfold!
What were you guys thinking, for pity's sake?!
Okay.
Paikuhan is the winner!
A-And so, the time for
the final round has arrived!
In the final round,
representing the West Galaxy,
Contestant Paikuhan!
Facing him will be,
representing the North Galaxy,
Contestant Son Goku!
Contestant Son Goku, if you are
present, please enter the ring at once!
No more helpings! Is this
any time to be taking it so easy?!
It's the final round! You're on!
What's this? Contestant Son Goku was eating!
For the love of... he's
trying to make fools of us!
Just a second! I ain't
finished yet! I ain't finished!
Is he sure of himself, or is he just plain stupid?
Fight! Fight! Fight! Fight!
Come on! Come on! Come on! Come on!
It looks like the final round is beginning.
You guys keep going!
If you slack off, you'll answer to me!
Go, go, West! Go, go, Paikuhan!
"West"
Very well then, please begin!
W-Why ain't you dodging me?
So that's it.
You're saying you don't even
need to dodge my punches, huh?
Still, I wasn't going at
you seriously just now, either.
I doubt you were!
All right...!
Paikuhan! You'll fall out of the ring! Be careful!
Goku! Get him once and for all!
Not too bad.
Is that the extent of your power, Goku?
What?
If so, I'll start going at you, as well!
I can't push him back!
T-That's impossible!
You're better than I thought, Goku.
That goes double for me.
I'm so happy, I'm all keyed up!
Oh, my!
Paikuhan has started to take off his gown!
What exactly could he be up to?!
I-Is this...?
I get it. So you were only
warming up just now, were you?
There's something about
you that's a lot like Piccolo.
Piccolo?
Yeah. He's a martial artist that got
me all worked up too, like you have.
You're pretty good.
In that case, me too...
Okay, let's hurry up and get going again.
I-Incredibly, Paikuhan
was not using his true power.
And neither was Goku!
The true power of both Goku, having
become a Super Saiyan, and Paikuhan...
Which one of them will be victorious?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Damn, Paikuhan's attacks
are too fast for me to see.
He can also evade my Kamehame-Ha,
even head-on! What do I do?
Goku, what are you doing?
If you don't win, I'm ruined!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Don't Let Victory Get Away!!
Finish With an Ultra-Fast Kamehame-Ha."
When it comes to guts, Father definitely wins!
"Next time"
"Don't Let Victory Get Away!!
Finish With an Ultra-Fast Kamehame-Ha"