Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
In the Other World, Goku runs himself
all-out in order to meet with Kaio-sama.
Elsewhere, Gohan was enduring some
harsh trials in the middle of the high plains.
And, deep in space, the Saiyans
were steadily approaching ever closer
as they headed toward Earth.
"The Saiyans, Mightiest
Warriors in the Universe, Awaken!"
All right, then!
What, you again?
You never learn, do you?
Over here!
Well then, I'll be
taking some meat again!
Your tail is going to disappear before long.
Looks like you've gotten a little bit better.
Wow, to think that Kami-sama
is going to be training us!
Damn, I'm just itching all over!
Take it easy, take it easy.
In any case, we have to
find Tenshinhan and Chaozu.
Those two are going to be so surprised!
Yamucha-sama, after you and everyone
else have Kami-sama make you stronger,
those Saiyans will be nothing to you!
That's for sure! If you're
coming, then bring it on, Saiyans!
Wake up, Nappa! Wake up!
Open your eyes, Nappa!
Have we arrived at Earth already?
No, not yet. I thought we might stop
off on the way, and set my wake-up timer.
Stop off somewhere, you say?
There's a pretty good planet
ahead of us. We can sell it for a lot!
Understood.
Sleeping for one year straight gets
you all out of form, so this will be perfect!
W-What is this?
You're sure we can sell a
place like this for a high price?
In any event...
...it looks like we'll need to inspect
this place a little more thoroughly.
What ugly creatures those are!
They look like they're space men.
To think that we would come
across space men on our hunt!
I'm sure that Moai-sama will be pleased!
Moai?
This planet's king! Our ruler!
You've come all the way from
outer space. Stay here for a while!
This will be interesting!
Stop, Nappa.
This could be an opportunity.
Let's let them introduce us to this Moai.
Here...
Don't scare us like that!
Freeze, you bank robber!
You're under arrest!
What pests!
This money is a present for Ten-san!
You guys stay out of it!
Just you wait, Tenshinhan!
I'll feed you all kinds of
nutritious things with this money!
Behave yourselves for a
little while now, space men.
It looks like quite an
enjoyable little planet, huh?
I-It's true! You're space men!
I've never seen any before!
Never mind, he's now finally
started reaching out after space men.
How far is he going
to go before he's satisfied?
You have come to this planet at a bad time.
Ever since Moai has claimed
the throne, things have been crazy.
Everyone in the general
population has become Moai's toys!
And as for me, I had my wife
stolen from me on our wedding day!
Do you understand how I feel?
Oh, my adorable Lemuria!
What's the matter, Lemuria?
Nothing special...
Don't tell me you're still
thinking about that other man.
Please, stop! Spare me!
L-Let me out!
I beg you! P-Please, I beg you!
D-Don't eat me!
Please! I-I don't want to die!
I'm bored.
What? You say you've
captured some space men?
Yes.
Interesting. Bring them here.
If they're cute, I'll make them my pets.
What is this?
C-Could they be the ones?
I-It's them! How did
they get out of the prison?
I-Incredible...
W-What power those guys have!
What ugly creatures! There's
no way I can keep them as pets.
Right, Lemuria?
Hey, space men! How would
you like to make a wager with me?
Wager?
Have a go at fighting against my warriors.
If you win, I'll give you anything you like.
Although, no matter how you look at it,
there's no chance of you beating them.
I'd like to see what kind of
blood is spilled by space men. Go!
W-What? What the hell's going on here?
You said you'd give us
anything we liked, right?
In that case...
...we'll take this planet!
What?!
Didn't you hear him? We're
taking this planet, and your lives!
I-Impossible!
Don't you get it yet? We let
ourselves be captured on purpose.
In order for us to be led in here, you see.
Kill them! Cut them to bits!
Ain't I at Kaio-sama's place yet?!
Yedi! Release Yedi!
So this monster is your ace in the hole, huh?
Let them have it, Yedi! Kill those two!
May I?
Suit yourself.
Fool! You intend to test
your strength against Yedi's?!
Y-Yedi!
I'm done playing around!
W-What's this?
I-Incredible! You guys are incredible!
You are indeed the
saviors of this planet!
Peace is sure to return to this
planet now, just as it was before!
Atla!
L-Lemuria?
This is hopeless. We won't be
able to get squat for this planet.
Let's go, Nappa.
Atla!
Get out of my sight,
you good-for-nothing planet!
Lemuria!
Atla!
They're beautiful when they're obliterated,
no matter what planet they happen to be.
Still, I hope this Earth turns out to be
a little bit better of a planet than this.
Hey, if it turns out to be
another good-for-nothing planet,
we'll just blow it away too.
After we've gathered those
Dragon Ball things, that is.
Eternal life, huh?
I'm looking forward to that!
Such terrible, heartless Saiyans!
Is there any future for Earth?
Elsewhere, Goku single-mindedly
continues to run in order to meet Kaio-sama.
This sure is long!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Whew! Even after all this
running, I'm only halfway to halfway?
What's more, that's hell
beneath those clouds. I'm exhausted!
Don't go soft on us, Son Goku!
The Saiyans are already so close!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Catnap on the Serpentine Road –
Goku Takes a Tumble."
Father, I'm not afraid to sleep by myself now.
"Next time"
"Catnap on the Serpentine Road–
Goku Takes a Tumble"