Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Unless you show your true power soon,
nothing else is going to mend matters.
No. 16...
S-Son Gohan...
Set your spirit free to your
anger. I know how it feels.
You just can't take it any longer.
Nature, and the animals that I, too, liked...
D-Defend them for me...
I'm counting on you...
Nobody asked you, you factory defect!
Goku had been waiting for this moment.
At last, Gohan's fury has erupted!
"Devastating True Power!!
The Cell Juniors Pulverized."
W-What?!
I-Is that...?
Gohan's ki is rising!
Gohan...!
Good, Gohan.
Is that the extent of it?
You've committed the same
mistake that Trunks there did.
You cannot beat me
just by raising your power.
Stop it.
Stop it!!
I told you to stop it!
Th-That's it! That will do nicely!
Y-You've changed...!
They're monsters, all of them!
Chichi!
I'm not going to put up with you anymore.
So you've finally shown
your true power, have you?
Now things are beginning to get interesting.
Impossible...!
You took the senzu...?
Why you...!
We've been having all this
trouble fighting these runts,
and he kills one in a single blow...!
I-Incredible...!
That was incredible, Gohan-san!
I knew it!
G-Gohan...!
W-What?!
H-He's fast!
What speed! It's equal to Cell's...
No, it might even be greater!
Gohan, don't mind me.
Blow these guys away!
Do it, Gohan!
U-Unbelievable... How can this be?
What? What's goin' on?
C-Chichi? Have you come to?
Pa, where's Gohan?
What's happenin' with my Gohan-chan?
He's fightin'.
Just as he was fightin'
magnificently, the picture went out.
My little child is still fightin'?
What do you mean, magnificent?
You gotta be kiddin'!
I'm goin' to let Goku-sa have it good!
Shut up, Chichi!
Gohan is no child! Right now,
he has surpassed Goku,
and has become a magnificent
warrior, who's defendin' the Earth!
Your husband and son are fightin'
for peace in this world for everyone!
Why can't you understand that?!
For my part, I'd wanna
be fightin' too, ordinarily.
But right now, Gohan's the
only one who can defeat Cell!
Okay? Understand, would you?
Just be quiet and pray for Gohan's safety.
That's all there is, huh?
That's all you've got to say?!
C-Chichi...
Why, you... Pa...
You're too permissive!
You're the one who
doesn't understand nothin', Pa!
Even if he does save the Earth,
he won't get into a good school!
He'll never be a decent scholar!
Even if he does beat Cell,
he'll lose when competin'
with the rest of the world!
H-Hold on, Chichi! C-Calm down!
Shut up!
What's so magnificent about Gohan,
now that he's gone delinquent?!
Goku-sa, you idiot!
Give me back my Gohan-chan!
So that's it, huh?
That's the power of his anger? Fine, then.
Let's have a good long look at it.
I-I'm not the center of attention...
This is ridiculous.
The video I set up to record will be worthless.
Should this get out to the
rest of the world? No, it must not!
H-He can beat him...
He just might be able to beat him...!
People of the world, this is a surprise!
That young boy is fighting
effectively against those miniature Cells!
Make sure you're getting all of this!
It's impossible. Not with this.
What?! This is the scoop of the century!
You're a pro, fix it somehow!
He blew away those Cell Juniors with
nothing more than a blast of his Kiai...!
A-And what's more, even after
displaying that level of fighting,
he's not the least bit winded!
Are you all right, Son?!
What do you think, Piccolo?
Just like I said, right?
Gohan...
I told you, there's no way
I'm putting up with you anymore!
Let yourself get carried away, will you...?!
There's no longer any
irresolution or hesitation within him.
His anger is governing his emotions.
He is the mightiest warrior.
That's what you get, Cell! You blew it!
Give these to everyone.
Right.
Gohan is displaying overwhelming strength.
However, Cell is still concealing
the depth of his power.
Will the victor end up being Cell or Gohan?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
It don't matter how much
you raise your power now.
Cell, you ain't no match for Gohan!
I-Impossible! How could
I have taken this much damage...
from just two punches?!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Cell gets KO'ed!!
Just 2 Super Ironfisted Blows."
Here it comes, Cell! This will
show you the pain you've caused!
"Next time"
"Cell gets KO'ed!!
Just 2 Super Ironfisted Blows"