Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Kuririn!
Kakarrot, I'll be taking the child.
If you want him returned alive,
you'll listen to what
your brother tells you to do!
So strong! Raditz is exceedingly strong!
Gohan's life is in the hands
of Raditz, Goku's older brother.
Can Goku solve this problem in
any way other than the unthinkable?
"All Right! This is the
Strongest Combo in the World!"
You got that? Let me
say it again just to be sure.
You are to kill a hundred
of this planet's people
and pile up their bodies here by tomorrow.
If you do, we will let you join our group.
And of course,
if there are no bodies here,
it will mean the death of your son.
Father!
T-That's gutless of you!
How can you use a child like that?!
–Yeah!
–He's right!
For one thing, there's no
way Goku could kill anyone!
That's fine.
If you don't mind letting this one die,
then there's no need
to have those bodies ready.
However,
one way or another, every person
on this planet is destined to die soon.
Once we finish subjugating
our current planet,
we've decided that our
next target will be this one!
Y-You what?
The three of us Saiyans ought to be enough
to wipe out the folks
on this planet in only a month.
Kakarrot, if you're the one
who kills a hundred people for me,
it's all the same in the end, isn't it?
Father! Father!
You got that, Kakarrot?
Any way you try to struggle out of it,
the only thing for you to do
is to join your brother's pals.
Give me back my child!
I'll be expecting a good answer from you.
For your sake, as well.
You cannot consider going against me.
With your incomplete battle power,
you can't possibly stand up
to your older brother, after all!
Father!
See you later!
I look forward to tomorrow!
Gohan!
Father!
Damn it all! He made a mockery of me!
Are you okay, Son-kun?
W-We're sorry! There
was nothing we could do!
G-Goku?
Kinto-Un!
Wait! That's crazy! Don't be rash!
You can't! You'll be killed!
If you go now, do
you think you could win?!
Damn! What should I do?
Think.
Hold on, now...
What a shock, huh? Here you
discover that you have a relative,
and of all people,
it turns out to be that guy!
Your brother... does have
greater than normal strength, and all.
His tail...
If I...
If I squeeze his tail hard enough,
his strength should drop off.
That's how it was for me.
N-Now that you mention it, that's true!
B-But still, are you going
to be able to grab his tail?
It'll be impossible for me to do it alone.
We will do as much as we can!
Yamucha and Tenshinhan aren't here, after all.
T-That's right...
And if the three of us fight together,
it just might work...
Though I'm not very confident about that...
Bulma-san, if we die, please bring us
back to life with the Dragon Balls, okay?
Leave it to me!
Kuririn, that won't work.
Kami-sama said that you can't ask Shen
Long to grant the same wish a second time.
Kuririn, both you
and Old Timer Turtle Hermit
have already had Shen Long
bring you back to life once.
And so... we can't do it another time...
Oh... really?
E-Even so, n-no problem!
You'd help me out?
O-Of course we will!
You bet we will! This time,
it's our turn to lend you a hand, Goku!
T-This time for sure, I'm dead.
Damn... And I wanted to get married too...
Speaking of the Dragon
Balls, what if we did this?
Get all seven together, and
ask Shen Long to save the world!
Oh, yeah!
Do you think we could get
them all together in a single day?
Oh, yeah...
All right! We launch a
surprise attack of our own!
He wouldn't possibly think
that we would attack him,
so his guard should be down.
B-But we don't know where he is, right?
Bulma, do you have your
Dragon Radar with you?
That's right!
The ornament at the top of
Gohan-kun's hat was a Dragon Ball, huh?
That's it, that's it!
Look! It's moving at tremendous speed!
It stopped!
Thank goodness! He's not
out in space, he's on Earth!
All right, let's go! It's all
or nothing! Just hang on, Gohan!
R-Right! Maybe we can win this!
The possibility is slim, though...
If we're going to be killed either way,
we'll feel better if we've done all we can.
This is too much for you guys!
–Piccolo!
What are you doing here?
I followed him here.
You've already met him?
That's right.
If you go with those two,
you won't be able to defeat him.
I will go with you.
You must have realized that
his strength is extraordinary.
He's an opponent that
neither you nor I can stand up to.
However...
...if you and I team up, then
there is a slight possibility that we...
...can defeat him.
Just what the hell has come over you?
Don't get me wrong.
It's not as though I have
become awakened to peace.
I don't care what
happens to your son, either.
It's just that he stands in the way of
the world domination that I am after!
We'll team up, but once we've
taken care of him and his two pals,
I'm going to defeat you, and this time,
I intend to take over the world for sure!
I won't let you do that!
I won't let you do that, but up through that
part where we team up, that's a good idea.
Looks like there ain't any other way, huh?
That's right! We'll
just have to put up with it.
As far as I'm concerned, teaming
up with you makes me want to puke!
Bulma, let me borrow your Dragon Radar.
Right.
Can you keep up with the speed of Kinto-Un?
Don't be absurd! My own
technique's a little different
from that pathetic
Bukujutsu skill of yours.
I'm not sure whether
I should be elated or not...
You know, I would have never
thought that those two would team up!
There's certainly no
stronger combo than them!
It's just possible that they might win!
B-But I wonder, is it safe
for us to trust Piccolo?
It's worrisome, isn't it?
What are you talking about?! This
is going to be an incredible spectacle!
Bulma! Do you remember the location
that reading was coming from on the Radar?
We're going too!
I wonder if Gohan-chan is havin'
fun at Muten Roshi-sama's place.
Oh, my! He still hasn't finished doin'
his developmental homework, has he?
I hope he'll be all right.
Father, I'm scared!
Will you shut up?! How long
are you going to keep blubbering?!
You carry the valiant
blood of the Saiyans too!
Get in there!
Let me out! Let me out!
Let me out, I say!
Now then,
how about I go find something to eat?
That's strange. A warning signal...
A battle power of 710? It's close!
What?
Damn. A malfunction, huh?
Don't scare me like that.
We're close!
I think we'd better descend pretty soon.
That won't work!
We're better off going in like this.
He's using a strange device.
It appears to be able
to clearly tell the position
and even the strength of a target.
You mean the fact that
we're closing in on him, too?
It stands to reason that he knows.
Really? Well, that means that the only
thing we can do is attack him head-on!
Again!
Battle power 710.
Sure enough, it's malfunctioning.
There are two readings!
They're heading this way!
One... two...
Battle powers 322 and 334...
One of them is the same as Kakarrot's ability.
But there's no way he would be coming here.
He has to know that there's close
to zero probability of him winning...
And he doesn't know
where I am in the first place.
I've had it. It's completely malfunctioning.
It couldn't be!
He's here!
Then it's not a malfunction?!
No! There's definitely
some kind of mistake here!
It's not possible for a kid that
small to have a battle power of 710!
So that's it. You're the other one, huh?
How did you know about this place?
You expect us to tell you?!
Very well. I'll ask you a
different question, then.
What the hell have you come here for?
It's obvious, ain't it?!
We've come to take my boy back!
It's Father!
Which means...
...even though you may be a Saiyan, like us,
you don't want to join our group?
That's what I said!
Oww!
Then you intend to defy your brother?
I ain't got any brothers!
Kakarrot...
I thought you'd be more sharp-witted.
To think that you'd be as
foolish as this... You disappoint me.
Don't tell me you've made
the ridiculous determination
that if the two of you
attack me, you can win!
That's enough of your tiresome drivel.
Piccolo,
have you been training
by wearing heavy stuff too?
Yeah, just like you.
It's been a long time
since I felt this light.
His battle power has gone up to 408!
I see. You've been desperately
training yourself too, huh?
Being able to fight together as allies
for the time being like this is encouraging.
Maybe now we can have
ourselves a little bit better of a fight.
Kakarrot is now at 416...
You guys think you've gotten
all stronger by doing that?
What?!
Don't make me laugh!
To think that you would stroll
on in here with that kind of power!
This is what they mean when
they say you don't know your place.
Just being stronger in
a fight ain't everything!
We've got ourselves a strategy!
I've had enough of your smart-mouth.
Kakarrot, I've decided not to
let you join our group any longer.
It appears you'd just slow us down, anyhow.
You're a disgrace to our family! Die!
H-He's fast! What speed!
And he came at us head-on! For him
to get behind us in that one moment!
Your defense, at least,
appears to be pretty strong.
However, your deaths are
only a matter of time now.
Little by little, I'm going to
increase the strength of my attacks!
T-To think that the difference
in our levels would be this great!
Somehow, I have to grab his tail,
and make his power drop!
It's hopeless! No matter what
strategy you may have come up with,
there's no way you can beat me!
I know... Why don't I let you in
on something good before you die?
The two other Saiyans
besides me who are still alive
have an even higher
battle power than I do!
What unprecedented terror!
Even if Raditz is defeated,
there are still even
more powerful warriors?
There is nothing that
Goku and Piccolo can do!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Damn, we're in way over our heads!
What's the matter? Are you finished already?
Where did all that gusto you had earlier go?!
Piccolo, I'll draw his
attention. The rest is up to you!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Piccolo's Trump Card!
Gohan, the Crybaby-kun."
Stop picking on my father!
"Next time"
"Piccolo's Trump Card!
Gohan, the Crybaby-kun"