The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
One month remains until
Gohan, Vegeta, Piccolo, Mister Satan,
Videl, and even Goku, in the Next World,
will be competing in the Tenkaichi Tournament.
Say, is it okay if I become like you, Big Brother?
That Super Saiyan thing?
Goten's talents were astonishing.
Even Gohan was unable to contain him.
Big Brother, if you're thinking of flying,
then you have to teach me
how to do it too, or it isn't fair!
You got it, you got it! Don't get so upset, Goten!
I'll teach you how to fly!
Wow! All right!
And then Videl dropped by uninvited...
You promised me you
would teach me how to fly, right?
U-Uh, of course I'll teach you.
Gohan's special training in Bukujutsu has begun.
"Ah, You're Flying!!
Videl's Introduction to Bukujutsu."
Okay, I'm going to teach you two Bukujutsu,
which is to say, how to fly through the air.
This only requires you to control
your ki, so it is not all that difficult.
Now, if you're thinking of flying at faster speeds,
then yes, it does become
comparably more challenging.
Ki control? Say, what's this ki?
What's ki...?
I get it, you guys must call it
something different where you're from.
See, there's this hidden energy or power or
whatever you want to call it inside your body.
Huh? What do you mean, hidden power?
What should I do here?
How should I explain this...?
He means this.
Right, right, right, that kind of power.
I see...
What do you guys call this kind of power?
"A trick," I suppose.
Trick? This is something
completely different from a trick.
There's nothing even to set up.
Well, to be frank with you, I don't
know anything about this magic-like power!
You don't know about ki?
That's going to be problematic...
Listen, are you saying that if
you don't have ki, you can't fly?
It's okay, it's okay, everyone has ki.
Controlling it is difficult, though...
Honest?
Honest!
Goten, could you wait a little bit on Bukujutsu?
First, I have to teach
Videl-san how to control her ki.
We'll do it after that.
Are you sure you're not asking too much?
She doesn't even know what "ki" means.
I-I'll learn!
It's okay, just go off and play somewhere.
Okay! I'll go play!
Hurry up and teach me how to fly, okay?
Yeah!
Ready? Be still, and relax...
Slowly, draw out the power within you.
You see?
Okay, you try it.
Let's see...
Be still, and relax...
No, no, don't force it. Unless you're
relaxed, you can't draw out your ki.
You have to concentrate.
–I humbly accept this meal.
–I humbly accept this meal!
Thank you for letting me have lunch.
Got no choice. I can't very well let
you go without eatin' all by yourself.
This is delicious.
Much more delicious than
what our own cook makes.
Cook? What, do you work as a chef or somethin'?
No, I mean the cook that
we employ at our house.
You hire a cook?! You're not,
by any chance, rich, are you?!
How many rooms do you
have in your house?! 10?! 20?!
How many are there, I wonder...
Around 50, maybe?
50?! You're stinkin' rich, aren't you?!
This really is delicious.
When are you two gettin' married?!
Big Brother, are you and
Videl-san getting married?
N-No! No! No! No! No, I tell you!
Yes, yes! That's the way!
You did it! That's your ki!
You practice the martial arts,
so sure enough, you got the
hang of it quickly, Videl-san!
Well, can I fly now?
That won't be possible yet.
You've got to be able to
control your ki freely, first.
Same old-fashioned training as ever, huh?
Oh, Kaio of the South,
is that you? It's been a while.
Ah, that's Son Goku, who participated in the
Anoyoichi Tournament several years ago, isn't it?
He might have gotten to the
final round on a fluke back then,
but it appears he still hasn't received any
special training from Grand Kaio-sama, huh?
Grand Kaio-sama is a busy man.
But, it will happen soon enough.
How heavy a load is there in
those weights he's wearing?
Oh, not all that much. Each one is two tons.
T-Two tons?
Apparently, that surprises you.
Don't be ridiculous! I'm not surprised!
This is Papoi, who has arrived
from my own southern area.
He is the Southern Galaxy's greatest
hero from the last thousand years.
He's incredibly strong.
If he had entered that
last Anoyoichi Tournament,
we would have been far and away the winner.
Compared to him, Son Goku is no big deal.
Oh? What do you think about
this–there's a martial arts tournament
being held on a planet called Earth coming up,
and he is going to be entering it specially.
How about you enter Papoi-kun, too?
Very well...
Papoi will win for sure, no doubt about it!
Hey, Goku! Do you want to try
some weights that are a little heavier?
Yeah, fine with me, but how
heavy are you going to make them?
Well, let's see, how about
you try going to ten tons?
T-Ten tons, you say?!
You're kidding, right?
Ten tons? Ain't that asking
a bit much, even from me?
I won't be able to move!
Yeah, right, yeah, right!
That would be impossible,
no matter how strong you are!
You still enjoy telling those same lame
jokes that you always have, Kaio of the North.
Goku, you're free to turn Super Saiyan.
Ah, in that case, it's perfectly fine.
Hey, Kaio of the South, go ahead
and change those weights to ten tons.
T-Ten tons! That will make
for a total weight of 40 tons!
I'll do it for real! You ready?
Yeah!
I'm really, really going to do it!
Just do it, will you?
It's not my fault if you break something!
Tha-at's done it!
The martial arts tournament
is 28 days away by Earth time.
Papoi-kun, you should be
excited about entering, too.
P-Papoi, now that I think about it,
that tournament sounds like a drag, huh?
Well, let's think long and hard about it.
It might be better if you didn't enter, huh?
Not some lousy tournament like that...
Now then, as to how you fly, you
have to be able to control your ki well...
like I showed you earlier... and then float...
You don't hop around;
you have to draw out the
power from your whole body...
...and concentrate your ki...
That's good, that's good!
I'm floating, I'm floating!
Way to go, Goten!
Goten, don't overdo it!
I'm okay, Big Brother!
Goten! Goten!
Goten, this is why I told you not to overdo it.
But it's all right. Soon,
you'll be able to fly freely.
Mm-hmm. By the way,
when are we going to do your
special training, Big Brother?
Shh, not until after Videl-san goes home.
Once she leaves, we'll do
it as much as we want to.
Uh-huh!
Gohan-kun! What about me?!
Right, right, right, right!
You know, it's getting pretty late.
Won't your father be worried about you?
That's all right. Flying is more important.
Well, let's continue. Let's see...
draw out more of your body's power...
...and, uh, focus your ki together...
That's the way, that's the way!
You did it! You're floating!
You're floating slightly!
Shh! Be quiet! I can't concentrate!
That was incredible, wasn't it?
It's amazing that you've gotten so
you're able to float in just one day!
You don't say...
I've done it, Big Brother! See?!
G-Goten was already able to control
his ki capably when we started.
Videl-san, once you get as good as
he is, it will be no problem for you.
If you just practice from now on
by yourself, you'll get so you can fly.
I'm coming back tomorrow.
W-Why? You've practically got it down,
don't you? Practicing by yourself will be plenty.
I want to know more about ki.
Or is my being here getting in your way?
N-No, it's not like that...
Well then, until tomorrow.
Bye-bye.
Good-bye.
C-Come to think of it...
What?
Videl-san, about your hair...
I think it would be better if it was shorter.
Gohan-kun... short hair is more to your taste?
N-No, it's not a matter of taste!
When you're in a match,
I just think that having it
shorter would be more convenient.
You see, when it's long, it can get in your eyes,
or it could be pulled by your opponent...
You just be quiet and leave me alone!
That's up to me to decide, isn't it?!
Why did Sissy get all upset?
I-I don't know...
But you know something...?
We can't train!
Don't overexert yourself, Trunks.
You should leave the room.
This 150x gravity is far too much for you.
Last night, I got a phone call from Goten-kun.
Goten-kun said he was going to
enter the Tenkaichi Tournament.
So I'm thinking of entering, too.
Hmph, this is going to be pretty festive, huh?
It's too hard like this, all right.
I think I'll turn Super Saiyan!
What the...?
Lucky! Lucky!
S-Since when has he been able to...?
Y-You've got to be kidding me.
He turned into a Super Saiyan,
the warrior of legend, that easily...?
Trunks...
Yes?
Can Son Gohan's brother
turn, too? Into a Super Saiyan?
Yes.
It's as if there's a Super
Saiyan bargain sale going on...
Come at me!
That would be too much
for me, no matter what I did.
Dad, you're too strong.
Come at me, right now! How about this–
if you can land just one blow to my face,
I'll take you to the amusement park.
Really?! You will, Dad?! All right...!
Come at me as hard as you can. Got that?
Here I come!
That was mean, hitting back like that!
Don't act so spoiled!
I never said I wouldn't hit back.
That's terrible...!
D-Don't cry! I'll take you to the amusement park.
Never mind that, tell me, between you and
Son Gohan's brother, which of you is stronger?
I'm just a little bit stronger.
Goten-kun is a year younger than
me and all, and he can't fly yet.
Just a little bit, huh?
What the hell is going
on here, for crying out loud?
Let's get some training in
fast, before we're interrupted!
Uh-huh!
Y-Yikes!
Big Brother, who is that?
Well, shall we continue from
where we left off yesterday?
V-Videl-san...
I just don't understand girls.
Goten and Trunks, who had been hiding
their talents, were having a good time.
What remains a mystery is what
is going on inside Videl's heart,
now that she has drastically cut her hair.
Gohan has absolutely no idea.
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Yoo-hoo! Long time no see!
It's been seven years.
You've all changed quite a bit.
How have you been?
Goku-sa! Welcome back!
We've been waitin' for you!
Look, Goten, it's your father.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Welcome Back, Goku!
The Entire Z Team Assembles!!"
We're all about to enter the
Tenkaichi Tournament together!
"Next time"
"Welcome Back, Goku!
The Entire Z Team Assembles!!"