The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
To defeat the outrageous Majin Boo,
Goku has begun his Fusion
special training with Goten and Trunks!
Elsewhere, where Madoshi
Babidi and Majin Boo are...
I just received some significant information!
It seems that one of
those three urchins, Trunks,
lives in a house called the
Capsule Corporation, in Metro West.
Perhaps we should go and see him.
You'd better come on out!
Otherwise, the city where
you live will cease to exist!
Son-kun, it really will be
bad if Metro West is destroyed!
The Dragon Radar will also be lost!
All right, Trunks...
You return home as fast as you can,
get the Radar, and bring it back for us!
I will delay Majin Boo
and Babidi for a little while.
Yo!
I'll kill him for you.
I hate him for acting goody-goody.
Majin Boo and Babidi are
headed toward Metro West.
Can Goku possibly stop them?
Well, shall I see about going
once more beyond a Super Saiyan
that's gone beyond Super Saiyan?
"An Astounding, Great Transformation!!
Super Saiyan 3."
Go even beyond having
gone beyond Super-whatever...?
What is all this?
What the hell is this guy saying?
I don't get it at all.
Majin Boo, hurry and put this
guy away, and let's go to Metro West!
By all appearances, he seems
to be utterly weak, and yet...
And yet, as an opponent, not even
Vegeta could do anything against him.
I have to do something to keep him
here until Trunks can get the Dragon Radar.
I wonder if Trunks has reached
the Capsule Corporation yet.
No, he's still on his way.
Hm? Trunks' ki ain't moving.
Is he just standing there?
Hurry it up, already!
If possible, I didn't want to take
my form even beyond Super Saiyan...
This is Goten's father's ki?!
It's an incredible ki!
Besides that, all of a sudden,
he's traveled way past me!
Is this that Instantaneous
Movement technique?
Do you hear me?! Come on!!
Go get the Radar now!!
R-Right!
W-What?
Who the hell are you talking to? What radar?
Nothing at all. Don't worry about it.
It could be that old guy is
about as strong as Papa was...
In any case, I have to go
get the Dragon Radar fast!
It would seem you've got
something futile planned, huh?
Perhaps.
There's no way around it.
Shall we buy a little time, then?
Why'd you go back? You giving up?
That ain't it.
What I'm doing is explaining
to you about Super Saiyans
so you can easily understand.
Super... Saiyan?
You needn't take the trouble.
We don't even want to know about it.
Aw, don't say that. Ready?
First, this is my usual state, right?
This is me as a Super Saiyan.
And then...
...this is a Super Saiyan that's
gone even beyond Super Saiyan.
So, I guess you could call it Super Saiyan 2.
Just insignificant transformations!
No great change between them, is there?
And then...
From a Super Saiyan that
has gone beyond Super Saiyan,
h-he's going beyond even farther?
Y-You're just bluffing, right Goku?
To think there's something even higher...!
...this...
G-Goku...
...is going even further beyond Super Saiyan...!
S-Stop, Goku! I-If you do that,
your remaining time will disappear!
Your time is limited!
I-Incredible! His ki is
swelling up more and more!
Father...!
W-What is this...?!
Awesome! It's even bigger than it was earlier!
Ah, I shouldn't be doing this!
I have to hurry!
Stop! Stop it, Goku!
...attacking the Earth...
Th-The entire Earth is shaking!
I-Is this Goku's power?
Even with us so far away?
W-W-What's happening?!
This is Super Saiyan 3!
Sorry it took so much time.
I'm still not used to this transformation.
I-Is that Goku?!
Th-This ki... Don't tell me
this is Father's, on Earth...
No, it isn't...
Y-Yes, it is!
It's Son Goku-san.
It's an extraordinary energy,
but I'm certain of it!
M-Most unbelievable!
For any power to reach
this sacred region from Earth...!
D-Dad! What in the world is happening?!
You might have made a scary face,
but I'm not at all scared!
Th-That's right, you fool!
What about this Super-whatever-3?
You're just trying to look tough!
Majin Boo! Give it to him right away!
That's right. Let's hurry and do this.
Through me, everyone on Earth is
watching this! Boo, put him to shame!
Ain't Trunks done yet?
I'm home!
He's there! Trunks has arrived there!
He made it! Now the
Dragon Radar will be all right!
Way to go, Trunks!
Grandpa!
Trunks, welcome home.
My, my, my! You're just in time!
I just prepared some tea.
There isn't time for that!
Oh! Would you have preferred milk over tea?
Or perhaps some cocoa?
No, it's not like that!
Um, so what are some of the other
things that Trunks likes? Juice, maybe?
Or maybe iced coffee?
No, no! Say, where's the Dragon Radar?!
Dragon Radar?
Uh-huh!
Ah, let's see... the Dragon Radar...
Mm... as I remember...
Hurry up! Hurry! Hurry!
Get him, Majin Boo!
Boo!
Majin Boo! What's the matter with you?!
Awesome! Incredible, Goku!
Father! You can beat him like this, for sure!
I'm not so sure.
To be sure, Goku is so
incredible that we can't believe it.
However, even so, I'm not sure
whether or not he can defeat Boo there.
This Majin Boo, is he really that terrible?
Yeah...
Someone is fighting with Boo!
Incredible!
I don't know who you are, but hang
in there! Take out Majin Boo for us!
What are you doing, Boo?!
B-Boo!
Hey, what was that? What was that?
–What happened!
–Did he get him?
Great! Great!
Sheesh! Hardly any damage at all?
That's Vegeta's technique!
You lousy rat...
It appears you absorb all
of an opponent's techniques
just by fighting with them a little bit.
What's the matter, Boo?!
Hurry up and take care of this guy!
Goku! That's enough. Leave it at that!
If you keep using that extraordinary power,
your time on Earth will be drastically reduced!
You have to teach Fusion to the little ones!
For a goody-goody, you're pretty strong.
Same to you.
Hey, Majin Boo! What's taking so long?!
Hurry up and beat that guy!
You shut up!
W-What? What's this?!
You dare take that tone toward your master?
Hey, see here! Are you listening to me, Boo?!
I'm telling you to hurry
up and defeat that guy!
Trunks still hasn't left yet.
Trunks! What are you doing?! Hurry up!
Trunks?
Radar! Radar! Come on, where is it?
I'm sure it's around here.
I knew it! You were contacting that Trunks kid!
Hey, Boo!
Beat this guy up thoroughly and
make him tell us where Trunks is!
Yeesh. I guess I have to
buy us even more time.
Way to go, Goku! That's the way!
Father...!
Goku has gone even beyond having
gone even beyond Super Saiyan!
His force is brutal!
Not here, not here, not
here, not here, not here!
Not here, not here,
not here, not here, not here!
It isn't anywhere!!
Hasn't Trunks found the Dragon Radar yet?
It's possible that Goku
might defeat Majin Boo!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Very impressive, Majin Boo.
If I had the time, I'd like to play
with you at a more leisurely pace.
Be more careful, Majin Boo! You imbecile!
Can't you fight more cautiously?!
I was almost put in danger!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Bye Bye Babidi!! Majin Boo Rebels."
Stop, Babidi! Don't make
Majin Boo any angrier!
"Next time"
"Bye Bye Babidi!! Majin Boo Rebels"