The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
The Tenkaichi Tournament
is drawing ever closer.
Goten and Videl were being trained
how to perform Bukujutsu by Gohan.
That was incredible, wasn't it?
It's amazing that you've gotten so
you're able to float in just one day!
You don't say...
Elsewhere, Vegeta and Trunks continued
their training in the heavy gravity room.
I-It's too hard like this, all right.
I think I'll turn Super Saiyan!
Y-You've got to be kidding me.
He turned into a Super Saiyan,
the warrior of legend, that easily...?
"Welcome Back, Goku!
The Entire Z Team Assembles!!"
Look! I've gotten so I can float pretty well!
Great, great! You've got it down perfectly!
At this rate, I doubt there's
anything else I can teach you.
Yay! Yahoo!
Say, how many days do you think it
will take before I can fly like that?
W-Well, good question. I don't know...
I intend to keep coming here until then.
J-Just a minute.
Big Brother, watch me, watch me! See?
Goten, don't fly any
faster when Videl-san is here!
Why not?
Doesn't matter why not, okay?
What was that?
Nothing, just a little advice.
Time for a short break.
Listen, don't let my papa know that
you've been giving me training in flying.
I plan on surprising him by showing it to
him for the first time during the matches.
Is that right? That might be best, huh?
Besides, if Papa found out that
I was going over to a boy's house,
it would be awful!
He's terribly protective about me.
Listen to me, Videl,
you are not allowed to see any boys
unless they are stronger than your papa.
And yet there aren't any
such boys in the whole world.
Papa is the world champion, after all.
You know, Gohan-kun,
you do pretty well yourself,
but even so, I wonder if
you'd be any match for Papa.
S-Say, do you often engage in
practice matches with your father?
Practice matches?
There's no reason to do that,
is there? He's the champion!
Lately, he hasn't been overseeing my training,
so I've been doing it all on my own.
I knew it! Videl-san hasn't yet realized
that she has already become
far stronger than Mister Satan.
S-Say, if your father were to lose to someone,
that would be a pretty big shock, wouldn't it?
No it wouldn't. Papa is a little too full of himself.
Sure, Mama has died and is no longer around,
but he uses his fame as champion to
dally around with all sorts of women!
It would do him a little good to lose once.
Okay, okay! Even if I defeat Mister Satan,
Videl-san won't be hurt by it!
Now then, I guess we should keep going.
Gohan-kun, come to think of it,
who did you learn Bukujustu from?
Oh, um, it was from a friend
of mine, and my late father.
So I bet your father must
have been fairly strong, right?
Mm-hmm, he was awfully strong.
You know what? Father is going
to be coming back for one day,
so he can enter the Tenkaichi Tournament.
Coming back? How do
you mean? He's dead, isn't he?
Y-You dummy, Goten! I told you not
to say anything about that, didn't I?!
Ah, I get it.
I'll bet your father walked out
on you a long time ago, right?
But he secretly contacted you to tell
you he would be entering the tournament.
Isn't that right?
Both of us have had a hard
time of it with our fathers.
M-Mm-hmm...
Well, never mind about them! Training, training!
Hey! Where's Videl? What happened to Videl?
She hasn't come home yet.
What is she doing, staying
out late every night like this?
And so, several days later...
Watch out, watch out!
Videl-san is something else, all right.
She's gotten so she can fly
pretty freely in just ten days.
Really, you're doing great.
There's nothing more I can teach you.
Thank you, Gohan-kun.
Now I can devote myself to training
for the Tenkaichi Tournament
without any worries.
Mm-hmm, me too.
Well, I have to get home.
I know! I could just fly home like this, huh?
Mm-hmm.
Okay, I'll see you at the tournament. Good-bye!
–Good-bye!
Sissy finally went home, huh?
Yeah.
Goten, now we can train!
We'll have to make up for all the time we lost!
Uh-huh!
Come on, Goten!
The Tenkaichi Tournament draws ever nearer.
Everyone was putting their final
efforts into the last of their training.
Vegeta...
9,993... 9,994... 9,995... 9,996...
Piccolo...
Kuririn...
Once you get married,
then the pressure is really on.
Videl-san has incredible drive, huh?
S-She's a lot stronger than before...
Put a new one up, would you?
S-Sure...
Papa...?
Oh, Videl...
Are you sure you shouldn't be training?
There's no need for that.
There's no doubt that Papa will win.
I'll end up on top again!
It's no use... I just can't
keep up with you, Big Brother...
That's only because I've been
training a lot longer than you, Goten.
But Goten, you're doing pretty well yourself.
I wonder if Father is really
coming to the tournament.
Goten, this will be the first time
you've ever met Father, won't it?
You must be looking forward to it.
Mm-hmm.
Goku–Where is Goku?
It's almost time for the
tournament to begin on Earth.
Goku is over there.
Right now, he has finished all of his training,
and is calming his mind.
Say, do you suppose
Son-kun will really be coming?
He's coming, that's for sure.
Wow, how many years has it
been since we've seen Goku?
I'm sure looking forward to this.
Kuririn-san, Father might not
recognize you with that hairstyle.
You're probably right.
It really has been a powerful long time!
I'm so glad everyone's lookin' so well!
Yamucha-san, aren't you enterin'?
There's no way I could enter.
Even if I did, I would just embarrass myself.
By the way, Vegeta-san and this
goes for you too, Goten and Trunks-kun,
would you mind if we didn't turn
Super Saiyan during the tournament?
Why not?
Don't you know? You were already
shown on TV during the fight with Cell,
and people might wonder
where they've ever seen you before.
Now, try turning Super Saiyan in front of them.
They'll say "Ah! It's that group from back then!"
Yeah, and when that happens,
it's sure to become bothersome,
what with the TV and everything.
Hmph, I could just blow those people away.
No, you can't very well do that.
Well, all right. As long as
nobody turns Super Saiyan,
the conditions are the same.
It won't affect my superiority.
That's okay with us, too.
Uh-huh.
Terrific. Thanks, everyone.
That will help me out, too.
That sort of thing should be against the rules.
There it is, there it is!
That's the island with the
Tenkaichi Tournament grounds!
Okay, it's just about time.
Now then, I'd better get ready.
Say, Gohan, are you going to fight in that getup?
Yes. It would be bad if people
at my school found out who I was.
Pretty nice, right?
Y-Yeah...
Hey, there sure are a lot people here.
You're right. What a hassle.
I wonder if Goku is here already.
–What's up?
–It's Mister Satan!
Mister Satan just arrived!
–Mister Satan, huh?
–I'm getting his autograph!
The hero who saved the world has arrived.
That guy sure is popular, huh?
Nobody knows what really happened, after all.
Videl-san's father, huh?
Satan! Satan! Satan!
Satan fans of the world,
sorry to keep you waiting!
Mister Satan, what do you think of
your chances for winning this tournament?
Well, to be honest, I am 120%
certain that I will be victorious!
I understand your daughter is
going to compete this time as well.
Have you cut your hair as a
means of expressing yourself?
How annoying. Leave me alone.
It's all mine, all mine!
That guy is the same as ever.
Pay no mind, pay no mind.
Anyhow, I wonder if Father is here yet.
I don't see him anywhere.
Big Brother, there's Piccolo-san.
Oh, you're right.
Piccolo-san...
Have you seen Father?
Gohan... No, not yet.
Are you planning to enter wearing that outfit?
Of course.
I wonder what could be keepin' Goku-sa.
Could he already have gone
to the contestants' waitin' area?
All right, I'll go see.
Yeah, me too.
Yoo-hoo!
Father!
Son!
H-Hey!
You've all changed quite a bit, huh?
Even so... how have you been?
G-Goku-sa...!
We're glad you're back!
Son-kun...
G-Goku!
–Goku!
–Father!
Goku-sa! I've been waitin' for you!
I've missed you, too.
Goten, it's your father.
Huh?! And here I thought
he looked just like me!
Is that really my son?
Father...?
Father!
You sure are spirited!
You look strong, just like me!
Goku...
I'll remind you one more time,
you've only got 24 hours. Got it?
Yeah, understood.
See you later.
Thank you, O-Baba!
Hey, we have to hurry and take
care of the tournament registration,
or we'll miss the deadline.
Huh? G-Great–
Great Saiyaman.
Great Saiyaman?
That's right.
What's that about?
The name and the outfit are awfully cool, right?
S-Sure they are!
Okay, next.
Let's see, you'll be
in the Junior Division.
Huh?! Junior Division?!
Children up to 15 years
old are in the Junior Division.
Hey, Goten, they say that if
you're 15 years old or younger,
they won't let you fight with the adults.
Oh dear, is that the rule now?
That's pretty convoluted.
I don't care! Let us fight with the adults!
No way, that's against
the rules. Absolutely no way.
Aw, this won't be any fun.
Contestants, please hurry
and report to the waiting area!
Good luck, Goku-sa, Gohan, Goten!
Earn us a big wad of prize money!
Right.
Okay then, it's been
a long time since I got wild.
I've got to see how much
stronger Father has become.
I won't be holding back, okay?
Me neither!
Dad's going to go give it
his best, now, so wait for me.
We're off!
You guys, don't get too carried away!
Good luck!
At last, Son Goku has
returned from the Next World.
The Dragon Team has reassembled,
and a new Tenkaichi Tournament
is about to get underway.
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Okay, the preliminaries are about to begin.
But Gohan, ain't you gonna
attract more attention in that outfit?
Gohan-kun, watch out. Shapner has his camera,
and has vowed to unmask the Great Saiyaman.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Watch Out, Saiyaman!
Beware Of Snapshooters!?"
It's such a perfect disguise,
no one will ever see through it.
"Next time"
"Watch Out, Saiyaman!
Beware Of Snapshooters!?"