Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
The Saiyans, strongest in the universe,
were drawing ever closer to Earth.
Goku had only just passed the
midpoint of the Serpentine Road.
Elsewhere, Gohan was
living hardily in the high plains.
"Escape from Piccolo!
Gohan Summons a Storm."
Let's see...
Goku-sa, look at this! Gohan is
already solvin' problems as difficult as this!
I can't wait to see what kind of
great scholar he'll become in the future!
Yeah, I'll bet!
Mother... Father...
Try taking this on! Makankosappo!
H-He avoided it! W-What kind
of bastard is he, with such speed?
You pierced through this armor
quite easily. That's quite a technique.
If I had taken that head-on,
I would have been out!
That doesn't mean anything if I don't hit you!
To think that you would inflict injury upon me!
You're going to pay for
this! I'm through playing around!
It doesn't mean anything if I don't hit you!
All right!
Wow, I did it!
I lost a great deal of
time to Old Lady Snake there.
If I don't hurry up, things will get nasty!
Oh, no you don't!
Hey, we meet again!
It sure is big!
I wonder how long this beach goes on for.
Mother...
Chichi!
I brung some of my special-made porridge.
Eat some of this, you'll feel better, Chichi.
Nope.
You ain't eaten nothin'
for a whole week now, have you?
Come on, just eat this.
I'm not goin' to...
Gohan...
Huh? That's what I made!
I've come back to the starting point.
All right, then...
This is an island!
Beyond there is Mother! All right, then!
Makankosappo!
This one looks like it's the best.
All right, then...
Thank you!
Move it, move it, you're in the way!
It's finished!
I did it! I did it!
All right, now...
All right, here I go!
It's okay, I'll be back right away!
I'm just going to go see
my mother for a little while.
That should be good enough...
–The kid!
–It couldn't be!
Rain?
There's a storm coming!
I can't turn back now!
I've got to tough it out!
Got to tough it out!
It's okay, it's okay. I'll get through...
I'll get through the storm soon enough!
Ah, this is bad! If this keeps up,
I'll be swamped! And I can't swim!
I... can't swim! I can't swim!
That dirty brat! Where the hell did he go?
Gohan, what about your training with Piccolo?
Have you forgotten
about the crisis the world is in?
Eight months remain until the Saiyans arrive.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
What? Gohan ran away from Piccolo?
You brat! Tell me your mission!
To defeat the Saiyans, and to save the Earth.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Run, Gohan! Longing for Mount
Paozu, Where Chichi is Waiting."
But I still do want to see Mother.
"Next time"
"Run, Gohan! Longing for Mount
Paozu, Where Chichi is Waiting"