The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
I've taken a lot from you.
Now I don't have any more to do with you.
I won't stand you any more!
Having slain Madoshi Babidi, Majin Boo
has become even more reckless.
Your remaining time is down to 30 minutes.
You better start getting
ready to go back, Goku.
Uranai O-Baba! Only 30 minutes?
Is that all I have left!?
Goku could only remain
on Earth for a brief time.
Goku began giving Trunks and Goten
special training to teach them Fusion,
a new finishing technique!
Carefully watch the angle of your legs!
"Ha!!"
Then you put your fingers together like this!
Again, carefully watch the angle of your legs!
What do we do!? That looks awful!
"See You Later, Everybody!!
Goku Returns to the Other World."
Listen up. The only thing that will
defeat Majin Boo is this Fusion technique!
You have to learn it perfectly
within the next two days.
Right!
Goku is breathing hard.
This must be due to him using up all his energy
by becoming Super Saiyan 3
during his fight with Boo.
Now then, both of you do that Pose from
a moment ago, and make it symmetrical.
Got it? Okay, give it a try!
What's wrong?
What does symmetrical mean?
Um, how can I explain?
All right! Me and Piccolo will try
doing it for you, so watch closely!
I will!?
Ready? Watch carefully!
Like this, as if being reflected in a mirror...
Both of you move opposite each other.
"Fu–"
"–sion!"
"Ha!!"
W-What is this?
They said they were training,
but is this dance training?
Are they really going to be
able to defeat Majin Boo like that?
All right! Trunks! Goten! You do it!
Right!
Goku, you said you wanted to try
doing this together with Vegeta...
But, even if he were still alive,
I don't think he would
have done this with you.
Why not?
How come?
Uh... n-never mind.
Hey, hey!
Like this?
Right, right! Huh? Goten, the
angle of your arms is a bit low.
Raise them higher.
Right! Now, step to the side...
Fu–
–sion!
Oops!
–Ha!
–Hey, hold on, more this way, this way!
Good grief...
All right! Well then, let's try it a little slower.
Gohan! Gohan!
Chichi, shake it off!
Is she still down from having
heard about Gohan dying? Poor thing!
O-Baba! How much time's
Goku-sa got remainin' here on Earth?
It depends on Goku's energy,
but I'd say about 15 minutes or so.
15 minutes!?
Chichi, please come to 'fore then!
Otherwise, you'll miss his leavin' forever!
Fu–
–sion! Ha!
It's starting to feel right!
All right... Keep going like that!
I feel terrible! Even as we're here,
Majin Boo is out wreaking havoc,
and continuing to destroy the Earth!
Yeah, even knowing that
we can return everything
back to normal with the Dragon Balls.
Hooray! Hooray!
Great! Great! Babidi's all gone!
Now there's nobody to order
me around! Great! Great! Yea! Yea!
Now which city should I demolish?
Yahoo!
I'm starting to get sleepy.
What are you doing, you dimwit!?
Why, you...
Didn't you hear me!? I'm telling
you to hurry and get out of the way!
Am I cool-looking?
What? Cool-looking, you say?
You punk! Of course you don't look cool!
Haven't you ever looked in a mirror!?
You lousy...
Majin–
I-It's Majin Boo!
This is a good place. Think I'll
build my house here and take a nap!
It's too loud, huh? Gonna make things quiet!
Living things, come together!
First, I'll turn everyone into clay!
Smoosh!
Next comes cleaning, cleaning!
Okay, now...!
Fu-sion! Ha!
No, no! Again!
Fu–
–sion!
Ha!
There's still a ways to go, huh?
The two of you ain't matched your breathing.
Goten, are you having fun with this training?
Not at all.
Come on! Snap to it!
R-Right!
Finished!
Looks cool!
Ups-a-daisy!
Here is where I eat food.
Here is the tub.
Heavenly, heavenly!
Pajama-jama-jama,
Pajama-jama-jama, Pa-pa-pa!
Pajama, Pa-pa-pa, pajama!
Pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa, pa-pa-
pa-pa-pa-pa-pa-pa, pa-pa-pa, pajama!
Here is the toilet.
Here is where I wash my
face and brush my teeth.
Be sure to brush your teeth often, okay?
Here is the bed.
I slept good! I bet I slept for five seconds.
Now then, he said it would be two
days 'til those strong guys come, right?
It'll be dull until then. All right!
Gonna go destroy cities again!
Away!
Okay, once again, from the beginning!
Okay, stretch out your arms!
Go! One-two, one-two, one-two...
What's the matter, Trunks?
Uncle, this technique makes us look bad!
Look bad? I ain't so sure.
Even so, this technique is awesome!
The Metamorans that taught it to me got
exceptional strength from doing it, you know!
Even so... Never mind that,
Uncle, show us Super Saiyan 3!
Earlier, I was gone getting
the Radar, and didn't see it!
I want to see Super Saiyan 3 too.
Rather than learn this cumbersome technique,
maybe we should turn
Super Saiyan 3 instead, shouldn't we?
Yeah! Then we'll beat Majin Boo for sure!
That ain't possible.
Unless you merge together with Fusion,
he's not at all an opponent you can beat.
Don't take Boo too lightly!
I-Is that so?
Now, let's continue your training.
I give up. All right! Just once,
I'll show you Super Saiyan 3!
Really?
In exchange, you have to train
as hard as you can on Fusion!
Stop, Goku! The time you
can stay on Earth will disappear!
There ain't any time anyway.
Trunks! Goten! Watch closely!
First comes Super Saiyan...
This is beyond Super Saiyan,
or Super Saiyan 2...
And beyond this...
What is it!?
This is Super Saiyan 3.
A-Awesome!
Father!
–U-Uncle!
–Father!
Goku!
I'm okay, Piccolo!
Okay, you promised.
Continue your Fusion training!
Goku, it's time!
You're going back to the Other World.
Already...?
Just now, the time you can
stay on Earth shrank remarkably.
I see. Piccolo, sorry, but the rest is up to you.
Knowing these two, they should
master Fusion before tomorrow's out.
G-Goku...
You're the only one who can
teach them now. I'm counting on you.
You got it.
Trunks! Goten!
You're the only ones that can
beat Majin Boo and save the Earth!
Train hard, now!
Right!
Chichi! Chichi! Wake up, I tell ya! Chichi!
W-Where am I?
I'll give ya the details
later, right now, Goku-sa...
Goku-sa's goin' back to the Other World!
G-Goku-sa!?
You've gone to such lengths, it's too
bad you couldn't have taken it easy.
Good-bye, Son-kun.
Goku, "Take care" may sound a
little strange, but take care, okay?
Yeah!
Goku-sa!
Yow-ow-ow!
G-Goku-sa, what am I supposed
to do? Gohan's gone and all...
Chichi, don't get all depressed like that!
You've got Goten, don't you?
B-But, what if he gets killed by Majin Boo...?
Don't worry. If they can master
this technique they're doing,
there ain't no way they'll lose!
Once I see Gohan on the
Other Side, I'll tell him you said hello.
Um, I think that Gohan-kun is still alive.
–Why?
–It's nothing, just a hunch.
I know how you feel,
but really, I don't think that's so.
We can tell by his ki.
Still, it'd be nice if he was alive, huh?
Yes...
Well, that's it. Let's go, Goku.
Yeah...
What is it, Goten?
I know! You're wantin' your
daddy to give you a hug, huh?
Oh! In that case, you might have
said something sooner! Whoosh!
Goten, take care of your mommy for me.
'kay...
Okay, it really is time, Goku!
I know.
See you later, everyone!
Uncle! We're going to try hard!
Everyone, take care!
Let's get together again after you die!
That jerk! He would have
to say something so hapless!
Gonna destroy more and more!
Gonna kill more and more!
Majin Boo's wild run continues.
And, at the furthest reaches of
the universe, in the Kaioshin Realm...
Gohan is also working
hard at his Z-Sword training.
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
I've been looking for you, Gohan.
I asked old man Yama,
and he said you ain't dead.
What are you doing here?
Goten! Trunks! In one day, you
must master Fusion, no matter what!
Get enthusiastic about it! Enthusiastic!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Where is Gohan!?
Ferocious Training in the Kaioshin Realm."
How well do I have to wield the
Z-Sword before I can beat Majin Boo?
"Next time"
"Where is Gohan!?
Ferocious Training in the Kaioshin Realm"