Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Having stolen five Dragon Balls from Freeza,
Vegeta at last had defeated
Zarbon, who had been chasing after him,
following an intense life-and-death battle.
And then, with great apprehension,
the Dragon Ball which Kuririn...
...had received from the
Grand Elder also went to Vegeta.
You guys are lucky.
I'm in a good mood, since I have
now found all of the Dragon Balls.
Now I can rule the entire
universe, instead of Freeza!
I will obtain eternal life.
Elsewhere, Gohan had discovered
the Si Xing Qiu Ball Vegeta had hidden,
and was on his way back.
"Freeza's Secret Weapon!
The Devilish Ginyu Special Corps."
K-Kuririn, you handed it over
pretty easily, considering, huh?
You had to work so hard
to get that Dragon Ball, too.
He said that was the last
Dragon Ball, so it's all over now.
If I hadn't handed it over, we
definitely would have gotten killed.
The fact that the two of
us are even alive like this...
...is nearly a miracle.
Besides, we're probably still
okay handing over that Dragon Ball.
I'm sure that the Dragon Ball
that Gohan went looking for...
...is the one that Vegeta hid
to keep that Freeza bastard
from gathering all seven of them.
That's right! Gohan-kun must
have found that Dragon Ball already,
and now he's heading back!
That means things aren't going
the way Vegeta had hoped, are they?
Mm-hmm. As long as Vegeta
doesn't find Gohan, they are.
He is late, is he not?
Y-Yes, sir!
It has been four hours.
What could Zarbon-san be doing?
Seeing as how he has not returned,
he has either fled,
or he has been killed.
If I had known this would happen,
I should have brought the Ginyu
Special Corps from the start, huh?
Yes, sir! C-Concerning that,
according to a message we
just received from Planet Freeza,
preparations for the Ginyu Special
Corps' departure are complete.
Is that so? I look forward to it.
Now then...
I have no need of cowardly men, like yourself.
Be gone.
Ginyu Special Corps, launch!
What exactly is happening on Planet Namek?!
W-What's this?!
There's an enormous power
headed for Planet Namek.
Is it Goku?
There are five of them. Is this...
...t-the Ginyu Special Corps?!
The Ginyu Special Corps?
Mm-hmm. They are the evil
overlord Freeza's special private squad.
The Ginyu Special Corps have always operated
in the shadows of
Freeza's rule over the universe.
I don't know about "Ginyu," or whatever,
but we'll put those guys
down "g-iny-ood" and hard!
That was funny, that was funny!
Kaio-sama, how was that pun–?
Kaio-sama...
The Ginyu Special Corps–
a fearsome squad of evil.
Each one of their powers
might be higher than even Goku's.
And there are five of them.
For some reason, it feels like my
body has suddenly become lighter.
All right, one more burst!
Something's coming from straight ahead!
It's a very strong ki...
Vegeta!
All of a sudden, there's a
strong battle power in front of me...
I have to mask my ki...
The presence just disappeared. Impossible...
I'm sure it was around here.
Vegeta! Hurry and get out of here!
Who's there?! Come on out!
I know you're there!
If you don't show yourself at once,
I'm going to blow this whole area away!
H-He wouldn't!
What's the matter?! Huh?!
All right, I wonder if I had better
jump out and fight Vegeta. But then...
Gohan, there's no way we can
match up against Vegeta now.
I have to protect this precious
Dragon Ball at this point.
You don't intend to come out, huh?
All right... as you wish, I'll blow you away!
Rats!
W–
Wait!
Please, don't let him find this...
I-It's me!
Kakarrot's son, huh?
Kakarrot's son, huh? I thought
that perhaps it might be you.
There were other Earthlings here.
You being here isn't all that surprising.
A Dragon Ball!
D-Don't tell me that's!
This? I got it as a present from
that bald-headed friend of yours.
Y-You... killed Kuririn-san... didn't you?!
If you'd like me to,
I wouldn't mind going back
now and killing him for you.
Be grateful.
To celebrate me getting all of the
Dragon Balls together, I let him live.
A-All of the Dragon Balls?
Hey, what's that you're holding in your hand?
T-This is a clock!
Heh, a clock?
With science that can only
make a clock as huge as that one,
I'm impressed that you
could make it to this planet.
N-Nobody asked you!
By the way, is that Kakarrot bastard here, too?
No, he's not!
We didn't know there
would be bad guys like you here!
Is that so?
That's too bad, huh?
The three of us...
...are the last of the Saiyans.
When you get back to Earth,
tell him something for me.
Tell him I said that I will
come to Earth before long,
and this time, I will blow
both you and the Earth away.
It's around time for you to be
missing your mother's milk, isn't it?
Hurry back to Earth, now.
That hurt!
But still...
...the Dragon Ball is safe!
Dammit! Isn't he back yet?!
Kuririn, I've taken down the house,
and returned it to its Capsule.
Isn't Gohan-kun back yet?
I-I don't see him yet.
I sure hope he wasn't discovered by Vegeta.
Vegeta has found out about this place.
We have to change locations, fast.
What is Gohan doing?! Hurry! Hurry!
Kuririn-san!
He's here!
Kuririn-san, I found this!
You did it! We've been waiting for this!
Gohan-kun, way to go!
Gohan, I'll fill you in on the details later,
but we have to hurry
and get away from here,
or things are going to get dicey.
I know most of it already. Vegeta found me, too.
But I managed to hide
the Dragon Ball somehow,
so I got away without him finding it.
Y-You were lucky, too, huh?
Kuririn, Gohan-kun, let's just get moving.
–Right.
–Yeah.
This is the lake.
The Dragon Ball is submerged in here.
Once I pull it out...
...I will have all seven Dragon Balls together.
Take that, Freeza!
As of right now, the universe belongs to me.
That's strange. It was
definitely submerged in this area.
It's gone! Impossible!
It was him!
The place where I ran into that kid...
...was exactly halfway between here
and the cave where those Earthlings were!
Why, that miserable brat!
But how did he search for the Dragon Ball?
This is a clock!
That was no clock! It was radar!
Damn it!
You Earthling punks!
Play me for a fool,
will you?! You'll pay for this!
Damn it all!
Damn it all! Damn it all!
Where are you, you punk kids?!
Come on out, or you'll be sorry!
Dammit, they've disappeared, have they?!
Damn it all, I can't
sense their presence, either.
Those brats are able to control
their presence all the way down to zero.
I can't find them like this.
Those rotten Earthlings!
That was an insolent stunt to pull!
But they are sure to come after the six
Dragon Balls that I have at some point.
And when they do...
It's okay.
He won't find us here.
Hold on a minute.
I can't even set up the house
in a place as tight as this, can I?
Please don't ask the impossible.
There aren't too many
caves like that last one, after all.
We just have to put up with it
until Father arrives, Bulma-san.
Huh? You mean, until Son-kun
gets here, a lady such as myself
is going to have to stay here, in a
place that doesn't even have a bathroom,
together with you guys?
Oh, you don't have to worry on that point.
I'll be taking Gohan with me,
and we'll be going to
Grand Elder-sama's place again.
Huh? How come?
What is this?!
You mean you're going to be
leaving me here all by myself?!
Please bear with us. Once
Gohan meets Grand Elder-sama,
there's a chance that he will gain
enough strength to rival even Vegeta.
Freeza's secret weapon, the Ginyu Special Corps,
had at last gone into action.
Goku was also headed for Planet Namek
while continuing to
train under 100-times gravity.
Vegeta was seething with anger.
And Kuririn and Gohan had
taken off to see the Grand Elder.
A grand three-way battle intertwining
good and evil was about to begin.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Two more days to Planet Namek.
I guess I'll tough it out
in this 100-times
super-gravity a little while longer.
That's it! I'm at the end
of my rope with this planet!
Aah! The Si Xing Qiu Ball is sinking!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Watch Out, Bulma!!
Si Xing Qiu Falls into Freeza's Clutches."
Father, do I really have
enough power to rival Vegeta?
"Next time"
"Watch Out, Bulma!!
Si Xing Qiu Falls into Freeza's Clutches"