Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
C-Curses! This was all a terrible
miscalculation, especially for me.
All that remains is for me to go back...
...to the laboratory.
W-Who is that guy down there?
He is who you were fighting with, isn't he?
What?!
Y-You mean it's not him?!
Are there even more Artificial Humans?
History is greatly different
from that of Trunks' future.
"Give Chase!! The Search for
Doctor Gero's Mysterious Laboratory."
What's that? You say he's different?
What?!
I-It can't be!
Who's been carvin' up the earth down there?
Look, over there, over there!
That's where everyone is!
That's them, right?
That's Son-kun and the others!
S-Stop, you idiot!
You seriously wanna go there?
It's all right, I tell you!
If everyone's still alive,
that surely means it's all over!
You take us any closer, an' I'll
drop this rugrat right outta here!
Oh? Be my guest.
Or didn't I mention that his father is Vegeta?
V-Vegeta?
This rugrat–er, rather,
this handsome young man's the
child of yourself and Vegeta-sama, is he?
That case, let's go!
Now you're talking!
Different? He's different, you say?
Well then, who is that guy? Tell me what he is!
It's no great matter, is it?
After all, our history may
have just changed slightly...
...from the one he told us about.
The Artificial Humans we're facing
have also changed from the ones he knew.
That's fine if it's true.
Now then, what should I do?
How can I get back to the laboratory?
If I try to fly away, I'll likely be overtaken.
The only thing I can do is use
this terrain to conceal myself as I go.
Hey, isn't that Bulma-san's?
Yoo hoo!
Hey, look! That's an Artificial
Human! One of em's still 'round.
Doctor Gero?
Watch out! Don't come any closer!
Now!
I wasn't lying when I said there's
absolutely no way you could win!
No. 17 and No. 18 will be
coming soon to kill you all!
No. 17?
No. 18?
Why, that lousy...
Ah, what a surprise!
Trunks!
Oh, Trunks!
Oh, thank goodness! Thanks, pal.
He's vanished, dammit!
He got away!
Bulma-san!
Are you okay?
Fine, fine! This boy saved me.
–Really!
–Thank goodness.
Damn! You're not getting away from me!
Why didn't you help them just now?
What?
They are your wife and child, aren't they?
How insignificant. I have
no interest in any of that.
You're in the way, mind your own business!
He's not flying up in the air,
which means he's running away
on foot so that we can't locate him.
He couldn't have gotten very far yet.
Say, was that strange old
geezer earlier an Artificial Human?
There, there!
Why, yes he was.
That was probably Doctor Gero himself.
I've seen him in a book of scientists.
That is strange, huh?
I wonder if he's converted himself?
There, there!
Ain't no one gonna pay me no attention?
Hey! That Artificial Human just
now was probably Doctor Gero!
Doctor Gero?!
That was Doctor Gero?!
What's that supposed to mean?
Like I said, I've seen his picture before.
He spoke of Doctor Gero, so I looked him up.
There, there, now...
Yes, he is pulling a scary face, isn't he?
You know what?
Doctor Gero was quite gifted and famous,
especially among other scientists.
It seemed he was rather
hard to get along with though.
Oh, there, there!
Everything you've told us
has been completely false!
Wasn't Doctor Gero supposed to
have been killed by Artificial Humans?!
And these Artificial Humans
were different from yours!
T-The only thing I can figure is that
history itself has shifted somehow.
Most likely due to me coming
back to the past before now.
He mentioned No. 17 and No. 18, right?
More than likely, those are
your two Artificial Humans.
Tell us how we can distinguish them!
We can't afford any more mistakes.
Yes, you're right.
No. 17 is a young man with long
black hair and a scarf around his neck.
No. 18 is a pretty female type,
dressed in clothes similar to mine...
F-Female type?!
They both have cold eyes and round earrings.
I think you'll know them when you see them.
They would have to draw energy in
through their palms, wouldn't they?
No, they aren't like that.
Their energy is... unlimited.
Unlimited? You mean it never runs out?
There, there!
Say, more importantly, where is Son Goku-san?
That heart disease, the
one you warned us about?
He just barely came down with it.
Is that how badly time has been shifted?
Goku-sa! Hang in there!
You don't suppose... we might be
too late with the medicine, do you?
You've got to hold on, Goku!
Goku-sa!
You just wait, Vegeta and Piccolo!
You're about to get a taste of just how
terrible we Artificial Humans really are!
What do you think you're doing, Vegeta?!
If you come any closer
with that scary face of yours,
you're going to make Trunks cry again!
There, there now...
I know, it's surprising
how scary his face is, isn't it?
Bulma, do you know where
Doctor Gero's laboratory is located?
He's heading back that way for sure!
The location?
Well, as I recall, it was somewhere in
the mountains surrounding Metro North.
There's a rumor that he converted
a cave up there into a laboratory.
Well, he's long gone by now.
Even if we were to take off after him...
We're all right. Did anyone see him flying away?
Now that you mention it...
He intends to use the topography
here to help him get away again.
He must still be running
through an area not far from here.
I get you. All we have to
do then is get there first,
and then destroy No. 17 and No. 18 before
Doctor Gero has a chance to activate them.
I wouldn't do such a cowardly thing.
I just want to be first in line to put
the others away with my own two hands!
The Artificial Humans we just took
on gave us such a poor fight, after all.
You must not!
You must not.
You underestimate the Artificial Humans.
As Piccolo-san said, we should
destroy them before they are started up.
If we're too late to do that,
we should avoid battle until Son
Goku-san has recovered from his illness.
We don't need to wait for Kakarrot's strength!
Can't you tell?
I've become a Super Saiyan too!
With both him and I turned Super Saiyans,
my elite skills obviously
place me several steps above him!
Now move it, you're in my way!
Hey, he's gone all right.
Vegeta has become a Super Saiyan,
and has gotten even stronger than Son Goku.
He just might be able to beat
the Artificial Humans, as he says.
I can turn into a Super Saiyan as well.
However, there isn't any way
I could match up against them.
They have unbelievable strength! I'm going too.
He may be a jerk, but I'm not
going to let my father die again!
Father? Did he just say father?
I wonder what he meant?
There's no reason to keep this secret any longer.
His name is Trunks.
His father was Vegeta, and you are his mother.
In other words, he's the grown-up
version of the baby in your arms.
You're kidding!
I-Is that right?
C-Come to think of it, they do look alike.
N-Now it all makes sense,
about how he is able to be a Super Saiyan.
You guys come with me and help
search out Doctor Gero's laboratory.
It seems best to destroy the Artificial
Humans before they get started up.
–You got it.
–Ok!
Trunks, you grow up to be
a pretty good guy after all!
Thank goodness!
Your mom was worried because
you have such a mean look about you!
B-Bulma-san, please let my
father know about all of this.
And tell him if he gets well in
time, we'd like him to join us.
That's fine, but how am I supposed to tell him?
My airplane got all smashed up.
Gohan, you take her with you.
The rest of us have what it takes...
...if we're just destroying the Artificial Humans.
Okay. But be careful.
All right, let's go! We have
to find it before Vegeta does!
Okay, we'll be going pretty fast, now.
Be careful, we have a baby here too.
Hey, don't forget 'bout me!
Yer takin' me too, yer takin' me.
I should be okay now.
Having run this far, I should
be able to fly without being seen.
Vegeta!
Shoot! Is he still trying to search me out?
Him too. They're both flying in
exactly the same direction as I'm headed...
Could they possibly be headed for my laboratory?
No, it's just a coincidence.
It has to be a coincidence!
There's no way they could
know where my laboratory is.
Only a very few scientists even know about it.
Was that Bulma?
The first daughter of the Capsule Corporation?
She might have asked her father about me!
T-That must be it, all right!
They're all headed toward my laboratory.
So, they intend to destroy No. 17 and
No. 18 before I can start them up, do they?
There's no way I'm letting
them get away with that!
I never told anyone the exact location,
so they shouldn't be able to
find it without some searching.
I can still take the roundabout
way and get there first.
Say, Gohan-kun, you can
speed up a little if you want.
Right!
Your late father?
He sure did a lot of wicked things.
He'd be in Hell now, no doubt about it.
But he had his good points too.
He was always so full of pride,
he'd never show his
gentle side clearly to anyone...
But I knew...
Is he thinking of
accompanying me the whole way?
How interesting!
That's right, he can become a Super Saiyan too.
He is my kid, which explains
where he gets his Saiyan blood from.
Yajirobe! Why don't you
get down and walk already?
Stuff it!
The warriors head toward
Doctor Gero's laboratory.
However, what is it that awaits them there?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Trunks, are those the Artificial
Humans you were talking about?
There ain't no mistake this time, right?
None of you know how truly terrifying they are.
We should definitely destroy
them before they are started up.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"And the Terror Becomes Reality...
No. 17 and No. 18 Awaken."
Oh, no! They've been started up already!
"Next time"
"And the Terror Becomes Reality...
No. 17 and No. 18 Awaken"