Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Five months remained until the Saiyans,
who are planning to invade Earth, would arrive.
Elsewhere, Goku had
finally reached Kaio's planet...
What's that?
What?! What?! What?! What?!
Is this Kaio-sama's training?
This is definitely hard!
"The Battle with Gravity!
Catch Bubbles-kun."
What are you doing there?
H-Huh? Who are you?
Me?
I am...
Scratch... scratch... scratch...
Eh, there's a mosquito...
A mosquaito...
'skaito...
Kaio!
Then, who is... huh?
That there is my pet, Bubbles-kun.
Ohhh...
I thought it was a little strange.
You're the strange one.
By the way...
Don't you think that play on
words just now was the greatest?
You don't have to be afraid to laugh at it.
At what?
You were too tense to hear it, huh?
What am I going to do
with you, for pity's sake?
Well then, at no extra charge,
I'll hit you with a different play on words.
Hello? Hello?
Huh? I picked up the phone,
but no one was home!
That's great!
What was?
What did you come here for?
Oh, I was hoping to
have you train me, Kaio-sama.
Train you?!
Go home now!
Anyone who hears a joke like that
and doesn't laugh has a flawed character!
You expect me to train anyone like that?!
That was hilarious! I should
have expected as much, Kaio-sama!
I ain't ever heard anything so funny!
It was, wasn't it?
You were just slow to notice it, that's all.
Are you going to train me?
Train you, huh? I wouldn't mind doing that.
Really?!
Provided that...
...you can pass my test.
You have to make me,
Kaio-sama, the mastermind of gags,
laugh at one of your plays on words.
I have to make a play on words?!
Are you getting cold feet?
If the pun is not at an adequate
enough level, I won't laugh at it.
Well, how about it?
Apparently, you're not up to it.
If that's so, then give up, and go home!
M-My futon...
flew away, gone!
Your futon... flew away gone?!
Just a little more!
My feline...
...has gone supine!
My stylus is sightless!
Ah, you laughed! Kaio-sama, you laughed!
My futon flew away, gone!
You're no slouch at this, huh?
You're a pro, aren't you?
Very well, I will give you
my training. I will teach you...
...my greatest gag!
N-Never mind the gags,
teach me martial arts.
What, you want to learn martial arts?
Why didn't you say so sooner?
All right, come at me! I want to
see what kind of skill you possess.
What's the matter?!
It's just that there's
something strange going on.
It's awfully hard to move,
and my body feels so heavy.
Where did you come from, Earth?
Then it would be heavy here, huh?
This is a small planet,
but it has incredible gravity, see?
I'll bet it's about ten
times what it is on your planet.
That means your own
weight is ten times greater.
See how high you can jump.
As hard as you can.
O-Okay...
It's no use! That little
bit is as high as I can go!
If he can jump that high
in ten times his normal gravity...
This guy here has a lot of promise!
Okay then, we will start your training.
How much time do you plan to spend with me?
I ain't sure how many days it took
for me to run down the Serpentine Road...
But I don't think I have much time.
I'm told that there are these
Saiyan guys who are coming to our
planet to do some awful stuff.
So I'd like for you to train me
until that time, however short it is!
Saiyans, huh?
You've had some nasty folks set
their sights on you, all right. Well then...
I'll check into when these Saiyans
are going to reach Earth for you.
The Saiyans are flying that way, all right.
They will arrive on Earth in...
let's see... about 158 days, I'd say.
Awesome! You can tell that?!
Yeah, these handy antenna
are reliable, an' tenna some!
That was great!
Maybe I should give up training you.
That was great! That was great!
Wasn't it?
Still, there's only 158 days
until the Saiyans arrive, huh?
Hey, 158 days will be plenty.
Me training you on this planet
for 158 days will have the same value
as if you trained for
a thousand years on Earth.
Really?!
However...
Even if you do train with me,
there's no guarantee that you
will be able to beat the Saiyans.
The two Saiyans that are headed for
Earth have just that much awesome power.
To be honest with you, their
strength is even greater than my own.
Even greater than yours, Kaio-sama?!
That's right.
Which means that if you
cannot at least surpass me,
it will be impossible
for you to beat the Saiyans.
Okay then, how about
we get started right away?
Hey! Bubbles-kun!
First off...
...you have to conquer the harsh gravity here.
Catch Bubbles-kun here, if you can.
For the time being, until you
can move fast enough to do that,
nothing else will matter.
A-All right...
Okay, run away, Bubbles-kun!
Wait up!
Damn! My body is really heavy!
Dammit! All right, then...
Watch this!
I'm going to get you!
Ho! So he's already wearing
super-weighted gear, is he?
That makes me quite a bit lighter, now!
Hold it!
Hold it! Hold it! Hold it!
All right, you're mine!
It can't be! You're kidding me, right?
What do you think?
He sure is fast! I'm not sure I can catch him.
If you can't, then go home right now.
That's right–I ain't eaten anything
since I left the Snake Princess' place.
Say, I hate to ask, but could
you give me something to eat?
Well, okay. That's unusual–
a hungry deceased person...
Hey, how about showing a little restraint?
I'm down ing the donburi!
Down ing the donburi!
Where's the joke there?
I'm full, I'm full!
The taste notwithstanding,
at least my stomach is full!
I get the feeling that maybe this
man isn't giving me enough respect.
By the way, Kaio-sama,
I'm surprised you don't find it
dull staying on a planet this small.
So young...
If you set your mind to it, there are
any number of fun things to do here.
Like counting how many
blades of grass there are growing...
gazing up at the sky...
long-distance peeing...
Recently, I've been
getting into a new hobby...
Going for drives.
Now, hurry up and catch Bubbles-kun.
Otherwise, you'll never be able to
get me to teach you any martial arts.
Right! I'll give it my all!
All righty!
Oh, right!
Put on those heavy-looking clothes and boots
you took off earlier and then run after him.
That will be more effective.
But putting that stuff on
makes it even harder to run!
Let me tell you something.
The planet that the Saiyans are
from had about the same gravity as here.
That's where they built up their bodies.
Do you now understand part of
the secret to the Saiyans' strength?
But it's more than just that.
Saiyans are born with
a natural fighting sense.
That's another thing
that makes them so formidable.
Hey, that's fine! I'm a Saiyan, too!
Nice thrust.
Don't slow down your attack!
Uncle...
help me.
Don't be so needy, you dirty brat!
Sure enough, he only exhibits
those dormant abilities of his
on the night of the full moon.
Yow-ow-ow-ow...
Looks like you at least cured yourself of
being a crybaby over the last half-year, huh?
Say, Piccolo-san, you fought
with Father a long time ago, right?
Our fight is not yet over.
If we're able to defeat the Saiyans,
your father's turn comes next.
But Father told me that
the reincarnated Piccolo-san
didn't seem to be the same
terribly evil person he was before.
I sort of think that, too. Mother and
Grandpa are still afraid of you, though.
Stop talking nonsense and get to sleep!
Tomorrow, we won't have the
kind of gentle training we did today!
R-Right...
Damn him anyway...
Since then, three weeks have
gone by in the blink of an eye...
These shao-mai dumplings taste so good...
...that you'll say "they taste s hao good...
they taste s hao good," I think you'll find.
That was great! That was great!
Huh? Nobody heard that one?
Hold it!
Hold it! Hold it!
I've got gyoza by the gross!
Hold it!
Now!
So close!
All right!
He's in good spirits, huh?
Hold it!
He definitely doesn't have
the slightest respect for me!
Yow-ow-ow...
He really is incredible, huh?
But I'm not giving in!
Hold up!
I'm so close!
I know!
All right...
Hold it!
Bubbles-kun, I found you!
I did it!
Wow! I finally did it! I caught him!
He's as amazing as I thought.
He's already overcome the gravity here, has he?
He might be able to handle it!
The Kaio-ken technique...
The Saiyans' assault is not far away.
What kind of training will
Goku receive from Kaio-sama,
now that he has finally met him?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
That's fast! I ain't ever
seen anything that fast!
Gregory is that fast, huh?
Then again, the foes that you
have to fight are even faster.
Kaio-sama, you know about the Saiyans?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Saiyan Legend Reborn! Goku's Roots."
Father, do you really think
I can become a great scholar?
"Next time"
"The Saiyan Legend Reborn! Goku's Roots"