Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
In the face of the overwhelming
power of the Ginyu Special Corps' ReaCoom,
Vegeta had at length
fallen into the worst of all crises.
However, just then...
Hey, Butta, Jheese!
Let me take out these two little squirts, too!
But then, Kuririn fell, too.
Kuririn-san!
F-Frankly, we're finished...
We're powerless against them,
and if we run, they'll catch us...
And the Dragon Balls have been taken from us...
There's nothing good about this...
I-I'll do as much as I can!
"Don't Die, Gohan! Goku Finally
Touches Down on the Battlefield."
Yeah, that's right, short
stuff, do as much as you can.
I, ReaCoom-san, will let
you match up against me, okay?
Darn it!
Ultimately, we're not going to get a turn, huh?
That's okay.
Taking out those two runts wouldn't
give us anything to boast about anyhow.
G-Gohan...
That's pretty good.
How about this, though?
All righty...
Masenko!!
Did you see that?
Yeah, for just a second,
his battle power was over 20,000.
Gohan...
Wow, you're good, you're good.
You made my handsies smart.
Now then...
Take this!
G-Gohan!
Oh, my. Is something the
matter, Goku-chan's wife?
Gohan-chan is in a terrible fix.
Gohan-chan...
My Gohan-chan...
Cheer up, Missus. Gohan-chan
will be fine. My Bulma said so.
Is it ready?!
Oh, is that you, Chichi-san? Have a look
at how wonderfully this is turning out.
You wouldn't think that I put it
together in just two days, would you?
I'll tell you, this second one
was a lot easier than the last one.
I even nailed down the
right location for the speakers.
All I need to do now is a test flight.
Just you wait, Gohan!
Ma is comin' to save you right now!
Hey, Chichi-san, won't you let me
explain how to use it before you go?!
Just which one of these is the startin' switch?!
Hey, just a minute, I say!
G-Gohan!
There, didn't I tell you so?
Gohan-chan!
Still alive?
Good, good!
Magnificent, Ginyu-san.
I would not have expected you to
bring me all seven Dragon Balls so quickly.
It was worth it to call in the
Ginyu Special Corps, all right.
It gives me, Ginyu, no greater joy
than to have you say so, Freeza-sama.
This means that I am
about to acquire eternal life.
What wonderful joy.
If you would like, shall
I dance the dance of joy?
P-Perhaps you could do that next time.
Really?
Who would have thought the immortal
youth I dreamed about would come true?
Even I, of all people,
am starting to get excited.
The birth of the perfect and everlasting
ruler of the universe is
about to happen, isn't that right?
Now, Dragon Balls, give me,
Freeza-sama, eternal life and youth!
W-What was that?
I've got an odd feeling of uneasiness.
No doubt about it,
the hands of evil will be extended toward
Grand Elder-sama in the very near future!
Forgive me, Earthlings. I have
a duty to protect Grand Elder-sama!
Darn it...
Father!
You got up, did you?
You got up, you got up!
I won't be beaten. Not by you.
I won't... be beaten...
What have we here? Did you
mean for that to be an attack?
N-Nothing is happening, huh?
Have you become immortally young yet?
N-No, I do not believe so.
W-Why?
G-Go on, take it.
Even if you do get the Dragon Balls together,
you guys won't be able to
get your wish granted anyhow.
As I recall, when I took the second
Dragon Ball, that is what the Namekian said.
I thought he was just being a poor loser.
"You guys."That is exactly
what he said. "You guys."
There has to be some sort of passcode for these!
A secret passcode to grant wishes,
that only the Namekians know!
A password! A place! Or perhaps
a way of arranging the Balls!
We will have to ask a Namekian for it.
A Namekian? Are there any of
them still surviving anywhere?
T-This reading is from Vegeta and company.
It's possible that Vegeta
or the others know what it is.
I-In that case, I must stop
my men from killing Vegeta!
Have a look at Point 8829401.
There are two readings which
I believe could be Namekians.
There is also a reading
that is approaching that point.
We have not once attacked this
area, so they must be survivors, yes?
Well then, I will go there at once and force
them to tell me how to get a wish granted.
That will not be necessary.
I will go ask them directly.
After all, I am more accustomed
to dealing with these people.
Ginyu-san, please stay here and
keep watch over the Dragon Balls.
Yes, sir, understood.
Please leave everything to me.
Now, to go flying...
I won't be beaten...
G-Gohan...
I have to... defeat you guys...
for Piccolo-san... Yamucha-san...
Tenshinhan-san... Chaozu-san...
Or I can't bring anyone back to life!
All right, here I come!
ReaCoom Bomber!!
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go! Go!
Whoops, I'm over here!
Have you finally reached your limit?
D-Don't get up anymore, Gohan...
Darn it...
I-I am... Father's...
...S-Son Goku's... son...
You won't... you won't...
Oho, you still have enough energy left
to be spouting that sort of nonsense, huh?
I don't know what planet you're from,
kid, but this is surprising.
Your opponent is too much for you, huh?
I won't be beaten!!
Whoa!
He's just about ready to croak.
He doesn't have any battle power left.
Of course not. His neck has been broken.
Gohan!
P-Pathetic little brat... And here
I thought he'd gotten a little better...
Gohan-chan...
Yo, are you awake?
Are you all right, Missus?
Gohan-chan is... Gohan-chan is–!
Oh, my...
Sheesh...
These guys were all just worthless scum.
I don't understand why Freeza-sama expressly
called in the Ginyu Special Corps for this.
Well, nonetheless, I guess
I should finish off all three of them.
What's that?
It's a ship. It's landing.
At last, Goku had touched down.
Goku, rescue the desperate Gohan and
friends from the devilish hands of ReaCoom!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
I've finally arrived. Sorry to
keep you waiting, everyone.
Hey, now, what is this?!
I was about to look good
while killing those three!
If that's how you want it, I'll kill you first!
Give it up! You can't beat me!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Uncommon Strength!!
Son Goku, the Legendary Super Saiyan."
Father's strength is astonishing!
"Next time"
"Uncommon Strength!!
Son Goku, the Legendary Super Saiyan"