Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
W-What's this? Goku's battle power is 180,000!
Even Ginyu is stunned by this!
However, at that time, Freeza's devilish hand
was already closing around the Grand Elder,
so he could learn the passcode needed to
have one's wish granted by the Dragon Balls.
I will show you the terror of
the strongest being in the universe.
"Surprise!! Goku is Ginyu
and Ginyu is Goku."
How audacious it was for them to
attempt to inflict even one injury upon me.
Such extreme examples of
those who did not keep their places.
Now then, Grand Elder-san,
it would appear that there is
still one foolish individual out
here who does not know his place.
I believe that if this
gentleman were about to be killed,
you would soon change your mind and tell me
how to have the Dragon Balls grant my wish.
You will also regret not
having spoken up sooner,
while you were still unharmed.
If you like, we can spare
your life right here and now.
You've probably already realized this,
but Grand Elder-sama has
only a short time left to live.
It would be bad for you and I both
if we were to fight here,
with him caught in the middle.
We will change our location.
I do not anticipate the extent
of our fight to be that great,
but very well.
Anywhere you like.
My apologies, Nail.
Please find a way to hold out
long enough for Dende to reach the Earthlings.
At this point, the fate of
our planet rests in their hands.
C-Commander Ginyu!
What are you laughing about?
How can I not laugh about this?
I didn't think anyone could be as strong as you.
So why laugh?
Because I'm happy to have found someone
much stronger than even I, Ginyu-sama.
Yes, yes! Such strength!
I'm so happy! I'm so happy!
It's been quite a while
since I've been so happy!
I'm so glad to be alive!
W-What?!
Jheese...
Y-Yes, sir.
S-So that's it! Commander Ginyu...
Take care that you do not drop my Scouter.
That's it, all right!
How far away are you going?
This is far enough!
There is no need to distance
ourselves any farther than this, is there?
I suppose not.
My, my. Those who wish to die certainly account
for a large number of this planet's inhabitants.
How troubling.
This is amazing! Your battle
power has risen to 42,000.
I see now. You certainly are quite
different from the other Namekians.
I am surprised. It is a wonderful battle power.
You certainly live up to your
classification as a "warrior-type."
I wish you were among my ranks.
Well, shall I inform you of the
battle power rating which I possess,
to use as a reference as you
begin your fight against me?
My battle power rating is...
530,000.
However, naturally I do not intend
to use my full power against you,
so you need not worry.
What?!
I know! What if I were to fight
using only my left hand for you?
That might make it more enjoyable.
Enough!
No, this will not do. Here
I stretched out my neck for you
so that you could not
miss, and this is all you have?
On the other hand, this is
about right for someone at 42,000.
Oh my, that was impolite of me.
I will return it to you.
You should not be straining
yourself so, should you?
I think it would be best for you
if you spoke, before you get killed.
This is a surprise!
You can regenerate?
Although, while you may be back in
one piece, your situation has not changed.
It appears that you cannot
regenerate your energy, as well.
Your battle power has dropped.
My, my. After having been
shown how mismatched you are,
you still wish to continue?
I have no idea what the people
of this planet must be thinking.
I will not allow you...
I will not allow you to...
W-What is this? What is going on here, exactly?
Does this planet have something
personal against me, or something?
This time, I've had it for sure!
Lucky! If I can just make it into that cave...
Just a little farther...
I-I made it! I'm saved!
Huh? Have I been saved?
This is so mean of you!
This is it! This time for sure!
Farewell, everyone!
Yow!
What? What happened?
Here.
Stay back! You pervert, grabber,
idiot, monster, whatever you are!
Bulma-san!
G-Gohan-kun! T-Then...
How could you, Bulma-san?
How terrible. There wasn't even any warning–
What have the two of you been up to?!
No sooner do you show up suddenly
with Vegeta and take the Dragon Ball away,
then you take off with him to someplace else!
Now, I want to know just what's going on!
Do you think you can just leave
a delicate lady unattended out here
in such a dangerous place,
and get away with it?!
B-B-But didn't we just
rescue you from that dinosaur?
B-Bulma-san, at any rate,
we need the Dragon Radar!
If everything works out, we may
still be able to get our wish granted!
What's this? You still haven't
gotten our wish granted?
I saw from the Radar all seven Dragon
Balls had been gathered in one place.
I was sure you were the ones
who had gotten them together,
and I was on my way to meet you.
And now what do I hear?
Unbelievable. What sort of
goofing-off have you been up to?
G-Goofing-off, she says. Scratch, scratch...
Bulma-san, pardon me for a second.
Kuririn-san, I've got it. It's that way!
Okay, we're off!
Hold on! Tell me what's going on!
We're in a hurry right now,
so we'll explain later.
Bulma-san, please wait
for us back at that island.
Huh?! You've got to be kidding!
You expect me to walk back from here?
How can you? This is so mean of you!
Oh yeah, Father has arrived!
R-Really? How is he?
Has he gotten much stronger?
Gohan, let's hurry!
Right!
Son-kun, huh?
I didn't think he would
turn out as handsome as he did.
With Yamucha as my boyfriend,
all he and I have ever done is fight...
Maybe I blew it.
Wha–wha–
What are you doing?!
What the?
Y-You're not a... Super Saiyan...
...b-but I've still taken a liking...
to that strong body of yours.
T-Taken a liking?
S-Sure enough, Commander
Ginyu is planning on doing that...
Amazing! How was he able to
find that much power in his condition?
H-Here it comes...
C-Change!!
H-How come... I'm... over... there?
I've made an exchange, your body for mine.
Y-You did what?
Commander Ginyu!
Here's your Scouter.
All right, we're returning to the ship.
Freeza-sama may be on his way back, as well.
Yes, sir!
This body is even faster!
I... can't... move!
So this is the reason why he injured himself...
Oh no! At this rate I, I mean,
he and Kuririn will meet up!
Dammit, not only am
I unfamiliar with this body,
but with this wound, I can't fly so well.
On top of that, if I manage
to safely get back to Earth,
I'll probably just get Chichi angry at me again.
L-Look at the face I've got now!
I'm done for!
What's this? Goku and
Ginyu have exchanged bodies!
Flying toward Freeza's spaceship
in search of the Dragon Balls were
Gohan, Kuririn, Vegeta, and Ginyu!
The battle revolving around the Dragon
Balls has taken yet another radical turn!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Kuririn! Gohan! That's Ginyu!
There's no way you'll be beaten by him now!
N-No way! That body is yours!
We don't have a chance of winning!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Come Forth, Super Shen Long!!
Grant Me My Wish."
We came all the way to
Planet Namek for this moment!
"Next time"
"Come Forth, Super Shen Long!!
Grant Me My Wish"