Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
In order to return those who had been
changed into demons back to normal,
Kami-sama and Popo take the Ultra Holy Water,
and rush to the bottom of the Heavenly Realm.
Elsewhere, while Piccolo fights Garlic Jr.,
who had been revived by the Makyo World,
his power drops suddenly to its lowest level!
"The Ultra Holy Water Worked!!
The World Awakens from Its Nightmare."
Are you all right?
Piccolo! Your body...
S-Something must be
happening to that wretched Kami.
K-Kami-sama...
Kami-sama!
So this is the revered form of the Kami
that formerly governed over the Earth?
You all are exalted,
all-powerful, all-knowing Kami?
How shameful for you!!
It is true, I am born of Planet
Namek, an alien to this world.
It is true that I have
been an inferior Kami to you.
However, I love this
Earth more than any of you,
and have the same love
for all living things upon it!
My hope is to be able to die for those people!
I will be allowed...
...to pour out this Ultra Holy Water
into the hole of the air currents.
Why don't you just... die!
You did it! You did it, Gohan!
Gohan! Don't let your guard down!
Right!
I-It can't be!
That was quite an attack just now.
Even I thought I saw into the
world of the dead for a moment.
I-Impossible!
How can he still be alive in his state?
Have you forgotten?
He has... Garlic Jr. has eternal life!
This is a nightmare.
Now it's my turn to lead off!
Piccolo!
Piccolo-san!
Worthless idiot!
What do you expect to do in your condition?
Dammit!
Brat!
Now then...
P-Piccolo, if I had a little
more power remaining,
I may have been able to protect you.
To think that it would come
to me needing your protection!
How low I've sunk!
T-Thanks a lot!
But I'll try to extend
yours and Kami-sama's life,
even if just by a little bit.
Even I...
...can be of use, right?
Why, you!
After everything else, you attack with this?
What are you...?
I-It's no use!
You'll pay!
You're gonna pay for that!
You piece of crap!
I'll kill you an inch at a time!
I'm going to kill you so very painfully!
K-Kuririn!
Piccolo... stop!
Haven't you died yet?
I'll send you both to Hell at the same time!
What do you think you're doing, you lech?!
Who're you callin' a lech?!
Lady, it's your fault for tossin' in yer sleep!
Look, look! What a pretty sunrise!
How lovely!
Huh? Karin-chan, what are you doing?
How much longer? There's no time left!
There, there, that's the spot...
Now stop doing that!
It's the kid, huh?
Shoot him! Gohan!
But...
Shoot him!
Blast him into so many pieces
there won't be anything left!
Gohan! Do it!
Hurry up!
Kami-sama!
Popo, here.
Get this Ultra Holy Water to
the hole with the air currents!
They're only after me.
Kami-sama, no use! No time!
If don't run away, Kami-sama will die!
Silence! If you don't hurry,
you're fired as my assistant!
D-Don't worry about me! Go, quickly!
K-Kami-sama!
Go! Get going!
Shoot him!
Gohan! Shoot!
Kami-sama!
What are you doing?! Hurry up!
Go!!
Shoot!!
Curse you all!
What's that?!
You did it, Kami!
I-It's... it's okay now.
Why, you...
How dare you trample on
my dream of a Utopian world?!
Don't think you're
going to get away with this!
Damn! Not that again!
Suck it in! Swallow the Heavenly
Realm and everything in it, Dead Zone!
Piccolo-san!
Kid! You really think that will protect you?
I'm sure you all remember!
A space that numbs your body and mind,
where not even a single ray of
light may enter! The Dead Zone!
I'll seal you all in here until you die!
Garlic Jr. once again creates his Dead Zone!
Do Gohan and the others
have a chance at victory?
And what of Kami and Popo?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
What are you waiting for, Gohan?
Hurry up and blast the Makyo World!
But the moment I remove this Shield,
Piccolo-san and Kuririn-san will be...
Never mind about us!
You're the only one who can
stop Garlic Jr.'s evil designs!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Gohan's Brief Chance for Victory!!
Blast the Makyo World..."
Garlic, even without
Father here, I can take you!
"Next time"
"Gohan's Brief Chance for Victory!!
Blast the Makyo World..."