The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
I've killed all the Earthlings. Now,
I will fight. Gimme the guy I will fight!
Understood! But we have to prepare
for the fight. Give me some time!
Two hours–no, just one hour will be fine!
Please!
One hour? How long is that?
Once all the sand in this sandglass has fallen.
In the face of a Majin Boo that
has become the ultimate in evil,
only one hour's worth of time remains.
Having come to this, there is no choice
but to have Goten and Trunks
train in the Room of Spirit and Time.
"The Special Training Is a Success!!
You're Finished Now, Majin Boo."
That's Majin Boo?!
He really has changed, huh?
And not just his shape, either.
Everything about him is
positively greater than before.
Now you understand, right?
Now, hurry and go into
the Room of Spirit and Time.
For every one minute here,
you can train for six hours in there.
Don't dilly-dally around!
Mother!
W-What?
W-What does she think she's doing?! That idiot!
Rotten Majin Boo!
How dare you kill Gohan-chan?!
Give him back! Give me back Gohan-chan!
Turn into an egg.
M-Mother...
Dammit... dammit...!
Dammit...
–Dammit!
–Hold yourself back, Goten!
Do you want all of this to be for nothing?!
Damn you, Majin Boo! How dare you...!
Goten...
Listen! We can bring your mother
back to life with the Dragon Balls!
That is, if you and Trunks defeat Majin Boo!
However, with your power now,
that's not possible, so you have to train!
In the short remaining time,
you have to desperately train!
Got it?
L-Let's go do it, Goten!
We'll train really well, and
then we'll flatten Majin Boo! Okay?
A-All right...!
Sure is hot in here! I wonder
if they have a cooler or anything.
Besides that, our bodies
seem heavier. Right, Goten?
W-Well, there's no reason
to be in that big a hurry, right?
Out there it's just one hour, but in here,
he said we would have all of 15 days!
You know something, this
is one awful place in here!
Hey Goten! All we have for food is
some yucky-looking powder and water!
What's going on? This is
unbelievable, completely!
W-Wait up!
Y-Yow! Let's do this together!
Um...
Majin Boo appeared to know who
my father is. Do you know why that is?
Yeah.
W-Why is it? I don't understand it at all.
It's simple.
Mister Satan is the only human that
Majin Boo has let his guard down to.
When we were trying to do anything
we could by force, Mister Satan,
no matter his motives, chose
to become Majin Boo's friend.
As proof of that, even though
every earthling has been exterminated,
only Mister Satan was not killed.
Even though he has become
nothing but a destructive beast like that,
at least that memory of him remains.
Even though he may not
be able to match us in power,
your father really is the
proud World Champion.
Papa...!
No more!! I won't wait any more!!
W-What?!
Wait! It hasn't even been 30 minutes yet!
You've got to give us at
least a little more time!
No way. I won't wait any more. I will fight!
Come on out! I'll kill you!
H-How come?
R-Right now, we'd better
go call Trunks and Goten out!
They've gotten way stronger now, I'm sure!
They just barely went in there, you know!
Yow-ow-ow-ow...
What's going on?
Okay, I'll let you fight. Come with me.
This way.
H-Hey! Is Piccolo planning to let
Majin Boo fight with Goten and Trunks
inside the Room of Spirit and Time?
Why would he make them fight
in the Room of Spirit and Time?
I think it's because once they're
inside the Room of Spirit and Time,
then even if Trunks-san and
Goten-san were to lose or anything,
you can destroy the entrance,
and seal that world up inside.
It is a separate dimension from this world,
and they will be unable to come out again.
Whoa...!
S-So then, what happens
to Trunks and Goten-kun?
It is all right. Even if killed,
it is possible to bring the two of
them back to life with the Dragon Balls.
Hmm... Piccolo has put
together an outstanding strategy.
How nice and bouncy...!
–Still higher?
–That's right.
Good grief! They're this way!
Can't you show some kindness to the elderly?
Anyhow, aren't they taking
quite a long way around?
Yes, they are. If they had
turned at the last corner,
they would have been right there.
He's buying whatever little time that he can.
Piccolo said that one minute
here is six hours in there, you know.
Still farther?! How far are we going?!
Don't be impatient. Your foe is at
the very bottom level of this place.
Bottom?! We were going up before!
You can't get there unless you do.
Say, we did it, huh?
Y-Yeah... Awesome! Who knew
there was anything above Super Saiyan?
We can win for sure like this!
Everyone will be completely stunned!
But it sure does wear you out! It feels
like we're using up all our power at once!
And this has time as its shortcoming. Look...
We can only be like that
for around five minutes.
Then even the Fusion breaks
up and we return to normal.
If that's so, it's no problem!
We'll just become like we did just now,
and given five minutes,
we can beat him for sure!
Dummy! That won't be very exciting!
We've trained for a whole week!
The way I'm thinking, I figure that
even in our regular Fusion state,
we've improved to about
the same level as Majin Boo.
Now listen! Let's make them think that
by having about the same amount of power,
the fight will be drawn out.
Everyone will get anxious.
After all, we can only hold
Fusion for thirty minutes.
But then, with five minutes to go,
we become Ultra Super Saiyan like
we just did, and put him away in a flash!
What do you think?
It will be totally cool, right?!
Sure! You're gonna panic,
Majin Boo, you scumbag! Take that!
We'll avenge my Papa,
Gohan-san, and Goten's Mama!
Yeah! Let's do it!
Still further?!
That's his limit...
A little further.
Can you hear me,
Trunks and Goten? It's me, Piccolo.
I'm speaking into your minds now.
O-Our minds?
Be quiet and listen well. Ready?
It turns out you'll have to fight
Majin Boo earlier than we planned.
I'm headed your way now with Majin Boo.
Th-That's bad! We just
barely got done with Fusion!
That will be okay. I'm buying time
by purposely taking the long way.
It should be a good deal of time in there.
Get yourselves ready to fight now
by getting some rest! Go to sleep!
I can probably draw it out another minute.
That will be six hours of your time there.
Got it?
Six hours will be plenty!
Once Piccolo-san learns how great we've
been training, he'll be so surprised, huh?
Say, how about something to eat?
Don't need to!! Enough already!!
You made us walk this long! I'll kill you!
O-Okay...
In here.
This is a strange place.
–Dum, dum dum–
–Dumm!
–We've been waiting for you...
–Majin Boo!
All right, that was perfect!
Them?
That's right.
Please, let there be a miracle...
Hey, the only spectator
is going to be Piccolo-san.
That's kind of disappointing.
Really, them?
That's right.
Well, that's okay. No choice
but to do like we planned.
–You're finished now...
–Majin Boo!
I was right, me just saying
"Majin Boo" was a let-down.
That's because you couldn't
remember your line, isn't it?
It was a waste to wait for this!
Stop complaining and let's
keep going, otherwise you'll forget.
Yeah, okay.
–Here we go!
–Okay!
O-Ouch! Hold on a minute, you!
You didn't give any warning!
I can't believe you! What an idiot! Really!
Stop and think a minute!
We were just about to do
something awesome, you know!
Just wait! Okay? Got it?
Let's do it over! Don't move!
This takes a lot of nerve
even without you doing that.
Let's go again, Goten!
Right! Ready, set...
"Fu–"
W-What?! Why aren't they
starting this as Super Saiyans?!
"–sion Ha!!"
All right, good! Right from the
start, they've merged perfectly!
Dum-dum-dum-dumm! It's Gotenks!
You, huh? I remember!
You're the guy I beat to a pulp before!
You stupid dirtbag!
You're badly mistaken if you
think I'm the same as I was before!
My time is limited!
I'll show you right away how I'm
different from how I was before!
H-He certainly is different!
He certainly is greatly powered-up!
C-Can this possibly mean...?
Can I attack you yet?
J-Just a moment, okay?
Th-This is strange. That should have
had some kind of effect on him. Aha!
He must be trying hard not to show his pain!
Gotenks finds himself in a
great pinch right from the start.
Fight like you mean it!
Life is not as easy as you might think!
Th-This might be hopeless!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
He can win! The way he is now,
Gotenks can definitely beat Majin Boo!
At least he should be able to.
What is he doing?!
Don't worry about nonsense
like the aesthetics of your fighting,
just go at him with all
you've got, right from the start!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"'I'm Going Like I Mean It!!'
A Wide-Open Super Gotenks."
There it is! His finishing move!
Super Ghost Kamikaze Attack?
"Next time"
"'I'm Going Like I Mean It!!'
A Wide-Open Super Gotenks"