Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
At last, Goku's super-giant
Genki Dama detonates!
I-I'll just take this and...
I'll just take this and...
"Transformed At Last!!
Son Goku, the Legendary Super Saiyan."
It's all completely changed.
Where's Father?
Where's Piccolo-san?
Father and Piccolo were right nearby.
You don't think they got
caught in the middle of it, do you?
They couldn't have been!
I don't feel their ki...
That's just because we've
lost our powers of concentration.
Piccolo was there with him!
They're not about to die!
Kuririn-san, over there...
P-Piccolo-san!
It's Goku!
Father! He's alive!
We did it, we did it!
Just like I told you, right?!
Damn! With barely any ki
left, we can't fly very fast!
Father!
Piccolo-san!
Piccolo!
Father!
G-Gohan...
Hey, Goku, are you okay?
Piccolo-san!
Gohan, you must have been worried.
It was incredible! That Genki Dama!
Wasn't it huge?!
That it was.
It had the hopes of everyone in
the universe packed inside it, after all.
I was afraid the two of you had died...
You expect us to bite the dust so easily?
Now we can head back to
Earth with our heads held high.
I didn't think I was ever going to be able to...
What's that?
I-I just wanted to give
it a shot once, y'know!
Marriage.
Goku did it!
With the Genki Dama I taught him!
He really did it to that Freeza
with a super-giant Genki Dama!
Freeza-sama beaten by that monkey scum?!
T-That can't be!
Never!
I don't believe it!
Goku won!
And we're going to stick it out too!
With Piccolo-san still alive,
we can all go back to Earth.
All right! Let's go!
Charge!
Dibs!
Purple Comet–
–Zed Crush!
W-What was that oni?
Order up!
Oh? We have so many guests today oni!
Jheese! Butta! ReaCoom!
Yeah, we won, we won!
We beat the Ginyu Special Corps!
Dammit! We can't just leave it like this!
It's no use, oni!
It's easy to drop down here into Hell,
but crawling out is very difficult oni!
Nothing is impossible for
ReaCoom-sama, of the Ginyu Special Corps!
ReaCoom Jump!
You fought well!
You guys have improved more than I thought!
To think that you could so easily
kick around those training partners
I took the trouble to call here...
Training partners?
To tell the truth, in order to give
you some training in actual battle,
I made a request of Yama the Great to
have the Ginyu Special Corps sent here.
Given their powers, it isn't likely
they'll be able to climb out of Hell.
Well done, well done!
Your training partners
have parted and run away!
Your training partners have parted!
Good joke!
Shall we go home?
The spaceship I came in can
get us back to Earth in five days.
I'll see Mother!
We'll see everyone!
Ouchie...!
I completely forgot! Bulma-san!
Don't scare me like that!
I thought that maybe Freeza
had shown up again, you know!
I-In some senses, Bulma-san
is even scarier than Freeza!
Ooh, ow! Don't make me
laugh so much, I ache all over!
You know, Planet Namek
has endured something terrible.
However, this should
allow the Grand Elder-sama,
and all the others who
have died, to rest in peace now.
H-How is it you know about the Grand Elder?
What is it, Kuririn?
Freeza!
He took that huge Genki Dama
head-on, and yet he's still alive!
I-It can't be!
Goku!
P-Piccolo-san...
P... P...
Piccolo-san!!
Wha... no way!
Kaio-sama, what is it?
Piccolo's been... Piccolo's been done in!
But I thought Freeza
was supposed to be dead!
Freeza is a frightful one!
More so than I had imagined!
Piccolo! Hey, Piccolo!
Free... za...!
Even I questioned whether or
not I was going to die this time.
I, Freeza-sama, nearly died!
Run... Kuririn, Gohan...!
There's a spaceship very near
the location where I first arrived.
Take Bulma and get yourselves
away from this planet, now!
Gohan, snap out of it!
I will fight! I'm going
to avenge Piccolo-san!
Get the hell out of here!
You guys are in my way!
Do you all want to die together here?
G-Goku...
Father...
You think I'm going to excuse you?
I'm not letting a single
one of you go home alive!
Kuririn-san!
Kuririn!
Stop it, Freeza!
Goku!!
A-And this time?
Kuririn...
Shall I do the little brat next?
Y-You're going to pay for that...
How dare you... How dare you?!
How dare you... How dare you...?!
W-What?!
Gohan, take Piccolo with you
and get yourselves back to Earth.
He's still barely alive.
Go home now, while I still
have some sliver of reason left!
Right!
Goku's fury has gone beyond its bounds.
What can Goku's transformation mean?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
My anger is turning to over flowing power.
You can destroy whole planets,
but it seems you can't even
destroy a single man, huh, Freeza?
Maybe you're a Super Saiyan,
and maybe you're not,
but there's no way you can beat me.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"An Explosion of Anger!!
Goku, Avenge Everyone's Deaths."
Freeza, we're not going
to accept your apology!
"Next time"
"An Explosion of Anger!!
Goku, Avenge Everyone's Deaths"