The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
In order to rescue Gohan and
the others, who had been absorbed,
Goku and Vegeta have slipped
inside the body of Majin Boo.
However, there was plenty
lying in wait for the two of them...
One after another, the two
were assaulted by many traps.
Will they indeed be able to
safely find Gohan and the others?
What the hell are you doing, Kakarrot?!
Tear those lower life forms off of you!
I know! But my body is...!
Kakarrot!
"Nightmares or Illusions!?
Goku and Gohan's Father-Son Confrontation."
Kakarrot!
My stomach hurts!
Of all the... You're such an idiot!
And you told me not to
make such a commotion!
He's sure to have found us out from that!
M-Maybe so. And I was even
trying to hold back quite a bit, at that!
Big brother!
Big brother! Big brother! Big brother!
Poppa! It's Big brother!
P-Poppa? I've got an
awfully bad feeling about this!
K-Kakarrot! Despite how I may seem,
I cannot stand squirmy things!
Sure enough, here he comes!
I think I'm gonna vomit!
Poppa! Those guys were bullying us!
Hey, Kakarrot! We've already been
found out from what happened earlier!
No need to worry about that any more, right?
Well, I don't know... H-Hey, Vegeta!
W-What?!
Poppa, hurry up and put those guys away!
Yeah, yeah!
What did you do that for, Poppa?
You've done something
naughty again, haven't you?!
How many times do I have to
tell you before you understand?
I told you, you can't go
straying off so far from the herd!
You really don't listen to
a thing your Poppa says!
Um, has this boy committed any misdeeds?
Misdeeds?
I-If that face moves any closer, I'll kill him...!
You see, this boy has the bad habit of
taking off after anything he sees moving.
I am not about to be attacked because
of someone's habit! For the love of...
Ah, that's right! Say...
There are these people
that are dressed like we are.
They would have looked a
bit less handsome than me.
I wonder, have you seen anyone like that?
I know who you mean!
There was one who was green, too!
Piccolo, huh?
Say, where are those guys now?
Y-You turn into a toilet!
All right...
W-What's this? What's Boo
making a toilet for all of a sudden?
Maybe he's upset his stomach or something.
Is that so?! All right, then...!
J-J-Just a minute!
This is our chance! Right now,
even I might be able to beat him!
Th-That's crazy! You can't!
Let's not do this! It's obviously not sensible!
No! Today, for sure, I, the strongest
man in history, Mister Satan, will...
Pee-yew!
Th-That was a fart every
bit worthy of the name "Boo"...
The green person went up above here.
Yeah. The people I saw
went up above here too.
Up?
It's Boo's toilet-time!
Why is that?! This is earlier than he usually is!
Hey! Tell us more! Where do
you mean by "above here"?
I'm sure I heard him
say it's toilet-time, right?
Yeah! Which, you don't
suppose means that we...
Aw, crap!
...is what we're going to become?!
Hey, Vegeta!
Hey!
Still, to think that while
I was sealed up by Bibidi's spell,
so many guys as strong as
them would appear on Earth...
However, now they have all become
my power! My muscle! My blood!
Looks like we've finally
come to the inside of Boo's head.
This is the only place left.
Gohan and the others must
be inside here somewhere.
Kakarrot, which way do you think?
Let's see...
The left way, I guess!
Is that so? In that case, I'm going right.
Hey, you can't just do that!
When I'm together with you,
nothing good happens.
Fine, suit yourself!
Who's that?! Who's over there?!
Gohan!
You guys! Are you okay?
Come on, we're breaking
out of here, quick! Hurry!
What?
They've done it! Everyone is safe!
Now, quickly, outside of Boo you go!
Don't you think it's strange?
Why do you suppose those little
squirts have undergone Fusion?
Gohan! I've been looking for you!
W-What are you doing, Gohan?!
Why, you... You're not Gotenks at all, are you?!
Now that I know that... I'll show you no mercy!
It's the whole lot of you!
Mess around with me, huh?
H-How come?!
What are Gohan-san and the rest
doing to Goku-san and Vegeta-san?
Is that it?
That is indeed Boo's brain.
The Gohan and Gotenks and such
that are in there are not the real items.
They're memories! Those are Gohan and
the others from among Boo's memories!
From among Boo's memories?
I figured it out right away
that you ain't the real Gohan!
Just by looking in your eyes!
Though it seems you have
the same power as the real thing.
You really have gotten stronger!
W-Where am I?!
R-Rotten Boo! You will face me! Come on!
Ah, I'm so hungry.
Before I extinguish this planet,
I first need to fill my stomach!
That Boo!
Have you once again grown afraid
of me, Mister Satan, and run away?
Come, let us follow after him.
Y-You can't mean it!
W-W-Why?! After he so graciously went away?
If the Earth is destroyed, then it will
be the same no matter where we are!
We have to do something to him!
W-W-What do you mean, do something?
Boo has gone off looking for something to eat.
While he's eating, I'm sure we can
create an opening! That's where...
That's where I go "Whammo,"huh?
And then "Kaboom"and "Bam!"
B-But, can I do that?
I can't betray his expectations...
What will you do, Mister Satan?
Come.
We're going already?
We don't have to go so soon...
Th-This can't be...!
Fighting against these
two opponents is truly hard!
And at a critical time like this,
Kakarrot is not around!
They gave me a lot of trouble!
W-What's this?
Ka... me... ha... me... Ha!!
Kakarrot!
We meet again, Vegeta!
It's the smell of cake!
Sheesh, these guys don't quit!
No matter how many times we beat them,
they just keep getting right back up!
Yeah... On top of that, they
ain't taking a bit of damage!
Th-This is bad!
Shortcake! Choux à la crème over
here! There's chocolate cake too!
W-What?!
W-W-What does this mean?!
Lucky! The instant he looked upon that cake,
his head became filled with thoughts of cake!
Now's your chance, both of you!
Where have Gohan and the others gone?
Have they been done in after all?
Hey, Kakarrot!
This way! They're here!
It's Piccolo.
Great! He ain't dead!
Hey, Vegeta, over there!
Gohan! Trunks! Goten! Everyone's here!
Finally, with great trouble,
Goku and Vegeta have
discovered Goten and the others.
Rescue Gohan and the others as
soon as you can, and defeat Majin Boo!
Before the Earth is destroyed!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Huh? What's this?
Boo has appeared inside Boo!
I thought something was funny,
and sure enough, it's you guys!
How dare you release
everyone that I've absorbed!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"A Majin's Secret!!
Two More Boos Inside Of Boo"
He's finally found them. Will we
be able to get out of here safely?
"Next time"
"A Majin's Secret!!
Two More Boos Inside Of Boo"