The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Goten and Trunks, having been
given sanctuary in Kami's palace,
finally regain consciousness.
The two have decided to learn Fusion,
a technique of unification, from Goku,
who has little time remaining in this world.
Okay, Kibit, restore Gohan-san's power.
Elsewhere, with Kaioshin and Kibit's help,
Gohan narrowly escapes death,
and is revived in the Kaioshin Realm.
Kaioshin-sama... W-Where is this...?
Use the Z-Sword to defeat Majin Boo!
Knowing you, Gohan-san, you should
certainly be able to use that blade!
This blade is the Z-Sword.
Please, pull it out.
Gohan challenges the
Z-Sword of the Kaioshin Realm,
said to be able to defeat even Majin Boo!
Will it prove to be the ultimate
weapon to defeat Majin Boo?
"It Came Ou~t!!
The Legendary Z-Sword."
You know, to think that
Gohan-kun, who even defeated Cell,
couldn't stand up to that meat roll...
Goku is now followed by Gohan...
And now, you gotta be feelin'
more sorry for Chichi than ever.
Hey, hey, hey! Everyone has
already decided they're dead,
even though we haven't
even found any bodies!
How come?!
It's strange that you should
know that Gohan-kun has died!
Look, we know how you feel,
but seeing as how we feel
absolutely no ki from him...
It must be that Gohan...
is no longer of this world....
I... don't believe it...
I... won't believe it!
I absolutely won't believe such a thing!
Gohan-kun...
All right!
Um, Kaioshin-sama, what
happens if I pull out this, er, Z-Sword?
It is said that you will
obtain tremendous power.
Yes, maybe even enough
power to exceed Majin Boo.
Really?
You suppose that means an
incredible capacity to cut? How dreadful!
Don't you worry.
You won't be able to draw it out.
Kibit, be quiet and watch on.
Okay, Gohan-san. Give it a try.
Right!
All right...
...why you lousy...!
Damn! Ow, ow, ow!
Are you all right, Gohan-san?
It's no good, it won't even budge.
Okay, okay, okay...!
Super Saiyan, huh? Well, I think
you'll have the same results.
It's no use!
How can a human extract something
so many Kaioshin-sama have
challenged and found unable to pull out?
Come on out!!
Look! He did it!
W-What?!
U-Unbelievable...!
How do you like it, Gohan-san?
The Legendary Z-Sword!
It's remarkably heavy.
R-Right now... I don't feel as if
I've gotten any incredible power...
Is that so?
I wonder if I can really
use this to defeat Majin Boo.
What are you saying?!
The Z-Sword is the mightiest
blade ever to come to this holy region!
It can surely defeat Majin Boo!
Of course, that might be impossible
if its bearer wields it so unsteadily.
Until you are freely
able to handle that blade,
you cannot very well
challenge anyone to battle.
You might say that, but try
holding this for a moment.
It really is incredibly heavy.
Ready? Here.
See? Just like I said.
W-Well, I suppose that's about right.
What's about right?
Good question.
In any case, you must become
able to freely use the Z-Sword!
R-Right...
Now listen. Even if your Fusion
succeeds and you join together,
you can only stay that
way for thirty minutes.
After thirty minutes, you return to normal.
Once you return to normal, you'll be
incapable of Fusion for a little while.
Only thirty minutes? That's pretty tough.
I think that, knowing these two,
if they can just do the Fusion,
they'll definitely defeat Majin Boo.
Fusion is just that fierce.
Okay, first, both of you turn Super Saiyan!
What's wrong?
Uncle, what were you doing when
Papa and Gohan-san were getting killed?
I was knocked out.
Knocked out? You were
unconscious at the time?
Are you sure you're not just a coward, Uncle?!
We're not going to become
stronger by learning techniques
from someone who doesn't
fight, but runs away and hides!
W-Why you rotten...! Goku is–!
It's okay, Piccolo.
I really am a coward. Unfortunately,
I ain't able to beat Majin Boo.
But even if I am a coward, I can
still teach you this Fusion technique.
If you really want to avenge
Vegeta and Gohan, this is the only way.
–What should we do?
–Even so...
Here I am again!
People of the Earth!
It's Madoshi Babidi and Majin Boo!
This time we've found a
city much larger than before!
This place is going to be wiped out!
That is, unless Ma Junior, Trunks, and Goten,
the three of you come here immediately!
Hey, this image, isn't this our city?!
No mistake about it! It's this city!
L-Look! O-Over there!
Majin Boo and him are there!
H-He's talking about us!
Trunks-kun, close your eyes and watch!
You can see Boo and him!
Don't look! You're better off not seeing!
Well, well, there's still no word
from those people themselves,
or from anyone else.
What a predicament! The casualties
are only going to increase!
I know, last time it was hard
candies, so... hmm, this time,
turn them all into chocolate
or whatever and eat them!
All right, Majin Boo, turn every
last person in this city into chocolate!
You turn into chocolate!
I-It can't be!
The townspeople, they all became choco!
"In Training"
Hey, isn't that Policious City?
No doubt about it! H-How can it be?!
What are you so upset about?
One who presumes himself to be a martial
artist is not perturbed by things such as this.
Besides which, you should be training!
Do not think about anything
else, and focus your mind!
Right!
Humans unmistakably can fly,
our bodies have just forgotten how
to use the power that allows us to.
Otherwise, Videl and those
others would not be able to fly!
All right, do it!
Now, let go!
Awake, my body, and grant me newfound power!
T-Terrible news, Mister Satan!
Fool! Haven't I always said that
during training, no one is permitted in?!
P-Pardon me. But there's terrible news!
W-What's this?
Our hero, Mister Satan! Please
defend the peace of our Earth!
You're up, Mister Satan! Put Majin Boo away!
Th-That's easy for you to tell me...
–Our Mister Satan!
–Satan, please!
Champion of justice, our hero!
Satan! Satan! Satan!
Ladies and gentlemen,
there is nothing to worry about!
Hiding nothing, I am currently training
to develop a new finishing technique!
As soon as the training
is finished, I, Mister Satan,
will punish that ridiculous Majin Boo
with the new finishing technique!
W-What do I do?!
'urp...!
W-Why those...!
Apparently, Majin Boo is full
from all that choco just now.
And so, we go on to the next city.
Let's see, which way should we go this time?
Babidi! Majin Boo!
You hear me?! This is Trunks!
This is Goten!
Well, well... At last, contact
from the people themselves.
Listen! Right now it's impossible,
but very soon, we are
absolutely going to slaughter you!
Absolutely!
Hey, stop speaking to Babidi!
He'll find out about this place!
Hey, where are you?
Where did you go? Come out here!
Are you hiding, you cowards?!
Let's do this Fusion training properly!
Goten and Trunks resolve to master Fusion.
At last, the training to
wipe out Majin Boo begins!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
This ain't good.
The Capsule Corporation's
location has been revealed to Babidi.
Son-kun, if the Dragon
Radar gets destroyed now,
the people who were killed
won't ever come back to life.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Metro West is Targeted!
Stop, Majin Boo!!"
We have to stop Boo somehow,
while the Radar is being fetched.
"Next time"
"Metro West is Targeted!
Stop, Majin Boo!!"