The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
At last, the seal was broken!
Er, is that Majin Boo?
Th-That's right! I would never
forget th-that terrifying face!
Finally, Majin Boo has been revived.
However, is a guy such as
this really all that strong?
"A Straight Line to Despair!?
The Grief of Kaioshin."
Wait, Vegeta!
A ki! An enormous ki has appeared!
He has emerged after all! Majin Boo!
Majin Boo, huh?
Here I was wondering how
incredible a brute he was,
and then he has this
sort of battle power rating?
I thought it would be something like this!
Listen, Kakarrot! We have
now become overly strong!
Altogether extraordinarily so!
Have you even once thought that Kaioshin,
who all else aside should be
this incredible guy, was impressive?
Just the opposite, Kaioshin has been the
one who was surprised by our power, right?
In other words, I'm saying that Kaioshin
may see Majin Boo as a fearsome enemy,
but from where we stand,
he's not all that formidable a guy.
N-No, that ain't it. There's something
different than usual about this ki!
Stop fretting around!
If you're trying to get out of
this fight, you're not going to!
Vegeta! You have to have realized it as well!
Hey, Majin Boo!
I-I'm Babidi, the child of
Bibidi, who created you!
I've revived you after you were sealed
up in your ball for an incredibly long time!
A-And so, starting
today, I will be your master!
Hey! What's the matter? Answer me!
You'll at least answer me! I am your master!
Hey, Majin Boo!
Hey, there!
W-What's the matter, Majin Boo?
He's a mere buffoon!
What is it he might be doing?
W-Why you...!
I do not know why, but it
appears his revival was unsuccessful.
Now that he has finally gone and appeared,
what is he but a mindless,
powerless, half-witted punk?
What is it? You have something to say to me?
I'm upset!!
What?! Are you saying you
want to have a go at Dabura-sama?
You don't know your own place!
That's why I say you're a fool!
It looks as though Majin Boo
has been botched, Kaioshin-sama!
Does it look like he was
botched? That is Majin Boo!
Worthless bravado!
M-Magnificent!
Incredible, Majin Boo!
To think how easily you defeated Dabura there!
Utterly magnificent!
It rose! Majin Boo's ki rose explosively!
H-He's strong! He's too strong!
Such unbelievable strength...!
It transformed into
an extraordinary ki there!
He's no ordinary guy after all, this Majin Boo!
J-Just now, for just a moment,
we felt an amazing ki, right?
Y-Yeah...
What's going on here, really?
Say, which way should we go?
Let's see... The ki over this
way is kind of a spooky ki, right?
The Majin must be this way!
Yeah! The Majin has to be more
interesting than the other, right?
Yeah!
All right! That settles it! Go!
That wasn't any kind of trick...
"Tenkaichi Tournament"
Who the hell are those guys?
Is there something...
Is there something about to happen again?
–Mister Satan, congratulations on your victory!
–Congratulations!
How was it? Any observations
about this tournament?
Well, of course, it ended
up just as I said, didn't it?
This ain't the time for us to
be doing something like this!
We're the ones that let that monster out!
Do I care?! It has nothing to do with our fight!
Everyone's going to be killed!
Everyone! Bulma and Trunks, too!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
I sold my soul over to Babidi in
order to wipe out that placidity!
It's none of my concern
what happens to anyone!
You're lying!
You're lying!!
You ain't sold your soul over entirely.
All right.
We'll postpone the fight.
After all, Majin Boo is apparently worrying you
and you can't seem to concentrate.
Vegeta!
Hand over one of those senzu things.
We've both lost quite a bit of power, after all.
If we all work together,
I'm sure we can beat Majin Boo!
Not even you could help
having been caught off guard.
I am the one who released Majin Boo,
and I will be the one to put him away.
Settling up with you will come afterward...
If I'm still alive.
Incredible! You're incredible!
Now, Majin Boo, do as I tell you!
I am your new master!
You defy me?
A-Are you sure it's okay to disobey me?
I've seen my papa's notes,
and I know something–the
spell to seal you up in your ball!
You don't want to go back in there, do you?
All right! That will do! That will do!
Kaioshin-sama, isn't Majin
Boo still something like a child?
If we defeat Babidi there, would he
perhaps not do such maniacal things?
Th-That won't do!
If Babidi is gone, then it will become
impossible to seal up Majin Boo again!
Despite how he appears, Majin
Boo is really a terrible monster!
Before long, he will grow
beyond Babidi's control,
and then, the time when he is
sealed up again is sure to come!
Until that time, all we
can do is patiently sit tight.
E-Even though I am a Kaioshin,
I am helplessly chagrined at
myself that there is nothing I can do.
It wasn't supposed to be like this.
I was sure I would be able to defeat
Babidi and halt Majin Boo's revival!
I-If I knew it was to be like this...
If I had known that
there were those such as you,
who even while being human, had
power which so greatly surpassed my own...
And despite having that other method...!
Other method?
No, it's too late.
We can no longer escape from Majin Boo.
The two of us will not likely return alive.
What are you saying?!
If it's just escaping, we can
manage something or other!
All right!
Okay, Majin Boo, this is your first command.
Kill those two there!
Kaioshin-sama!
It's okay! I can count on my speed!
What are you doing, Boo?
You're letting them get away!
H-He's disappeared!
It can't be!
You die!
W-What's this?! Majin Boo
is one extraordinary fellow!
He has wondrous speed and power!
Behind that merciless
smile lurks the terror of death!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
What a beast! Gohan's
full-power attack had no effect at all.
Now it's our turn! Majin Boo,
get them back good!
Go! Send them off into space!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Terrifying Majin!!
Death's Dread Draws Near Gohan."
"Next time"
"The Terrifying Majin!!
Death's Dread Draws Near Gohan"