Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
At last, Goku has recovered.
However, it is already too late.
A battle between Piccolo and the
Artificial Human No. 17 is already underway.
Too bad. That's a pity, isn't it?
Ha! I'm still just getting started!
This ki is that of Piccolo.
The opponents he would be
fighting at such a high power...
...could only be No. 17 and the others!
You just wait!
My power is far greater than yours!
Cell has begun moving out in earnest,
heading toward his perfect form!
What has been feared is now coming true.
"How I Have Waited for This Day!!
Cell's Prologue to Perfection."
For not even being an Artificial
Human, you have fantastic power.
It is certainly apparent that
you are not Piccolo Daimao.
Of course, I have no interest in your identity.
I only want to know where Son Goku is.
As usual, I don't suppose you
are of the mind to tell us, are you?
Your objective is to kill Goku.
There's no reason that
I should tell you where he is.
Well then, shall we continue the fight?
I think you'll come to want to speak.
This time, I'm fighting like I mean it!
Your speed is decent.
But your punches don't seem
to have enough weight behind them.
What was that?!
How nice of you to talk so big.
As you face the strongest man in history,
Artificial Human No. 17...
That guy really is strong.
He's evenly matched against No. 17.
Piccolo-san, hang in there!
Keep it up, Piccolo!
Until Vegeta and Trunks' training is finished...
Yeesh. How many islands
are you going to destroy
before you're satisfied?
A-Awesome. Piccolo still
seems to be hanging in there.
Dammit, are we just going to stay here like this?
How can this be?!
W-What's wrong?
H-He's coming closer! At a time like this...!
C-Cell?
I-It can't be!
I've waited a long time for this day to come!
The day when I become my perfect form!
Ah, there, there! There,
there! Googley googley goo!
Don't cry, now. Don't cry.
Bulma, I can't manage him!
This is the last frequency.
Once I finish punching in
this data, it will be complete!
Say, Dad, keep Trunks quiet a bit longer!
Yeah, well, you see...
You're his mother, ain'tcha?
Come look after yer baby
some! It's more'n I can stand!
'nbelievable! Bein' raised by
such a cold mother like this,
in time this kid's gonna go bad!
Horsefeathers! There's no
need to worry about that!
Trunks is going to become an incredibly
cool and handsome young man, after all.
Aren't you, Trunks?
Is it okay now? Are you finished?
With this, we'll be able to utterly
terminate Artificial Humans' actions!
My, my!
What do we do, Kuririn?
H-How can I answer something like that?
If this Cell monster were to
absorb the Artificial Humans now,
all of our hopes would vanish.
Damn!
Kuririn! Bulma's callin' on the phone for you!
Come take it!
She's sayin' somethin' about havin'
found a weakness in the Artificial Humans!
–What's that?!
–What?!
That's right!
No. 17 and No. 18 have
emergency shutdown circuitry...
...incorporated into their bodies!
Once we shut off activity in those circuits,
then no matter if they are Artificial Humans,
you can destroy them easily, right?
Yeah! I just completed
a controller that will do it!
Say, can we beat the Artificial Humans?
Uh huh...
Beg your pardon, but could
you bring it here right away?
Right now, Piccolo-san is fighting
with them–the Artificial Humans!
Sure! I'll leave right away!
Great! If we destroy No. 17 and the others,
Cell cannot become his perfect form!
Destroy, huh?
What is it?
I-It's nothing.
Well, I'm off.
Take good care, if you please.
What's this "if you please"?!
You were gonna leave
here all by yerself, weren'cha?
The Earth is in great danger! Let me go!
F-Father! Cell has... Cell has started to move!
Yeah. I know.
Still not yet?
Vegeta is extremely gifted.
He should have overcome
the Super Saiyan wall long ago.
Please hurry, Vegeta.
What will happen cannot be undone!
Our powers may be evenly matched,
but there appears to be a gap
widening between our stamina.
My energy will never drop!
C-Cell!
At length, Cell has appeared!
Has the time at last come...
...for him to merge with No. 17 and No. 18?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Damn, what a ki. Cell has
raised his power like crazy.
Stop, Piccolo! Not even you're a match for him!
Curse you, Cell! Just how
many people have you sacrificed!?
There's no way I'm letting
you reach your perfect form!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Suicide Counterattack Proves Ineffective!
Piccolo's Flame Burns Out!!"
Oh, no! Piccolo-san's ki is fading out!
"Next time"
"The Suicide Counterattack Proves Ineffective!
Piccolo's Flame Burns Out!!"