Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
At last, Goku had advanced to the
final round of the Anoyoichi Tournament,
where he would fight Paikuhan.
Th-That's impossible!
During the battle, Paikuhan
acknowledged Goku's power,
and removed the weighted gear
that he wore to train himself with.
In that case, me too...
"Don't Let Victory Get Away!!
Finish With an Ultra-Fast Kamehame-Ha."
W-What sort of man is this?
His ki is rising sharply!
W-What could this be?!
Contestant Goku has transformed,
and there is a golden glow about his body!
W-What?
W-What in the world happened to that kid?
Don't be so surprised. Goku has
just turned Super Saiyan, that's all.
Super...
...Saiyan, did you say?
That's right. You see, to put it simply,
so that even you can understand,
up until now, Goku hasn't meant business.
That's what this means.
What?!
Don't forget our bet, Kaio of the West!
If Goku wins, West Kaio's World is mine.
I know!
But as for not meaning business,
the same goes for Paikuhan, too!
E-Exactly what kind of fight are we
going to see unfold before us now?!
I cannot even make a prediction!
I ain't going to make any predictions either.
Kamehame...
...Ha!
You ain't getting away!
Over here, Goku!
When did he have time to get over there?
I wasn't able to read his movement at all!
By transforming, your power
appears to have risen quite a bit.
But even so, you still
can't keep up with me, huh?
I was expecting something a little better.
Take this! Hyper Tornado!!
D-Don't forget our bet, Kaio of the North!
I-I know!
What?
Goku! Your body has reached its limits!
W-What?!
Super Kaio-ken!!
Ka... me...
ha... me...
Ha!
What?!
He was so close! Just a little bit further and...
I-Incredible! It's not surprising
that the guys from my galaxy
didn't reach the second round like this.
It'll be another 500 years before
they're ready to fight those boys!
Grand Kaio-sama, it
looks like after all this time,
there's going to be a martial
artist good enough to receive
the Grand Kaio-sama's
personal training, doesn't it?
Th-That's right. I did make that promise,
didn't I? I had completely forgotten.
I-I'm impressed you could take it this far.
Frankly, you're better than I anticipated.
That's because you're so strong.
When I fight against those who are strong,
I get happy, and become high-spirited.
The same goes for me about being happy,
enough so that I hate to have to end this.
What?!
Thunder...
...Flash!!
Thunder... Flash!!
I-Incredible...
It's almost as if that technique
ain't got any vulnerabilities...
He's going to get me!
Thunder...
...Flash!!
I almost got burned to a crisp!
O-Our ring, which we worked so hard to build!
Th-That lousy Paikuhan!
He launched that technique,
knowing that I was here!
I'm going to have to chew him out good later!
W-What in the world is happening up there?
I can't tell.
Contestant Paikuhan and
Contestant Goku have both risen so high,
we are unable to see them!
Just what is going on
with the match right now!?
Not bad...
Kamehame-Ha!!
I shot at him head-on,
and he evaded it with ease!
All right, now to finish you.
I'll knock you out of the
ring with my Thunder Flash!
Yikes!
Stay calm...
there has to be a vulnerability
somewhere in that technique.
Spot it!
Thunder...
Now!
...Flash!!
Kameha...
me...
Ha!!
C-Contestant Paikuhan is out of bounds!
The winner of the Anoyoichi
Tournament is Contestant Son Goku!
You got me.
You shouldn't have launched
your Thunder Flash all of three times.
It was that third time that
I first saw your motions clearly.
I see. You really are something else.
Train hard with the Grand Kaio-sama.
I'll keep training, so I don't fall
behind, and beat you next time for sure.
Yeah. But then, I ain't
going to fall behind, either.
Goku won! Goku won!
So then, I guess I'll be
taking West Kaio's World, huh?
Y-Yeah, I know!
And so, will the victorious
Contestant Goku please join me over here!
Just a moment!
Since there was a rule
violation during this match,
both Goku-chan and
Paikuhan-chan are disqualified!
Goku-chan, you and
Paikuhan-chan did indeed
touch foot on the ceiling of this arena, right?
The ceiling?
Yeah, we touched it.
According to Article 1351 of this
Anoyoichi Tournament rulebook,
the arena's ceiling and floor
are regarded as one and the same.
The reason being that if
you turn the ring upside-down,
the ceiling becomes the floor.
That's what it says here.
Grand Kaio-sama, after
everything that happened,
isn't that asking too much?
I-It can't be!
That's a fantastic rule violation!
Fantastic! Fantastic!
Is that right? I guess I can't
help it if I broke the rules.
That's right. But you two did fight very well,
so if you train for another
two or three hundred years,
I wouldn't mind having another look at you.
Two or three hundred years, huh?
All right, I'll do my best!
Phew, thank goodness!
Lately, I've been slacking off in my training,
and I'd probably get tuckered out
training with Goku-chan at his pace.
As such, Goku came to live
out his days in the Next World
in merry, spirited training.
And so, seven years' time went by...
Okay, Mother, I'm off!
Oh, just a minute, Gohan!
Here! You forgot this!
For cryin' out loud,
you're just like Goku-sa when
it comes to bein' scatterbrained.
Okay, Mother, I'll be back soon.
Uh-huh. Make sure you listen
to what the teachers tell you.
Right.
Kinto Un!
Don't go speedin' too fast, now!
Son Gohan, not having any schools as
such out in the country where he lived,
had relied upon self-study
and correspondence courses
from home up until now,
but his mother, Chichi, decided
that that alone wasn't enough,
and so starting today,
he would start going to
a high school in Satan City.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
You sure have grown up, Gohan.
I hear that starting today,
you're going to high school in the city.
Gohan, you don't have to punish bank robbers,
and other dangerous stuff.
Go straight to school, and study hard.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"7 Years Since Then!
Starting Today, I'm a High School Student."
It sure is hard being normal
without people finding out who I am.
"Next time"
"7 Years Since Then!
Starting Today, I'm a High School Student"