The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
The third match of the Tenkaichi Tournament,
between Videl and Spopovitch, has begun.
Videl, having received Gohan's training,
should have won easily. However...
Just what kind of mystery is hidden
within this unusual strength of Spopovitch's?
"A Tragic Videl!!
Are You Coming Out, Angry Super Gohan?"
H-How can this be?!
Contestant Spopovitch is also flying!
It can't be!
H-Hey, do you suppose this
flying thing is becoming a trend?
U-Unbelievable! He can do that? Spopovitch?
Absurd!
How is it he too can fly?
A Kikoha blast?!
What kind of guy is this?!
Th-That lousy creep!
It wasn't all that powerful,
but he used a Kikoha on her!
Not quite!
By killing her, he would lose.
He purposely kept the blast weak.
Why would he?
He seems to have a lot more power
than his own abilities can account for.
He shouldn't have the kind of power it takes
to use the Bukujutsu and Kikoha techniques.
So what does it all mean?
I don't know. How is it he
came to possess such power?
I don't care who or what he is!
I'm Videl! I'm the daughter of
Mister Satan, who defeated Cell!
I am going to beat him for sure!
Contestant Videl is down!
Was that the decisive blow?
Oh, Contestant Videl has not yet given up!
With her indomitable fighting
spirit, she's trying to get up.
W-Who were you expecting would give up?
What?!
Th-This is terrible!
What kind of guy is he?
Stop, already!
If this keeps up, it'll mess up Videl's face!
It doesn't look like she's going
to get off as easy as just that!
Hmm, they say my first round
opponent is a woman, so when I win,
I'd better not strike too much of a "guts pose"
or it'll look like I'm being sarcastic...
This would be playing it up
too much to the spectators.
Hmm. It sure is hard having
a woman for an opponent.
Mister Satan!
Videl-san is having the daylights
beaten out of her by Spopovitch!
You've misspoken.
You mean Spopovitch is having the
daylights beaten out of him by Videl.
No, that isn't...
I'm very busy right now!
I don't need these updates, just tell
me what the outcome of the match is.
The outcome that Videl has won, that is.
R-Right...
Don't toy with me!
Contestant Spopovitch
has thrown Contestant Videl!
This could be all for her. Defeat by Ringout!
I-It's no use! I don't have the power left to fly.
Oh! Contestant Spopovitch has saved
Contestant Videl from a Ringout loss!
What could he be thinking?
Videl-san...
He's just playing around now.
However, Contestant Videl is not getting up.
Could she be unconscious?
Reluctantly, I must begin the count.
That's enough! That's enough!
Just keep lying there like that.
Don't get up! You can't get up!
"Martial"
Oh, she's up! Contestant Videl has gotten up!
Such perseverance!
What wonderful force of mind!
She's gotten up...
It's senseless! He's out of
the ordinary! Concede, already!
V-Videl-san!
Th-This is terrible!
Contestant Spopovitch is beating
Contestant Videl black and blue!
That bastard...
That's enough! Please, concede, Videl-san...
I guess Videl-san's match must
be over by now. That's too bad.
It's all right! Videl-san
will last until the final round,
so she has plenty of matches to go.
It's terrible, it's terrible!
Videl-san is getting beaten senseless!
What?!
Hurry up! With our support, we can
cheer some spirit back into Videl-san!
Yeah!
Dammit! Stop already!
Videl-chan is going to die!
You've held up long enough! Concede!
Concede, already! Videl-san!
Videl-san, I agree with what
the Great Saiyaman-san is saying.
Don't you think it best if you concede?
N-No way!
I'll never concede!
W-Why are you being so stubborn?!
You're really going to get killed here!
He's not holding back because you're a girl,
he doesn't have that kind of compassion!
That's awful! How could he?!
V-Videl!
You bastard!
Damn you! Any more and I'll arrest you!
H-Hey, Gohan, relax!
It's all right, she ain't going to die.
Th-This is terrible! Contestant Spopovitch,
I can't believe these are
the actions of a human being!
A-Ain't there anythin' left that can be done?
If this keeps up, that girl will be
dead before she marries Gohan!
Gohan...
No!
I don't... I don't want to lose!
Why you... You're going to
pay now. You damned bastard!
H-Hey!
This isn't right! Calm down, Gohan!
No way!
Stop!!
The goofing around ends now, Spopovitch!
I don't believe this is what we came here to do.
Hurry up and win!
R-Ringout! Contestant Spopovitch wins.
Videl-san!
Um, should I call for a stretcher?
No, I'll carry her.
Spopovitch!
You'll pay for this! Every last bit of you!
You got that?!
Kuririn, do you have any senzu?
No. We all came here half for the fun of it, so...
I see. All right.
I'll go up to where
Karin-sama is and bring some back.
Relax, Gohan! Goku has just
gone off to get some senzu!
Senzu? Really? All right!
W-W-What?!
Videl has massive injuries and was defeated?
Y-Yes.
B-But that's impossible!
Videl should be the strongest
in the world, second only to me!
That fool! She must have got caught up
in her techniques and dropped her guard!
Videl! Videl!
Videl!
Th-This is awful!
It's all right. There's no threat to her life.
Who the hell are you?!
Are you the one who did this to my daughter?
No, not him.
This boy kindly carried her in this far.
O-Oh yeah, that's right.
Her opponent was Spopovitch, huh?
Nice job. I'll give you an autograph later.
Right, thanks.
Well, you're in our way here, you can leave now.
Right.
G-Gohan-kun...
Get... get him for me...
Once I win this next match,
I'll meet him in the second round!
What are you saying, Videl?
That crazy kid doesn't have a chance!
I will be the one who takes out Spopovitch!
I-I-It can't be!
You two aren't together, are you?!
I-I won't allow it! Especially not
that aggravatingly weak looking boy!
I say it all the time, don't I?
You can't have a boyfriend
unless he's stronger than your Papa!
Silence.
Here are your senzu.
Thank you, Karin-sama!
Now then, you mustn't let
your defenses down, Goku.
I have a bad feeling about
what's about to happen.
Yeah.
So do I.
What is this "bad feeling"
that Karin-sama also has?
Is there something extreme waiting
to happen at this Tenkaichi Tournament?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Gohan, your friends are in the stands cheering,
and it looks like they've
seen through your disguise.
Gohan-kun, good luck!
You look better without the sunglasses!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Exposed!! The Saiyaman is Son Gohan."
Oh, no. If the others find
out what my real power is,
I won't be able to go to school anymore.
"Next time"
"Exposed!! The Saiyaman is Son Gohan"