Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Having finished his training in the
Next World, Goku rushes to the battlefield.
However, the ferocity of
the Saiyans knows no bounds.
You brat!
This is where it ends!
Die!
"Ferocity of the Saiyans!
Kami-sama and Piccolo Both Die."
Die!
P-Piccolo-san!
Get out of here... Gohan...
Piccolo-san! W-Why did you... save me?
I-I told you to get out
of here... Hurry, or else...
D-Don't die! Father will be
here soon to beat him for us!
Please, don't die!
Miserable fool! My killing order might
have gotten switched around, but oh well.
Either way, it will all turn out the same.
One ki is rapidly growing smaller.
I-Is somebody dying!?
K-Kami-sama...
I-It looks like my life is about at
its end... G-Goku didn't make it in time...
H-However, at the very end, Piccolo
surpassed even me, Kami... I'm so pleased...
Kami-sama!
W-What a pitiful tale...
Imagine, Piccolo Daimao,
of all people, protecting some kid...
Nothing could be worse...
U-Uncle!
Gohan... you're the only one
who ever spoke decent to me...
T-This last year that
I spent with you wasn't bad...
Uncle!
Don't you die, G-Goha–
Mister Popo, I leave the rest to you...
Kami-sama!
G-Gohan...
Interesting! You want to fight?
Masenko!
T-That's an incredible ki!
700... 1,200...
2,400...
Battle power 2,800?!
Sure enough, these guys can
alter their battle powers intensely!
2,800, huh?
Gohan!
For a kid, you can do
some amazing things, huh?
My arm tingles a little.
His battle power just plummeted.
It looks like he used up
all of his power just now.
T-They're too strong...
T-They're just too strong...
–Let go of me!
–See here, Chichi Calm down!
–Let me go, I say!
–Come now, Chichi-san...
–Let me go!
–H-Hold on, now, that's dangerous...
–Come on, calm down, okay? It's not safe.
T-That's dangerous like that! Stop that!
Aren't you spirited?
–Uranai Baba!
–Sis!
Goku just passed by Karin Tower.
But will he be in time?
I know! Even without a TV,
we can always watch what's
happening using Baba's crystal ball!
Don't be ridiculous! You want to
use my sacred crystal ball to do that?!
–What are you doing?!
–Never mind, just come on inside!
Piccolo-san, I'm sorry.
I wasn't able to avenge you.
Gohan! Run! Get out of there!
Pipsqueak, I'm sending you
to the Next World for sure this time.
I don't have the strength to run away anymore.
D-Damn it all!
I can't wait to see the
look on Kakarrot's face...
...when he sees his own son smashed to a pulp!
Kinto Un?
What is that?
Father!
G-Goku!
So you've finally shown up, huh?
G-Goku! We've been waiting for you!
Father!
What have you come all this way for, Kakarrot?
Don't tell me you're here
to tell us some nonsensical joke,
such as you've come
to defeat us, or something.
Piccolo...
Piccolo-san died to protect me.
Tenshinhan...
Yamucha...
Shocked over your dead idiot friends, are you?
Come to think of it, there was another,
puny little guy, that went to pieces.
He had more power than
you'd expect for such a runt.
Naturally, he was no match for Nappa-sama.
Is that so? Even Chaozu?
And Kami-sama, too... Damn...
There's no need to grieve for them.
You'll be joining your friends soon.
After going through all the
trouble to come back to life,
you just had to stroll on by, huh?
His battle power is rising higher and higher.
W-What? You want to die already?
Here's something by way of greeting!
He's fast!
Gohan, over here.
Kuririn...
G-Goku...
Sorry I'm late. Way to hang on, you two.
Each of you eat half of this.
I-Isn't that a senzu bean?
K-Karin-sama still has them, huh?
Mm-hmm. This is the last one.
T-Then, you eat it.
That's all right. I ate one before I came.
N-No, you save it in case you need it.
Even if we recover, we
won't be much help to you.
Don't worry needlessly.
If you don't eat it, I'm throwing it away.
Here.
Thanks.
Gohan, you too.
Kuririn, you've gotten a lot
stronger, huh? I can tell by your ki.
I thought I had, but to no avail.
I'm no use against them. They're too strong.
I-I just stood by and let everyone else die...
Gohan, I hardly recognized
you, too. You sure trained hard.
Mm-hmm. Piccolo-san trained
me, but I wasn't able to do anything.
With Piccolo-san dead, we'll never
be able to use the Dragon Balls again.
No one is coming back to life.
Let's avenge them–the three of us!
With you joining us, Goku, we
might be able to deal with one of them!
Hey, Goku, you trained under
some incredible guy named Kaio, right?
Yeah.
But I'm going to fight them by myself.
You guys stay back and watch, so
you don't get caught in the middle of it.
B-By yourself?!
No matter how strong
you are, Goku, that's crazy!
Their strength is far
greater than we can even imagine!
H-He's right, Father!
G-Goku...
Father!
Let Goku handle this!
B-But...
I've never seen Goku show that much anger.
W-We've got no place getting in his way.
Remember, you're going to be
paying me a viewing fee for this.
Goku!
Goku-sa!
Where's Gohan?!
Gohan!
G-Gohan is alive! T-Thank goodness...
Chichi! Goku and Gohan
are fightin'! Keep it together!
Son-kun, hang in there! Beat those Saiyans!
P-Piccolo!
Even Piccolo has been done in!
Which means we can no
longer use the Dragon Balls!
T-Then, nobody is coming back to life?
What's with that look
on your face? I don't like it.
Is this how badly you
want me to effortlessly kill you?
You're going to pay for this!
Father, you're incredible!
Battle power 7,000... 8,000... impossible!
What is Kakarrot's battle power?!
Higher than 8,000!
Higher than 8,000?! There has to
be some mistake! It's a malfunction!
Don't worry, I still won't be
using the Kaio-ken technique on you.
Kaio-ken?
Shut up!
There's no way you can
stand up to Nappa-sama!
What?
H-How did he do that just now?
W-When did you get behind me?
Why, you!
For as big as you were
talking, you ain't all that great.
W-What did you say?!
I-I'm not all that great, am I?!
That's right. I could tell
from your attack just now.
Why don't you tell me...
...exactly what it is that you can tell?!
Strange... His battle power is completely
different from when he fought Raditz.
Over here!
D-Did you see your father's moves?
But he's amazing.
What's going on?
How did Kakarrot get this much
power in such a short amount of time?
Why, you!
That punch just now was for Chaozu.
Goku is strong!
But will Goku be able to protect the
Earth from the hands of the Saiyans?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Woah, awesome! I ain't ever
seen anyone as awesome as this guy!
Brace yourself! Your life will only
last for a moment against Vegeta!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Father is Awesome! Kaio-ken,
the Ultimate Finishing Technique."
Father, avenge Piccolo-san!
"Next time"
"Father is Awesome! Kaio-ken,
the Ultimate Finishing Technique"