The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Majin Boo was beginning to
display an unexpected kindness.
However, two gunshots changed everything!
Satan...!
Run away! Take the dog... far away! You'll die!!
Boo's intense anger had given
birth to another, purely evil Boo.
There are two Majin Boos!
What is going to happen to the Earth?!
"Which One Will Win!?
A Good-and-Evil Boo-Boo Confrontation."
Who are you?!
–I'm Majin Boo!
Th-There are two Majin Boos!
W-What is going on?!
H-Hang in there, Majin Boo!
What are you doing, Majin Boo?!
Get him! Get him, Majin Boo!
Don't you lose, Majin Boo!
They're both Majin Boo, huh?
That sure makes it hard to root for him.
What does this mean, exactly?
I feel a tremendously evil ki coming
from the new one that came out.
It's probable that the evil part within Boo
has surged up and has been spewed out!
Nice going, Boo! Attaway! Keep it up like that!
This is bad! There's no
chance the original Boo can win!
When they split in two, the evil Boo
took most of their power with him!
At this rate...!
You must be tired, Goten. Here, drink up!
Trunks! Goten! What are you doing?
We're going to train right now!
Again? I want to rest a little.
We just barely got back here.
You saw the power we had
during our Fusion, right?!
Leave the destruction of Boo to us!
Don't get so full of yourself!
We must make your
Fusion even more impeccable!
Your power is still not enough!
There's no time to be playing around!
If things continue, everyone
will be done in by this new Boo!
Piccolo, what are you lordin'
it over on them so much for?!
Don't go bullyin' Goten around just
because you figure Goku-sa is gone!
B-Bullying?
That's right! Who do you think you are?!
Goten and Trunks are still children!
This is usually the time they'd
be takin' their naps, you know!
If you keep up nothing but
their special training like this,
then when the time comes,
they'll be all tired out and get beaten!
Let them rest for a little while!
A-All right. So then, for a
short while, we'll take a break.
But after you've rested a bit, we're
going to train even harder than before!
Yeah!
–I'm hungry! Let's go eat something, Goten!
–Yeah!
Don't go overdoin' it, Goten!
You're still a child, after all!
In a pinch, you can leave
the fightin' up to the adults!
Okay, mother!
You too, Trunks! Got it?
I got it!
Will that be all right, do you think?
There's still one day left before the
appointed time. We'll manage something.
I-I'll turn you into chocolate!
H-He's turned into something
funny again! W-What's going on?!
W-What is this?!
Goten, don't panic! Stay calm! Stay calm!
Huh?
What's that?
It's coming from Earth, huh?
Is that Majin Boo?
That's an incredible ki! I wonder
what in the world is happening on Earth.
H-How can this be?!
Hey, Piccolo, what was that just now?
Majin Boo has transformed!
Thanks to some foolish Earthling,
he has become pure evil,
and his body is now more suited to fighting.
Th-This... This means...!
W-What, Piccolo? Don't tell
me this means more trouble!
I-It's all right! Trunks and
Goten have their Fusion!
Goku said Fusion was the
strongest there is, didn't he?
This ki is enormous!
What in the world is happening?
A good question.
U-Um,
can I ask you to please
power me up a little faster?
At this rate, the Earth itself,
which I have to save, will be lost!
Don't worry so. I'm doing it full-tilt.
I don't expect that you are.
Die!!
He's gone! He's gone! H-He was afraid!
He was afraid of me,
Mister Satan, and ran away!
I know it! I know he did!
That's only right! I am the
strongest man in the world!
Not even Majin Boo is so
reckless that he would fight with me!
H-He heard that...!
Sa... tan...
B-Boo... We're saved...!
He still remembers me...!
Piccolo-san, what do you
suppose will happen to the Earth now?
In any case, all we can do is
strengthen Trunks and Goten.
Those two half-pints are the
last card we have left to play.
Once the break is over,
we'll begin training immediately!
I'm full, I'm full!
Now that my stomach is full,
I've become sleepy.
Me too! How about we take a nap?
Yeah!
Trunks, before you take a nap,
make sure you take a shower!
Goten! Same goes for you!
Yeah, we know.
–Trunks-kun, let's take one together!
–No way, take it by yourself!
What's the matter, Piccolo?!
He's coming! He's headed for this temple!
Ah, hell!
This Majin Boo is able to seek out our ki!
Majin Boo, having become the very essence
of evil, has at length intruded at the temple!
Gohan is still in the middle of his training.
Is there anything that can actually be done?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
It's no use. If we let Boo fight
Goten and Trunks now, they can't win.
What are we supposed to do?
We have to buy some time
somehow. If we had just one hour,
we could get them to train
in the Room of Spirit and Time.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"A No-Timeout Catastrophe!!
Earth's Humanity Exterminated."
How could this happen?
The remaining people on
earth have become casualties!
"Next time"
"A No-Timeout Catastrophe!!
Earth's Humanity Exterminated"