Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Don't get too full of yourself, kid.
You don't seriously think
that you can defeat me, do you?
I'll defeat you, all right.
Faced with Gohan
demonstrating his true strength,
Cell had finally begun fighting at his full power.
W-Why, after only two punches...?!
Gohan had already gone over the top.
"Something Amiss With Cell!!
His Perfect Form Crumbles."
Hey, haven't you got the camera fixed yet?
Uh, just a little bit longer.
Well then, hurry up and at least fix the mike.
This is the moment of the
century, when Cell is done in!
Why, you...!
Stop mocking me!
How can something like this happen?!
I'm Cell, in my perfect form!
I am not about to lose to
the likes of that Saiyan kid!
I am the one who is the ultimate warrior,
who stands at the peak of all things!
Kienzan discs!
Gohan...!
Take this!
What?!
He caught them! He caught the Kienzan!
Impossible!
Gohan-san...!
Don't you take my... my infinite,
perfect power, and dismiss it!
Now what are you going to do?!
Not a thing.
Why, you...
Take this!
H-How can this be?
How can I be letting this happen?
All right! I've made up my mind!
I'm going to make that bento
salesboy my number one pupil!
Then, what about our positions?
What happens to us?
You fools! You guys are expressly expelled!
Y-You don't mean it!
How nice for you, Mister Satan!
With that boy along, the Satan
Dojo will become even more glorious!
Probably so, probably so.
U-Um, Mister Satan...
The way I see it,
that bento salesboy appears to
have abilities far greater than yours.
No. His fighting style is still too slack!
If I were to coach him in actual combat practice,
I could make him even stronger!
How can he be showing off this
much difference in power against Cell?
I-It's unbelievable, huh?
Gohan...
At that moment, Cell distinctly felt fear.
He then regretted having angered Son Gohan,
and drawing out his true
power, just for the fun of it.
Ka...
me...
ha...
That bastard...!
me...
Take this! A full-power Kamehame-Ha!
If you dodge it, the Earth will be blown away!
You have to take it on!
Don't do it! You've got to be kidding!
Ha!!
I-It's over...!
Ka...
me...
ha...
Ha!!
What?!
I-It's overwhelming...!
That runt! He repelled Cell's
ridiculously large Kamehame-Ha
with an even bigger Kamehame-Ha...!
I can sense his ki!
Cell is still alive!
That's impossible!
Sure enough, he's surpassed me.
Ever since that moment, he's
been beyond the Super Saiyan barrier.
That's it, Gohan!
You've gotten so you can
control your ki pretty well.
O-Oh, no! I put more power
into that without realizing it!
Come on, Gohan. Let's call it a day already.
We've been at it for 20 hours straight, after all...
F-Father...!
We're done... already...?
What an awesome ki!
He's completely surpassed me!
You've surpassed me,
and put Cell away. Well done!
H-How...? How can he
have that much power...?
No! Cell has my cells included in his!
He can still regenerate
from that degree of injury!
Gohan!
Gohan, finish him off! Finish him right now!
Finish him already?
It's too soon, Father!
I've got to make this guy suffer some more!
W-What?
What's he saying?
Gohan...
Gohan! You're the only one who
can finish Cell off! Do it quickly!
Don't push him any more!
There's no telling what he'll do!
Dammit...
Dammit... dammit... dammit...!
Damn it all!!
Not by you...!
There's no way my perfect form
can be beaten by the likes of you!
Why, you...!
He may have increased his power,
but he can't keep up with his speed!
Cell isn't aware of his own mistake!
He's flown into a frenzy!
I-I'm not done yet...!
W-What?
Cell's condition has changed!
It couldn't be...!
That's what it is, all right.
Cell's ki just dropped sharply.
Just as I thought.
He can no longer remain in his perfect form.
What exactly do you mean?
I-Is that...?!
N-No. 18! He threw up No. 18!
The Artificial Human that Cell swallowed...!
It's all over now.
Having spat up No. 18,
will Cell's perfect form collapse?
Or something else...?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Cell is swelling up...
He's going to blow himself up,
and the whole world with him!
This fight ends in a draw.
I may die, but the earth will be lost, too!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Bye-Bye, Everyone!!
Goku's Last Instantaneous Movement."
It's my fault... It's my
fault that Father will die!
"Next time"
"Bye-Bye, Everyone!!
Goku's Last Instantaneous Movement"