The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Vegeta!
It's Babidi's magic! Please, calm your heart!
The magic of the great Madoshi Babidi,
who is intent on reviving
Majin Boo, has enslaved even Vegeta!
"Tenkaichi Tournament"
Vegeta!
Vegeta commits the utmost in
destruction at the Tenkaichi Tournament!
The warrior, steeped mind and
body in wickedness, now attacks Goku.
"The Super-confrontation of Destiny!!
The Clash of Goku vs. Vegeta."
Vegeta-san! How could you?!
What's this? There's something about Vegeta...
I've never felt a ki like this before.
What's the matter with you, Vegeta?
What kind of guy do you suppose
this Majin is? I wonder if he's strong.
You don't suppose our Papas
have already defeated him, do you?
Oh, no!
Well, figure, there's my Papa, and your old man,
on top of which there's Gohan-san.
No matter what kind of guy he
may be, they're going to beat him!
No, no, no! That's no fun at all!
I want to see this Majin Boo guy!
Okay! Well, let's fly even harder, Goten!
Yeah!
Great! Great! 200 people just died!
"Tenkaichi Tournament"
What should we do, Mister Satan?
W-What should we do, you ask?
Save us, Satan!
Beat that guy for us!
Satan! Get him!
Mister Satan... I mean, Champion...
That's right! I am the World Champion!
No matter the opponent, it
will not do for me to run away!
S-See here! You guys!
What the hell do you
think you're doing?! Huh?!
Hey! You pull a selfish stunt like that,
a-and I, the World Champion,
Mister Satan, will...!
Mister Satan will...!
Satan will...
What is it you'll do?
Guys, violence won't do now, no violence!
Don't break anything, and fight more fairly!
Afterward, I will especially
take on the winner at their leisure–
Aay!
What are you going to do, Kakarrot?
Fight against me! Unless you want
to add to this mountain of bodies!
Vegeta, don't tell me you...
Don't tell me you fell under
Babidi's spell on purpose.
That can't be...
Answer me, Vegeta!!
Help me!
Please stop, Vegeta-san!
Out of the way!!
Stay back, small fry!
This fight is between me and Kakarrot!
Vegeta, no matter what?
You mustn't, Goku-san!
If you were to fight here, you
would play right into Babidi's hands!
Your energy would be absorbed, and
Majin Boo will most assuredly be revived!
Vegeta, you let yourself fall under Babidi's spell
and lost your self-control, and did all this,
all in order to get me serious.
Am I wrong?
What's that?
If I hadn't done all this,
you wouldn't have fought me!
In only one day, you'll
disappear from this world.
And yet all this gets in the way!
S-So for that... just for that,
you've done this foolish thing?
Foolish thing?!
Foolish thing, you say?!!
This is everything to me!
It does not matter to me
what happens with Majin Boo or anything else!
He... he surpassed my strength!
He is a Saiyan, same as me, yet he outpaced me!
Me! The prince, at the height
of his overwhelming power!
I-I've even had my life saved by him!
I cannot forgive him for that! Absolutely not!!
Babidi! Change us to a place
where no one else is around!
I have decided to fight Vegeta!
Look, we did it! We did it!
Just a moment!
If you're going to confront him no matter what,
then do it after you have defeated me!
F-Father...!
Understood.
Do as you like.
I'm sorry, Kaioshin-sama.
They've started fighting amongst themselves!
Take that, lousy Kaioshin!
The return of Majin Boo
is now just a matter of time.
As you wish, I will change your location!
Papparapa!
Huh? They vanished!
Where on earth do you suppose
they've disappeared to, Mister Satan?
Damn! And I was just about ready
to beat some punishment into them!
You shouldn't have any
complaints about this place.
Nope.
You can't, Father!
It is all right.
Having come to this, there is nothing we can do.
You two feel free to fight.
Son Gohan-san and I will
break through this entrance
and go fight with Babidi and Dabura.
We cannot help that applying such a shock
might mean Majin Boo could emerge.
In this event, it is better than having
your damage energy taken from you
and allowing Majin Boo
to be revived at full power.
If we are fortunate, we may be
able to prevent his revival entirely.
What was that?
You think I'm going to allow that?
Vegeta, stop them!
Kill those who are in our way!
Kill them!
Vegeta, kill those who are in our way! Kill them!
Is this Babidi's magic?
Go, Vegeta! Kill them!
Do it! Do them in!
–I refuse!
–What?!
Whatever Kaioshin and the
others do is none of my concern!
I-I'm going to say this one more time,
okay? You are to put Kaioshin away!
Well, Vegeta?
Like I said, all I want to do is fight Kakarrot!
I-I am the proud prince of the Saiyans!
You think I would allow
myself to become your serf?
You may control my body and my heart,
but at least you will not have your way...
with my pride!!
This is the first time something
like this has happened!
What a man of pride he is!
It does not matter, does it, Babidi-sama?
In any case, his role is to take energy, after all.
Even if Kaioshin does come, he
can do nothing so long as I am here.
Besides, is it not what you wanted?
To see Kaioshin die before your very eyes?
U-Unbelievable!
To think there's a person that could
defy Babidi while being controlled by him!
So, this is how badly you wanted
to settle things between us, Vegeta?
If anything, would it not be better for us
to open the door and
allow Kaioshin to come here?
It would not do if he forces it
open and traumatizes the ship,
forcing Majin Boo's return before
he attains his perfect power, would it?
Indeed. You're right, I got you.
He opened it himself!
He would be disserved if
his spaceship were damaged.
Well, Father, we're off!
Mm, hang in there!
Ah, hold up, Gohan!
There's still two senzu left.
They're what are left over from
what you gave your girlfriend.
Eat one before you go. You must
have used quite a bit of power earlier.
Th-Thanks.
Get angry, Gohan! Get angry, remember
what happened when you fought Cell,
and call up all the power you possess!
G-Get angry?
If you do, you can't lose to any
kind of guy in the whole world!
Any kind of guy, you hear?
Right. But Father...
It's a shame your one
precious day turned out this way.
Well, we're off!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
I have waited, Kakarrot!
I have been waiting so long for this!
I do not want to take damage from you
and contribute it to Majin Boo's energy.
I'm going to end this quickly,
with my highest power!
I look forward to it. You'll show me
the fruits of your training in the Other World.
As I expected. Even greater than
the power Gohan had back then.
Judging by that, it doesn't look
like this is going to end quickly.
Here we go! I'll kill you, Kakarrot!
The determination of Goku,
who turned aside even Kaioshin!
The pride of Vegeta, who
thrust aside Babidi's orders!
Vegeta versus Goku! The most
incomparable conflict in history,
one nobody is able to stop, begins now!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
While I'm fighting Vegeta, somehow or other
you have to reach wherever
Babidi is, Kaioshin-sama.
Let's hurry, Gohan-san!
If we just stand idly by,
all that damage energy will
keep being delivered to Boo's egg!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Just You Wait, Babidi!!
Your Aspirations Will Not Be Allowed."
There's no way I'm going
to let the Majin be revived!
"Next time"
"Just You Wait, Babidi!!
Your Aspirations Will Not Be Allowed"