Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Looking toward the Cell Games,
the martial arts tournament
that Cell is holding,
each warrior is determined to train. However...
Let's pick up your mother and go home.
There, we can settle down as much as we like.
We'll rest for three days,
then train for three days.
After that, we'll rest another three days.
And then comes the martial arts tournament.
S-Say, Father...?
Are you sure that's okay?
Will we be able to beat Cell like that?
Well, not to worry, not to worry.
Come on, let's go call your mother.
Goku and Gohan try to live
their lives in a natural state.
Can they really beat Cell
in his perfect form like this?
"A Warrior's Rest...
The Girl, the Lies, and Gohan's Resolution."
That was a close one, huh?
What are you doing, you pervert?!
P-Pervert?
Nyah!
I wonder what that could be.
Oh well... Shopping, shopping!
Have all the people here run away too?
I've been around to five places already,
and haven't been able to
get a bit of shopping done.
I can't just go taking things from
stores without telling anyone, after all.
I sure hope there's someone here.
Ah, good. There are people here.
Look! I'm telling you, hurry up
and give us the food and liquor!
I have nothing to give you guys.
Now go on back where you came from!
What? Do you mean to
defy us, Bourbon's men?!
Old man, I'm telling you, if you do as we say,
we'll let you into Bourbon-san's Shelter Dome.
That thing won't do any good!
How many times do I have to
say it before you understand?
Um...
Who are you?!
I wanted to buy some seasoning.
This store doesn't have anything to sell.
Now go on and get out of here.
And yet there's so much here?
This has all been bought
up by the Bourbon estate!
Don't be ridiculous!
–What?!
–Young one, what seasonings would you like?
Let's see, um...
Old man! Why don't you
stop being so stubborn already?!
Everyone from around here is
cooperating to build the Shelter.
Cooperating, you say?!
After threatening the villagers
and driving them to work so hard?!
Apparently, we aren't going to come
to any understanding with just words...
Now stop that!
It's Cell! Cell is here!
What?! It can't be!
Cell, they say?
This is bad! We have to
hurry and escape to the Shelter!
Geezer!
If you want to have everything your way,
then you can just stay here and be eaten!
Cell is in a place like this...?
Everyone! Cell is here! It's Cell!
If you don't run away quick,
you'll be in big trouble!
You're the girl who I just...!
Now see here, Lime! Was that you again?
I told you, you cannot tell such lies!
Lies?
That's the Shelter to
protect everyone from Cell?
That's right.
Several hundred people from
the city have fled inside there.
But, why do they think it's safe around here?
They say that once Cell attacks a place once,
he doesn't show up there again.
Or so that's the worthless
rumor they seem to believe.
Then that means...
Yes. A little while ago,
Cell appeared in this village.
I can't absorb any decent
life's energy in a place like this!
This girl's parents were taken at that time.
Is that right?
Anyone who has seen that monster once
knows one thing right down to their souls:
Wherever you run, it's still all the same.
That thing is good for nothing
more than easing your mind.
It's like they're all fools!
Eight more days.
There isn't anyone in the
world that can beat that monster.
Until the world ends, we're
just trying to live here quietly.
Gramps, are you getting tired?
How about if I trade with you?
It's too much for you to do just yet.
I'll help you out.
Well then, if I can ask it of you.
Big Brother!
Yow-ow-ow-ow-ow!
Big Brother, you're such a fool!
You have to use an ax
to cut the firewood. Here.
T-That's right, huh?
Goku, are you really sure it's okay
to just be taking it easy like this?
What do you mean?
There's only eight days left!
There has to be something
you can do before then, right?
Watching you yawn so widely,
it's putting my sense of
tension through the ringer!
It is? Sorry.
You really aren't someone that gets nervous.
Hey, hey, you guys! Don't dawdle around!
We have to get all of the non-perishables
carried in here in under an hour!
You got that?!
You stupid bastards!
Cell hasn't shown up anywhere!
What were you thinking?!
Geez, you've been fooled again and again!
We're sorry, Bourbon-san.
When we get frightened by Cell,
there's nothing we can do...
I don't even want to look at your faces!
Get lost, right now!
There's no reason for that Cell
bastard to come here, is there?
And even if he does come,
as long as I'm inside this
Shelter Dome, I can relax.
Those of us who survive
will need power and money.
And I have both of them!
You're in a good mood.
If it isn't the sensei!
Is something the matter?
I am gratified that you have
hired me as a professional killer,
but I cannot stand being as bored as this.
As such, I wonder if there's
anyone you wish to have killed?
I will take care of one
person for 50 million zeni.
When the time comes, I will
have plenty of work for you to do,
Tao Pai Pai-sensei, the
greatest assassin in the world!
Is that so? That's a shame.
At that time, I will not
have my special discount rate,
so you will use up all the
money you have there in a flash.
T-That's okay! I still have more, you see.
Is that right?
Piccolo, just you try to go even
one second past twenty-four hours!
I'll march right in there and chase you out!
What's the matter, Piccolo?
Are you saying that you can
beat me with that level of power?
W-Why you...!
Damn...
I'm not done yet!
Hey there, young one!
Do you want anything
besides these seasonings?
I wonder where those two went.
Big Brother, you're a kind person, aren't you?
You think so?
I can tell just by looking at you.
You're definitely someone who doesn't fight.
But I like people who are strong. Like Gramps.
Like Gramps?
He may not look like it, but
Gramps used to be a martial arts master.
A long time ago, he even
entered the Tenkaichi Tournament!
Oh, is that right?
In fact, I think it would
be best if Gramps went and,
bam-bam, took care of Bourbon.
What could that be?
The Shelter Dome has been
completed. It has to be that.
Why don't we go see?
Mm-hmm.
Thanks to everyone's efforts,
the Shelter Dome has at last been completed!
It pleases me down to the bottom of my heart
that I am able to save the lives of so
many people here in this Shelter Dome!
How does he dare say that? All right, then...
It's Cell! Cell is here!
Lime-chan!
C-Cell?!
I can't be killed like this!
Cell is here! Run away, quickly! It's Cell!
Hey, close the gate, quick!
But there are still people out front!
You dumb bastard!
Who cares about them?!
Open up!
See, Big Brother?
He's shown his true colors now, right?
So, it's you!
You're the one who tricked
us earlier too, aren't you?
Hey, Bourbon! This isn't what you promised us!
That's right! We already paid you our money!
I guess you're just out of luck, huh?
We're what?!
Bourbon-san, please, take it easy!
It was just some brat who
was playing a prank on us!
What?!
Some brat playing a prank, you say?!
Bourbon-san, she's the one.
You're quite a dreadful little girl, aren't you?!
Bourbon-san, I have something to say.
Surely, it isn't good for
this girl to be telling lies,
but I don't think
you're in the right either.
Who are you, now?
I don't have any business with you!
You can't escape from Cell
inside a Dome like this. Besides...
Shut up! Shut up! Come on,
men, make this kid shut up!
Right!
Hey, stop that! He's just a child, you know!
Don't do anything cruel!
You shut up!
If you want to come inside the Shelter Dome,
then stop complaining about what I say!
Hold it!
Oh! Gramps!
I will not allow you to do
anything to those children!
What?
There's no reason to be afraid
of that old man! Give it to him!
Gramps, I'll help too!
No, I can take care of this alone.
You bastard!
Damn you!
How dare you do that to my partner!
Why, you...!
D-Dammit! Sensei! Tao Pai Pai-sensei!
Is there something I can do for you?
Sensei, the time for you to work has come.
That guy! Dispose of him, please.
Very well then, I shall put
him away with no trouble.
Oh, weren't you lucky to have dodged that?
Gramps!
Young one, if you were to fight
him, something awful will happen.
Leave him to me.
Have you realized who I am?
Sensei! Get him once and for all!
It may be more than you deserve,
but I'm going to let you
have my Super Dodon-Pa!
Die!! Super Dodon-Pa!!
Gramps!!
W-What?!
I-Impossible!
I will take you on now!
Big Brother!
You're an impudent little turd, aren't you?
Very well, I'll kill you first.
Then again, it seems as though
I've met this kid somewhere before...
Kid, what is your name?!
Son Gohan!
S-Son, you say?! Then, you must be Son Goku's...
Son Goku is my father!
What?!
Yow! Yow-ow-ow-ow-ow-ow!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Now you've fallen for it!
What's the matter, Sensei?
Let him have it good, please!
That's it. I'm quitting.
I'm quitting as your bodyguard.
Farewell!
Tao Pai Pai-sensei!
Sensei! I'll pay you any
amount of money you want!
Please, do something about them!
You mean me?
Yes, I do! Don't be silly, Sensei!
W-What are you doing?
Don't you know?
Someone with my level of power
was able to destroy it that easily, see?
There's no way you could have
protected yourselves against Cell, is there?
Everyone, it's all right.
There will surely be
someone who can beat Cell
appearing at the martial
arts tournament in eight days.
Please, do not worry,
and go about your usual lives.
Gohan!
Father!
You never came back after you went shopping,
and now your mother is furious!
I forgot!
Here, Big Brother!
T-Thanks.
You must be this boy's father.
Yeah, that's right.
Both of you have uncommon power, huh?
You can tell that, Old-timer?
Gramps,
thank you very much.
Come visit us again.
Right!
Let's go, Gohan.
Be sure you defeat Cell for us!
You're entering, aren't you?
Into this Tenkaichi Tournament?
Big Brother! Bye bye!
Eight days remain until the Cell Games are held.
Will Goku and Gohan be able to
surpass Cell's perfect form before then?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Hey, Kuririn, take a look.
This brings back fond memories.
These are pictures of when Gohan was a baby.
Oh, yeah? He sure was cute, all right.
What kind of a child was Gohan back then?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Hidden Power!!
When Gohan Was a Baby."
Come to think of it, how did
I ever get the name "Gohan"?
"Next time"
"Hidden Power!!
When Gohan Was a Baby"