Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
With his all of his remaining power,
Vegeta launched his Final Flash at Cell.
However, not even that ultimate finishing
technique was of any use against him.
And now, with his father Vegeta in crisis,
Trunks has unleashed ultra power that
goes far beyond the Super Saiyan wall!
"Save Your Father!! Trunks' Fury,
Which Scorches Even the Heavens."
What's this?
Trunks!
H-He still hasn't gotten
fired up, yet what a terrifying ki!
W-What is going on with these Saiyans?
Every time an awesome opponent
appears, they rapidly get much stronger!
Are there no limits to the warrior Saiyan race?
What sort of guys are they?
Kuririn-san...
Would you take Dad,
and go to Muten Roshi-sama's
place or somewhere for me?
Thank goodness.
You can talk like normal, then.
I was worried that you had gone nuts,
like Goku and the others did
when they became great apes.
I'm all right. Never mind me, here...
When you think the timing
is right, give that senzu to Dad.
S-Sure. But are you sure you're okay?
Are you sure you have a senzu for yourself?
I will not need a senzu for myself,
because I will be sure to win.
F-For him to say something like
that, he's awfully sure of himself.
He's strong! So he's been keeping
all that potential strength hidden?
I will kill you, Cell.
That's a pretty aggressive statement, Trunks.
They've vanished!
Above me!
W-What?
D-Don't tell me that he's defeated Cell, there!
W-What the hell kind of training did he do
in the Room of Spirit and Time?
Gohan, anything goes. Try to catch me.
All right!
That was a good reading!
But you've still got a soft touch!
That was close, that was close!
Father!
Caught you!
Oh, my...
You did good, huh Gohan?
Yes!
However, we overdid it, didn't we?
I-I got all caught up in it, and all...
We'll have to fix this, or
we'll have Popo mad at us!
Right!
H-He did it!
Awesome! That Trunks...
saying he's gotten stronger doesn't even cover it!
He's defeated that monster–Cell!
Kuririn-san, watch out!
W-What?!
You're something else, Trunks.
Damn! Cell is still alive and kicking!
That settles it!
What kind of power is this?
I might have known!
To think that you could
dodge me by a hair's breadth!
T-Trunks!
T-This is hopeless...
I-Is that it?
This is to allow me to rescue Vegeta.
So this is the result of your allowing
Cell to become his perfect form,
for your pride's sake?
Trunks is now fighting at incredible power!
He's gotten a lot stronger than you have.
And the reason I can't
watch this magnificent fight,
it's all due to your ridiculous pride!
For my part, I wouldn't
care if you weren't around...
...but as far as Trunks goes,
that doesn't seem to be so.
Really, what does he see in a father like this?
Now, can you finally fight
without any other concerns?
Vegeta has been taken away, and all...
S-So you knew?
Of course.
As well as knowing you were moving
me away from Vegeta on purpose.
This is unexpected!
To think that you would let him go knowingly!
Naturally. My interests no longer lie with him.
They lie in your true power.
I didn't think you knew so much.
I look forward to this.
The time for me to know the
strength of this perfect form has come.
W-What power he has!
He's far exceeded Super Vegeta!
Is this it?
Is this the Saiyan power
that goes beyond Super Saiyan,
that Goku was talking about?
As Super Trunks finally reveals
himself, he demonstrates ultra-power!
Will this power be able to rise
above the perfect form of Cell?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Trunks, what happened in the future,
where Vegeta and me are dead?
The Artificial Humans were strong.
The warriors that stood up to them
were all killed by their tremendous power.
Even Gohan-san!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"A Future of Despair!!
Trunks, the Man Who Lived Through Hell."
I won't leave the earth to the
whims of the Artificial Humans!
"Next time"
"A Future of Despair!!
Trunks, the Man Who Lived Through Hell"