Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
In order to combine with No. 17
and No. 18 to become his perfect form,
the terrifying Artificial Human
Cell has come from the future!
During all this, Trunks
and Kuririn discover the plans
for No. 17 in Doctor Gero's laboratory.
I-If I have Mom look at these,
she just might be able to
catch on to a weakness in No. 17!
However, even as they are doing this,
Cell continues his cruelty
and slaughter over and over,
steadily storing up life energy for himself.
"Goku Awakens to Battle!
Go Beyond Super Saiyan!!"
Right! One-two, one-two...
One-two, one-two...
Hello? What's the matter? Hello?
And so, as we continue, we relay
this report from a different city.
Following the incidents of the
Metro West suburb of Gingertown,
the citizens here in Nickytown
have also suddenly disappeared.
There is only one person who can be
thought of as the perpetrator here...
That devilish being with the power to
annihilate the Metro West Armed Forces,
and then turn this city into
a ghost town in an instant!
Just how long will this terror continue?
Where is he now, and what is he doing?
Investigators are combing the city,
but have not as yet located his whereabouts.
This has been a report from the scene.
Right. That was a live relay from Nickytown.
At the present time, this
calamity seems likely to continue.
We urge everyone to please be cautious.
Be cautious? That's a good joke!
Sense anything?
No! I'm sure I felt his ki a moment ago, though.
Damn!
We have to make sure he doesn't
become his perfect form no matter what!
Sis!
Kuririn, huh?
How nice of you to find me here!
I can't have you taking stabs at these people!
Here I am taking a shortcut
back to the Kame House,
and I have to run into this terrible guy!
Uh, ahem...
Thank you very much.
N-Never mind, hurry and run away!
–Right!
–Thanks!
Suits me just fine.
Why don't I just have your life energy first?
Hurry and get in!
I'm taking off!
It pains me to say it, but
he's not an opponent I can beat!
In this situation...
Taiyo-ken!!
We did it!
Where is he? Where'd he go?!
Oh, hell!
Mister!
This would seem to be the end, wouldn't it?
Kuririn!
It's those guys.
He's hidden his ki once again!
Are you all right, Kuririn?
I'm saved!
Oh, Son Goku is still alive?
Of course he is!
It appears things are starting
to turn out slightly different
from the history I know.
History is starting to turn out differently...
Evidently, ever since I came
here in the time machine,
things have been changing in subtle ways.
At the time,
I thought that if only
Goku-san hadn't died of his illness,
and instead lived,
he could save us from a
future wrought with devastation
by the Artificial Humans.
However, when I came
once again three years later,
Goku-san and the others were fighting
against different Artificial Humans...
Artificial Human No. 16, whom
I had never seen before, appears,
and then, this guy Cell or whatever also appears.
On top of that, the time
machine he came back in...
It was definitely my own.
Does that mean that Cell
coming here four years ago
was my future self's fault,
in that other dimension?
By coming here from the future,
with the changes to history,
have I instead plunged
this world into a crisis?
I will go beyond, count on it!
Beyond even Super Saiyan!
Dad...
Mom, I'm going to go try to train with Dad.
If Dad can overcome Super Saiyan, why not me?
Mom...
Dammit! Has he gotten away again?!
If he's able to search out our ki and
escape every which way from us this well,
we have absolutely no way to strike at him!
If I keep taking life essences at this pace,
then the time when I absorb No. 17 and No. 18
and become my perfect form is not far off.
Come on!
Aren't there any decent roads?
Hmph, isn't this more fun?
No. 16, aren't we at Son Goku's house yet?
Yeah. It's right nearby.
Indeed! How nice for you two to be so carefree.
Won't it be easier if I do this?
See? I feel much better.
Aw, how could you do such a thing?
This isn't any fun at all, is it?
You know, you really are strange.
There's quite a bit of humanness left in you.
And so, two days pass,
and while a third was passing...
This time, the monster has
appeared in the southern zone,
in a large city in Sector 48.
We have also had reports
that over half the inhabitants
have been killed already.
Damn!
Now it's the southern zone?
They said there were already a good
deal of casualties in the Metro West area.
I know!
Gohan! Be careful!
If we come up on him like this,
Cell won't be aware of our ki!
This time, we've got him for sure!
Let's defeat him before he
combines with No. 17 and the others,
and becomes his perfect form!
Yeah! The way we are now, we can do it!
That's right! Piccolo-san is here,
and he's merged with Kami-sama
and gotten incredibly strong!
Cell is a crafty one.
Even if we do get close,
if he hides on us, there'll be no way to find him.
W-What's that?!
Have the Artificial Humans come attackin'?!
"Yaaaa!" is uncalled for, there's no "Yaaaa!"
Here you are pouring water over people–
It's been a long time since
I've had the pleasure of a gal!
Then again, it might be a little bit
difficult to still call you a gal, huh?
I should've expected as much from
a former martial artist. Well done!
Ah, Goku-sa!
Goku-sa?! Huh?
Goku-sa?
What's wrong?
–Goku-sa!
–Goku!
Well, me too!
Goku-sa!
Chichi!
Sorry to make you worry so!
Looks like I'm completely over my illness!
Are you really okay?
Yeah! See for yourself!
Goku-sa!
Hey, cut it out!
I inadvertently put too much power into that!
Goku-sa!
Sorry, sorry!
Goku!
Old-timer!
You've recovered from your illness?
Yeah, I'm all right now!
I heard what everyone has
been saying in my dreams.
I pretty much know what's going on.
Looks as though things
have gotten awful again, huh?
Goku, don't tell me you're already...
You gotta be kiddin'!
You're thinkin' of fightin' already? You'll die!
Don't worry, I ain't fighting yet.
If Vegeta can't win against
them now, I can't win either.
That's why I'm thinking of
aiming for something higher, too.
Higher?
Higher than Super Saiyan.
Son Goku has finally recovered.
However, is it really possible
to go beyond Super Saiyan?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
I'm gonna take Gohan and go somewhere–
a place where you do a year's
worth of training in one day.
Vegeta, you guys do it, too!
Hurry and get going, Goku!
If Cell achieves his perfect form,
it will be too late for anything!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Hasten Your Training, Saiyans!
In the Room of Spirit and Time..."
All right, I'm going to
surpass Super Saiyan, too!
"Next time"
"Hasten Your Training, Saiyans!
In the Room of Spirit and Time..."