Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Cell kills again and again, powering himself up!
At the same time, Goku, at last, fully recovered...
There's a room in the temple at
Kami's home where you can get
a year's worth of training in just one day.
Really?
Enter.
The training to try for something even
higher than Super Saiyan has begun.
However, as one day had just about passed,
the worst situation of all came up!
Where is Son Goku?
If you don't tell us, we
intend to force it out of you.
I see. Well, you can try.
There's an island over there
with no one on it. Let's do it there.
Dear, dear, you never learn.
"The Gekiretsu Kodan That Split the Heavens!!
Piccolo vs. Artificial Human No. 17."
Unless you say something,
I'll kill you for sure this time.
Got it?
It won't be as easy as it was last time.
It taxes my comprehension why
you would fight a battle you can't win.
Are you buying time?
Or is it that you're just a fool?!
So, if you're going to bring it, bring it!
Will you alone be the one fighting, No. 17?
Of course!
Someone the likes of you
naturally won't even be a match for me.
Yes! If I have only one opponent,
something just might come of this!
If I can defeat either
No. 17 or No. 18,
I can prevent Cell from becoming his perfect form!
Here we are so far away,
and yet it's as if he's raising
his ki right before our eyes!
A-Awesome!
To think it was this high!
No. This isn't anything!
Piccolo merged with Kami-sama
can raise his ki much, much higher!
This is just the beginning.
I-Is that true?
K-Kami-sama!
It's started! The one who's fighting is Piccolo!
Could his opponent be that Cell guy?
No, I can't feel his opponent's ki.
It's probably the Artificial Humans!
It can't be!
Piccolo-san will be killed!
There ain't no use in going!
Our levels differ too much right now!
Do you want to weigh him down?!
Very soon, Vegeta and Trunks
will come out all powered up!
Wait until then, it'll be all right!
Besides which, Piccolo has become
a master like you couldn't believe!
Right! Kami-sama and
Piccolo are not easily beaten.
Not yet, Vegeta?
Was it impossible to go
beyond Super Saiyan after all?
How can this be?
That's not Piccolo!
What?!
A-Annoying pest!
You're not getting away!
What?!
Dear me...
Impossible! With my speed...!
It's impossible!
Get cocky with me, will you?
♪ My gentle, good little boy, ♪
♪ Fortune smiles on you... ♪
Hey, he's finally fallen asleep.
Really? That's good.
So, how's your shutdown device coming along?
Ah, there's still a lot of hard work!
According to these plans,
there are several dozen
shutdown sensors all wired in here,
and unless you cut them all off at
the same time, it'll be meaningless.
You don't say.
Even if I can create all the
code it takes for the shutdown,
I still have to input it on all
the frequencies for each circuit.
It's making me feel faint.
Of all the...! What kind of thing
has Doctor Gero created here?!
There, there, there! There, there, there!
I want to cry too!
Brace yourself, you oversized-scumbag!
Take this!
How about this?!
He repelled it!
This certainly is much better than before!
It's quite entertaining of you, isn't it?!
He's half-playing.
He really is disingenuous, isn't he, No. 16?
W-Who the hell has the upper hand here?
Is it Piccolo? Or is it the Artificial Humans?
Hey, it has to be Piccolo!
Can anyone overcome such ferocious power?!
I'm not so sure.
Since we can't sense his opponent's power,
we'd better not get caught up in the excitement!
Yeah, the Artificial Humans
don't dissipate ki, after all...
What's the matter? Finished already?
Really! Enough, already!
No. 17, hurry up and put him away!
Or shall I take over?!
Don't be ridiculous!
You expect me to switch with
you during the part I enjoy most?!
You're the same way too, I bet.
I suppose so.
This isn't it at all.
This isn't yet my power, the greatest in history!
It isn't? Well, let me see it!
This again?
It's no use, no matter
how many times you do it!
You disappoint me!
Did you really think such a
technique would work against me??
Where the hell are you aiming?!
There's nowhere left for you to run!
This is as far as the greatest in history goes!
Go to hell!
W-What is it?!
A B-Barrier?!
Too bad.
That's a pity, isn't it?
Ha! I'm still just getting started!
Let's change locations.
Someone has destroyed the island, after all.
You have to take better care of nature!
This intense ki is that of
Piccolo, combined with Kami.
The opponent he would be
fighting at such a high power must be...
It could only be No. 17 and the others!
I've found you! This is good timing!!
I'm saved!
I'm coming now! You just wait!
My power is already even greater than yours!
At last, Cell realizes where
No. 17 and the others are!
The situation deteriorates even further!
Goku, please hurry with your training!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
This is bad! Piccolo's
stamina is starting to wind down!
At this rate, he'll be done in!
Hurry and come out of there, Vegeta!
Ain't you done with your training yet?!
How can this be?! Cell is
closing in, at a time like this!
If he shows up now, it will
mean the end of everything!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"How I Have Waited for This Day!!
Cell's Prologue to Perfection."
Let me go, Father! I'm going to fight, too!
"Next time"
"How I Have Waited for This Day!!
Cell's Prologue to Perfection"