Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
At last, Goku and Gohan have
finished their training. However...
I will be sure to come for the matches.
So until then, don't you kill
even a single person! Got that?
Son Goku, huh?
It seems that this will be an even
more enjoyable event than I thought.
I won't know until I try,
but the way things are,
I probably can't win, I bet.
You'd better use the
Room of Spirit and Time again.
There is still time.
No, me and Gohan have had enough.
What?!
We'll train in the outer world.
We have nine whole days,
so something will turn out.
W-What did you say?!
Goku has made an unexpected declaration.
Does this mean that he has
some theory on how to beat Cell?
"Goku's Composure!?
Let's Rest and Wait for the Cell Games."
You've had enough?
You mean you aren't going to stay in
the Room of Spirit and Time any longer?
Yeah, that's right.
Why not? You could still stay
in there for another full day.
Being inside there is pretty hard on the body,
even if you ain't doing anything.
You can't get enough rest like that.
Hmph! Well, well...
...has even the great Kakarrot-san
finally started to whine
about the harshness of that room?
Maybe so.
But trying to force our bodies to
get any tougher than they are now
would only be asking for pain.
And that ain't training.
But I ain't saying anything against
you guys going in the room again.
It looks like you still have room to train.
What was that? I don't like how that sounded.
From what you just said,
it sounds like you're saying that
your power is greater than mine.
Yeah. Quite a bit greater, I think.
What?!
Well, let's all hang in there together.
I'll see you again at the martial arts tournament.
Let's go, Gohan.
Right.
Gohan...
Is it okay if we stop off somewhere for a bit?
Yeah...
Good day, Karin-sama.
Good day. It's nice to see you again.
Ah, you sure have grown.
Yo, Yajirobe! Are you back here?
What've ya come here for, Son?
I'm warnin' ya right now,
no matter what happens,
I ain't gonna enter that
martial arts tournament, got it?
That's okay!
I ain't asked you to enter, have I?
I-In that case, fine...
When it's all said an' done,
I hafta be ready to get turned to
if the worst comes 'bout, y'know?
If ya wanna call it that, I'm the
secret weapon guy who's held in reserve!
Listen to you.
Still, the Earth has come
to be in quite a fix, hasn't it?
The lower realm is in a big fuss.
Cell really is an awesome guy.
Now that he's in his perfect form,
he's also obtained his complete strength.
And you're pretty unflustered
about it, considering.
What is it?
Did you make some sort of marvelous
discovery inside the Room of Spirit and Time?
Oh, you know...
I-Is that true?
I was there together
with Father the whole time...
Say, Karin-sama, watching from here,
you can pretty much tell
what Cell's strength is, right?
Uh-huh.
He hasn't shown his true strength yet,
so I can't say for sure,
but I have a pretty good idea.
Well, make a comparison for me.
I'm going to fire up my ki now.
S-Say, were Goku and
Gohan Super Saiyans just now?
They felt so... how should I say...
natural, for being like that.
I don't think there's any mistake
that they were Super Saiyans.
However, they must have trained so
that they can maintain themselves like that
as if it were their usual, everyday form.
T-Then, when they fight,
they go through another,
more extraordinary transformation?
What are you, an idiot?
Apparently, you haven't
reconsidered anything, have you?
Kakarrot has judged that state to be best.
Once re-training yourself
so that it is your usual state,
you can get away with raising your battle power,
while only placing a slight burden on your body.
He sure thought that through!
I-Is that right...?
Transforming just to power-up
doesn't bring about anything...
That's why I was unable to beat Cell.
What is this ki?!
I-It's Goku!
S-Stop already!
Y-You're going to destroy this place!
Waah! Somebody!
That was about half of it. What do you think?
H-Half, you say?
You are one terrifying fellow!
How strong are you going to
get before you're finally satisfied?
Is that so? Has Father really
become all that incredible?
So, Karin-sama, how
about comparing that to Cell?
You sure ask a difficult thing.
Like I said before, I can only
make a guess as to an answer...
...but to be honest, I still
think that Cell has it over you.
He's one outrageous
bastard then, huh, this Cell?
Just as I thought, huh?
My estimate wasn't wrong, then.
Thank you, Karin-sama.
Let's go, Gohan.
R-Right...
S-Sorry to bother you.
T-They vanished! That guy
ain't even human no more, huh?
Anyhow I think about it, there doesn't
seem to be any way for Goku to win.
So why on earth is he so composed...?
I can't believe that he's
just turned his back on this...
Still though, what a ferocious ki that was!
However, even at that...
...he wasn't putting out all of his power.
If he were to put out all of his power...
Incredible!
He might be able to defeat Cell.
T-That piece of crap! Kakkarot...!
He's always doing that!
He's always keeping one step ahead of me!
He really knows how to piss me off!
Just when I think I've overtaken him,
he pushes ahead of me!
Piccolo! If you're going in,
then get yourself in that room now!
We're all waiting for you!
Let's pick up your mother and go home.
There, we can settle down as much as we like.
We'll rest for three days,
then train for three days.
After that, we'll rest another three days.
And then comes the martial arts tournament.
S-Say, Father...?
Are you sure that's okay?
Will we be able to beat Cell like that?
Well, not to worry, not to worry.
Come on, let's go call your mother.
Heya!
What's the matter, everyone?
G-Goku?
Yeah!
Are you really Goku?
Yes, I am! What are you saying, Old-timer?
So, you're Gohan? I hardly recognize you!
It's true!
T-Thanks...
Goku, did you hear about the martial
arts tournament that Cell is holding?
Yeah. I heard from Trunks.
I've also gone and seen Cell,
now that he's in his perfect form.
Y-You what?!
Ah! W-With that Instantaneous
Movement thing you talked about, right?
Yeah, that's right.
And you know, he really is strong!
There's no way I can match him!
H-Hey, you don't need to
be so modest. It's not like you.
I ain't being modest, it's true.
But you still have some breathing
room for strength, don't you?
Are you sure you're not hiding something?
Never mind that, where's Chichi?
I was planning on taking her home with us.
Chichi-san is up on the second floor.
Hey, Chichi!
What? Is that you, Goku-sa?
Good grief, where have
you been up until now...?
Yo, Chichi! Let's all go home together.
Mother, let's hurry and go.
Are you Gohan-chan?
T-That's right...
What are you saying, Chichi?
N-Now, Chichi-san...
W-What's goin' on with the color of your hair?!
Is this dyed?!
Yow-ow-ow-ow!
No, that's not it, Chichi.
My Gohan-chan has gone
and become a delinquent!
It's not like that, I tell you.
Now then, how about a little light warming-up?
It's times like this when Freeza
and his father's cells come in useful.
This may be nothing more
than trivial entertainment,
but how about I show
the humans something nice.
How pretty!
–What could this be?
–Shooting stars, at this time of day!
There's nothing to be done...!
Goku-sa?
Huh?
Gohan-chan?
Huh? Where did those two go off to?
It sure is quiet here.
Yeah.
Say, Father....
I'm glad.
How come?
You promised me, a long
time ago, that we'd go fishing.
I promised you that?
You know, when you first fought Vegeta.
Huh? When?
You know, that one time...
Kuririn!
Don't you remember, Goku?
Goku, it's too bad we're always
having to leave our fate up to you, huh?
Don't you die now, my friend.
Right!
Father...!
Gohan...
Once your daddy comes back alive,
let's go fishing or something again, okay?
Right?
So, back then, huh?
Since then, all we've done
is training and other stuff,
so we never once went fishing together.
Sorry about that, Gohan.
Goku, the truth is,
I need to apologize to you for something.
For what?
The reason Cell was able
to become his perfect form
is because I wasn't able to shut down No. 18.
Don't worry about that.
We're thrilled to be able to
fight against somebody this strong.
Somehow, it doesn't seem right, you know?
Always having you save us...
What's with you, Kuririn?
You're acting like we're strangers.
That's right!
It's not like you to be like this, Kuririn-san.
Nah. Recently, there's been so
much distance placed between us...
It almost seems like it couldn't be
true that we ever fought each other.
Really? For my part, I remember
when we trained together
under Old Timer Turtle Hermit
like it was yesterday.
Cut it out. That was long in the past.
Oh, you don't know what you're saying!
H-Help me! Goku!
Kuririn! I'm sorry!
You're the same as ever, Goku!
Falling for a simple trick like that!
You got me, huh Kuririn?
This feels great!
Goku really is unaffected.
It's as if nothing at all has
changed from how he was in the past.
I get it!
Goku and Gohan are still training,
even though they're like this!
All right, why don't I test him out?
I'm sure that, even though
it looks like he's asleep,
he's well aware of
everything surrounding him...
He'll dodge this stone like it was nothing!
That has to be it!
Ee-yow!
What did you do that for, Kuririn?!
S-S-Sorry...!
Even if I am Super Saiyan,
whatever hurts still hurts, you know!
Huh...?
Yum!
Thank you for providing this feast!
Now, Gohan, since you're
through eatin', you've got studyin'.
Right.
Th-This is the training in the
outside world that Goku talked about?
Can they really beat Cell by doing this?
I'm full! I'm full!
Are you really sure it's
okay to be doing this, Goku?
Nine days remain until the
martial arts tournament of terror,
the Cell Games, are held.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Gohan sure is taking his time.
He just went out shopping, so what is he up to?
The whole world is in an uproar,
but you really are laid back, Goku.
Oh, right, I saw Gohan
talking to a cute girl earlier.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"A Warrior's Rest...
The Girl, the Lies, and Gohan's Resolution."
Father, do you know a man named Tao Pai Pai?
"Next time"
"A Warrior's Rest...
The Girl, the Lies, and Gohan's Resolution"