Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Thanks to the young boys who were
drifting along in their mirrored spaceship,
Bulma and the others learned of a new
evil that existed separate from the Saiyans.
We made it! We've arrived at Planet Namek!
Is that really–?
Sure it is. Isn't it obvious?
Just like those kids said.
"Kind-hearted Aliens.
There's the Wu Xing Qiu Ball Already."
Both of you, fasten your seat belts.
There'll be quite a jolt when we touch down.
Oh, right.
Commence landing in a suitable location.
We did it! We've landed on Planet Namek!
Amazing!
What kind of place is it?
We can't see much through this mist.
Are you sure this is it?
No mistake about it.
But...
I rebuilt this spaceship!
Are you trying to put it down?!
No, it's not that...
Then what is it?
We should be able to tell right
away by looking at the Dragon Radar.
Y-Yeah, yeah, right!
Good grief, you're so skeptical...
K-Kami–?
You're finally awake, are you?
–Who are you?
–Lychee.
The biggest quack doctor on the planet.
And this loudmouth is Zarkuro. He's
been bad company for me for 300 years now.
T-Three hundred years?!
Nice to meet you.
That's how we say hello on this world.
Nice to meet you. I'm Bulma.
You know, you're lucky that
I was the one who discovered you.
If it weren't for me taking the proper measures,
all three of you would have croaked.
Thank you.
Come on, now, how long are you going
to sleep? Both of you, hurry and wake up.
Come on.
Nice to meet you.
Um, this is Planet Namek, right?
Yes, it is.
We can tell just by looking at
your faces. You look just like Kami-sama.
That's right. You look
just like Piccolo-san, too.
I sure hope you find
them okay–the Dragon Balls.
H-How did you–?
We know everything there is to know about you.
Well, you are Kami-sama's relatives, after all.
I guess there's no reason why you wouldn't.
You needn't worry. We won't stand in your way.
Oh, right, where's our spaceship?
Oh, we put it in the storeroom in back.
Here it is.
It's pretty damaged, but still okay, right?
Probably.
Thank you for everything.
Don't mention it.
You really are kind-hearted
people for doing all this, aren't you?
–Look! They're here!
–All right!
There, look, look!
See? There are three of
them grouped together near here!
How lucky for us!
Let's hurry and go look for them.
With any luck, we can get three of them today.
All right, let's go!
Okay, let's go!
Right.
That thing won't do you any good.
This area is a dangerous
one, and teeming with monsters.
If you go out in that toy-like thing,
you'll get yourself stomped on easily.
Monsters?
Bulma-san...
All right, what choice do
I have but to let you use my goku?
Goku?
What do you think? My dear
little Goku is pretty fast, huh?
Yeah...
There it is! It's around here!
Could you land around here?
A-All right. Goku, here! Land!
Oh, no!
With a spaceship like this one...
Was it down there?
No, it wasn't.
Search carefully. It has to be around here.
Sorry to have to make you do this, as well.
That's okay, this is staving off boredom.
It's a big help.
After all, right now, Earth could be
facing a great crisis at any moment, and...
Oh, you know all about it, huh?
Yes.
It's definitely down there
somewhere, no doubt about it.
Did you find it?
We couldn't hold our breaths any longer.
This is going to be really hard.
Still, there's no mistake
that it's around here someplace.
Huh? Where's Lychee-san?
Here it is!
Lucky!
R-Really?
He's completely regained consciousness.
K-Kakarrot...
Why? Why, when my battle
power is far and away higher than his,
did I take that attack dead-on?
What?!
What did you do that for out of nowhere?!
Ee-yow!
Patients should act like patients,
and lie there quietly, you know!
I'm just so bored, so bored!
I can't wait to go cut loose!
Patients shouldn't be talkin' nonsense.
Goku-sa, until your body is doin'
better, you're to behave yourself.
Is that for me?
This? If you can put it on, you can wear it.
I guess not, then.
These ancient ruins are from
four or five-thousand years ago.
Wow, five-thousand years?
Look here, the Dragon Ball is
within a five-meter radius of us.
Bulma-san, over there.
Find it?
There are stairs over here.
The Radar's readings are getting stronger.
It must be in here.
All right, let's go.
Bulma-san, wait!
Wow, these are ancient Namekians.
Their faces are completely different
from the way they look now, aren't they?
Yeah, it would seem so...
W-What are these?
I wonder if there's treasure in them.
It's right close by.
In here.
T-That's–!
Ulp... Is that–?
Okay, let's find one
more before the day is over!
You're sure a chipper old man, huh?
He's a nice fellow, isn't he?
Doing this for complete strangers like us.
That's what's so fishy
about it. We should be careful.
It's possible that once
we get all seven together,
he might be planning to swipe them from us.
He couldn't be.
It's in this area. Could you set us down soon?
Yes, yes!
Huh?
What's the matter?
The Dragon Ball is moving.
A-Are you all right?
I'm fine, but the Radar–
C-Could you hand that over?
Hey! Hold it!
Bulma-san!
Telling him that isn't
going to get through to him!
Wait!
What are you doing?!
Y-You can't go any farther!
We have to hurry, or he'll get away, you know!
Why are you stopping me?! Let me go!
If you go any farther,
your life will be in danger.
He's gone.
Listen, you're not planning to
swipe the Dragon Balls from us, are you?!
I-I wouldn't do that.
You're acting funny. You're being
far too nice to perfect strangers like us.
That's his voice.
Something has happened to him.
Let's go have a look.
I'm sure it was around here...
Whoa! That's that thing from earlier!
The water in these swamps is dreadful
stuff that will dissolve any living thing,
and the gasses that rise from it will take
out any ordinary person who breathes them.
Is that so? So that's why you stopped us, huh?
I'm sorry for saying something so terrible.
Just so long as you know, it's all right.
Thank goodness.
Still, we're in a jam.
If he's ended up like that, that means
the Dragon Ball is in the swamp, right?
How are we going to get it out of there?
Oh, that would be impossible.
Under any circumstances?
Well, I do have a bodysuit for
that sort of thing, but even if you
were to wear it to dive down there,
it would only be good for ten seconds.
Any longer than that,
and the suit will dissolve.
I'll do it.
After all, we can't do anything
unless we have that Dragon Ball, right?
That may be so, but...
I just need to come back
up within ten seconds, right?
I'll give it a try. Please let me do it.
I know. What if we tied a
special rope around his body,
to pull him up before ten seconds is up?
Mm-hmm, that sounds good.
All right, let's give it a try.
Judging from the readings on the
radar, it's right underneath us. Good luck.
We'll pull you up with the
rope after seven seconds, okay?
Okay.
2... 3... 4... 5... 6... 7...
Now!
Oh, no! The swamp water
is stronger than I figured...
–Gohan-chan!
–Gohan!
All right, great. Now to hurry up on the rope.
The rope!
I have to act fast, or I won't make it!
It's no good! I won't last
until I make it to the top like this!
It's no good!
Masenko!
Gohan-chan...
Gohan!
I'm back.
–He made it!
He made it, all right...
Bulma and the others were ecstatic
over already obtaining three of the Balls.
Now then, will they be able to get
all of the Dragon Balls without any trouble?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
I wonder if Gohan and the others
have found the Dragon Balls yet.
I can't just sit around, either.
I have to start training.
Oh, no! Goku-sa has slipped out of the hospital!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Planet Freeza No. 79
Vegeta Recovers!!"
I wonder if Father is all better yet.
"Next time"
"Planet Freeza No. 79
Vegeta Recovers!!"