The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Majin Boo had at length escaped
from the alternate dimensional
space of the Room of Spirit and Time.
Lucky! There are many here!
I'm getting a little hungry, so this is
just right. What should I make them?
And then, having merged through Fusion,
Goten and Trunks also
transformed into Super Gotenks 3,
and escaped from the Room of Spirit and Time.
Now I'm completely mad!!
Renzoku Super Donuts!!
Ultra Boo-Boo Attack!!
Yo, yo, yo! Majin Boo! Come on out!
I know you aren't going
to keel over from just this!
"Truly 'Great'!!
A Reborn Gohan Returns to Earth."
Phew! That was a close one!
I-If the Earth had taken that head-on,
it would have been wiped out without a trace!
You dirty bastard!
You've done it now, you Boo-Boo swine!
Here I go!
Renzoku Shine-shine Missiles!
[Renzoku Shine-shine: Continuous Die-Die]
Stop, you fool! Are you trying to
blow away the Earth as we know it?!
It's okay, isn't it? After all,
there's nobody alive down there!
Don't forget that the Dragon Balls
are scattered all over the Earth!
If you destroy even one of them,
we can never return the
Earth back to the way it was again!
Oh, is that right?
Well, that's okay. I've
already gotten him quite a bit!
Boo must be fairly weakened!
He hasn't been weakened at all!
This is pissing me off!
N-No, he is weaker!
I don't know about his physical strength,
but mentally, he's beginning to weaken!
This is a first for him–fighting
with someone as strong as you are.
At the very least, fighting with someone
of equal strength has him thrown off.
In other words, Majin Boo is flustered, right?
I guess that would be true! My strength
leaves nothing to be desired, after all!
You could say I'm the strongest in the universe!
Don't let your guard down, Gotenks!
If you get too over-confident,
you'll be hurting later!
He's going to start coming at
you like his life depends on it now!
I don't mind, I don't mind! I hope he does!
Damn it all! Our hero left himself wide open!
Why, you...! Let me go, you big–!
Oww! You're not getting
away with that any more!
Hang in there, Goten! Trunks!
Th-They're incredible!
To think they can fight
blow-for-blow with Majin Boo!
I wonder how much longer.
If it's not soon, then I won't be in time...
You scum!
I'm going to put you away here and now! Yea!!
Dammit!
This hurts!
Gotenks!
Why, you...!
Huh?!
Now I'm mad! You've made me furious!
D-Don't get irritated, Gotenks!
You rotten...!
Back at you!!
Awesome! Awesome!
Gohan won't get a turn like this!
Now to finish you!
I'll blow you to pieces, then into little
chunks, then to shreds, then to bits!
This time, you won't be
able to return to normal!
Once I blow you apart,
I'm going to completely wipe
you out with my ki, you see?
Die!!
H-Huh?
U-Uh oh! H-He went back to normal!
Hey!
Yeah, you got me, you got me!
How funny, how funny!
I-It's hopeless!
I-It's all over now! Damn!
Say, old man Kaioshin-sama! Hurry it up!
The little runts' Fusion has powered down!
Really, Father?
Yeah! They're going to get killed like this!
Okay, you can go!
You've been finished for a while now.
–F–
Finished?!
For a while now? Since how long ago?!
Hmm, since about five minutes ago, I suppose.
W-Why didn't you tell us sooner?!
You were just saying that since I got distracted,
it was going to take longer, didn't you?!
Ignorant fool! It's more dramatic for
you to go once there's a pinch, you know!
Th-This is awful! In that case, I have to hurry!
A-At this point, bluffing and
anything else is fine! All right...!
Super Ghost Kamikaze Attack!!
I may have returned to my normal form,
but the force of my
techniques has been powered up!
Go ahead, ghosts! Knock Majin Boo flat!
Hey, what should we do?
No way I'm doing that! He looks pretty strong!
Stop fussing around and go get him!
All right! Now, while I still can... Run!!
H-How do I become the mightiest of
warriors, with strength beyond my limits?
Ah, well, you transform into that
Super-whatever-you-call-it often enough.
That's the gist of it. You just
have to get yourself fired up.
The gist of becoming Super
Saiyan, right? Understood!
H-Hey, just a moment!
U-Unmindful fool, becoming
like that while I'm nearby!
I-Incredible...
This is incredible, Father!
Y-You're right! It really
is incredible! Amazingly so!
Magnificent! Gohan-san has
certainly surpassed his limits.
It's unbelievable! Absolutely!
By looking at you, you
haven't changed all that much!
You ain't even Super Saiyan,
yet you've come to this extreme?!
Hmph. It's not as though he has to transform.
That Super-whatever-thing is depraved!
Gohan-san, quickly, to Earth! If we
don't hurry, the irreparable will happen!
Come with us, and we'll go to Earth!
No, I shall take Gohan-san there alone.
What are you saying, Kibit?
It is the Kaioshin's responsibility
to see things through to their end!
Once I have taken him, my
intent is to come right back here.
Begging your pardon, but if both of us go,
we will only be slowing him down, will we not?
I do not want to get in the
way of this magnificent savior.
Kibit-san...
I see. You are correct.
I understand. If you please...
Sorry, Gohan. I'm a man
of the Other World now.
Even though I want to go, it's impossible.
I sure wish I could have seen you up
close–the way you've gotten so big...
Father...
I ain't gonna see you again. Not until
you come to the Other World, that is...
Good luck! Go blow Majin Boo away!
Right!
All right, go on!
Farewell, Father!
Why, that rotten...!
He left and forgot to say thanks
to me, and I worked the hardest!
And so, excuse me. We're counting on you.
Right! Um...
Kibit-san, I have a favor to ask.
Can I have you change this clothing?
I'd like you to make it the
same clothing as my Father's.
Please, I want to fight wearing my Father's gi!
You don't say. It is a simple enough task.
Um, the color is the same as the
droppings of the frogs on Planet Popol, right?
Um, it's the color of a kerria rosebush.
Ah, that's perfect! Thank you very much!
Well then, I will be going.
From the far distant Kaioshin Realm,
we will be wishing
victory for our grand warrior!
Farewell. Give my regards to
the two Kaioshin-sama as well.
All right, let's go!
Dammit!
Huh?! Th-This is bad!
Our Fusion has come undone!
Gotenks had pressed his attack
to within one step away, but now,
even his Fusion has come unbound!
Goten and Trunks are in an absolute pinch!
However, after having finished his training
and achieving the ultimate
power-up, Gohan has returned!
Can he indeed become
the savior of the Earth?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Okay, Gohan, show off
your powered-up strength!
Majin Boo, don't go weak
in the knees from the shock!
Unbelievable. What in the world happened?
How can his battle power top Boo's,
when he isn't even Super Saiyan?!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Boo Overwhelmed!!
Gohan's Miracle Power."
What's the matter, Boo? I thought
you were going to blow me away!
"Next time"
"Boo Overwhelmed!!
Gohan's Miracle Power"