Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Kami-sama and Mister Popo finally pour...
the Ultra Holy Water
into the hole of air currents,
all the while facing harm from the
spirits of the Kami that came before them.
However...
Why you...!
How dare you trample on
my dream of a Utopian world?!
Suck it in! Swallow the Heavenly
Realm and everything in it, Dead Zone!
"Gohan's Brief Chance for Victory!!
Blast the Makyo World..."
Die! The Dead Zone will be your grave!
G-Gohan!
K-Kami is...
K-Kami-sama!
Damn!
If we don't beat him, then dispersing
the Ultra Holy Water won't matter!
Piccolo!
Kami-sama!
W-What is happening now?
Don't know. Probably Garlic Jr. behind it.
T-The Dead Zone?
How can he use that technique again?!
Once I finish you off, I will
revive my Demon Clansmen,
and rule the world!
As long as I have the Makyo
World, my power is unbounded!
I will continue to spread
terror and hopelessness...
...by the effects of the Makyo World!
It's no use!
Gohan, not even you can
blast your way through him now!
G-Gohan... The Makyo World...
You have to destroy the Makyo
World, the source of his power!
There's no way he can
handle something like that!
It's all he can do to generate this Shield.
It's the only way...
Y-You don't mean...
he has to remove this Shield?!
Do it, Gohan! At this rate, no one will survive!
How long do you think
you can stand up to this?
You can regret your
foolishness in this endless hell!
W-What are you loafing around for, Gohan?!
Hurry and blast the Makyo World!
But the moment I remove this Shield,
Piccolo-san, you and Kuririn-san
will be drawn into the Dead Zone!
Blast it, Gohan!
Gohan! Remove the Shield!
Kuririn-san!
We don't matter!
You're the only one who can
stop Garlic Jr.'s evil designs, Gohan!
I... I couldn't do such a thing!!
Kami-sama...
What's this?
Have ancient Kami-sama forgiven Kami-sama?
You rotten bunch of know-nothings!
Haven't you figured
out yet why I've done this?
W-What's that?!
Where are we?
Kami!
K-Kami-sama!
My power!
My power is back to normal!
Why, you...!
You fool! You have returned
just so that you could die!
Piccolo!
Piccolo-san!
So you've chosen your own death?
Stay alive just a little longer, Kami!
P-Piccolo!
Idiot! What are you planning?
Fine, then!
If you want to rush your death,
that's up to you. Go to hell!
Now, Gohan! Blast it!
Piccolo-san!
Blast it, Gohan!
Now, while Piccolo has his attention!
But...
There's no time, Gohan!
Kuririn-san!
Fall! Fall!
Is this all you've got?
W-What?!
You think you're clever?!
Annoying insects!
Now! Gohan!
Blast it!
What?!
O-Oh hell, no!
Wherever you may be,
I'm going to find you, Kakarrot!
I'll teach you who the Number
One Saiyan in the universe is!
Ahem, have I done anything... inappropriate?
Of all the...
Where's Gohan-chan gone off to?
What does he mean by
leavin' me in such a place?
You there!
You guys stop spendin' all your time
ridin' those useless toys, and study some!
Right!
Piccolo-san...
Kuririn-san...
Piccolo-san! Kuririn-san!
Kami-sama! Mister Popo!
Thank goodness! You've survived!
Yeah, somehow or another...
Hey... Gohan...
Move it, would you?
Yo, everyone.
Kuririn-san!
Kuririn-san, thank goodness!
Boy, that was a real close one there!
It's thanks to you
destroying the Makyo World!
Piccolo-san!
If that rotten Garlic's
body hadn't gotten smaller,
we would have been drawn
into the Dead Zone instead.
I see.
At the moment Garlic Jr. lost the
power he was using to brace himself,
he could no longer endure the struggle!
With the Makyo World destroyed,
there's no way he can
possibly revive himself.
He really was an idiot.
Piccolo-san, even without
Father around, we won, huh?
Against an opponent the likes of
Garlic Jr., we don't need his power.
B-But...
Ordinarily, you would have
been a match for him by yourself.
Forgive me.
I will keep training.
Gohan!
You've done well, Gohan.
Garlic Jr.'s latest designs had been thwarted.
As such, it was thought that everyone...
...would continue spending
their days in peace. However...
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Kuririn, you're gonna
propose to Maron-chan, right?
What are you dawdling around for?
There's a legendary giant
pearl, the Mermaid's Tear,
at the bottom of the sea around here,
that will make one's girlfriend happy.
I'll do it after I get it.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"You're My Guy... Kuririn –
A 101st Proposal."
Kuririn-san is going to get married!
"Next time"
"You're My Guy... Kuririn–
A 101st Proposal"