Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
In the face of Freeza's overwhelming power,
Gohan, Kuririn, Vegeta and Dende's
fates were like candles in the wind.
However, just then...
...Piccolo finally arrived!
Having merged with Nail to
become several times more powerful,
Piccolo was quite sure of himself.
"Piccolo's Self-Confidence!
I Will Be the One to Defeat Freeza."
I'll do this by myself. You guys stay out of it.
It's senseless! Not even Piccolo has
a chance of winning against that guy!
Piccolo-san...
Piccolo's ki has increased
considerably since he left his training here.
What's going on?
In that case, Kaio-sama,
are you saying Piccolo has the
potential to win against Freeza?
No...
They have touched that which
should have remained untouched.
Freeza's power is unmatched.
If Piccolo is beaten,
Kami-sama will also die.
If that happens, our chance at
resurrection will probably be forever lost.
Piccolo, you have to stick it
out until Goku has recovered!
That is the issue, isn't it?
Leave this to me, he says.
He doesn't understand how terrifying Freeza is!
He'll realize it soon enough.
Piccolo-san isn't the kind of person
who doesn't know his opponent's strength.
But Gohan, Piccolo hasn't–
I'm sure of it! Piccolo-san
has a chance of winning!
A chance of winning?
There's no way he can win!
Even though he may have shown up,
our situation hasn't changed a bit.
But Piccolo-san is...
This ki is Piccolo's.
Piccolo has been resurrected!
But this time his ki is different,
more incredible than ever!
H-He looks just like Nail-san,
but is this Piccolo fellow
also a Warrior-type Namekian?
You appear to be quite sure
of yourself. But soon enough,
that surety will shatter, give way and
turn to your begging for your life from me.
Enough from you.
Take this!
He did it!
Way to go, Piccolo!
Struggle though he might,
there's no way he can win.
I hate to admit it, but all I can do
is escape and wait for another chance.
I'm not stupid enough to just
wait around to be killed by Freeza.
Well, come on out!
You've got greater power than that, haven't you?
Piccolo-san!
You're not that bad.
I mean, you were able to dodge that
from close range by a hair's breadth.
Vegeta!
Where are you going?
Don't tell me you need to go pee, now.
Dammit!
Vegeta...
It won't do to have the prince
of the warrior race Saiyans...
...sneaking away with his
tail tucked between his legs.
However...
No matter what you may try,
your destiny is to be killed by me.
You just sit still and wait for it.
Once I kill the Namekian, your turn comes next.
Sorry for the delay.
Now, show me the power
of that confidence you hold.
You are a fool not to feel my terror!
Gohan! Piccolo has greater
power than we can imagine!
We may be able to hope for something here.
Right! Piccolo-san will do it!
He's your sensei, after all, right?
Right!
N-Nail-san!
Could it be?
Piccolo-san...
Piccolo-san!
Do not be upset.
It will take more than that to kill him.
But I will show you how I'll take him apart!
You fought well, for a Namekian.
I'll give you credit for that.
But it's over. The fun stops now.
Damn.
Piccolo-san!
We are now completely out of Namekians.
What?!
Piccolo-san!
Don't take me so lightly.
G-Gohan! We might be able to win!
You could be right.
With Piccolo and the three of us,
this could turn out all right after all!
Okay then, it's decided!
Stay out of this!
I thought I told you I'd do this by myself.
But...
We can contribute at least something.
Leave this to me.
That fool! This is our
one chance to defeat Freeza!
He's no match for Freeza's
power just by himself!
You filthy maggot!
Haven't you realized it yet?
We can see through your every move!
What?! What do you mean "we?"
What does this mean?
Piccolo!
Piccolo...
Piccolo's ki has surged yet again.
What's happening?!
You've become a giant, and you're using
both hands, yet this is the best you've got?
That voice...
I know! What if I were to fight
using only my left hand for you?
Something like that cannot
possibly work against me, can it?
Surely you see there is no way you can win.
I have merged with Piccolo.
What?!
I-I knew it!
By doing so, my power has
increased several times over.
Unite with me.
I am the... last Warrior-Type
Namekian left on my world.
What? Unite with you?
That's right.
If you do, your current power
will be increased several times over.
What incredible power!
What an unbelievably fearsome power this is!
Is this what uniting with someone is like?!
Awesome!
Impossible! I don't believe it!
I have obtained the ultimate power!
Piccolo-san!
Piccolo!
Impossible!
What?!
He did it!
Why, you!
Nail has merged with Piccolo,
but can Piccolo defeat Freeza?
And what about Goku?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
There's no end to Freeza's power!
At this rate, everyone will be killed!
You are capable of more than I imagined,
so I decided to show you my
true power. You should feel honored.
You're the first ones I've ever
shown this transformation to!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Attack, Goku!! An Enraged
Freeza's Second Transformation."
Father! Hurry!
"Next time"
"Attack, Goku!! An Enraged
Freeza's Second Transformation"