Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Change!!
I did it!
Finally, the battle against the
mighty Ginyu comes to a conclusion.
However, the damage inflicted
upon Goku is great, and as for Vegeta...
I know that Freeza is probably there too,
but if we can't get the
password, nothing matters anyhow.
Me too!
No. I can handle this myself. You wait here.
And so, in order to learn
how to summon Shen Long,
Kuririn takes off toward
the Grand Elder's location...
"Thou Who Hast Gathered the Seven Balls...
Now Speak Forth the Password."
I wonder if I look any stronger.
I bet if Mother–
or Piccolo-san were to see me
in this outfit, they'd be surprised.
But for some reason, I sure
feel as though I'm stronger now!
I'm the strongest warrior
in the universe, Son Gohan!
Hey, you there!
That pip-squeak friend of
yours said something about...
...taking two hours
before he would return, right?
Yeah.
All right, then.
Stand guard over those Dragon Balls well, then.
I'll be taking a nap inside the spaceship.
Wake me when he gets back.
A nap?
I haven't had any sleep now for quite a while.
Just sit tight, Gohan and Goku!
I'll find out how to summon
Shen Long and be back soon.
That rotten creep!
I can't even be sure he hasn't
already killed the Grand Elder-san!
Please, let me make it in time!
I have to tell Kuririn and the others
about the password as soon as possible!
There they are!
Strange.
I don't feel any ki.
I'm too late!
Kuririn-san!
It's not him!
Okay then, where is Kuririn-san?
Kakarrot.
Once Freeza is out of the way, you're next.
Until then, I need you on my side.
I can't believe I've let myself come to this...
I'll sleep for thirty minutes.
That should be enough to
allow me to count on my full power.
When I open my eyes again,
I will be able to obtain
eternal life and youth for myself.
That should make for some pleasant dreams.
Freeza could show up at any minute.
He's got a lot of nerve going to sleep.
I am only using my left hand,
yet you have still done so poorly.
Surely now you see
there is no way you can win.
How about speaking to me now?
Tell me how the Dragon Balls grant my wish.
You have continued to expend
your energies so pointlessly.
Such actions cannot possibly
work against me, can they?
Have you not fully realized this yet?
I cannot understand
why you continue to defy me,
when you must certainly
know you are beaten?
Is it because your friends have been killed?
Or perhaps, is it due to
common stubbornness?
Let me make this my final warning.
Tell me how the Dragon Balls grant wishes.
You will die, otherwise.
Even if you were to find out,
by now, it no longer matters.
Very soon, Dende will arrive at the...
location where the... Earthlings are.
He is there to tell the...
the very same password you're after!
What?!
Him?
Why you! You've just been buying time for him?!
The Ginyu Special Corps–
I get no reading on them!
Can it be that all five of
them have been eliminated?
In any case, something's happened
between Vegeta, the Earthlings,
and the Ginyu Special Corps!
So what's happened to the Dragon Balls?!
Rotten punks!
It will be to me, Freeza-sama,
that that wish is granted!
It will not be to you lower life forms!
How regrettable that it must come to this.
I should have told the Earthlings
the password when I had the chance.
Now I've caused Nail to suffer so terribly.
Move swiftly, Dende.
It seems my end has drawn near.
Kuririn-san!
Gohan-san!
I wonder if it really will take
Kuririn-san two whole hours to get to
the Grand Elder-san and back.
What am I supposed to do if
Freeza comes back before then?
I hope Kuririn-san gets back soon.
A ki!
Someone is flying towards Goku's direction.
I recognize this ki.
I knew it! It's Dende!
Hey!
It's me, it's me!
I'm just dressed this way is all.
Kuririn-san!
–Thank goodness!
Hey, you...
You're that bad Ginyu fellow, who took
over my father's body and such, aren't you?
I knew it! Come here, you!
You can't do anymore bad stuff now.
This really saves our necks.
We've gotten all the Dragon Balls together,
but we couldn't get Shen Long to appear,
So I was just on my way to the
Grand Elder-san's place to find out
what the password is.
That's what I thought.
I was told by the Grand Elder-sama to find you
and tell you how to get your wish granted.
Oh, really? So, what is
it we're supposed to say?
The password must be spoken
in the Namekian language,
or else the wish will not be granted.
Namekian, huh? That makes sense.
The Grand Elder-san isn't very good with people,
or else he could have told
us that while we were there.
He must not have thought...
...you were going to be able to get all
the Dragon Balls together, or he would have.
Maybe so.
Never mind that, we must hurry!
The Grand Elder-sama's life is nearly at an end.
Freeza might be on his way, as well.
Yeah, you're right.
Something's coming...
It's Kuririn-san... But I can feel two ki...
He's hidden his ki!
It really is Kuririn-san.
But who's with him?
It's Dende-kun! Yeah!
–We made it! It's Gohan!
–Thank goodness!
That was incredibly fast!
How did you manage it?
Easy. Dende here was asked by
the Grand Elder-san to come to us.
You mean, to tell us how to use the
Dragon Balls and get our wish granted?
Right!
Now then, what's Vegeta up to?
I've been holding my ki since before we
got here so he wouldn't realize we're back.
I don't think he's noticed.
He said something about
not having slept recently,
and is napping inside the spaceship.
Great! This is working out nicely.
Okay, then. Very quietly,
so Vegeta doesn't notice,
we'll carry the Dragon Balls over to this area.
That way, even if he realizes
that Shen Long has appeared,
we'll have bought some time.
Yahoo! We did it!
Okay, it's up to you now, Dende.
Right!
Kuririn-san, something's coming this way.
Very fast.
It's Freeza!
Hurry, Dende! Hurry and get our wish granted!
Right!
Nothing's happening.
Hey, Dende, are you sure
you didn't goof up the password?
They're glowing!
The sky is getting dark!
Just like the Dragon Balls on Earth!
What's this?
Why has it suddenly become night?
It looks like the wish will soon be granted!
–They did it!
–Yeah!
We can finally return to life!
Isn't this great, Ten-san?
He-He's huge!
Far bigger than the one on Earth.
Is-Is that Shen Long?
Here, he is called "Polunga."
It means "God of Dreams."
This is the first time I've seen him, too.
Thou who hast gathered the
Dragon Balls, now speak thy wishes.
I shall grant thee any three wishes,
whichsoever art within my ability.
Three? Did he just say three?
That's right. You can have three wishes granted.
Really?! Looks like Nail-san was right!
What should we do?
We have three wishes, three!
Polunga, the "Super"
Shen Long finally appears...
What will Kuririn and the others
ask for with their three wishes?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
They did it! The original Shen
Long brought Piccolo back to life!
You have really done it now,
have you not, gentlemen?
You have done an outstanding job of
shattering my dreams of eternal youth.
I trust that you are prepared to pay the price.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Kami-sama Also Returns to Life!
Piccolo Is Resurrected by Super Shen Long."
I really will be glad
once Piccolo-san gets here.
"Next time"
"Kami-sama Also Returns to Life!
Piccolo Is Resurrected by Super Shen Long"