Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Doctor Gero...
W-What's this?
The Artificial Human No. 20's true identity...
...is that of the maniacal Red
Ribbon scientist Doctor Gero himself?!
With Trunks traveling through time once again,
we learn that the Artificial Humans
responsible for turning the future world...
...into a hellish existence were No. 17 and No. 18.
"And the Terror Becomes Reality...
No. 17 and No. 18 Awaken."
What an utterly self-centered know-nothing!
I get you. All we have to
do then is get there first,
and then destroy No. 17 and No. 18 before
Doctor Gero has a chance to activate them.
I wouldn't do such a cowardly thing.
I just want to be first in line to put
the others away with my own two hands!
The Artificial Humans we just took
on gave us such a poor fight, after all.
You must not. You underestimate
the Artificial Humans.
As Piccolo-san said, we should
destroy them before they are started up.
What foolishness! I have
to find a way to stop this.
Until Goku-san returns to us...
I am the Prince of the Saiyans!
I will not be placed on the same level
as that lower-class warrior Kakarrot!
It is I who am the Super
Saiyan among Super Saiyans!
Be they No. 17, No. 18, or anything
else, I'll turn them to scrap quickly!
It's already too late! You will all be killed!
T-This is my first time against anyone
like this–against anyone this strange!
Goku-sa! Goku-sa!
Goku! Hang on, Goku!
Goku-sa, are you all right?
Get a hold of yourself, Goku-sa!
He must be havin' a pretty terrifyin' dream.
Goku, I beg you, please get better soon!
Goku-sa!
How much farther is this Metro North?
We should nearly be there.
I see it!
What about Vegeta?
If we don't find the
laboratory before Vegeta does,
things are going to get really bad.
How long were you
planning on watching over me?
Get lost! You're annoying me.
I can't do that.
You want to fight with the
Artificial Humans, don't you?
What do you think you're going
to do once we get to the laboratory?
Are you planning on
destroying the Artificial Humans,
even if you have to fight me to do so?
That's probably what it will come to.
How many times must I tell you?
You underestimate how terrible
No. 17 and No. 18 really are.
Being told such a thing only makes
a pure Saiyan want to fight even more.
So then, where is this
laboratory of Doctor Gero's?
You don't understand any of this!
Gohan, ain't we at yer place yet?
I'm gettin' worn out.
What are you talking about?
That huge bulk of yours
is just being carried along.
You've got some nerve.
Think about what Gohan-kun
must be going through.
I don't really mind.
Yajirobe, did you hear that? How big of you!
Trunks, you be sure to grow
up like big brother Gohan here!
He'll be fine. Didn't we just
see how sharp Trunks-san was?
You're right, he was pretty sharp, wasn't he?
You sure you can believe that 'bout him?
I beg your pardon?!
How dare you speak so rudely of my son!
Bulma-san!
Sorry, but Yajirobe's–
There's no mistakin' he was your kid, Bulma,
but ya hafta consider he's also Vegeta's kid.
What's that?! Let's tell Vegeta he said that.
F-Forget I said that, 'kay, Bulma-sama?
Trunks-san is a good man.
He came back through time just to
warn us about the upcoming danger.
That's right! Leave it to
Gohan to come up with that.
He still has a mean look about him, though.
And that's just what we'll
relay to your father, Trunks!
Please stop kiddin' 'round, Bulma-sama!
If Trunks-san hadn't warned us ahead of time,
we wouldn't have known
about Father's illness...
...or about the Artificial Humans, or any of this.
On top of that, he prepared that medicine.
He really is a bright, considerate young man.
I sure hope Father is taking
his medicine and getting better.
Of course he's getting better!
Yeah, you're right. I'm going to speed up some!
W-W-Waitaminnit!
She said Doctor Gero's laboratory was
in a cave around here somewhere, right?
It sure is cold here in the north.
You think we can find it?
There are nothing but mountains all around us.
What's more, he may be able to sense our ki,
but there's no way we can feel out his ki.
We'll have to split up and search.
Whichever one of us finds
it first will signal the others.
So, what kind of signal should we use?
Suddenly raise your ki.
We'll know what you mean.
Indeed.
It's so cold! We should have dressed warmer!
Live with it! I'm cold too, you know.
How inconvenient for you Earthlings.
If we don't act fast, No. 17
and No.18 will be started up!
All right. Let's split up and find it.
Our future as Earthlings depends on it.
Hold on!
What, so you can tell us
how cold you are again?
T-That's not it!
I was just thinking of dividing
up the remaining senzu among us.
That's right! They'll be helpful.
There are six of them left, here.
There are three of us, and
since three times two is six,
we each get two.
I sure would like to take care of
all this without having to use these.
So, they're here, all right.
But they won't find my laboratory so easily!
Just keep prowling around!
I'll kill you all soon enough!
I mistook ya fer some game! You okay?
Good golly!
What's the matter?
There was this nutty old man...
That's Doctor Gero! Which way did he go?
Thattaway.
All right!
Hey! Don't leave me here like this!
I thought this was supposed
to be a "No Trespassing" area.
This way!
Kuririn!
This is terrible...
This must have been done by Doctor Gero.
That way!
Meddlesome insect!
Your level of energy will be
of absolutely no use to me.
Dammit! Mock me, will you?!
I'll crush you once and for all!
Piccolo?
There's no need for me to
dirty my hands at this point.
You get to live a little while longer.
Consider yourself fortunate.
It's just a matter of time now.
I-I have to let the others know...
But first, I have to locate the laboratory!
Here it is! I finally made it back!
I-I found it!
I found it! Now to inform the others!
He intends to call his friends, does he?
Well he's too late. Time is on my side now.
I have to hurry and call everyone.
Everyone, come quick!
He found it?
What's with this ki?
If there were another way,
I wouldn't think of activating these two.
But at this point, I have no choice.
I hope they're back in order...
So, have you awakened, No. 17?
Good morning, Doctor Gero-sama.
Cordiality towards me?
Of course. You are my creator, after all.
Looks like he's in good working order all right.
Now, for No. 18...
Good Morning, Doctor Gero-sama.
Oh! Even you greet me so cordially.
It is only natural.
Apparently they're both working properly.
I see you have also become an Artificial Human.
I wanted eternal life as well, you know.
Frankly, I'm a bit relieved.
What with most of your parts being
hooked in to an eternal energy source,
and having so much power at your disposal,
it was hard for you to keep control,
and you would not accept
any of my commands until now.
From now on, I will
have you do as I command.
Now, I have to put you to work right away.
Very soon, some friends
of Son Goku will arrive.
Deal with them all, and
spare no one. Understood?
–Yes.
–We understand.
That's Doctor Gero's laboratory.
Kuririn, nice work finding it!
I guess so.
We've done it. We can take care
of them before he comes back.
Great!
Yeah, well, about that...
What's wrong, Kuririn?
Doctor Gero already has returned.
What?!
S-Sorry.
You should have said so sooner!
What can we do if we're too late?!
They're here! Those fearless, contemptible fools!
So, you guys are on.
This door is awfully strong.
Stand aside. I'll destroy it.
Nice of you to find this!
Beat them all to a pulp!
No. 17! What's this?!
This is your Controller, used to execute
an emergency interrupt on us, isn't it?
Just in case anything were to happen.
I have no use for such a thing.
Why you–what do you think
you're doing?! Is this a joke?
You think we're going to let you
put us to sleep again, you old geezer?
Destroy the Artificial Humans,
and you'll pay for it!
That cannot be allowed!
You do not understand how terrifying
these Artificial Humans really are!
You shut up!
No. 17! Stop kidding around and destroy
our enemies on the other side of that door!
T-The Artificial Humans
have already been activated!
Out of the way, you jackasses!
You must not!
We should get out of here right now!
Please, wait until Son Goku-san
is back on his feet! After that–
That won't be necessary!
A scarf around the neck...
of a young man with long black hair.
That's No. 17.
No. 18 is a cute female type.
Trunks, they're just as you
described, unmistakably so, right?
R-Right.
At last, the Artificial Humans
No. 17 and No. 18 are awakened.
At first look, they do not
appear to be too imposing.
Can they really be the mighty
foes that Trunks says they are?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
No. 16? Trunks, who is
that huge Artificial Human?
Stop, No. 17! Do not start him up!
Do you want to destroy the world as we know it?!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Too Late to Do Anything!?
The Ultimate Weapons to Kill Goku."
I won't let you add any more Artificial Humans!
"Next time"
"Too Late to Do Anything!?
The Ultimate Weapons to Kill Goku"