Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Five years' time had
passed in the blink of an eye
since Piccolo's schemes for
conquering the world were shattered,
thanks to the actions taken by Son Goku.
Every day that went by, the
world was the very picture of peace.
However, there was a new
specter creeping its way forward...
"Mini-Goku is an Overprotected Boy!
I am Gohan."
Gohan-chan!
Lunch is ready!
This one will do!
Gohan-chan!
Welcome back.
Goku-sa, where's Gohan?
I'm famished already!
What are you talkin' about?
Have you seen Gohan-chan?
Huh? I ain't seen him.
Where could he have gone off to?
If you don't eat and get out of here soon,
Muten Roshi-sama and the others
will grow impatient waitin' for you.
All right, I'll go look for him.
I don't think he's gone too far off.
Right. Leave it to me!
I'm countin' on you!
Really, what am I goin' to do with that boy?
Just a little bit more now...
W-What was that just now?!
A meteor?! A UFO?!
How's about I go look?
Okay, now...
Ah, that's no meteor! What in tarnation is it?
Huh?
So, the folks on this planet
are still alive after all, huh?
That miserable Kakarrot!
W-Who are you?!
Your battle power is a
mere five, huh? Piece of trash!
D-Don't come no closer!
I-I'll kill you!
Hmph. What a fragile people.
There's somebody with a great
power around. Range: 4,880.
Is that you, Kakarrot?!
Father! Father!
Father!
Hello there, butterfly!
Wait!
You're way over there...
All right!
Play dead!
My hat?
Father gave that to me!
Hey, Gohan!
Father! Mother!
What a nice headdress!
You sure are pretty.
My name is Son Gohan.
Wait!
Mother! Father!
Hey, you, about that hat...
That belongs to my son, Gohan.
Where did you come by it?
Where did you come by it?!
Father! Mother!
Gohan!
It's Father!
Just wait there!
I'm coming to save you now!
Gohan!
A little farther!
Father!
Gohan!
Father! Mother!
Father!
Gohan!
All right...
I'm scared!
I'm scared! I can't get down! I'm scared!
Father, that was scary!
That was so scary!
Gohan, did you–?
I-I don't know.
Gohan, let's go home!
Your mommy is worried!
We have to go to Old Timer Turtle
Hermit's place right away too, you know!
That lousy Kakarrot!
W-What kind of power is this?
It couldn't possibly be...
Son Goku?!
No, it's not!
You're not Kakarrot.
Who are you? Do you have
some sort of business with me?
I don't have any
business with the likes of you.
Then what have you come here for?
Do you want to die?
You sure are in high spirits.
Ho... Battle power 322.
So, there are folks like you around, huh?
However, you are still no match for me.
What did you say?! Do you know
who it is you're talking to here?!
Not really...
W-What is the deal with this guy's power?
That was a worthless technique, huh?
Is merely kicking up dust all it can do?
Now it's my turn. Let me show
you a sample of my techniques.
There's another great power here.
That way... Range: 12,909.
It's large... the largest
power on this planet...
This time for sure, it's Kakarrot!
T-This is ridiculous!
I-I was shaking so much, I couldn't move!
Have you lost sight of your pride as a Saiyan,
the mightiest warriors in the universe...
...Kakarrot?!
Who are these Saiyans,
the mightiest warriors in the universe?
And who is Kakarrot?
It appears that the mysterious alien
and Goku are somehow connected.
Next time, Goku's past
will finally become clear!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Old Timer, guys, let me introduce
you to my son, Son Gohan.
You've grown up.
Who are you?
Remember your pride, Kakarrot,
as a Saiyan, the greatest
warriors in the universe!
What?!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Mightiest Warrior in All of
History is Goku's Older Brother!"
Father, do you really think
I can become a great scholar?
"Next time"
"The Mightiest Warrior in All of
History is Goku's Older Brother!"