Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
T-The Land...
the Seas...
and...
all living things...
Each of you, share with me
just a little bit of your Genki energy!
All right!
Take this!
This is the end for you, Kakarrot!
Die!
N-Now, I ain't even got
enough strength left to blow my nose...
D-Do as you like...
Why, you...!
I'm going to squeeze you to death!
Goku's body, along with the fate
of the Earth, was about to be crushed!
"Don't Die, Father!!
This is the Depth of Gohan's Power."
Don't you die, Goku.
Father...
That guy's intense.
It's no use. This is all over.
It's not like I'm desertin' ya, though.
There's just nothin' I can do.
Don't go holdin' it against me, 'kay?
Suffer good and long, and then die!
It's close! We're almost there!
Even though it's the evening, because
of that strange light, it's as bright as this.
W-What the hell is that thing?
K-Kuririn-san, o-over there!
Get down, Gohan! Get down, and hide!
W-What is that?
Hurry up, you stupid twit!
Ah, it's those guys.
It can't be... He's turned into a Great Ape!
Feels like most of your bones
just broke, huh? Does it hurt?
Goku is getting done in! This is bad!
This way!
Right!
Hey!
Yajirobe!
Hey, who d'ya think that monster is?
It's the Saiyan, I tell ya, the Saiyan!
I know.
There's no way you can stand up
to that monster, you know! Give it up!
I know that, too. But if we cut
off his tail, he'll return to normal.
His tail?
Listen up.
Gohan and Yajirobe, you guys circle
around in front of him, and get his attention.
I'll find an opportunity to
cut off his tail from the back!
Hurry! Goku is going to die!
R-Right.
Y-Ya gotta be kiddin' me.
Get his attention, did'ja say?
You guys don't even know!
Even after he's back to normal, he's
still gonna have unbelievable strength!
Father, don't die!
Goku's ki is almost completely gone!
Dammit, he's moments from death!
Eh, do whatever you wanna.
There's something out there.
Where is it?
Over here!
L-Let my father go!
This is a surprise. If it isn't Kakarrot's kid.
I get it. So you've come here just to
see your father meet his end, have you?
You've got good timing.
He was just about to die.
I was right about to finish him off.
Kienzan!
Damn it all...
Watch very closely. I'm going to
crush him until there's nothing left.
Kuririn-san, hurry!
Unfortunately, it appears he
has already lost consciousness.
I-I-It can't be!
Did you think I wouldn't notice
that there was another one of you?
You guys seem to share some
worthless attachment for each other, after all.
There's no way this kid would
just come strolling back by himself,
so I was just waiting to see what would happen.
Apparently, you know
about our tails. Too bad for you.
Just you wait. Once I've taken care
of Kakarrot, it will be your turn next.
D-Damn! What kind of beast is this?
Even after turning into a monster,
he still has his presence of
mind and his guard is flawless.
I'm sorry, Goku. I don't
want to just let you die,
but this guy's ki is so incredible,
I can't even get close to him.
You guys were mistaken
to have challenged me to battle!
Dammit! If we don't do something...
Stop...
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop!
So, you want to die
ahead of your father, do you?
T-This is bad!
What's the matter? Too scared to move?
Dammit! I didn't know
there was yet another one!
My tail!
H-He did it!
I got nothin' to do with this...
I-I got nothin' to do with this from here on...
I-It's gone! His tail is gone!
You did it, Yajirobe!
He returned to his original form!
It's not my problem... Whatever
happens now, it's not my problem...
W-Why, you...!
You want to die so badly
that you've made me angry?!
W-What's going on? Why did that monster–?
In that case, as you wish,
I will kill you, you miserable scum!
There, ya see?
Gohan! Get out of there!
I'll start with you.
What's the matter? Wasn't a
Super Saiyan supposed to be strong?
Show me your true power.
Maybe the order has been changed.
There, you see? Don't say I didn't warn ya.
Come on, get up! Amuse me a little while longer.
Hey, what's wrong? Is that the best you can do?
I guess the son of scum...
...is scum, as well.
You may be scum, but it looks
like your blood is red, at least.
How awful!
How can he be so cruel to a child?!
She's strangely tranquil, huh?
I'm sure she must have run out of tears.
She hasn't fainted, has she? Hey!
Hey!
Ee-yow!
–Yow! Yow! Yow!
–Fight...
Fight.
Fight! Fight, Gohan! Fight!
Avenge your daddy's death!
Get up, Gohan! Fight, Gohan! Fight!
How about I at least let you
die next to your father? I'll be kind.
G-Gohan...
Oh? Kakarrot, you're a tough one.
You're still conscious, are you?
Gohan, can you hear me?
Gohan, your daddy's whole
body is a mess. I can't move anymore.
Fight in my place. His power
should have dropped considerably.
I-I can't, Father! He's
too strong! I can't beat him!
All right, I'll do it this way–
I'll follow my order, and kill Kakarrot first.
Next will be Kakarrot's kid.
After that, I'll finish off
that bald bastard from earlier.
Finally, I'll kill the bastard
who cut off my precious tail!
He remembered me, huh?
You don't have to beat him...
Just keep him bottled up...
Your power should be even
more incredible than his... even more...
While you're doing that,
I'll have Kuririn finish him off...
I can't! I can't even move anymore!
You stupid jackass! Do you want
everyone else's deaths to be in vain?
What did Piccolo teach you?
I'm counting on you, Gohan...
For left-behind scum, you're
sure giving me a lot of trouble!
G-Gohan!
What's the matter?! Eh?!
S-Stop... that...
Die!
Stop... that!
What's the matter? Die! Die!
Stop that!
What?!
I'm going...
...to defeat you!
You are going to defeat me?
What the...?!
Kuririn!
Kuririn, please! Come here!
D-Dammit...
Don't you mess around with Vegeta-sama!
G-Goku, it's hopeless. He's just too terrible.
Why didn't you tell Gohan to run away?
I'm going to give this to you now, Kuririn...
The Genki Dama that
I gathered from all over the Earth...
Eh? What did you say?
What are you going to give me?
A-A Genki Dama... Ki that I've
collected from everything on Earth...
About half of it got away, but I think
it will still defeat him, the way he is now...
W-What?
Kuririn... take my hand...
I don't understand this at all.
Hurry! Gohan is going to die!
I just have to take your hand?
Please...
Like this?
Your bones are broken, aren't they?
That's okay... Don't let go...
I'm giving it to you now, so take it...
W-W-What is this?
I-It's awesome... This is
a tremendous amount of ki!
Turn your palm upward, and focus it...
You can make it into a ball...
You dirty brat!
Hang in there...
Gohan ain't able to control this kind of ki...
I-It came out! Is this–?
A Genki Dama... You did it!
You're a pesky brat!
Kuririn... hit him with it...
I can't make another Genki Dama...
M-Make sure you hit him! Please!
U-Understood. I'll try.
Will the Genki Dama that has been entrusted
to Kuririn be able to put a stop to Vegeta?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Kuririn, we're counting on you.
That Genki Dama is filled
with the hopes of everyone.
It's no use! He's too fast!
I can't tell how he's going to move!
What're ya doin', ya dimwit?!
Hurry up and hit him!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Shoot, Kuririn!
The Genki Dama, Packed with Hope."
Vegeta! Die already, would you?!
"Next time"
"Shoot, Kuririn!
The Genki Dama, Packed with Hope"