The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
The fearsome Majin Boo!
Vegeta staked his life
challenging him to no avail,
and fell, shattering to bits.
Was there no way remaining to
stop Madoshi Babidi's schemes?
However, having arrived at Kami's palace,
Goku told Piccolo and the others
about a way to oppose Majin Boo.
We'll use Fusion!
Fusion! Merging together, right?
It's a unification technique that can be used
only if the powers and body
sizes of two people are pretty close.
Unification technique?
In other words, by having
two people unite into one,
they become a new individual,
with awesome powers that neither
one of them could have on their own!
Knowing Goten and Trunks,
they might be able to do it!
There's still some hope remaining!
"Goten and Trunks–
The World's Most Wanted."
K-Kaioshin-sama!
W-What in the world happened?
Oh... you're alive?!
G-Gohan-san is alive... still... Gohan-san...
Hey! Majin Boo, where
do you think you're going?!
Hey!
Hey, you! Why don't you
watch out?! Really, you bastard!
You're finished now. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye?
You're a smart-aleck!
Squeeze!
W-Where are you going?!
Hey, hey, hey! Boo!
C-Customer, sir, are you hurt?
Welcome! What can we get for you?
Everything!
Everything, you say?
Majin Boo! What are you doing?! Let's go!
Still don't feel like I've eaten.
What's this?! Who are you?!
Okay! That should be about enough, right?!
Let's go!
Still don't feel like I've eaten.
Ah, wait a minute! Majin Boo!
W-What are you doing?!
Let me go! How ill-mannered of you!
You're the ill-mannered
one here, aren't you Uncle?
Uncle?!
Please pay for those cakes!
Include the cost for repairs
to the door, the show window,
and everything else, if you please!
I won't let you go until then.
Sweetheart, you don't
seem to know who I am.
Not in the least!
You'll learn whether you want to or
not soon enough, but I'll tell you anyway.
Whether or not this world
continues on its way to destruction
is entirely up to my will!
I am Madoshi Babidi-sama!
I don't care if you're a Madoshi or a
Keiyoshi, you'll have to pay your bill!
How rude of you! Papparapa!
She vanished!
Would you like to try vanishing too?!
Help me!
Attention criminals! Cease your
futile resistance and come out quietly!
Majin Boo! Haven't you had enough yet?!
No good. This cake is yummy,
but doesn't make my tummy full.
Majin Boo! Right now!
Do you want to be sealed up again?!
Don't move!
You're under arrest for destruction of
property and failure to pay your check!
Dammit!
Still don't feel like I've eaten.
Don't get so mad.
Come on, let's go agonize that
green guy and those two runts now!
I'll teach them! I'll show
them quite a scene real soon!
K-Kaioshin-sama!
K-Kaioshin-sama! Kaioshin-sama!
Thank goodness! There's still time!
Kaioshin-sama!
K-Kibit!
What is this? Were you not killed by Dabura?
Is that so? What an odd occurrence.
Yes. It's surprising that the
power to return one from death
would be found on this planet.
That's right!
Kibit, please hurry! Gohan-san is also in peril!
We absolutely must not allow Gohan-san to die!
Kaioshin-sama!
Majin Boo! How about getting
back into a good mood already?
I'm hungry!
Kibit, can you feel it?
Majin Boo's enormous power energy?
Yes, of course!
Quite honestly, I am filled with despair.
There can no longer be any days of rest
for any living thing throughout the universe.
The situation that we most
feared has become a reality.
It's not necessarily hopeless.
I have come to see a faint light.
Don't tell me this is
somehow related to Son Gohan!
That's right.
His power, already beyond imagination,
can become something even more fantastic,
perhaps even surpassing Majin Boo!
What's that?! Impossible, how can that be?
You did not see how
incredible those three Saiyans are,
so you probably cannot imagine it.
We must find him quickly!
Gohan-san's ki is very weak,
but I feel it coming from those trees.
He should be around here somewhere.
There he is! Over there!
He's alive! But he's in as much
jeopardy as you were, Kaioshin-sama!
Thank goodness!
Kibit, let us perform
Gohan-san's power restoration...
...after we arrive in the Kaioshin Realm.
D-Don't tell me you intend to allow a human
to set foot inside the Kaioshin Realm!
That holy region into which not
even the Grand Kaio has set foot?
That is correct. Come, let us hurry!
–Right.
–Kai-Kai!
What's up with Bulma's father and mother?
They couldn't stand to leave their pets behind.
They said if they do get killed we can just
bring them back to life with the Dragon Balls.
That's just like your parents, huh Bulma?
I guess so.
If only we knew where
Tenshinhan and them are,
we could let them
take shelter here too.
More importantly,
where are Gohan and Goten?
And Trunks and Vegeta?
So, where are they at?
Goku?
I'll say it, since it's
something that has to be said.
Goten and Trunks are fine...
but Gohan and Vegeta are dead.
They've been killed by Majin Boo.
G-Gohan-kun... It can't be!
Gohan...
Ch-Chichi!
V-Vegeta...
No!!
Bulma! Get a hold of yourself! Bulma!
Chichi!
I-I won't have...
...such a thing...!
Goku, things have gotten awful, huh?
Karin-sama...
I couldn't just sit still, you know?
This is an enemy even
greater than Freeza or Cell
you've fought up to now, Goku.
An evil one has now indeed appeared.
I'm hungry.
There's no helping you!
I know! I just had a good idea!
This should cheer you up.
Goku, let's hurry and teach them Fusion.
That's right. Popo,
where are Trunks and Goten?
Can you hear me, people of Earth?
I am the Madoshi Babidi!
Oh, don't look for me, you won't find me!
I'm speaking to your minds through magic.
Sorry to interrupt while
you're living peacefully.
The thing is, I had a rather
disagreeable thing happen to me today,
at the hands of a certain trio of fools.
I'm looking for those fools now.
What is this?
–Are you hearing this too?
–Yeah. What's going on?
Close your eyes and watch,
I'm about to project their images.
What's he doing?!
Can you see them now?
I'm looking for these three.
Come on out! You must
know who you are yourselves!
If you don't come out...
I know, why don't we introduce ourselves?
I am the terrifying Madoshi Babidi-sama!
And this is my servant, the
even more frightening Majin Boo!
He's a strong one!
There is utterly no one
around who can beat him!
Can you see this city?
If those three fools do not come forward,
let me show you just a
little of what will happen.
S-Stop!
I don't much care for things to get all messy,
so I will kill everyone in
this city in a smartly manner!
Okay, begin, Majin Boo!
Help!
Th-That scum! What is he planning to do?!
What should I make you?
I've had enough cake, so... okay!
You turn into hard candy!
All the people on this
planet will end up like this!
Babidi's terrible plans to call out
Piccolo and the others have finally begun.
Will everyone be devoured up by Majin Boo
before Piccolo, Trunks
and Goten show themselves?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Whew, Gohan, good for you,
getting saved from danger like that.
Gohan-san, using this legendary
sword of the Kaioshin Realm,
I want you to defeat Majin Boo.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Gohan Revived –
Kaioshin's Secret Weapon!?"
Legendary sword?
I wonder if it's incredibly sharp.
"Next time"
"Gohan Revived–Kaioshin's Secret Weapon!?"
It's a little bit scary.