The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Majin Boo's rampage remains unstopped.
Boo, with his overwhelming power,
has destroyed cities, one after the other.
And, incredibly, he has even turned
living things into clay with his magic,
and built his own house!
Elsewhere, Goten and
Trunks' training continued.
However, halfway through their
training, Goku's time limit arrived.
Goku placed his hopes in Goten and Trunks,
and cheerfully returned to the Other World.
Let's get together again after you die!
"Where is Gohan!?
Ferocious Training in the Kaioshin Realm."
Wow, the number of dead is incredible!
So, are you sure you were right
leaving the Earth up to those little guys?
Yeah! Knowing them, it'll be okay!
If they can just master Fusion,
they'll defeat Majin Boo for sure.
You were right.
The Earth should be protected
by those who live on the Earth.
Okay, Goku, you can go the
rest of the way by yourself, right?
Yeah! Thank you, Ba-chan!
See you later, Goku!
Ba-chan, you come see
me once in a while! See you!
Hey, you there! No line-jumping
is allowed! No line-jumping!
Please stay in your place!
What in the world is going on here oni?
You...!
Sorry! Excuse me!
Oni...
Okay, next!
Yama-san...
Yama-san!
Oh, is that Son Goku?
You're back awfully soon.
Say, Yama-san, I got
something I need to ask you.
What the hell is going on down on Earth?
Just look at the number of dead here!
On top of these, they just keep
coming one after the other like that!
Well, a lot is going on.
It's possible that every
Earthling will be coming here.
What?!
More importantly, just before all these
Earthlings started coming here like this,
did a Son Gohan die and
come through here? He's my son.
Son Gohan? Just a moment...
Son... Son... Son...
Son Gohan...?
No, he hasn't come.
After all, being your son,
I'd probably know it right away,
and I'd have some memory of him.
He hasn't come? Which means...!
He ain't dead! You don't say, you don't say!
Never mind him, there was this
awful guy that came through earlier!
This Dabura,
King of the Demon Realm guy!
Dabura?
You know, to think that guy would die...
Ordinarily, I would have
naturally sent him to Hell,
but Hell is a lot like the Demon Realm.
He would have just been thrilled if I sent
him to Hell, so I sent him to Heaven instead!
"Heaven"
That's great!
Thank you, Yama-san!
Yahoo!
Gohan is alive!
It's just like that girl Videl said!
He came out safely against
Majin Boo! Not too bad, Gohan!
You know something,
seeing as how we didn't feel
Gohan's ki at all, what does that mean?
Th-That's Gohan... It is!
Unmistakable! That's Gohan's ki!
But why would Gohan's ki be in
a place like this? Huh? Where is it?
It ain't in here, nor in the Kaio Realm.
So, where in the world...?
All right, then...!
F-Father!
Whew, that was close, that was close!
W-What are you doing in that outfit?
It's just... there is a reason for it.
Is that...? Kaioshin-sama!
And that what's-his-name old guy,
who's supposed to be dead, to boot!
W-What is this?!
Yet another human has
entered this holy region?!
So anyway, where in the world are we?
Father, how about you? Why are you here?
It hasn't even been 24 hours yet, right?
Yeah, about that...
Is that so?
Majin Boo has torn up
the Earth just that much.
That cursed Majin Boo!
Let me borrow that sword for a minute.
The Z-Sword, did you call it?
Okay.
Please be careful. It's heavy.
All right!
You're right! This is incredibly heavy!
You see?
And this... will give you...
fantastic power? Awesome!
I-Impossible! This man is also just
swinging the Z-Sword around easily?!
What sort of people are these Saiyans?!
Say, Kaioshin-sama,
do you suppose it would be okay
if I stayed here until Gohan
goes to fight Majin Boo?
Sure, I do not mind.
And I hate to ask, but could you
give me something to eat right off?
I'm starving!
V-Very well, Gohan-san, will
you take a short break as well?
Yes.
I shall lead the way. Please come with me.
So, it must be incredible, this Super Saiyan 3!
Yeah, it is awesome! Once we've
eaten something, I'll show you, Gohan!
Since then, one day's time has nearly passed.
Get up!! How long are you planning to sleep?!
Yow-ow-ow-ow!
Okay, as soon as you've washed
your faces and eaten something,
it's back to training! Got that?!
Yeah...
Listen! In one day, you must
fully master Fusion, no matter what!
Get enthusiastic about it! Enthusiastic!
Come... on... you... two!!
Yow-ow-ow-ow-ow-ow...
He didn't have to slug us!
In a critical time like this,
you guys don't have enough time!
You two are the only ones
now who can save the Earth!
Now pull yourselves together!
Piccolo is sure all fired up, huh?
All right, we're resuming the training!
Over here!
W-What?
The training is fine and all, but before that,
show us the proper Fusion Pose once again.
After all, we've only had it
properly shown to us one time so far!
That's right, that's right!
If we don't have an accurate
example shown to us, we can't learn it!
–Okay?
Kuririn, give me a hand!
M-Me?!
You saw that much yesterday.
You remember the Pose, of course.
Th-That may be true, but why me?
Everyone else here saw that Pose too!
That's a dirty trick! Huh? Hey! Where are you?
Kuririn!
All right! I'll do it! I just have to do it, right?
Ready? Watch closely!
Right!
A-As I remember, it was like this, right?
Here goes, Kuririn!
Y-Yeah...
"Fu–"
"–sion!"
"Ha!!"
W-We're doing that ridiculous-looking thing?!
It's embarrassing!
I'm embarrassed too, you know!
W-We're doing this because you guys
said you wanted to see it, didn't you?
Come on! Quit griping,
and let's start training again!
Okay...
Can you believe this?
Two-thirds of the Earth's urban population
has already been eradicated by Majin Boo!
At this rate the Earth will become
a dead planet in less than a day!
W-What?!
Next!
Not even one of you gets away!
Good day! Who's there?
Can't you tell by looking? I'm–
I'm sorry. I cannot see.
Say, who are you? Are you a famous person?
You're a dummy. You just have
your eyes closed. Open them up!
I can't see even if they are open!
That's what kind of disease it is.
Ever since I was born, see?
Is that it? You can't get
scared that way. All right!
What have you done?
Dummy! Try opening your eyes!
But, even if I open them–
Just open them!
I can see... I can see!
I can see. I can see! M-My eyes, I can see!
It's no dream! I really can see!
Now, look at me!
Thank you...
Thank you, mister!
Really, thank you! I can see!
I can see!
He's not scared.
So, mister, are you from a foreign country?
Foreign country?
Yeah. I mean, we don't have that
kind of thing attached to our heads.
Hey!
Do I look cool?
I'm not really sure,
but yeah, I guess you're cool.
After all, you healed my
eyes for me with your magic.
I'm cool! I'm cool!
I know! I'll give you my money as thanks!
Money?
I was going to buy milk with it,
but all the stores were closed.
There it is! Here!
It's yucky!
You wait here.
Incredible! People from
other countries can fly!
Majin Boo!
You turn into milk!
He came back!
Hey, money is yucky. Milk is yummier!
Um, er...
You take it.
Thanks!
Um, thank you!
Really! Really, thank you!
Money is yucky! Milk is yummy!
I am cool!
The Z-Sword and Fusion training continue.
Hurry, Gohan, Goten, and Trunks!
You're the only ones now who can
save the Earth from the risk of extinction!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Say, Gohan, ain't it about time
we see how well thatZ-Sword cuts?
Goku-san, if you want to cut something,
try cutting through katchinko,
the hardest metal in the universe.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"You're Kidding, Right!?
The Z-Sword is Broken."
Huh? Huh...? A strange old man
came out of the broken sword.
"Next time"
"You're Kidding, Right!?
The Z-Sword is Broken"