The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Majin Boo has strength beyond imagination.
In the face of this strength,
Kaioshin and Gohan,
unable to take any action, were beaten.
D-Dabura!
Babidi-sama, he... Majin Boo is by no means
the kind of guy who will
be a loyal follower of yours!
Gonna eat'cha!
And so, Majin Boo closes in on Dabura.
"'Gonna Eat'cha!!'
A Hungry Majin's Supernatural Power."
If I break this cover and go through,
I'll be in Babidi's spaceship.
I should be able to reach Majin Boo's location
quickly if I demolish the spaceship. Most likely.
Gohan's ki has already disappeared, huh?
Forgive me. It's my fault.
Kakarrot...
I'm gonna eat'cha!
E-Eat me, you say?
What?!
Gonna eat'cha! Gonna eat'cha!
Gonna eat'cha! Gonna
eat'cha! Gonna eat'cha!
Gonna eat'cha! Gonna eat'cha!
Aw, that's okay! So long as Majin Boo is
revived, I have no more use for Dabura!
Gonna eat'cha! Gonna eat'cha! Gonna eat'cha!
Dammit!
Gonna eat'cha! Gonna eat'cha!
Why you!
Majin Boo!
How about that, Majin?!
Great! Great, Majin Boo!
I'm gonna eat'cha!
Gonna eat'cha! Gonna eat'cha!
That guy's ki is getting bigger and bigger, fast!
All right then, how about this?!
After that, no matter the
Majin he may have been...
I-Impossible! The Majin! I-It can't be!
You got him, didn't you?
Gonna eat'cha! Gonna eat'cha! Gonna eat'cha!
W-What?!
Gonna eat'cha! Gonna eat'cha!
That's every bit my Majin!
All right! Get him good, Majin Boo!
Gonna eat'cha! Gonna eat'cha!
You turn into a cookie!!
Magnificent! Magnificent!
Nice going, Majin Boo!
He ate him! That guy turned
him into a cookie and ate him!
Y-Yeah...
Kuririn-san!
You guys!
What are you guys doing here?
Huh?
Yet up until just a moment ago,
you were a stone mannequin!
A stone mannequin?
That's right! I was spat upon
by that guy with the horns–
Dabura or whatever–-and turned into stone!
I'm back to normal.
I wonder, could that be
the guy who was just eaten?
That's it, that's it!
Since that guy died, Kuririn-san
returned back to normal, didn't he?
I'm g-going to go look at something.
What's the matter?
Trunks-kun knocked over
Piccolo-san's mannequin and broke it.
Trunks-kun!
Y-You'd better not look.
T-Trunks, did you–
P-Please, keep this from
everybody, okay? Okay?
Keep what from everybody?!
W-What is it?! This terrible ki?! I-Is it him?
Don't tell me it's Majin Boo!
Say, Piccolo-san? How did
you get back to normal? Huh?
As long as my head is
unharmed, I can regenerate.
But never mind that, tell me
what the hell is going on here!
Where are Goku and the others?!
I don't know! We just barely got here too.
Hey, what is that strange guy over there?
Is he that M-Majin Boo guy?!
Probably.
Y-You've gotta be kidding me!
Th-This terrible ki belongs to him, right?!
I know! Majin Boo!
Him too! Eat up Kaioshin too!
Is that Kaioshin-sama?!
Hey, stop, Piccolo!
If you go out there,
what do you plan on doing?!
Be patient! I know how you feel,
but you have to be patient!
Frankly, he's an opponent not even
you can match up against! That's for sure!
He was stabbed through with a spear,
but it was no big deal to him!
And he turns his opponents
into candy and eats them!
What am I gonna turn you into to eat?
Maybe choco? Maybe jelly drops?
What a tragic end, for someone such as yourself!
W-What?!
What?! What?!
M-My spaceship!!
I-It can't be!
Dammit, dammit, dammit!
What's the meaning of this?!
Hey, Majin Boo, do you know
who did such an awful thing?
Is someone there?
Y-You're...!
Yo!
It's Papa!
Vegeta?
Vegeta, what are you doing here?
Vegeta-san...
Y-You don't mean, you're the
one who destroyed my spaceship?!
Yeah. It was a bit rough of me,
but I used it as a shortcut.
Vegeta! Why you...!
H-How come?! You were never
ordered to destroy the spaceship, right?!
Indeed! Why can't you
listen to what you're told?!
I've never seen anybody like you!
Is that uncomely,
ridiculous-looking guy Majin Boo?!
Why, you... How dare you kill Gohan!
S-So, what did Papa say?
Piccolo!
G-Gohan...
Un-come-ly?
What's that? What's that?
He means you're ugly,
that you have a strange face!
Hey, now!
Majin Boo!
Such a pleasant fellow!
Now I'm mad! Gonna kill ya! Gonna kill ya!
Rotten Vegeta! Fine!
Majin Boo, get him!
He defies me like crazy, so I'm done with him!
Hey, that monstrous freak
just made his ki even larger!
What kind of guy is this?
Papa! Give it to that Majin!
Vegeta...
Kill him, Majin Boo! Kill Vegeta!
Kakarrot...
You were someone who
entirely grated on my nerves.
Not only did you always
stay one step ahead of me,
but after you ended up saving my life...
...you died on me!
However,
this one time, I'm going to settle things.
You have a good, long sleep.
When you awake, everything will likely be over.
Though I may not be around.
I'm not going to hell alone!
I'm taking you all with me!
Th-This won't do! Vegeta-san is intent on dying!
Papa's awesome!
This just might be–just possibly might be it!
W-What power!
This can't mean...! Boo! Majin Boo!
Way to go, Papa! Give it to him! Give it to him!
With his life at stake,
Vegeta has begun his battle.
Will Vegeta's super power be enough
to defeat the invincible Majin Boo?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Are you all right, Vegeta?
Going off on your own like that?
What are you planning to do
against that freak opponent?
How can this be? That Majin bastard is strong,
on top of which, he's immortal–it's ridiculous!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"A Warrior's Resolution!!
I Will Dispose Of the Majin."
What can he do? What can
he do to defeat Majin Boo?
"Next time"
"A Warrior's Resolution!!
I Will Dispose Of the Majin"