Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
After successfully stealing all five
Dragon Balls from Freeza's spaceship,
Vegeta showed up in front of Kuririn and Bulma,
who had the last remaining Dragon Ball.
However, just then, Zarbon, who
was under orders from Freeza, appeared.
Elsewhere, Son Goku, who
was speeding to Planet Namek,
was caught in a sudden magnetic storm,
and had fallen into a life-or-death
crisis, due to unstable controls,
which had suddenly subjected
him to 100-times gravity.
"I'm Back to My Old Self Again!!
Goku Under 100-Times Super-Gravity."
G-Goku!
No matter how strong Goku-san may be,
if it takes an hour to get through
that magnetic storm, he won't last!
Can't you do something?
I'm completely like this.
Huh?
I give up.
I-I'll cut the chain!
Kamehame-Ha!!
Go, Kamehame-Ha!
T-This is the worst!
How is this the worst?
He's a pretty nice-looking man, isn't he?
P-Please don't go judging people
by their faces at a time like this!
But usually, the handsome
guy fights for justice.
This isn't Earth, it's Planet Namek.
Yeah, I understand that.
Bulma-san, you don't understand anything.
You've managed to mock me
pretty good, haven't you, Vegeta-san?
I see.
I recall seeing that runt over
there holding the Dragon Ball before.
You guys have joined forces, have you?
Yoo-hoo!
Yoo-hoo, yoo-hoo! Beat up Vegeta!
I don't care about them.
None of that matters.
Vegeta, where have you
hidden the remaining Dragon Balls?
You're going to stand before Freeza and tell us.
Try and make me.
You'll never learn.
Come on, why don't you transform, already?
What?!
Zarbon, until you change
into that hideous form of yours,
you can't fight toe-to-toe with me.
To someone like myself, who prefers beauty,
those words are the greatest insult!
Vegeta, you have gotten me genuinely angry.
But you can relax.
Freeza ordered me to bring you back alive.
You're too soft, Zarbon.
That softness is what
has restored me back to life.
Shut up!
How handsome!
Bulma-san...
Bulma-san, now's our chance!
Let's get out of here!
But he said he'd kill us if we ran!
He'll kill us even if we don't run!
I won't let you do that!
Damn! He doesn't miss a single thing!
Don't you sell me short!
You are prepared to answer for this, yes?
If you are unable to bring
Vegeta back here in one hour...
If this keeps up...
You've finally made up your mind, have you?
H-He's a villain, all right!
W-What was that?! He turned into a monster!
What's more, his power shot up like mad!
Vegeta, you're the only one
who has seen this form twice!
I wonder why it was at
the bottom of that lake.
I know! The villagers might
have been in a rush to hide it.
There are two incredible ki!
They're coming from
where Bulma-san is waiting!
Whichever one of them
wins, it's bad news for us.
S-Son-kun, hurry and get here!
What are you doing, Goku?! Stop that!
I ain't about... to die here!
Goku, it's no use! You can't cut that chain!
G-Goku!
Goku-san!
It's designed so that it
won't break when you do that!
Kaio-ken!!
He did it! He did it!
What a guy! That was amazing!
Damn... that's 100-times gravity for you...
The bones throughout my
body are broken to pieces...
Goku! Goku!
Goku-san! Goku-san!
I know... I can't die here...
I've got bones broken all over...
Vegeta, just you wait!
Goku-san!
Goku!
Goku! Don't worry about
your face! Hang in there!
He did it! He did it! He did it!
Whew, that was a close one.
A little bit more, and
I would have been dead.
But still, I did it.
I experienced 100-times gravity.
At this point, I can go
right to training at 100-times.
You fell for it, Zarbon.
Dammit!
You planned that!
Vegeta! How dare you!
Looks like that hurt pretty bad.
Your strength has dropped
quite a bit, hasn't it?
Zarbon-san, it appears your death is near.
My death is near?!
Don't make me laugh!
My battle power is higher than yours!
Zarbon-san, aren't you supposed
to be well informed about Saiyans?
Carelessly treating me after
I was near death was a bad idea, huh?
Isn't that right?
It's a good thing I brought these senzu...
I'll have to thank Yajirobe...
Yahoo!
Ups-a-daisy!
All right, I'm back to my old self!
Now for some 100-times training–
Before I do, maybe
I'll go have something to eat.
Saiyans are able to increase
their battle power dramatically...
...every time we recover
from the brink of death!
So that's it.
Now that he mentions it, Goku got
stronger every time he had a fierce battle.
Damn, so that's the reason why
Vegeta's ki has risen like crazy, huh?
Listen, even if your battle power has risen,
there's still no way you can
beat me after I've transformed,
and can exhibit my true power!
The Saiyans are a fighting race!
Don't underestimate us!
V-Vegeta... I was only acting
under orders from Freeza-sama...
Let me go... please...
After as much as you've worked me to the bone,
don't you dare go asking
for anything for yourself!
I know... The two of us
could team up... If we did...
...we could even beat Freeza...
If I could defeat Freeza
just by teaming up with you,
it wouldn't be very sporting.
Now then...
I don't know how you did it,
but you've raised your battle power
a bit since we were on Earth, haven't you?
But you're still not at the level where
you can fight me on even terms, are you?
What will it be? Would you be inclined
to hand over that Dragon Ball to me nicely?
I-I doubt it will do any good
to make any agreements with you,
but if I hand this over, do you
promise to leave here without any trouble?
A promise, huh? Well, all right.
As long as I have the Dragon Ball,
there's no sense in playing
around with you, small fry.
Y-You mean it?
What a pest. If that's
how badly you want to live,
then hand it over before I change my mind.
K-Kuririn...
You guys are lucky.
I'm in a good mood, since I have
now found all of the Dragon Balls.
Now I can attain eternal life,
which will allow me to rule the
entire universe, instead of Freeza!
W-We're not about to let
Vegeta get all seven of them!
C-Come on, Gohan!
At length, six of the Dragon Balls
had fallen into Vegeta's hands.
All that remained was the
Si Xing Qiu Ball being held by Gohan.
Will Gohan be able to protect it?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
I've finally gotten all of the Dragon Balls!
The whole universe is now mine!
W-What is this?
There are five enormous
powers headed for Planet Namek!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Freeza's Secret Weapon!
The Devilish Ginyu Special Corps."
I'll never hand over the Dragon Ball!
"Next time"
"Freeza's Secret Weapon!
The Devilish Ginyu Special Corps"