The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Goku and Vegeta merged together
to give rise to the ultra-warrior Vegetto.
Vegetto, with his overwhelming strength,
avoided Majin Boo's attacks,
and instead finally hammered on him!
And then, Vegetto finally
had the Majin cornered.
However, Majin Boo played his
nastiest ace, and absorbed Vegetto!
Had Vegetto gotten careless?
Or instead, was this part of his strategy?
"A Demonic Maze!!
What Is There Inside Boo's Belly!?"
Take that! You're finished
now, you piece of crap!
Eliminate me, you say?
Now that you've been eliminated instead,
you can't cause me any more trouble!
I-It's over...
It's all over now. There is no
other means of saving the universe.
In the end, even as a Kaioshin,
I was unable to do anything... I... I...
No, we don't know that.
Don't you think it's a little strange?
Strange?
Here, have a close look.
Up till now, every time
Majin Boo has absorbed a warrior,
he has powered up, and his
form has changed. But this time...
H-He hasn't changed!
He's the same as he was before
he absorbed Goku-san and company!
W-What could this mean?
I-I'm not too sure.
Maybe this is different–and if so...
...that guy is really something else!
That was a close one!
Goku-san... Vegeta-san...
H-Hey, what the hell is
going to happen to Earth?!
There are no longer any warriors
left that can fight Majin Boo.
All that is left is to wait around
quietly for Majin Boo to destroy us.
That's ridiculous! You're in
together with that man Goku, right?
So don't you lay claim to
some trick that can do something?!
I'm sorry. I am not a fighter-type,
and so I wouldn't be able to...
Damn!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
He has come back!
So, I've already gone around once, huh?
What a puny planet.
It's not even worth destroying like this.
Never mind that, what's going on?
Even though I've absorbed that guy,
there has been no change at all.
Why is that?
No matter. In any case,
he's still been absorbed by me.
Now, I have without question become peerless
among all worlds–the mightiest of Majin!
There is no longer anyone in
existence who can stand in my way!
I can enjoy the death and suffering of
any living thing to my heart's content!
Looks like I was more or less
successful in making my way inside here.
How annoying! How long is he
going to go on laughing like a fool?
Being inside him, I guess there's
no helping it being so noisy.
Never mind that, my barrier
seems to have indeed worked well.
I've gotten away without
being absorbed by him.
All right, that's probably long enough.
I have to dispel this barrier and
quickly find Gohan and the others.
I have no idea how the
inside of Boo is made up.
I'm not sure I can find them.
It'd be nice if they aren't already dead.
Look! He let himself be
absorbed by Boo on purpose,
so he could save his
friends who were absorbed!
S-So that's it!
That's why, even though he
could have beaten him at any time,
he provoked Boo into absorbing him!
Incredible! How incredible he is!
H-Huh? How come the
moment we dropped the barrier,
our merging broke up as well?
How am I supposed to know that?
That's strange! They said
once you merge with the Potara,
you'd never return again
to the original two persons.
Come to think of it, you
did say something about that.
In that case, it's lucky that this happened.
I am not about to merge with you ever again!
H-Hey! What are you doing?!
Don't take off your Potara!
I'm sure that once we leave
Boo's body, we can merge again!
It's probably the awful air in
here that prevents us from merging.
Th-The Potara...!
V-Vegeta! How could you do that?!
Now we ain't capable of
merging again, you know!
On top of that, you're dead!
Unless you're merged, you'll have
to go back to the Other World, right?!
Hmph! I'll take that
over being merged with you!
Besides, there's no need
to merge again, is there?
You don't know that!
Even if we do rescue everyone
who has been absorbed successfully,
there ain't any guarantee
Boo will return to the way he was.
In that case, we'd better hope
that we can find our people fast,
and that everything goes right!
How can you...?
Come on, hurry it up! Boo may
intend to blow the Earth away!
I don't know about this!
Hey, wait up a bit! Hey!
You know, this is one nasty place.
Sure it is. We're inside something living, and
moreover, of all places, it's Majin Boo's belly.
Sheesh! Whereabouts are we?! I can't tell at all!
What?!
Vegeta!
W-W-What's this?!
What's going on?
This is...
Yeesh. Apparently we're inside his stomach.
What's this smoke?
Y-You idiot! That's his stomach acid!
If you're not quick, you'll
be dissolved without a trace!
What's that?
That bastard! He's planning on digesting us!
W-We're surrounded!
Th-This is bad! If this keeps up...
Stop! Vegeta!
Yow!
W-What was that just now?
Have I eaten something bad?
I know! This is because
I absorbed that strange guy!
It must be causing indigestion!
Hey, Vegeta, you sure are reckless!
What do you plan on
doing if Majin Boo finds us out?
After all the trouble it took to sneak in here!
Hmph! What do I care?
I saved us from being dissolved.
I'd rather you were grateful to me for that.
More importantly, you stay sharp, Kakarrot!
If we don't find Gohan and the others soon,
we won't be able to save the Earth that
we otherwise might have been able to.
I know!
Boy, doesn't this guy
eat anything but candy?
Everywhere you look, there are snacks!
Eating nothing but sweet things is
bad for the body, and makes you fat.
Stop saying such rubbish!
After shrugging off the pounding we gave him,
it'd be a big laugh if he were to
die from eating too much candy!
That's for sure!
What's wrong?
Silence!
What's that sound?
Above us?
What?!
What are these disgusting things?
That thing tried to dissolve me!
They've got incredible appetites!
Apparently, these things
break down what Majin Boo eats,
and supply him with nourishment.
S-Say, Vegeta, could it be that
these things are about to eat us?
If that's the case, let's show them
that we're not all that appetizing.
Y-You don't mean...?
Here they come!
Geez, these things are stubborn!
Hey, Vegeta, if you make
that big a commotion, Majin B–
Why, you rotten scum...!
Kakarrot!
What's that?!
What?
What is that monster?!
What the hell are you doing, Kakarrot?!
Tear those lower life forms off of you!
I know! But my body is...!
Suddenly, Goku finds himself in a great pinch
with the giant monster that has appeared!
Will he be able to weather this pinch,
and rescue Gohan and the others?
There is barely any time remaining
before Majin Boo destroys the Earth!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
I've been looking for you, Gohan.
H-Hey, what's come over you,
suddenly attacking me like that?!
And over here are Gotenks and Piccolo!
Each one of them is screwing with us!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Nightmares or Illusions!?
Goku and Gohan's Father-Son Confrontation."
Father, those aren't us! Be careful!
"Next time"
"Nightmares or Illusions!?
Goku and Gohan's Father-Son Confrontation"