The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Goku has returned from the Other World,
and an unprecedented
Tenkaichi Tournament has begun.
"Martial"
First, the kids showed off what they could do
as the Tournament's Junior Division began.
You talk too much.
I don't need you to tell me what to do.
Both Trunks and Goten easily advanced
through their matches, and as predicted,
the two of them now face
each other in the final round.
Wow! So many people here to watch!
I'm telling you now,
I won't be pulling any punches, Goten.
Yeah, me neither!
"Happiness Times A Million!
The Junior Champion is Decided!!"
W-What is the story with them?
Hang in there!
I-Incredible! I knew since they
were together with Son Goku-kun,
they'd be incredible!
This is it! I've been waiting so long for them.
This is how the Tenkaichi
Tournament ought to be!
They're pretty good!
Yeah, better than I expected.
They're both hanging in there.
Goten-chan! Stay tough!
Trunks! Don't drop your guard!
Not bad, Goten!
You've managed to get a
lot better in just that short time.
Big Brother taught me a lot.
Well, can you do this?
D-Don't tell me he's going to
launch a Kikoha blast from there?!
–I-It'll blow into the spectator seats!
–Don't do anything stupid!
Nah, it'll be okay.
He realizes that much.
You've got to give him more credit.
O-Oh no!
W-What was that just now?
It looked like some kind of
amazing rocket came from his hands.
Whew, that was close!
See?
I-I-I've seen that before...
I-It couldn't be...
How's that? Pretty cool, huh?
I can do that too.
I just barely had it taught to me though.
Watch this! Ka-me-ka-me...
You dummy, it's KameHAme-Ha.
Ha!!
"Tenkaichi Tournament"
That was close! Goten ain't got
control over his Kamehame-Ha.
C-Can't be!
Hey, he did the same thing as that other kid.
What the hell was that?
I-It-It looks like him. He looks just like him!
That guy that was there
during the fight with Cell.
I hit the house!
Looks like we better stop
doing Kikoha-like blasts.
You're dangerous with them, Goten.
Let's go on without them.
Okay.
I want to see the final round!
Me too!
Ikose-chan, Idasa-chan...
Mama is upset that you two
got beat up by those vulgar kids!
But dear, those two were special.
They had incredible victories
in their later matches too.
No, we cannot lose.
At the next Tenkaichi Tournament,
you have to beat those two brats!
In order to do that, starting now,
it's training, training, and more training!
Keep going, Idasa, Ikose.
All right, I think it's about
time I bring this to a close, Goten.
I am going to be victorious!
I'm going to win!
Huh? Trunks-kun is gone!
Oh no!
Uh oh, Goten!
How's this, Goten? Now say you give up!
Hey, no matter how you look at it,
they're floating in mid-air, right?
Yeah.
Hurry and say you give up!
If I grab you any tighter, you'll die!
N-No way!
It looks as though Trunks wins this one.
Goten, stick it out! Stand up to him!
I said say it, and I mean it!
He can become a Super Saiyan?!
Oh, Goten, you fool!
That was dirty, Kakarrot!
It's no use telling me...
That one kid, didn't he seem
somehow different just now?
I had the same feeling.
What is this, a dream? A vision?
I-It's them all right. N-No mistaking it.
It's his child, he's a dead ringer.
That's cheating, Goten!
We aren't supposed to
become Super Saiyans, you know!
Sorry, couldn't help it.
I won't do it again, for sure!
Well, okay then.
Goten...
What?
If I really wanted to,
I could win without even using my left arm.
You're kidding! You couldn't win!
Yes I could!
No you couldn't. Just try! You can't
use your left arm, no matter what!
Right, I know! Here goes!
Trunks!
Goten-chan, go! Go on!
How about it? Can you fix it?
It's no use.
I don't even know what
the cause of the malfunction is.
Hey, aren't there any other TV cameras?
Even the spare camera is broken.
The other station's cameras, as well as
the spectator's home videos and cameras,
they all seem to be ruined.
Isn't that strange?
Unbelievable, how can this be?
How is it we can't record such
an incredible fight?! Dammit!
You cheater!
H-He's flying entirely in mid-air,
that's all there is to it.
You've completely mastered
the Bukujutsu technique, huh Goten?
What do you suppose he's up to now?
Gohan-kun, you've been giving
him some kind of special training
behind my back, haven't you?
N-No, it's been about the same as always.
Really?
Well then, how did he get so...?
Charge!
He's building up his speed as he
drops and plans on dashing at me...
...as he watches which way I go.
Okay, I'll just dodge him in the nick of time.
He's just barely started to fly.
He won't be able to follow my moves.
Now!
Crash!
What?!
Goten...
You dummy!
Ringout! Contestant
Trunks wins. He is the victor!
The Junior Division has a victor!
I did it! I did it!
Trunks won!
G-Goten-chan...
Goten and Trunks both fought well.
I'm going to do well, too!
You mean, even Lil' Trunks
can become a Super Saiyan?
Hey, too bad.
Looks as though my son
comes from the better stock.
Y-Yeah.
Not sure what all happened,
but that was an incredible match!
I've never seen anything like it!
What was that, Trunks-kun?!
You cheated, didn't you?!
You turned Super Saiyan,
and you used your left hand!
Cheater! Cheater!
Sorry, sorry, I couldn't help myself.
But what about you?
You turned Super Saiyan
earlier too, so we're even.
And I didn't actually
use my left hand to hit you.
A real man wouldn't complain about it.
What's the matter?
Look, don't get all sore at me,
and I'll give you any
three of my toys that you like.
Really? You have to now! You promised me!
Okay?
"Tenkaichi Tournament"
And now, following such a tense match,
it's time for this delightful attraction!
We will now have Trunks-kun,
the winner of the Junior Division,
fight against the World Champion, Mister Satan!
Satan! Satan! Satan!
So, what do you suppose that guy will do now?
What if he decides to cry "trick" again?
There's no way he can match up against Trunks.
Pay no mind, pay no mind!
Lucky you, Trunks-kun!
The children's match
ends with Trunks as the victor.
And now comes the
showdown against Mister Satan.
W-What am I going to do?!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Mister Satan sure has it rough, huh?
He has to fight a Super Saiyan,
even if he's just a child.
If I run, my reputation will be tarnished.
If I fight him, I'll be killed...
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Now What, Satan!?
The Greatest Pinch in History"
Y-You dummy, Trunks!
You can't hit him that hard!
"Next time"
"Now What, Satan!?
The Greatest Pinch in History"