The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Majin Boo, having become
the embodiment of evil,
had stormed his way into the Heavenly Realm,
and destroyed everything on Earth.
According to Piccolo's strategy,
he had been led to fight Goten and
Trunks in the Room of Spirit and Time,
with the fate of Earth at stake.
The strength of this new
Majin Boo was beyond imagination.
Then, finally, Gotenks brought out the
great technique he was keeping in reserve.
I went to a lot of trouble
training for this great technique!
Super Ghost Kamikaze Attack!!
Hi! It's a ghost!
I've won!
"'I've Done It!!'
Boo Successfully Eliminated With Ghosts!?"
I'm scary! I'm scary!
Here goes! I'm ridiculously scary!
W-What technique is that?!
This is the first time
I've seen anything like that!
"Kaboom," he appears! "Kaboom," it's a ghost!
This time, even you're dead, Majin Boo!
Now, go ahead, ghost!
Show him how dreadful the
Super Ghost Kamikaze Attack is!
Okay!
Ready, set...!
Yea!! You fool!
If you touch a ghost even the slightest
amount, you'll cause a huge explosion!
Yea! Yea! Yahoo! Yahoo! Yahoo!
Hurry up and finish him off!
He'll turn back to normal!
I know, I know, already!
I'm going to finish this with one big hard blow!
Super Ghost Kamikaze Attack!!
I'm going to finish him
with ten ghosts all at once!
All right! Fall in!
Ten-hut! Stand at arm's length!
You stupid jerk! Be more careful!
Touch me and we'll explode, you know!
You shut up! You're just too far forward!
See here, you two! Line up, and no more "shigo"!
[shigo: talking]
–What does "shigo" mean?
–That's the place where us ghosts live!
–No, that's the world shigo, you know?
–It's a calculation, isn't it? Shi times go, 20!
[shigo: after death; shi: four; go: five]
Quiet already, and just line up!
Now, Ten-hut! Count off!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8, 9, 10!!
–All right!
–Hey!
He's long since returned to normal–Majin Boo.
You punk! Make a fool out of me, will you?!
You drink your creme
sodas now, while you still can!
Yo, yo, Majin Boo!
Hmm? You ready now?
Go! Numbers 1 and 2, charge!
Fool! I won't fall for the same trick twice! Nyah!
Hey, gather around!
Did you see that?
That not-too-bright look on his face just now?
–Mm-hmm! We saw, we saw!
–Can he really be a Majin looking like that?
He made this face, and went "Nyah" at us!
Kaioshin-sama, have you noticed it?
How Majin Boo's ki has
disappeared in the last little while?
N-Now that you mention it...!
What does it mean? Is he dead?!
I don't know. I can't feel the
Fusion ki from the little guys either.
They ain't seemed to have fought...
I wonder why their ki has just up and vanished.
Ah, they're fighting in a world
with a different dimension of time.
–What? Time?
–A world with a different
dimension of time. Any ideas about that?
The Room of Spirit and Time!
Why are they fighting in that place?
Were the half-pints broken-in
on while they were training?
No, the Namekian seems to
have let him inside on purpose.
I don't know why, though.
How does he know that?
Awesome, huh? He's pushing
Gohan's power up and all, too.
He's certainly got what you'd
expect of a Kaioshin, ain't he?
Hmph! Phooey! I'm not of any use at all here!
Where are you going?
I'm sending in some
snacks for them, some snacks!
They say you can't fight
on an empty stomach, right?
They won't have any
time to eat them, you know.
What is it with you?!
How can you all be so calm?
Bulma-san, it's okay!
They're Goku and Vegeta's sons!
I'm sure those two are
going to save the world for us!
So then, Numbers 3 and 4 will...
W-What's up with this... battle?
There's no sense of tension!
All right, here goes!
Fight-o!!
Okay! Let's give it to him!
Serves him right–!
Dammit! Those jackasses!
Those two stupid ghosts are gone,
so everyone but Number 10
go on according to the plan! Go!!
Again?!
Oh! What do you suppose this is?
What could it be?
–That's strange!
–What's it doing in a place like this?
It's–you know–one of those!
–It's poop, isn't it?
–Dummy! Don't say that!
This sure is something nice, huh?
–I wonder if it's yummy.
–Good question!
Now!!
We did it!
Yea!!
I-It's an incredible fight, but
something about this is absurd!
All right! Number 10, you finish him off!
Enter in through Boo's mouth and
blow him away so there's nothing left!
Yes sir!
It's over!
I'll turn you into a hot dog! Bam!!
Boo...
Let's go...
You know something,
there's nobody around, is there?
Where has everybody gone?
That was kind of childish, huh?
Me, of all people, giving it
to him like I meant business!
There's no time for you to be
breathing easy! Majin Boo will regenerate!
You have to burn all the
fragments that have been blown apart!
I'll help too!
I know, I know!
Geez, and I still had one
more last great technique, too!
It's kind of a shame I didn't
get to show off my best stuff.
Be quiet, and hurry it up!
Okay, okay...
That's the end of it.
That was a bit disappointing, huh?
You did well! You really have done well!
To be honest, I didn't think
you could do as much as all this.
W-What is it? This wind...!
D-Don't tell me...!
H-Hey! The smoke is gathering together!
Dammit! It's Majin Boo!
Oh? You don't suppose
he's returning to normal?
Th-That's it, all right. Say,
now what are we supposed to do?
What does it mean, that
even burning him up is no use?
My, my, my... He looks completely pissed off...
Damn, now we've done it!
We should have used our
ki to entirely obliterate him,
not just burn him up!
A-And then, just in case,
we should have destroyed
the entrance to this room,
sealing Boo up in this world,
which is in a different dimension.
That would have been perfect!
Can you do it again?
That Super Ghost Attack you just did?
Or for that matter, did you
have another great technique?
I do have one more in reserve!
But why don't I get Piccolo-san all anxious?
That will make it more exciting, and all...
Well, what about it?
I-It's hopeless!
I don't have the kind of power left that
it takes to perform my great technique!
It's all over!
It's the end of the world!
L-Let me go, you slimeball!
Yow! Now I'm pissed off! You bastard!
Ding dong, ding dong! Ladies and
gentlemen, thank you for waiting!
At long last, I present my
ace-in-the-hole technique!
W-What?
P-Piccolo-san, was that...?
This is the end for you, Majin Boo!
I've destroyed the only
doorway between this world
and the one that you and
we had previously been in!
You certainly are strong.
Unfortunately, not even
Gotenks here could defeat you.
However, no matter how strong you are,
it will be impossible for you to
ever leave here for the rest of your life!
P-Piccolo-san, you mean, we...?
So, you can go ahead and kill us,
and then spend eternity living here all alone!
Here, in this world of nothingness...!
Were you too hasty, Piccolo?
Will they never be able to
return to their original world again?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
This ain't good. Using out-of-this-world power,
Boo has come out of the
Room of Spirit and Time alone!
Everyone at the temple is in danger!
We have to generate the power to
somehow open a dimensional hole.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Escape From Another Dimension!!
Super Gotenks 3."
Way to go! If Gotenks can produce
Super Saiyan 3 power, he can't lose!
"Next time"
"Escape From Another Dimension!!
Super Gotenks 3"