Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Go to Shinsenkai. Can spread
Ultra Holy Water to whole world.
You may have obtained the Ultra Holy Water,
but you are out of time!
Piccolo and the others saved Kami,
and managed to obtain the Ultra
Holy Water from Garlic Jr. However...
"A Battle of Extreme Measures!!
Kami-sama Breaks the Covenant."
Those two as well...
Now then, to show off
our true power to the fullest!
Gohan! Kuririn!
Before you worry about others,
you ought to be concerned about yourself!
You were the former Kami-sama!
What?!
Mister Popo can tell.
Feel familiar. No doubt about it.
Please wait! It is I, the one to
whom you yielded the Throne of Kami!
I am aware a being such as I is
unworthy to come to this place.
However,
due to our situation...
Look out, Kami-sama!
Former Kami-sama, something
terrible is happening down on Earth!
We must take this Ultra Holy Water
to the bottom of the Heavenly Realm!
Look out, Kami-sama!
Mister Popo!
Mister Popo not bothered by this.
But Kami-sama, this no good.
He not let us pass no matter what.
Mister Popo, let's go!
Quickly, Mister Popo! There is no time!
Kami-sama!
Too slow!
Hurry, Mister Popo!
Kami-sama, so spunky!
Finished so soon?
Come on. Hey!
What's the matter? Get up!
You unresponsive wimp!
K-Kuririn-san!
You're not getting away!
Kuririn-san!
Impossible!
H-He's a freak!
Kuririn-san!
Our powers are far too unlike, yours and mine.
I guess it was something of a mistake for me...
...to let Kami die by defeating this one.
The Dragon Balls will disappear,
and I will be unable to
wish my father back to life.
But it's no matter.
In time I will think of another way.
Son Goku's son, huh?
Looks like he was too much
for the others to handle after all.
What a shame! You just
missed your mentor, Piccolo,
leaving for the Other World.
Not to worry. You'll meet again soon. In Hell!
You make me laugh.
To think you would be so
proud of that level of power.
Perhaps you think becoming a
giant has given you greater strength.
In order to truly... become a giant,
you have to do this!
What?!
I-Incredible! Piccolo-san!
Your larger scale certainly
bestows its own kind of power-up.
However, in exchange, you
lose some of your edge on speed.
There's no longer any way you can win!
Popo, this is a dead end.
Mister Popo forgot.
Shinsenkai laid out in several sections.
Need former Kami's permission go further.
Kami-sama, all over!
Get hit again, Kami-sama die!
It is nothing.
Let's go, Mister Popo!
Kami-sama, incredible!
What's matter, Kami-sama?
Suddenly, it's hard to breathe...
Kami-sama! Y-Your hand!
I-Is this a precursor to
having my spirit drawn from me?
Kami-sama, must go back. Body
not last until reach hole of currents.
After coming this far,
I can't just turn around now...
Kami-sama!
What?!
P-Piccolo-san!
What's wrong? You're already tired out?
You appear to have
forgotten that I have eternal life.
What happened to all that
energy you had a moment ago?
I cannot allow myself to expire in this place!
Kami-sama! There's another wall!
Kami-sama, wait!
Hang in there, Popo.
K-Kami-sama, your body...
I know...
Piccolo-san!
Piccolo and Kami share
the same mind and body...
In the Shinsenkai, Kami is about
to have his spirit pulled from him...
And so, Piccolo is also...
Kuririn-san!
Between you and Kami, which
of you will be the first to die?
Over there!
Is that it?
This is where it ends, Piccolo!
At last, Kami-sama reaches
the bottom of the Heavenly Realm.
However, his life has all but expired.
And how does Gohan
plan to challenge Garlic Jr.,
who has obtained eternal life?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Hang in there, Kami-sama! You're almost there!
You'll be able to return everyone
to normal with the Ultra Holy Water!
I'm not about to let you ruin my schemes!
I'm not letting any of you out of here alive!
I'll suck up the Heavenly Realm,
and everything in it!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"The Ultra Holy Water Worked!!
The World Awakens from Its Nightmare."
All that's left now is you, Garlic Jr.!
"Next time"
"The Ultra Holy Water Worked!!
The World Awakens from Its Nightmare"