The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Incredibly, Majin Boo has turned
Dabura into a cookie and eaten him!
Challenging the Majin to battle alone,
Vegeta was overwhelming
Majin Boo with his super power.
"A Warrior's Resolution!!
I Will Dispose Of the Majin."
V-Vegeta...
W-What's the matter? What is Majin Boo doing?
A-Awesome! Vegeta is unbelievably strong!
Way to go! Way to go, Papa! You're incredible!
Give him some more! Way to go!
Way to go! Give him more!
Him as well–Vegeta has also
surpassed even Super Saiyan...
Such inordinate power... As when Gohan
fought against Cell–no, even greater!
H-However, that same Gohan
was himself done in by Majin Boo!
So long as we don't know
the whereabouts of Goku,
if this current Vegeta is ineffective,
there's no one in the world
that can stand against Majin Boo!
Vegeta, the fate of the Earth–no, the
entire universe rests on your shoulders!
M-Majin Boo! Impossible!
There's no way my Majin Boo can lose!
Awesome!
He got him! He got him!
He got him! He got him! He got him!
That's my Papa for you!
Uh huh! Did you see that,
Goten, my Papa's strength?
Yeah! Uncle is incredible!
Of course he is! After all, he's my Papa!
What?
Great! Great! Majin Boo, this time it's our turn!
Kill Vegeta!
Papa! Go!
He did it! He did it! He did it!
It's true! That was amazing!
I-It can't be!
Majin Boo... My Majin Boo...!
He did it!
That hurt a bit.
What are you, immortal?
Great! Great, Majin Boo! Get him! Get him!
Why, you...
Why, you...!
Th-This is bad!
Hey, w-what are you...?
Why, you...
I hate you!!
B-Barrier!
G-Get out of there!!
That was close!
You guys, are you all right?!
That was close, that was close!
Ow! Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Huh? What about Goten?
D-Don't scare me like that, Goten!
Here. Thank goodness, huh, Lizard-san!
Kaioshin-sama!!
Papa!!
D-Damn it all!
Hmph! How can this be?!
Y-You're strong, on top of which,
you're immortal... it's ridiculous!
Dirty bastard!
You're a tough one!
To think you're still alive!
If only you hadn't defied me, you
could have been such a good servant!
What a shame!
Papa...
Even Vegeta is utterly no match for him...
Gohan is dead, and even Kaioshin,
the legitimate ruler over all
the world, has been vaporized.
W-What is to become of this?
Papa... Papa can't lose, right?
Not to the likes of that Majin!
You're finished now. Bye-bye.
Bye-bye. Bye-bye. Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
W-What do I do? What the hell
can I do to beat this monster?!
You're one creepy punk!
What are you thinking of doing?
Don't you toy with me!
Hmph! I could handle that
scale of attack with my eyes closed!
What?!
This is bad!
Oh boy, oh boy! Oh boy, oh boy!
He'll be killed! What the hell
happened to Goku and Gohan?!
A-Are they already dead?
Y-You think my Big Brother would die?!
K-Keep it under control, Trunks!
Even if you were to go,
there's nothing you could do!
You'd just die for no reason!
You'd only be hurting Vegeta all the more!
No way!!
Trunks-kun!
Trunks has sprung forward in
order to save a critical Vegeta!
However, the menace posed by Majin Boo
is surely closing in on the warriors.
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Vegeta, you can't fight Majin Boo
head-on if you want to defeat him!
Trunks... take good care of your mama...
Majin Boo! I've figured out
how to defeat you, at long last!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"For Those Whom He Loves...
Vegeta Perishes!!"
For the first time,
Vegeta-san is about to fight
for someone other than himself!
"Next time"
"For Those Whom He Loves...
Vegeta Perishes!!"