Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Nine months remain before
the Saiyans arrive on Earth.
Gohan, Piccolo, Tenshinhan, and
the others who were to go against them
were each preoccupied
with their own training.
Elsewhere, Goku had been
intently running the Serpentine Road
in order to meet Kaio-sama. However...
Where is this place?
I wonder if I've arrived at Kaio-sama's
place without even realizing it.
That smells good!
That fruit looks delicious!
"Hands Off! Yama-sama's Secret Fruit"
"Pond of Blood"
You are one incredible bastard
to try to take the fruit of the Enseiju,
the Tree of Circular Life oni!
You mean I can't eat those?
Of course not oni.
Those are precious fruit that only
the Great King Yama-sama may eat oni.
I'm just so hungry, you see...
You're hungry?
You say the most ridiculous
things oni. Who are you oni?
What have you come here for oni?
I'm Goku. Son Goku. I came here to
train. Which one of you is Kaio-sama?
Kaio-sama?
Then you guys ain't Kaio-sama?
Of course not oni.
Where do you think you are oni?
This is the third street of
the first district of Hell oni.
We are the watch-keeper ogres of this area oni.
This is Hell?! Then I've fallen
down from the Serpentine Road!
Damn it, man, how am I supposed to
climb up this thing, for crying out loud?
Hey, Tenshinhan!
Don't you leave me behind!
Goku, I will travel the
same road that you have!
But I will become even
stronger, just you watch!
Ten-san, how do you
suppose Kami-sama will train us?
I don't know. But this
is Kami-sama, after all.
It will probably be something
we couldn't even imagine.
Chaozu, no matter what the training is,
don't become disheartened!
Mm-hmm!
This sure is one hard-up house...
What are you doing?
Oh, you know. If there was an
airplane capsule or something in here,
I was going to borrow it.
There is nothing like that in there.
You should leave here at once.
You do have money in here.
If I do not have it, it's not in there.
Just do as I tell you
and give me an airplane!
What is the matter, Noble Father?!
Upa!
It's nothing, Upa.
What are you doing to Noble Father?!
Don't come any closer!
Why, you–!
Huh?
We can kill some time
with him for a while oni!
It's been 1,500 years since we had
a flesh-and-blood dead person here oni!
He seems to be pretty lively, too.
It's been so long since we had
someone to make us move about oni.
You can't oni! You've got a
mountain of paperwork stacked up oni!
It doesn't matter oni! We have
equal responsibility for that oni!
–Then it's no use oni!
–You wanna go at it?
–Rock, scissors, paper!
Look that way now!
Work hard, now oni!
Be sure to leave some for me oni!
First come, first served oni!
Maybe this is impossible after all...
What are you doing oni?
You can tell just by watching, can't you?
I want to hurry and get
back to the Serpentine Road.
You want to get back
that badly, do you oni?
What are you doing?!
I'll send you back oni!
"River Sanzu Branch Office"
Oh? That Gozu bastard is finishing
everything so easily again oni! I knew it!
What a simple-minded, foolish ogre oni!
Whoa-oa-oa-oa!
That guy!
Pops, you ain't got any power, huh?
I didn't even make it there!
What?!
I'm the second strongest ogre next to
Great King Yama-sama in all of Hell oni!
I heard that Great King Yama was incredibly
strong, but maybe he's not all that great.
You want to try taking me on then oni?!
I ain't got that kind of spare time.
If you can beat me in a contest,
I'll give you a chance to get
back to the Serpentine Road oni!
It's the jump device we keep just in case oni.
Really?
We don't lie oni.
If we lie, then we get our tongues
pulled out by Great King Yama-sama oni.
I'll do it! I'm going to do it!
In exchange, if you lose,
you forfeit your soul oni.
You won't be able to keep
your body while you're dead oni!
That's fine. I'm going to win, after all.
If you go outside of this line,
you lose oni. You got that?
Whatever is fine,
let's just do this quickly!
You're one bothersome guy, huh oni?
It takes some preparation...
to get ready for this oni...
All right, let's go oni!
You got it!
Take your marks...
...begin oni!
You're better than I thought, Pops.
Wha– oni?
U-Unbelievable power oni!
Here I go, Pops!
This is the jump device, is it?
That's right oni! I'm going to jump
up as hard as I can and land up here,
and when I do, you jump oni.
Fine, just hurry up and do it.
All right, here goes!
It's working, it's working!
A little farther...
Ka... me... ha... me...
...Ha!
That did it!
What's with those clouds?
They're terribly hard!
"To the summit. Please do not litter."
Number 34,265...
Number 34,266...
"Mountain of Needles"
"The Original Needle Bean Jam Buns"
Number 34,267...
Number 34,268...
Number 34,269...
No one is absent, then.
Today, as I'm sure
everyone is looking forward to,
we will be having an outing
on the Mountain of Needles oni.
Stay sharp as you ascend
and come back down oni.
Hurry up and get going oni.
Come on, come on, step on it–
Geez, is he still playing all by
himself oni? That's not fair oni!
How long are you going
to keep goofing around oni?
It's my turn now oni.
It's no use. No matter how many times I try,
I can't break through those clouds.
Your head is just too soft oni.
But then, has there ever been
anyone who has broken through there?
Not yet oni.
What? Have you tricked me?!
Hey, you!
So, in a nutshell, you just want to return
to the Serpentine Road, is that right oni?
If so, there's a very
good way to do so oni.
Really? Tell me!
There's a secret path that
nobody else knows about oni.
Mezu, you can't show him that oni!
Tell me about it! I'm begging you!
There is one condition oni.
Condition?
I'm going to start running
around through Hell here oni.
If you are good enough
to be able to catch me,
I'll tell you where
the secret path is oni.
I'm supposed to chase you?
That's right oni! In this game, you
really will have to run like the devil oni!
Over here, over here!
I think this should be enough for today.
Hurry, hurry!
Over here, over here!
Are you ready oni?
Any time is fine by me.
I'll just warn you that they say my speed
is second only to Great King Yama-sama oni.
If you lose...
I know! Come on, let's hurry and do this.
All right then, let's begin oni. Ready!
He is fast!
Wait up!
Wait up, wait up!
Now he'll just run around
until he's all worn out oni.
What a waste. And
flesh-and-blood dead people are so rare...
You're pretty fast, aren't you oni?
Yeah, I suppose so.
If you weren't, then this
wouldn't be any fun oni!
I was so close! And he
even dropped his guard, too!
That's awesome! All right, then!
No matter how tough he may be,
he can't come all the way up here oni.
W-What oni?!
Hold it!
This is fun oni! How
about you live here with us oni?
If you do that, we can play tag every day oni!
You're right! But I can't... let that happen!
What's the matter oni? You'll never
get to where Kaio-sama is like this oni!
Damn, I was so close, too.
He's something else oni.
Hold on a minute, would you? I'm all tired out!
You're just a wuss oni...
Say, let me eat some
of the fruit on that tree.
No way oni! If you eat
one of those precious fruits,
they say that you will avoid
hunger for a hundred days,
and your power will be bolstered oni.
They're that valuable, are they?
That's right.
Hey, you! Hold it!
If one of those gets eaten,
I'll get chewed out by
Great King Yama-sama oni!
Come on! Come on, come on!
Hold it oni! Come on! Come on!
Before you know it, the game
of chase got switched around oni.
Here goes! Gotcha! I did it!
You idiot oni!
Okay, you promised.
Show me the way out.
I was off my guard oni.
L-Let's do it again oni?
Are you thinking of breaking your promise?
Great King Yama will yank your tongue out!
It's over there oni!
If you climb the stairs inside here,
you'll return to the Serpentine Road oni.
See you later, then!
Get out of here now oni!
Sorry about this, but I took one of them.
Because of you, I'm famished!
See you!
You dumb bastard oni!
Don't come here again oni!
He's gone oni.
There's absolutely nothing
to be done about him oni.
Eh, oh well oni.
That was fun oni...
Okay then, to work, to work!
There's a mountain of paperwork piled up oni.
Let's go at it as best we can oni.
These stairs sure are long!
Is that the exit?
Huh? It won't move. All right, then!
I made it!
What are you doing in there?
G-Great King Yama-sama?!
Did you see Kaio-sama?
Um, by any chance, is this–? Goodbye!
W-What's with him?
What's this?! I have to
start at the beginning again?!
You've got to be kidding!
I really have to hurry now,
or I ain't going to have enough time!
That's strange. It's a lot
easier to run now than before.
I wonder if that's because of that fruit.
Goku has unexpectedly
returned to the starting point.
The road to Kaio-sama's
place is incredibly long.
Hurry, Goku! The Saiyans
are getting closer every minute!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Huh? A house, here? I get it, this must be
Kaio-sama's house, right?
The Snake Princess-sama approaches!
K-Kaio-sama, you're a woman?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Such Sweet Temptation!
The Snake Princess-sama's Hospitality."
Father, that lady scares me.
"Next time"
"Such Sweet Temptation!
The Snake Princess-sama's Hospitality"