Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
The Super Saiyan Son Goku and the
Artificial Human No. 1 9 finally come to blows.
However, there is something
physically wrong with Goku.
What could be happening?
I knew it! Father is sick! It's his heart!
What? His heart?!
You mean like that guy
from the future was saying,
a viral infection of his heart?!
"The Might of Vegeta!
The Blood of a Super Saiyan Awakens."
Just a minute. What happens
to me? Am I killed too?
In a short time, you will become very sick.
Soon after, you will pass away.
It will be a viral infection of your heart.
Not even a mighty Super Saiyan
can win against this illness.
Oh no, senzu won't have
any effect on the illness either.
Aw, crud!
When your symptoms first appear, take this.
What have you got?
It's medicine for you.
There is no treatment in this era, but
twenty years from now, we have a cure.
That medicine will allow
you to make it through alive.
Gohan, stop kidding around.
That special medicine of his must
have cured his heart virus a long time ago.
Goku's just had his ki sucked
out of him by those guys.
Such pain! What's going on?
What's wrong with me?
Goku! Here's a senzu! Take it!
Thank you.
This will see me through.
So that's a senzu, capable of healing
great injuries and restoring energy, is it?
Judging by the fact
that he was all but dead,
but is back here among us
now, they must be for real.
The senzu had no effect!
It has to be his heart!
How could it be?
Didn't he take the medicine to cure himself?
He never got sick.
He's been healthy the whole time,
so he never took the medicine!
Father!
Now he's no longer Super Saiyan!
How can this be?
This is bad! Goku's having
his energy drained from him!
You cannot proceed one
centimeter further than this.
Do you want to try it?
I will.
Piccolo-san!
So fast! He's unbelievably quick!
I can't call Piccolo's actions just now brave.
He was only being a reckless fool.
At this rate, Son will soon be...
It is my task to defeat Kakarrot.
You flea market mannequins
have no place in this.
Vegeta!
Vegeta-san!
Did you say Vegeta?
Piccolo-san!
Here I am doing a lousy job acting hurt...
...just so I can save Goku
when they aren't looking...
Then Vegeta, you had to butt
in where you weren't wanted!
Piccolo-san, you mean...
No matter how strong
those guys may say they are,
I won't be defeated by
an attack such as that one.
I saw everything.
Even realizing there was
something wrong with yourself,
you went ahead and turned Super Saiyan.
You Idiot!
Doing something like that only assures
the disease will progress that much faster!
My life's goal, no matter how
long it takes, is in you, Kakarrot.
Father!
Stay with us, Father!
Goku!
Are you all right, Son?
Hey, Goku, hang on now!
Someone get Kakarrot out of here,
take him home and give him
that medicine he received back then!
Father! I'm going to take you home now!
No, I'll go.
It's pathetic of me to say so,
but I'm the least use to anyone around here.
This heart disease was said to be viral in nature.
It may be contagious, so you should
take a little of that medicine yourself.
Yeah.
Please be careful, Yamucha-san.
So, get going!
Well, everyone, hang in there!
I'll be back, I promise.
Goku! Get better soon!
No. 19, let him go!
There's something to be
said for saving the best for last.
Let us take care of these
other annoying insects first.
Now that Vegeta has joined in,
it should prove somewhat entertaining.
Lookie lookie lookie, they call me Yajirobe!
You're much more a family
man than I would have guessed.
Sure. You'd make a good papa for someone.
Up high, up high, up high, up high!
Looks like he's wet himself again.
Okay now, okay now...
Uh oh, I didn't bring
anything else to wrap you up in.
Now what do we do?
Now we're stuck. If only there
was something else we could use...
Good, everything's okay now.
You really saved us!
We can always count on you, Yajirobe-kun!
Leave me outta this.
Now then, let's go!
Where to?
Isn't it obvious? After coming this far,
I'm not going home without a good
look at those fearsome Artificial Humans.
Well, I ain't goin'.
Hey, you, how can you just sit
there and silently watch a helpless lady
and her little baby head
off into an area of danger?
You don't suppose he's
chicken, do you Trunks-chan?
Well, hurry and get in!
We're just goin' to watch, now.
Soon's we see 'em, we head home, 'kay?
I got it already. Hurry up and get in!
Blast-off!
Hey, Gohan, don't you think it
might be better if we pulled out?
What?
No, seriously. Didn't that boy from
the future tell us this would happen?
Goku would be stricken with a disease,
and all the rest of us, even Vegeta,
would be killed by these Artificial Humans.
Some of the circumstances may have changed,
but isn't everything still just as he warned us?
But if we run now...
these guys will destroy the whole Earth,
just like they did that city earlier, I'm sure of it!
I'm saying, just until Goku
recovers from his illness...
There's no reason to still think that
we will all be wiped out, like he said.
Look at how the time of Goku's
predicted sickness was way off, for example.
It's likely that his coming here has
generated subtle changes in history.
History has changed?
That doesn't make these
guys any less fearsome, does it?
No. 20...
If you please, allow me to finish off Vegeta.
Selfish pest!
After you've already taken
so much energy from Goku,
raising your own absolute power?
Oh, very well.
In exchange, I will take
all four remaining others.
Yes.
I've watched all of your little moves up
until now, and I've got you figured out.
You guys aren't the terrible
punks you've been made out to be.
Apparently you draw energy
out through your palms;
that's all I need to watch out for.
You may have been
observing us all this time,
but there's one important
thing you haven't heard yet.
Vegeta, I know everything there is
to know about your own fighting style.
So you say,
but when Goku turned Super Saiyan,
you had a look of surprise on your faces.
In other words,
your data from the time before our fight
with Freeza up until now is mere conjecture.
You can't rely on calculations for understanding.
Not when it comes to the power of us Saiyans.
There's something I want to know.
Do even you Artificial
Humans tremble with fear?
What?!
Him too?
V-Vegeta-san also turned into a Super Saiyan!
How can that be? How
could he be a Super Saiyan?
I thought if you didn't
have a calm, still heart,
you couldn't become a Super Saiyan.
My heart was calm and still. Still and pure.
However, it was purely evil.
The only thing I desired was to grow stronger.
I put myself through much fierce training!
Damn...
The time came when
I realized I was at my limit.
I'll never surpass Kakarrot like this!
And then, from the anger I felt toward myself,
the Super Saiyan within me suddenly awoke!
I was left shaking from the joy it gave me.
Finally I had overcome Kakarrot,
and the time for me to return
as Prince of the Saiyans had come!
That's enough of your rambling.
You may have changed yourself,
but you are still no match
for us Artificial Humans.
Just like Son Goku before you.
At length, Vegeta has become a Super Saiyan.
Has Vegeta really surpassed Goku?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Your power is awesome, Vegeta.
The Artificial Humans don't
stand a chance against you now.
Who would have thought
Vegeta could be so strong?
He has no vulnerabilities.
It looks like I have no choice
but to return to the laboratory.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"No. 20's Defiant Smile...
The Secret of Doctor Gero."
Run now, while you can, No. 20!
"Next time"
"No. 20's Defiant Smile...
The Secret of Doctor Gero"