Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Kaio-ken!
T-Thanks, Vegeta...
Not at all.
Die!
The curtain is rising over a final
battle, with the fate of the Earth at stake.
"A Hot, Unbounded Battle!
Goku vs. Vegeta."
We're going to change
the location of our battle.
Suit yourself. It will all end up the same.
I should have guessed.
He's following with confidence to spare.
Gohan...
Hey, Gohan!
–Yes?
–Let's hurry back to Kame House.
Let's stop worrying about him already.
We've left the fate of the Earth up to him.
It's okay, Gohan! I'm sure
Goku will come through for us!
Come on, let's go. Show
your mom that you're all right.
Right.
All right, there won't be any
people or animals around here.
I see...
You've chosen here to
be your gravesite, have you?
You should be thrilled.
A lower-class warrior such as yourself
is about to be toyed around
with by a super-elite, after all.
Saiyans have their warrior ratings
examined right after they are born.
When they do, the scum that
have lower ratings, such as yourself,
are sent off to planets that do not
have terribly formidable opponents.
In other words...
You were a left-behind!
And as a result, I was sent to Earth here?
I should be thankful. But what's more...
Even a left-behind might be able to overcome
an elite, if he tries desperately enough.
An amusing joke.
Now then, allow me to show you
a barrier that you cannot overcome,
no matter how hard you try!
What's the matter, Kakarrot?!
You can do better than this, can't you?!
When you defeated Nappa, you had
to have been doing better than this!
Let me see it!
I should have expected as much...
He still ain't the least bit serious,
but his speed and techniques
already surpass my own.
Show me what you've got! Or have
you already used up all of your power?
You got it. I'll show you!
Kaio-ken!
If that's the limit of what you've got,
then I'll be greatly disappointed!
What a powerful bastard!
And yet,
even though I'm in this kind of
trouble, I'm starting to get excited.
I don't see a thing.
What's the matter?
This is because you got violent with it!
What, are you blaming someone else?!
Well it's the truth!
No, no, that's not why, Sis.
It's not because the crystal ball is broken,
it's because the terribly
fierce power of their ki
is concealing them from even
the spiritual powers of your crystal ball.
Then, at least they're still fighting, right?
Probably.
I know! If I use that thing, I can tell!
How about it?
There are two large readings to the west.
Just two?
He's smiling. Has he given up,
and adopted a defiant attitude?
Or is he poised because he can
raise his battle power up even higher?
What's the matter?! Finished already?!
You seem to be at your limit.
In that case, let me show you
something, as your dying gift.
The overwhelming power of a super-elite Saiyan!
Let's see it!
That smirk of yours is
going to disappear very soon.
What a ki! It's as if the
whole Earth is shaking!
As before, images from the site of
battle have been completely broken off.
A-As of now, there is no way for us
to be able to conceive what is happening,
or indeed if it has all ended.
Now then, changing the schedule a little,
we now join this discussion of "What will
become of the Earth, and what is left for us?"
They ultimately don't know anything, do they?
Hey, if you're going to sleep, go sleep at home.
Shut up. Give me another.
Eh? That's your tenth one!
Do you have any money?
Tenshinhan is dead and all...
I don't have any need for this money anymore.
Hey, are you all right?
B-By the way, do you have
a place to stay? If you like–
I can hear it.
W-What?
Can't you hear that sound?!
W-What are you going on about?
H-Hey, look!
W-What is that?!
T-The crows are fleeing from something!
It's like there's a typhoon!
The trembling of the atmosphere has stopped.
A-All the clouds have been blown away, too.
It's over, Kakarrot!
You fool! Behind you!
Kaio-ken times two!
All right, nice going. Way to avoid it.
Damn... What power and speed! I can't
even keep up with him with a 2x Kaio-ken.
I guess I ain't got much choice.
Even if I wreck my body, it's better than dying.
I'll have to raise the Kaio-ken to 3x.
I intentionally made that
one easy to dodge for you.
It wouldn't be any fun to have
you die on me so easily, after all.
They came close by, so I can't help but
come take a look at 'em, but what's this?
Both Goku and that bastard're so strong,
it's like I'm havin' a bad dream here!
Now then, I wonder how long my body
will hold out once I raise the Kaio-ken to 3x...
What's the matter, Kakarrot?! Come get me!
Either way, I have to do it.
Ain't no way I can win like this.
Have you lost everything up your sleeve?
Looks like you picked the wrong opponent.
I was the number-one most
powerful man, even among the Saiyans.
No matter how much training
you've done, you're still just a left-behind.
Looks like your time of death
has been extended by only a little bit.
T-This is bad. That Saiyan
bastard's overwhelmin'ly got it over him.
I'd best be gettin' outta here now,
while I can, huh? Yeah, I'd better get goin'.
It won't do no good
for me to be here anyhow.
May my body withstand this!
Times three Kaio-ken!
No! You can't go any
higher than 2x, Son Goku!
Although, there's definitely
no way he can win like this.
I never imagined he'd
have that much strength.
He may not be able to win this fight.
W-What's going on?
H-Has something happened?
I think it's probably Son-kun, but this
battle power reading is rising incredibly...
–Goku!
–Goku-sa!
17,000... 19,000... 21,000...
It can't be!
W-What?
Ignoring Kaio's warnings,
Goku uses a times three Kaio-ken.
Will Goku's body be able to
withstand a battle power beyond its limits?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
My body is at its limits! I need a
times three Kaio-ken Kamehame-Ha!
At this point, as much
as I dislike how ugly it is,
I'll transform into a Great Ape, and crush you!
The strength of my Great
Ape form is nothing to sneeze at!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Now, Goku! A Final Technique
With Everything On the Line."
My father is the strongest guy in the universe!
"Next time"
"Now, Goku! A Final Technique
With Everything On the Line"