The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
Within the alternate dimension
of the Room of Spirit and Time,
the battle between
Majin Boo, the ultimate devil,
and Gotenks, the mightiest of
warriors, born of Fusion, has begun.
Go! Numbers 1 and 2, charge!
However, the situation
had turned for the very worst.
I-It's hopeless!
I don't have the kind of power left that
it takes to perform my great technique!
It's all over!
It's the end of the world!
An anxious Piccolo
destroyed the only entranceway,
locking Majin Boo into an
alternate dimension of space!
Will Piccolo's desperate strategy be successful?
"Escape From Another Dimension!!
Super Gotenks 3."
Majin Boo, if you're going to kill us, then kill us.
However, you will never be
able to leave this space again!
Um, Piccolo-san, does that
mean we can never leave too?
Yeah, unfortunately.
The entranceway has been closed off.
Nobody will be able to go outside
of this world of unlike dimension.
M-My precious candy!
There's none of that here!
No reason it should be, is there?
Not even cookies, ice cream, and chocolate?!
Gone! There's nothing at all!
Damn it to hell!!
W-What was that just now?
What the hell happened?
I-It's awful! Doorway to
Room of Spirit and Time closed off!
So, Piccolo has employed
the final measure, then?
The final measure? You mean
what you mentioned before?
Hmm. Not even Trunks and Goten
appear to have been a match for Majin Boo.
And so, Piccolo has destroyed the entranceway
to the Room of Spirit and Time,
shutting them all inside.
Now that Majin Boo is closed up
in a different dimension of space,
he will forever be unable to leave.
Th-Then, does that mean
that Trunks and Goten-chan
were done in by Majin Boo?
Hmm... P-Probably so.
You've got to be joking!
This is why I was against this!
B-Bulma-san! We do have the Dragon Balls,
so even if they have died
once, we can return them to–
That's not the issue, is it?! You're all cowards!
How can you have children fight against
that bad guy, no matter how strong they are?!
How can you leave the fate
of the whole Earth up to them?!
You're all just cowards!
My candy...!
My candy is... gone!
Hey! Piccolo-san! Why did you
do that without saying anything?!
I still had a great technique held in reserve!
Y-You what?!
You said something to the effect
that you were at your limit, didn't you?!
That was just a light joke!
One of those little white lies!
I absolutely, absolutely had a
technique that was sure to stop Majin Boo!
And now... now...!
What are you, brainless?!
There are no little lies at a time like this!!
It's not even the slightest bit little!
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
You're the stupid one! Stupid! Stupid!
I want to go back to our prior world!
Make the entranceway go back the way it was!
It's been blown apart! How am
I supposed to make it go back again?
Stupid! Stupid! Stupid!
I want candy! Candy...!
I can't stand this!!
Huh?
What's that?
Piccolo-san, what's that?
I-It couldn't be! I-I don't believe it!
That's it! With the fantastic power of his ki,
Majin Boo has opened up a hole
in the wall between dimensions...!
This is bad! He can escape!
The hole is disappearing!
I can't stand to be in this place!
He's escaping!
D-Dammit, no!
Yow!
It's vanished!
What's that?
It's Majin Boo's ki!
Looks as if he's finally come
out of the Room of Spirit and Time.
What about Goten-san and Trunks-san's ki?
It's no use! I can't feel the half-pints' ki.
Damn it all! What the
hell is happening on Earth?
I wanna see... I sure would like to see!
Want a look, Goku?
Here!
Awesome! I can see! I can see it!
The temple is being shown! Whew!
We can see it, even this far away?!
What is that?!
This isn't good! That ki...!
What?
I-It's Majin Boo!
You! How dare you do that
to Trunks and Goten-chan!
Lucky! There are many here! I'm getting
a little hungry, so this is just right.
What should I make them?
I choose choco!
What kind of choco should I eat them as?
Choco bars would be good, I guess...
Maybe powdered choco? Maybe
choco ice cream would be good...
I'm scared! I'm scared of that man!
He's gotten away, hasn't he?!
Are we going to live the rest
of our lives out in here?!
Stop blubbering! Your blubbering
isn't going to allow us to leave here!
So then what do we do?!
Boo's gotten out of here!
The Earth might already
have been blown away by now!
Gotenks, how sure of your voice are you?
My voice?
The two of us are going
to yell as loud as we can.
It might break down the
wall between dimensions.
If Boo did it, there's no
reason we can't do it too.
All right! Let's go!
All right, one more time...
I wonder which will be the yummiest.
I'm scared!
Damn. So it's Majin Boo–an opponent
not even Goku or Vegeta could beat?
Then I sure won't be beating him.
But if I don't do something,
who else is going to protect her?
No. 18, I'm going to rush him.
When I do, you take her and
hide yourselves inside the temple.
You got that?
Goodbye. If things go well,
I'll see you again when I'm brought
back to life with the Dragon Balls!
Kuririn!
Kuririn...!
Now!!
Run!!
Tha'th one...
You're next!
No. 18!
That's two... that's three...
Who should I choose next?
Too much trouble! Everyone at once!
H-How awful...!
Damn it all...
That bastard! But, from here,
there ain't anything we can do!
U-Um, what's happened there, Father?
It's nothing. Gohan, don't
concern yourself with anything extra!
Just concentrate, and become able
to fight as soon as possible! Got it?
O-Okay!
What about Goten-san and the others?
I still can't feel their ki.
Have they been done in?
Th-That can't be it!
If Goten and Trunks have been beaten,
then that leaves no one to protect the Earth!
Still, something has to turn up! As long
as the Dragon Balls are left on Earth...!
I-It's no use! We haven't
even opened up a pinpoint hole!
While we're in here doing this, time
keeps passing on rapidly out there!
This is bad! Everyone will be...!
Sheesh, got no choice, huh?
Guess I have to use that.
I was hoping to turn during a
cooler scene than this, though.
W-What are you talking about?
What do you think?
Ow-ow-ow-ow!
Stop being so pretentious, you idiot!
Understood! Okay then, here goes!
Ta-da!!
Hey, what are you...?
Yea!
H-How did y-you do that?!
I don't know how I do it! You're shocked, huh?
Still, I'm extremely strong! Even so,
you get the feeling from my face that
I'm supposed to be playing a bad guy.
Well, I guess that makes me
the same as you, Piccolo-san!
I-It's Super Saiyan 3!
You guys couldn't possibly...!
Now then, this is no time to be talking, is it?
I can only be like this
for an incredibly short time!
I did it! I opened a hole!
Piccolo-san, why are you
standing there looking dazed?
Hurry up, or the hole will close!
Yo, yo, yo, Majin Boo!
We've come out of there too!
Oh? You were lucky to get out.
Huh?
Did you change a little bit?
Fool! I haven't just changed a little bit!
I've gotten incredibly,
incredibly, incredibly stronger!
Oh, they've come out!
Those pipsqueaks are alive!
Such an incredible ki!
Is that from their Fusion?
Yeah! That's Fusion for sure!
And what's more, he's Super Saiyan 3!
Super Saiyan 3?
Haven't I told you about that, Kaioshin-sama?
It would take too long to
tell you about it, but in short,
it's where you go above when
you've gone above Super Saiyan.
Going above going above Super Saiyan?
Unbelievable! Those little turds!
It took me many years until I was
finally able to reach Super Saiyan 3,
and they had no trouble with it!
Awesome! That's so awesome!
Th-The temple...
W-Why, you! What have you
done with the group that was here?!
They're right here.
Y-You ate them?!
Yeah! Once I turned them
into choco! They were yummy!
Mother too?!
Everybody!
N-Now I'm completely mad!!
Gotenks and Piccolo at last have escaped.
However, neither Bulma
nor Kuririn are at the temple!
An angered Super Saiyan 3
Gotenks now takes off!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Super Saiyan 3 power
sure is awesome, all right.
Majin Boo is being run ragged.
Nice going, Gotenks! Attaway!
Don't let your guard down,
Trunks-san, Goten-san!
Majin Boo isn't beaten yet!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Going Too Far!? Boo-Boo Volleyball."
Guys, can't you perform your moves
without doing those poses each time?
"Next time"
"Going Too Far!? Boo-Boo Volleyball"