The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
The terrible Majin Boo, having
exterminated all earthlings in a single instant...
–Them?
–That's right.
...has been led to set foot
inside the Room of Spirit and Time,
as a last-ditch strategy by Piccolo.
–You're finished now...
–Majin Boo!
It was a waste to wait for this!
"Fu-sion Ha!!"
The mightiest versus the mightiest–a fierce
battle between Gotenks and Majin Boo,
with everything on the line, has begun!
Th-This is strange. That should have
had some kind of effect on him. Aha!
He must be trying hard not to show his pain!
"'I'm Going Like I Mean It!!'
A Wide-Open Super Gotenks."
Miserable fool! This is all because
you didn't start out as Super Saiyan!
This really was a waste. You're not strong!
I wasn't even being serious,
so of course I didn't!
I'll show you what will
happen when I mean business!
Dynamite Kick!!
Don't you toy with me!
Dynamite Kick Boomerang!!
What was that just now?!
Yow-ow-ow-ow!
You're sure putting up with a lot...
Rolling Thunder Punch!!
Now, look...
Right here, right here.
Dammit! You're mocking me!
Why, you...!
Ouch!
Inoshishi Attack!!
[Inoshishi: Wild Boar]
Power Tackle!!
Miracle Super Punch!!
Great Kick Special!!
Dangerous Machinegun Punch!!
Spiral Shooting Sobat!!
Huh? Next comes...
Magnum Sundae!! Ultra Missile
Parfait!! Hyper Plasma Shortcake!!
Burning Annindo... Burning Annin-daa!!
[Annindo: Almond Tofu]
Yowch!!
You're pretty tough, aren't you?!
W-Well, that's all j-j...
...just what I was planning on!
Ow!
Time out a second.
Pardon me, Piccolo-san, but
is it possible you think I'm losing?
I don't want to think so, but given the difference
in your strengths, it cannot be avoided.
Hold on, now!
W-What?!
Now look, like I was just telling Boo,
everything up to now was taken into account!
Taken into account, you say?
So you see...!
I've got a bunch of things
that I thought up, you know?
Oh, is that right? What kind
of scheme do you have going?
See, at first, I was going
to get ridiculously beat up,
and at the last moment,
turn the tables on him, right?
That's the most exhilarating
pattern of winning there is, isn't it?
As long as I'm at this, I'd like for
them to say it was an incredible battle!
Stop thinking about that trivial stuff
and go get him at full
power right from the start!
Geez! You don't understand the
aesthetics of fighting at all, huh?
There's no need for you to have kept
me in the dark about your little ruse!
Time out is over!!
All right! I'm starting the second round now!
He's not taking that guy seriously enough!
Right about now, inside
the Room of Spirit and Time...
I'm sure a life-and-death battle is unfolding.
Hang on there, you guys!
How can you say that so casually?
What if they lose to Boo, and
Piccolo destroys the doorway?
Neither Trunks nor Goten-kun will
ever come out of that room again!
Th-That's why, once we bring them
back to life with the Dragon Balls...
So, are you saying to them that
once they lose, they have to die?
Is it okay for Kami-sama to say such a thing?!
When a person dies, it's
incredibly painful for us, you know!
Senju Kannon Punch!!
[Senju Kannon:
Thousand-armed Goddess of Mercy]
Daikaiten Kick!!
[Daikaiten: Great Spinning]
I-Is that part of his plan as well?
Is that what they call aesthetic?
That's enough! You're weak!
This is no fun. I'll kill you!
What did you say? Talk big to me, will you?!
You don't get how fearsome I am at all, do you?
You'll be sorry! Now
you've made me seriously angry!
Su-per Saiyan!!
Oh! You can turn Super Saiyan
even while you're in Fusion?!
Piccolo-san is surprised!
In that case, how about I provide
him with a little more service?
H-He just might win!
I'm putting all of this to an
end–the playing around, that is!
Here I go!
Which technique should
I start concluding this with?
There's that one, and this one...
I thought so many of them up...
What are you doing?! Hurry up and decide!
Okay, I've decided! But he might
die with just one blow... Oh, well...
Take this! Galactica Donuts!!
Stop!!
Oh! This is pretty good!
This settles it, huh?
Just kidding.
W-What kind of guy is this?!
W-Well, I thought it would come to this...!
Just you going isn't fair!
It's my turn now for sure!
You dummy!
W-What?!
Gotenks!
He got me...
It wasn't me!
Out of the way, now!
You're giving me no latitude, huh Piccolo-san?
Why, you...!!
Get carried away, will you?
All right, in that case...!
Ow-ow-ow-ow!
Ha! Ha ha-a! Serves you right!
I was thinking of showing
you even more than this,
but it's getting tiresome, so I'll
finish you off with the best I've got!
Take this, and be gone from this world!
I went to a lot of trouble
training for this great technique!
Super Ghost Kamikaze Attack!!
It just might be that this will beat him!
W-What's that?
Hi! It's a ghost!
An unusually cheerful ghost of Gotenks...
Can this really be a last
great technique to defeat Boo?
I've won!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Ten kamikaze ghosts are
attacking Majin Boo, one after another.
All right! Majin Boo has been blown to bits!
It's an amazing fight,
and yet somehow, it's still silly.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"'I've Done It!!'
Boo Successfully Eliminated With Ghosts!?"
Huh? Did he really
defeat Majin Boo with those?
"Next time"
"'I've Done It!!'
Boo Successfully Eliminated With Ghosts!?"