The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
In order to revive Majin Boo,
who was sealed up by Kaioshin,
Madoshi Babidi has come
to Earth to gather energy.
Goku and the others, who
have entered Babidi's spaceship,
have broken through his
prepared Stages one after another!
I will go to Stage 3 for you!
Dabura has volunteered for the third Stage,
and confines himself to a
meditation chamber to heighten his ki.
Good, Dabura! Raise that ki even higher! More!
Elsewhere, at the Tenkaichi Tournament,
a Battle Royale among the
five people left had commenced.
Who will it be that survives to the end?
Goten and Trunks' Mighty Mask?
No. 18?
For that matter, Mister Satan?
"Such Strong Kids!! No. 18's Close Fight!?"
Still not yet? This is too long...
You don't think that since Vegeta-san
and Father were so overly incredible,
they've lost their nerve?
Well, let's just wait them
out. There ain't any rush.
Terrific!
Dabura's ki is rising steadily! Go even higher!
Good, terribly good, Dabura!
Majin Boo's revival has now come into view!
This is the Battle Royale, to determine
the victor of the Tenkaichi Tournament.
And what's this?
Up in the sky, a terrific battle
between Contestant No. 18
and Contestant Mighty Mask is unfolding!
Damn!
Punch! Throw a punch, Trunks-kun!
I know! But I can't get the leverage!
Nice going, nice going!
Of the five contestants who have entered,
Contestant Jewel and Contestant Killa
have been eliminated by ringout!
All that remain are Contestants
No. 18 and Mighty Mask,
as well as the top contender Mister Satan!
Awesome! I've never seen anything so awesome!
Go, go, No. 18-san!
Keep it up, Mommy!
Blow that masked jerk away!
We're not getting many cheers, huh?
I guess this Mighty Mask
guy must not be too popular.
That guy's pretty good.
Y-You can't get so serious about this...!
He's a strange freak.
Considering the size of his body,
his arms and legs are pretty small.
And yet he's unusually strong!
No. 18-san is strong, all right!
She's way different than Killa was.
Hang in there, Trunks-kun!
Goten! You haven't been
doing anything for a while now!
Kick or something!
But I can't see so well!
This is no time to be
saying that! If this works out,
I'm willing to give you one more toy!
Really?! Yea!
Okay, I'll try it!
Here goes, Goten!
Yeah!
Strange... I can't read his movements...
Trunks-kun! That was some good punching!
Yep! Goten, you keep it up too! Let's go!
She's losing!
She'll be okay!
Hey! What's wrong, No. 18?!
C-Cut it out already, okay? I'm begging!
All right! We're winning!
Yeah!
Whoa, he's dead!
To think that I have to fight
against one of those two!
Why does this have to happen?
I have not fallen out!
Ooh, oww...
You okay, Trunks-kun?
That one was fierce!
Okay, let's switch! I'll be on top now!
Y-Yeah, that might be good.
C-Contestant Mighty Mask, do you give up?
No way!
–Oh, he's gotten back up!
–He's up, he's up!
Nice going, nice going!
Contestant Mighty Mask
is doin' pretty good, huh?
Hmm...?
His movements have changed!
Now! Go, Goten!
Yeah!
We did it!
Okay! Keep it up now!
All right! Now to finish her!
Th-That was close!
It really is hard to move around like this!
This guy really does move strangely.
Mommy! Hang in there!
Be sure you win!
All right! I'm not losing this!
Just what you expect of the King
of the Demon Realm of Darkness!
Now we can beat those three, and
gather lots of energy to revive Majin Boo!
It's a good thing I brought Dabura along.
The higher he raises his evil ki,
the easier it is to control his heart!
Stay on him!
I'm winning this, that's for sure!
Something about the look in
No. 18-san's eye has changed!
Never mind that, keep closing in on her!
I'm not giving you a toy for just that!
Oh, no you don't! You
promised me! Cheater, cheater!
Ah! You idiot!
W-What an incredible battle! It's a fight worthy
of the final match of the Tenkaichi Tournament!
To be perfectly honest, I did not think that
Contestant Mighty Mask would come this far!
You have to keep your eyes forward, you know!
I'm going on top again!
Yeah.
M-Might you be giving up this time?
Contestant Mighty Mask has risen once again!
Such tenacity, which we did not see
from him at the previous tournament!
We can no longer think of this as a Battle
Royale! This is now completely a fight between
Contestant No. 18 and Contestant Mighty Mask!
I've had it!
I-Incredible!
Look out, Goten!
We can't win like this!
Trunks-kun! Let's turn Super Saiyan!
Th-That's it! As long as we're wearing
this, no one can tell! All right! Shall we?
Yeah!
Goten, ready?!
Okay!
What's this? What's happened?
What's that? He's glowing!
Any way we look at it, this
outfit is working against us.
We have to finish this with a Kiai-Ho blast.
B-But, will she be all right?
Relax! If we control it right, she
won't die. It's No. 18-san, after all!
So that's it. Super Saiyan, huh? I've finally
realized who you are, my little gentlemen.
Trunks-kun, you can't hit her full blast!
I know!
I knew it!
I missed!
Let's go with a bigger blast!
Y-You've got to be kidding! That energy blast
had staggering speed and destructive power!
Those kids, they must have unheard-of power!
This is bad! I have to finish this fight now!
You're going to allow me
to win now! Trunks! Goten!
W-We're found out!
She's serious about this!
C-Contestant Mighty Mask
has been snapped apart!
Y-You idiot, Goten! Why did you run that way?
What about you, Trunks-kun?!
Huh?! Goten! Here I am
wonderin' where you'd gone!
Then the other one is Trunks?!
So it was those two after all!
W-What do we do now, Trunks-kun?
No choice! At this point,
we'll just have to take her on!
Let's go!
H-Hey!
Y-You cannot fight as two people!
You are disqualified! Disqualified!
We're disqualified?!
Uh oh, let's get out of here!
Yeah.
–See here! Goten! Where are you goin'?!
–Trunks! Come back here!
What an incredible match!
However, according to the rules,
the two people fighting as
Contestant Mighty Mask are disqualified!
And so, all that remains is
Mister Satan and Contestant No. 18!
Whoever wins this is the victor!
Hang in there, Mister Satan!
Mommy, good luck!
W-What do I do? This time
for sure, I really am dead!
So late...
I wonder if they're coming out soon...
Oh, Dabura!
My apologies for the delay.
At last, the King of the
Demon Realm of Darkness,
has completed preparations for his attack.
And so, can Gohan defeat Dabura,
and safely break through Stage 3?
And who will triumph at
the Tenkaichi Tournament?
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Aw, Gohan, you ain't been
training while I've been away, huh?
Dabura has got you all bottled up.
You think you can take me on, at your level?
What kind of a weakling do you take me,
the King of the Demon Realm of Darkness, for?
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Confrontation with the Demon King!
It's Your Turn, Gohan!!"
Rats! It's been so long, I can't find my groove!
"Next time"
"Confrontation with the Demon King!
It's Your Turn, Gohan!!"