The craziness surges toward us,
This is no time for tears.
I will raise my anticipations a hundred-fold,
And become our party's leading man.
That which you can lose yourself in
Will someday make you an incredible guy.
NO... TEN P-KAN
The sky is clear
IPPAI OPPAI
I am feeling fine.
The trouble is here, so enjoy,
You naughty little boy,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
NO... TEN P-KAN
My head is clear,
RA-MEN ROPPAI
Mother doesn't care.
It's the century's end, so twist and twirl,
You mischievous little girl,
We Gotta Power!
Dragon Ball Z!
What would happen if I rip this guy out?
P-Please! You must not rip that guy
out by force! I won't be me any more!
That sounds interesting! Did you
think I would listen to what you say?!
Come on!
At last, Goku and Vegeta,
together with Gohan and the others,
escaped from the inside of Majin Boo's body.
However, Boo once again began to transform.
He's intent on transforming again!
I wish he'd cut that out already.
H-He's turning back...!
We did it, huh Vegeta? We may be
able to manage something like this!
Stay sharp, Goku and Vegeta! That's
no ordinary way that Kaioshin is terrified!
"Earth Disappears!!
Boo's Reverse-Transformation of Evil."
Is that Boo? He's just a child now, isn't he?
All right! This will work!
I'll settle things this time for sure!
No, you won't!
That's not the way it is.
I'm having a chill run through
the very core of my body...
Apparently, Boo has turned back into a kid.
In any case, let's carry Gohan and
the others to someplace where it's safe.
Snap out of it!
Hey, snap out of it, Gohan!
Vegeta, it's all right! Everyone's still alive!
Turned back, you say?
What do you mean by that? Tell me!
I-It's like this...
At the time, Earthlings were
first beginning to walk on two legs.
In the Kaioshin Realm,
under a kind and gentle
Grand Kaioshin-sama,
there lived the Kaioshin of the North...
...the Kaioshin of the West...
...the Kaioshin of the South...
Come on, give that back!
Come and get it!
...as well as myself, the Kaioshin of the East.
That is, until Madoshi Bibidi
created the terrible Majin Boo.
Get them! Give it to them!
Kill them all!
That was quite over-the-top
of you, again. Incredible, Boo!
Papparapa!!
You idiot! A little closer and you
would have done me in as well, you know!
So then, onto the next planet...
At first, two of the Kaioshin were killed.
In order to oppose Boo, Kaoishin of
the West and Kaioshin of the North acted...
I'm sick of listening to the Kaioshin!
They can't stand up to us, can they?
Where does he think he's going this time?
Good grief, he doesn't listen
to a single order I give him!
K-Kaioshin of the West!
K-Kaioshin of the North, too!
And then, Kaioshin of the South,
who was the most hardy and strong of us,
was absorbed by Boo...
And that's how he became that
huge Majin Boo from earlier, then?
Yes.
I was the youngest, and most
powerless, but somehow I was spared,
and was only badly hurt.
That was thanks to
the Grand Kaioshin-sama...
G-Grand Kaioshin-sama!
The next one to be absorbed was the chubby,
yet kind and gentle Grand Kaioshin-sama.
H-Hey, Boo! Are you really Boo?
Hey, I've been playing a lot,
and now my tummy's empty.
Gimme something to eat.
I-I'm sure there was some cake back at home.
Cake? Is that yummy?
Y-Yeah!
It's quite yummy! Cake is the
most delicious food in the universe!
It's really that yummy?
I'll let you eat cake every day from now on.
In exchange, you have to obey
everything I tell you to do. Okay?
Yep!
The Majin Boo that Bibidi
created was the very essence of evil.
It was a failed creation, that not
even Bibidi himself could handle,
but by absorbing the Grand Kaioshin-sama,
he became somehow or
other able to control him.
So then he finally became complete.
Which then would mean...
That little Majin Boo now is the
very first, most difficult one, then?
Yes. His heart, which through absorption
had allowed his power to even be reduced,
has returned back to its original form.
To an existence without
any self-control, of evil itself.
Boo is on the move!
W-What is that?!
His screaming is impossibly loud!
What is he...?!
Th-That was close! That bastard!
He tried to blow the Earth away
all of a sudden! Thank you, Vegeta!
He's got to be joking! Was he
trying to blow himself away too?!
No. Even if he were blown to bits,
he'd soon return to normal again.
Hey, Boo! If you're going to
blow up this planet, that's up to you,
but how about you do
it after you've fought us?!
That's more like it.
W-What's this?!
I-It's huge! He's kidding, right?
Is he planning to launch that?
We can't repel something like that!
H-Hey...
Go hand over your Potara to them!
R-Right! O-Okay!
S-Stop, Boo!
Please! The Earth will be...!
You were going to fight us, right?
H-Have to save everyone...!
Vegeta! This way! I'll do
Instantaneous Movement with everyone!
All right!
Grab on!
It's no use! There ain't enough time!
It's hopeless! I can't do Instantaneous
Movement in such a brief amount of time!
H-Here!
H-Hey!
So you see, he wanted to get
a better grade, but it dropped!
Really?!
Thank goodness! You made it!
We may have made it, but the
Earth, and Gohan and the others...
W-Where am I? H-Heaven?
Hey!! Kakarrot!!
Why the hell did you save these guys
and that dog before Trunks and the others?!
I am sorry.
In the end, Goku was unable to
save the Earth, or Gohan and the others.
However, there's no time to be
despondent! Boo is not yet dead!
Angel... Angel... Angel...
Buried in time and distant memories,
That's right, we were angels.
From high in the sky we
scattered the seeds of love,
We wanted to rid the world of sadness.
Say, look at that blue sky,
As you stare into it, doesn't
your courage swell up inside?
Even now?
To my friends, we may have lost
the wings from our backs, but still,
There's some mysterious
power that remains with us.
To my friends, let's embrace
the light and dare to dream,
Look! I can see the rainbow in your eyes.
(Angel... Angel... Angel...)
Heya! I'm Goku!
Boo has arrived at the Grand Kaio's world,
after seeking out strong ki.
We have to do something, quick!
Kakarrot! Let's both increase our ki
and attract that Boo punk
here to the Kaioshin's World!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Boo's Assault!!
A Conclusion in the Kaioshin Realm."
Father and Vegeta are going to
fight Boo without merging together!
"Next time"
"Boo's Assault!!
A Conclusion in the Kaioshin Realm"