Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Why, you!
You're not taking this seriously, are you?!
I did say this would
just be warming up, didn't I?
When I have become
Super Vegeta, do not mock me!!
What?!
Even a kick with Vegeta's full power behind it...
...has absolutely no effect on Cell.
Super Vegeta is in an ultra-pinch!
"Breaking Through the Boundaries of the
Super Saiyan!! Trunks Summons a Storm."
Vegeta's attack had to have
struck Cell's vital point flawlessly.
And yet, Cell has taken no damage whatsoever!
I-Is that how much difference
there is in their powers now?
What's the matter?
Where's all that enthusiasm
you had up until now?
M-My...
...my kick had the power
of my whole body behind it...!
W-Why?!
What's the matter? Smile, Vegeta!
Well, well. I suppose I'll
have to return your remark...
...that there is too great
a difference between us,
and this fight is dull.
W-What are you doing, Trunks?
If you don't hurry up and help him,
Vegeta really is going to die!
If he dies, he won't be able to give
you any business about his pride!
W-When Dad loses consciousness
fighting Cell, then I'll step in to help.
Having lost consciousness,
I can get away without having to
have Dad see that I've surpassed him.
Are you still worried about that?
Kuririn-san!
For Dad, pride is something you cannot be without!
Dad without his pride
would not be Dad at all!
That's what makes Dad even stronger...
...as well as making him more solitary.
However, I'm sure it's that
part of Dad that attracted Mom!
And me, as well!
Trunks...
Fine then, assuming he doesn't get
killed before losing consciousness.
You scum.
Vegeta, unfortunately it seems
you'll be finished while I'm warming up.
Y-You piece of crap...!
Before we part ways,
I must express my gratitude...
...to the degree of your foolishness that
assisted me in becoming my perfect form.
Don't go exerting any uncalled-for effort,
when you know what
the outcome will be, No. 16.
You are no longer anything
more than a powerless pile of junk.
D-Dad!
W-What is he planning to do?
Cell!!
No matter that you may
have attained your perfect form,
do you still have the
courage to catch this head-on?!
It's too much for you, I bet!
You're nothing but a pantywaist!
H-He's provoking Cell!
To keep him from avoiding the attack!
Y-You've got to be kidding!
D-Does he really intend to
unleash that technique here on Earth?!
Please don't do it!!
The Earth...!! The Earth itself will be...!!
Get out of there, Trunks!
Final Flash!
H-Holy s–!
I'm so hungry!
Let's see, this... and this, and this.
Gohan likes this one, after all. Okay!
Gohan!
It's about time for us to eat!
Right!
After all, if you don't keep
your body in good health,
I'll get Chichi mad at me, too!
Right.
Okay. Gohan, cook this for me.
Thank you!
Y-Your hair...
Gohan, you have to hurry and
learn how to control your power, huh?
Y-Yes...
Ee-yow!
W-We survived...!
Dad calculated perfectly, and
narrowed his range down just right!
I-It paid off!
Take that!
N-No...!
H-He did it! H-He really did it!
Y-Yeah...!
S-Something like this... c-can't happen!
It can't happen! Not to my perfect form!
Damn it to hell!!
Gotcha!
You're laughing a fool's laugh!
Have you forgotten that
I have inherited Piccolo's blood?
Disappointed?
T-This can't be...!
Now then, isn't it about time I killed you?
D-Dammit!
H-Hey... He's no longer S-Super Saiyan.
H-He's lost consciousness... Or else he's d-d–
You're tough, huh?
I'll put you out of your
misery right now, Vegeta.
Trunks! It's now or never!
Now's the time to become
that drastic Super Saiyan!
Hey, now...
T-Trunks?
Hey, Trunks?
Are you all right? Hey!
And so, this is where it ends, Vegeta.
At last, Trunks' Ultra-Power is unleashed!
Take that power that surpasses the Saiyan wall,
and use it to take down Cell here and now!
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Vegeta, Trunks is fighting
Cell with awesome power.
He's gotten a lot stronger than you.
Kuririn-san, take Dad and get
him someplace far away, quickly.
You need not worry about me,
because I will be sure to win.
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Save Your Father!! Trunks' Fury,
Which Scorches Even the Heavens."
Is this the power of a Saiyan
that has surpassed Super Saiyan?
"Next time"
"Save Your Father!! Trunks' Fury,
Which Scorches Even the Heavens"