Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
Wait... Let him go... Please...
let me have another chance to fight him!
Following a fierce battle, Goku
and the others had saved the earth.
However, there was no telling
when Vegeta would come to attack again.
Meanwhile, as for Bulma and company...
If we go to Planet Namek, we
might be able to obtain their Dragon Balls.
Once we do that, we could
also bring everyone back to life!
You're naïve! You're absolutely naïve!
I calculated how much time it
would take you to reach Planet Namek.
It would take 4,339 years and three months.
You'd have to live to a ripe old age, huh?
If that's the problem, we'll be all right.
We're sure to make it if we
use that Saiyan's spaceship.
Yay! Hope is in sight!
But whether or not it will work out that well...
"Mysterious Yunzabit!
The Search for Kami-sama's Spaceship."
Yow!
"Science"
Gohan-chan, you're goin' to catch up
with everythin' that you've fallen behind on.
Anything but that!
What's the matter, Kuririn? You're trembling.
I-It's nothing.
Oww!
All we're doing is changing his
bandages. What a loud patient this is.
On second thought, I shouldn't be here.
We have to find that Saiyan spaceship quickly.
Let Bulma handle that. You need to
hurry and recover from your injuries.
B-But...
We never know when that
Saiyan is going to attack again.
You need to completely
recover before that happens.
Gohan-chan is not havin'
anythin' to do with that anymore!
I'm not lettin' him get into any more
dangerous situations like that again!
Next, please.
M-My injuries aren't all that serious, so...
Neither are mine!
Now, look here!
You've got to get treated properly,
or you're not goin' to get any better!
Come on, Gohan-chan!
No, anything but this!
Wow, we're lucky.
They said that after Gohan and I spend
three days in the hospital, we'll be fine.
You've got me beat. They said it would
be four months before my injuries heal.
They also said I might
not be back to my former self.
Hey, not to worry. In another month,
I'll have some new senzu beans.
You know, you look
just like a mummy in there.
Tch! I went through all that nastiness,
and they ain't even gonna keep me here.
You're just after the
hospital's food, aren't you?
When Yajirobe thought he was
going to be done in by that Saiyan,
he was like, "Sorry 'bout that! I got
lotsa respect for ya! Lemme be your friend!"
Why, you! What're ya talkin' 'bout?!
I was just sayin' that to get him off his guard!
Well, in any case, you all really done well!
Nothin' could make me happier. And
everyone who's dead is comin' back to life, too.
Mm-hmm, that is, if we can get to Planet Namek.
It will be all right, that's for sure!
Hey, everyone! The TV! Watch the TV!
Oh, it's you, Bulma! I thought
you were some weird nurse.
Shut up, would you? Here, watch the TV.
According to those who found it, this object,
which was discovered in
the devastation of Metro East,
appears to be a vehicle that came from
space, though that cannot be determined.
That's the Saiyan's!
It sure is!
I-I can't see!
Apparently, when this object
was found, there were two of them,
but soon after, one of them
suddenly flew away from the scene.
This is bad. Those scientists
have already carried it away.
W-What do we do?
This should be interesting.
Let's use the remote control that
Kuririn brought back, and call it here!
That will surprise them, I'm sure.
Are you sure that's going to work?
What are you talking about? I'm a genius!
I thoroughly checked it out last night.
Watch this.
It's nice that we can watch it right
here on TV, huh? Okay, beep, beep, beep...
Ready? It's going to start moving...
I want to see, too!
W-What in the world could have happened here?!
T-The object suddenly exploded! What happened?
There is wreckage from the object all over!
It can't be!
W-Why? Could that have
been the self-destruct switch?
What do we do?! Without that
spaceship, we can't go to Planet Namek!
Our last hope...
Completely wiped out.
I-It's hopeless now...
This is a problem. I probably
couldn't get there using Kinto Un, either.
This is your fault for
picking up strange remote controls!
Bulma-san, you're the one who
was hasty to push those switches.
Well...
Hey.
Mister Popo!
Hey there.
W-What the...?!
Someone come with me. There is spaceship.
A-A spaceship? You really have one, Popo-san?
Probably.
–W-Who is that?
–Mister Popo.
Mister Popo?
He stays at Kami-sama's place.
But he's been there at Kami's palace
since long before this
current Kami-sama was ever there.
Say, what do you mean, "probably"?
Probably, it is...
...spaceship. But Mister Popo not know for sure.
Someone come with me to
check. Mister Popo show way.
Bulma-san!
–Me?!
–Well, Bulma-san,
nobody else would know if it's a spaceship.
Bulma-san?
Would I be all right? I mean, doesn't
that man have a dangerous look in his eye?
–What is that?!
–There's someone riding it!
–What is it?!
Bulma, what's taking you
so long? Hurry and hop on!
Oh, no! Save me!
I'm falling down!
I'm done for! I'm going to die!
We're counting on you, Bulma!
Be careful. I'm not like
those guys. I'm delicate, okay?
Okay, we go.
Easy... easy, now...
H-How did he do that just now?
Still, what kind of spaceship is it?
Could there really be one?
Here.
Already?
Get off.
W-Where is this? It's pretty cold.
Yunzabit Highlands.
Y-Yunzabit?!
That's the ends of the earth, you know!
You mean, we came
this far in that one instant?
Here, maybe...
This way, maybe...
W-Wait up!
Say, do you mean there's
something like a spaceship here?
Hey, are you listening to me?
You haven't brought me
here to this far-flung place...
...for the purpose of doing
anything indecent to me, right?
H-Hang on!
Hurry up.
Y-You're kidding, right? I can't do that!
Geez...
This thing.
Is this spaceship?
I-I'll have to examine it...
What is this? It's not metal. Could this be?
Hang on, what's going on?
Tell me what this is, exactly!
About a hundred years ago,
Kami-sama told Mister Popo of old times.
Strange story.
Kami-sama said lived here in
Yunzabit when child. Mister Popo asked him...
"Yunzabit remote region. People
not live there, so why you there?"
I don't know why I was
there. I must have hit my head,
and lost all of my memories up to that point.
Had no parents?
No, I didn't. All I had was a letter
that said they would be coming later.
What does that mean?
I don't see where this story is going.
Kami-sama as child waited long time for
parents. Not knew what happened, but waited.
I had my house there in Yunzabit, after all.
I trusted that my parents
would surely return there.
However, no matter how long I waited,
nobody ever came. It was hard on me.
There was hardly anything there
to eat, either. How long did I wait there?
Twenty years? No,
it must have been thirty years.
Finally, I gave up, and, leaving
my house behind, I left Yunzabit.
Once in a while, I went back to see how it
was doing, but there was never any change.
So, what does that have to do with this?
You impatient. Here come point of story.
But you know, thinking back
on it now, it was a strange house.
I didn't realize it until I had
learned more about the world,
but that house was really quite unusual.
It was round, with four legs,
and looked almost like an insect.
Its door didn't have any knobs or locks,
but would open when a word was spoken to it.
"Piccolo."
An entrance!
Get up on there.
This is Kami-sama's house?
Say again to close.
"Piccolo."
Look close. This not
house, but rather, spaceship?
That's right! Kami-sama is a Namekian!
That Kaio person said that long ago,
Planet Namek went through some
abnormal weather, and they nearly died out.
Mister Popo also heard
Kaio-sama's voice speaking.
Then remembered story of this house.
Thought "what if," came
here searching, and this here.
If this really is a spaceship, then your
story earlier would indeed be consistent.
When Planet Namek had bad time,
Kami-sama's parents put child
Kami-sama aboard, sent to Earth.
His parents meant to escape
afterward, when they were able to,
but there was some kind of accident...
which is to say, they died...
That's it! After all, no matter how you look
at this thing, it doesn't seem like a house.
This has to be a spaceship!
But even if that's so, can we use it or not?
The door moved, so it has to have power, right?
Is this the main switch?
Nope. Well, what about this?
It's not this, either.
That's odd. I wonder if
there's a code number or something.
Sure, that's it. If it worked as easily as that,
then when Kami-sama was a child,
he would have tried pushing them, too.
It looks like this thing
doesn't work using switches.
I wonder if Bulma-san
will really find anything for us.
All we can do now is pray.
We're counting on you,
Bulma. This is for everyone.
I don't get it.
Could it be some kind of sensor?
Voice?
Yes! Like with the entrance! Words!
Say what? "Piccolo"?
Not that! After all, that's the
password you use for going in and out.
Work! Do you hear me?
Fly! Let me see you fly!
It's no use. The language is different.
You have to speak Namekian.
After all, back at that Tenkaichi Tournament,
Kami-sama and Piccolo
spoke in that strange language.
That must be the Namekian language.
Supposing that Namekian language,
Mister Popo knows those words.
Really?!
Really. "Piccolo" means "other world"
in those words. That why password for door.
Why didn't you say so sooner?
So that's it. "Piccolo Daimao"
means the Demon King of Another World.
Try saying something
in Namekian. Tell it to fly.
Fly where?
Anywhere is fine!
I know, how about
around Jupiter for now?
It says "acknowledged."
What is this?! Doesn't this
spaceship have any safety belts?!
What is that thing?!
Just now, you said
"want to go toilet" in Namekian.
You said "safety belt," right?
This is all too complicated!
We have to be careful what we say!
"Complicated" means "time for bed."
Incredible! It's Jupiter!
This is an incredible spaceship!
We did it! We did it, we did it!
Thank goodness. Now
Kami-sama come back to life.
A spaceship has been found.
Now all that remains is a
departure for Planet Namek.
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Chichi, let Gohan go off into space willingly.
Mother, we have to bring
those who died protecting the Earth
back to life, to fight
against the Saiyan once again!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Blast-off for Planet Namek!
The Terror Awaiting Gohan & Co."
G-Gohan-chan, you've turned into a delinquent!
"Next time"
"Blast-off for Planet Namek!
The Terror Awaiting Gohan & Co."