Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
W-Wh-What the hell are you?!
As you are surely well aware...
I am the Saiyan who came
from Earth to defeat you.
Despite my calm, quiet heart,
I am the legendary warrior,
awakened by intense anger.
I am the Super Saiyan, Son Goku!!
"The Destruction of Planet Namek!?
A Demonic Flash Pierces the Ground."
I-Indeed.
It appears that somehow
you really are a Super Saiyan.
Having a calm, quiet heart,
then awakened by intense anger, huh?
I see.
Which is why no matter how hard Vegeta
worked at it, he could not become one.
Kuririn-san... Dende... Father
will surely win against Freeza!
He will surely win, and avenge you,
Kuririn-san and Dende!
You bastard!
W-What humiliation on my part!
That I–that Freeza-sama
should take this from him–
from this Saiyan monkey scumbag!
It's unbelievable! I didn't think
this sort of thing could happen!
Contact with the gentlemen from the
Ginyu Special Corps has been cut off,
and the signal from Freeza-sama's
Scouter has also disappeared!
What... what the hell is
happening on Planet Namek?!
Perhaps it has finally come!
A new era, that is!
A new era?
Freeza, the one who wiped out
my species, has finally been defeated!
You miserable fool!
C-Commander!
That we may stand here this day,
triumphant over the rest of the
universe, is due entirely to Freeza-sama!
And that is not all,
he has promised me that some day, my
clan would be raised higher than any other!
Isn't that true of your races as well?!
Freeza-sama is the
very savior of the universe!
Treachery will not be tolerated!
Signal on sensors! It is Freeza-sama!
It's an incredible battle power reading!
That's it! Freeza-sama must
finally have gotten serious!
Another one! What is
this other giant reading?
What's the matter?!
There is another, incredible
reading right near Freeza-sama!
What?!
I will give you a level reading.
You're finished, Freeza.
I-I...
I am Freeza!
You're telling me I'm finished?!
That's it!
The spaceship that Father rode here in!
Still not yet?!
If you don't cut that out,
I'm really goin' to get angry!
I have mentioned that this
would be a piece of cake–yeow!
–if you would not rush me so.
Someone has gotten
aboard Goku's spaceship!
I installed sensor devices in there.
So, who could it be?
Gohan-chan!
Piccolo-san, wait here a moment.
Mother!
Gohan-chan! You're alive, aren't ya?!
Thank goodness! Really, thank goodness!
Mother!
–Gohan, what about Goku?!
–What are you doin'?!
How are Goku and Kuririn?!
Father is fighting against Freeza.
Kuririn-san has died.
W-What did you say?!
I'm sorry,
I don't have the time to go into
detailed circumstances right now.
I have to go get Bulma-san!
Gohan-chan! Don't you be goin' anywhere!
You stay right where you are!
–I'm waiting here for you!
–Wait, Gohan! Wait, I say!
If it is to come down to me
being killed by the likes of you,
I will choose death by my own hand!
Whichever you like.
Fool. You expect me to die?
It is you who will die.
I can continue to live,
even in the vacuum of space.
I wonder though, how about you Saiyans?
Now perish, together
with this whole planet!!
Blow up!!
Now perish, together
with this whole planet!!
Oh no!!
W-What is it? What's that light?!
Gohan-chan! Gohan-chan!
What is this? What's happening?!
Father!
K-Kaio-sama!
D-Don't tell me...!
Son Goku did well.
Against Freeza,
his overwhelming strength proved
him entirely triumphant in their battle.
So then, Goku is...?
He's defeated Freeza, hasn't he?
No. Having been cornered, Freeza...
...destroyed the entire planet of Namek itself.
So then, what about Goku and the others?
If the planet is lost, no one can survive.
No one except Freeza.
T-That can't be!
It's over. All of it.
Kaio-sama...
Kaio-sama, are you able to hear me?
It is I, the Kami of Earth.
Yeah. What is it? I hear you!
I am now having Mister Popo
gather the Dragon Balls of Earth.
I believe he will have all
seven together very shortly.
Is that so?
If I could have you wait briefly,
I can have those who have
been in your care resurrected.
However, Chaozu there is
now dead a second time, and so...
That is...
J-Just a moment! Are you alive?
Y-Yes, gratefully so, thanks to
the Dragon Balls of Planet Namek...
Which would mean that
Piccolo is not dead either, correct?
A-As I believe you are aware, myself
and Piccolo were originally one single...
That's right! Then perhaps...
Kaio-sama!
Er, Kaio-sama? Kaio-sama?
Are you hearing me?
Hey, keep it down!
What a start!
I-I'm not going to let myself die
in a place like this!
Father!
Planet Namek has not been lost!
Goku and Gohan and Piccolo and
the girl called Bulma are all alive!
–All right!
–Thank goodness!
–Okay!
I restrained my power too much, didn't I?
That's because you were fearful of
being caught in the explosion of the planet.
You failed.
As a result, I've hung on to life.
Hung on to life, you say?
You don't seem to understand at all, do you?
You have avoided the
planet's instantaneous explosion,
but I've completely destroyed its core.
Do you understand what that means?
Five more minutes.
Five more minutes,
and then Planet Namek will undergo
a great explosion, becoming space dust!
Five minutes will be plenty.
I will defeat you, then leave
together with my friends in my spaceship.
Unfortunately for you,
it will be I who can hope to do so.
At least, it's a much
greater hope than you have.
In this event, I will show
you my 100 percent full power!
There's no way you can defeat me!
Prepare yourself for this!
Why wait until now for full power?
I know why.
If you used all your power,
your body couldn't withstand it!
I can't let you stall for any more time!
I'm going to settle this now!
There are five minutes until
the destruction of Planet Namek.
What will be the outcome of this fierce battle?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
Freeza ain't holding back anymore.
He's finally planning to
take me on at full power.
Sorry to keep you waiting. Here
is the 100% full power you wanted.
I'm going to fight you at your best, and win!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"I Will Be the One Who Wins...
Risking Survival, a Final Attack."
Father, hurry! The planet is about to...
"Next time"
"I Will Be the One Who Wins...
Risking Survival, a Final Attack"