Break through the shining clouds,
and fly away (fly away)
As a panorama spreads itself
throughout my being!
The earth, having been kicked
in the face, gets angry (angry)!
And makes one of its volcanoes explode!
If, within the thawed polar ice,
There is a dinosaur, then I want
to train him to balance atop a ball.
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
No matter what may happen,
I feel as though nothing can bother me,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
However hard your chest pounds,
the Genki Dama will roar!
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
The emptier your head is, the more
room there is to pack with dreams,
CHA-LA-HEAD-CHA-LA
With a cheerful face and an Ultra-Z,
today is ai-yai-yai-yai-yai...
Sparking!
I thought you weren't
going to use your hands, right?
The service time has run out.
Well, let me offer my service,
if you want to call it that,
by giving you some advice.
You put too much faith in your own strength.
As a result, you leave
yourself wide open to attack.
My thanks.
Amazing! Can both fighters still be
in the initial phase of their battles?
Just how far will their powers extend?
"That Was No I dle Boast!!
Son Goku, an Audacious, Wonderful Guy."
You're strong!
Enough that I would
even say marvelously so.
Why, thank you.
However, I am growing tired of this fight.
I'm thinking it's about
time to bring it to a conclusion.
Before the end, let me ask you,
just in case. How about it?
Wouldn't you like to work underneath me?
It would be a shame to have to
wipe out all that power you have.
You would be able to do work so
much better than Commander Ginyu.
You've got to be kidding.
You really expect me to accept that offer?
I thought you would say that.
You Saiyans as a group are
stubborn to the point of being fools.
Well, there is only one
route left for you to take.
Just death.
We'll see. It won't be so easy.
Such confidence! But I am
aware of what you're doing.
While you say you're being serious,
you're still keeping back
a good deal of your power.
My secret's out, is it?
Keeping that in mind, the way I figure it,
using about 50 percent,
or in other words, half of my max power,
I can turn you into space dust!
What?!
That's a bit of an exaggeration!
You're trying to feed me too large a bluff.
It's been fun.
It's been quite a long time
since I've had this kind of exercise.
W-What's going on?
Those two are just
staring at each other now.
Both of them are searching for
the right timing to begin again.
Besides which, it feels
like we're about to be crushed
by both of their tremendous ki alone.
Father can win this, right?
There's no way we can tell.
Their power is particularly greater
than anything we can comprehend.
That's true.
Yahoo!
H-Hey, you mecha-no sense!
I'm not this poor a pilot!
Why is it, with all my beauty and
glamour, and my super-cute face,
that I have to be turned into a frog?!
Everything that's happened
to me, it's all those guys' fault!
H-Hey you, what are you doing?!
Hurry up and give me my body back!
I can't see in front of us!
Look out!
T-That was perfect!
B-Bulma-san!
B-Bulma-san, why have you come here?
It's extremely dangerous!
Bulma-san?
Huh? What's that?
Goku and Freeza are over there...
What?
Bulma-san, you shouldn't go there!
T-That's Freeza-sama?
It's a shame. It really is a shame.
If you were to become one of my men,
wonderful things would await you every day.
King Vegeta, Vegeta...
...and that lower-class warrior Burdock...
Every single one of them, so terribly obstinate.
Dammit...
That's what cost them their lives.
H-How marvelous!
Freeza-sama's body is responding
spontaneously to Goku's power!
After taking Goku's attacks, every
nerve in his body has a precise read on him.
Is this the power of Freeza?
Fantastic!
Bulma-san...
That over there isn't me! It's a frog, a frog!
I'm Bulma! You have to understand!
All right! Nice!
Ah, I get it! You're...
You've finally gotten it, huh?!
You're that Ginyu guy!
What are you doing hanging
around in a place like this?
You'd better hurry and seek
shelter somewhere, it's dangerous here!
That's not it!
Using about 50 percent, or in
other words, half of my max power,
I can turn you into space dust!
He ain't bluffing...
What speed!
I didn't see that at all!
–Son!
–Father!
Bravo! What an attack to behold!
To think that I should be able to
see Freeza-sama's form like this! I... I...
Freeza-sama, I'm so glad
I trusted and stayed with you!
What are you saying, Bulma-san?
Father is the one getting beaten up!
That's right!
Bulma-san, please go somewhere
safe and take refuge right away!
What are you talking about?!
I'll never see another fight like this!
I wonder if she hit her head or
something back when we left her by herself.
Again, I couldn't see Freeza's movement...
Can there be this much
difference in our powers?
Didn't I say so? If I use
only half of my max power,
I could turn you into space dust, as I recall.
Dammit!
On you go!
All righty.
Takeoff preparations are complete.
Sensei, give Son-in-law our best!
Tell Gohan I'm waitin' for him here on Earth!
Ask Bulma-chan to bring us back some
souvenirs of Planet Namek's cakes, okay!
Sit tight, Gohan-chan!
We're comin' to save you right now!
Is this for real?
Are we actually going to Planet Namek?!
Yamucha-sama!
(Amidha sutra)
Is everyone ready for this?
It's about time for the countdown.
10... 9...
8... 7...
–6...
–I don't wanna go to Planet Namek!
–5...
–(Amidha sutra)
4...
3...
–2...
–(Amidha sutra)
1...
Blast-off!
Here it goes...
Y-Y-Yamucha-sama!
Lemme off! I don't wanna die yet!
Lemme off! Lemme off, 'kay?! 'Kay?!
Hey, forgive me, forgive me.
I made a mistake!
Welcome!
Your speed is too low! Anyone can see that!
What's the matter?
Never mind half my max power,
I'm not even using a third!
Serves you right!
Looks like you're finally
starting to get a little winded.
Then again, it's amazing you haven't died yet.
I-It's no use. He's too strong!
To think he's this strong...!
Kaio-sama, Goku is still
wearing that heavy gi, isn't he?
What he has on now is
only tough, it's not heavy.
I-I see...
O-Oh no! Is there anything else?
Goku...
There's nothing to worry about, Chaozu!
Goku is going to win this fight!
Aren't you forgetting
about the Kaio-ken technique?
With Goku as he is now,
he should be able to withstand as
much as ten times his regular power!
Oh, yeah!
That's it!
–All right!
–All right, all right!
No...
Regrettably, what he's using right
now is that very times ten Kaio-ken...
It can't be!
T-This isn't good! There's too
much difference in their abilities!
Father...
Bulma-san?
That's our Freeza-sama!
Against Goku... such grandeur!
W-Who the hell are you?!
Who, me?
Watch out, Piccolo!
As Kaio's words cut off any
encouraging news about Goku,
who is already using a ten-fold Kaio-ken,
is there any glimmer of
hope remaining for him?
And what of Ginyu, as he closes in
on Piccolo with his finishing technique?
Here it comes a-fighting,
an apple-colored monster,
Here it comes a-flying,
a nut-scented alien,
They meet and the heart beats faster.
Sparkle, sparkle, the galaxy's a popcorn shower.
Yesterday goes bye, bye, bye, (Gohan),
Mystery, (far as the eye can see),
Gather up your energy, (substitutes are okay),
Come over here, lai, lai, lai.
Ooh, miracle ZENKAI power!
A hungry, naughty Kinto Un,
A mountain full of horizons.
They meet each other, they come apart,
they meet each other, they come apart, Oh, no!
Aah, enough! Even Kami-sama has it rough.
So sorry.
Ooh, full-bellied ZENKAI power!
Come on out, full-on ZENKAI power!
Heya! I'm Goku!
This is the only way to defeat Freeza!
I'm raising my Kaio-ken to times-20!
Son-kun, what are
you dawdling around for?!
Hurry up and beat that guy, and
turn me from a frog back to normal!
Next time on Dragon Ball Z,
"Showdown!! The Embodiment of Flame
in a 20-Times Kaio-ken Kamehame-Ha."
Stop your futile resistance, Freeza!
Father is the strongest in the universe!
"Next time"
"Showdown!! The Embodiment of Flame
in a 20-Times Kaio-ken Kamehame-Ha"