SHIN GODZILLA
Tokyo Bay off the coast of Yokohama
.
Offshore of Haneda Airport
,
A pleasure craft has been spotted adrift offshore of Haneda.
Japan Coast Guard Patrol Boat PC16
,
Roger that.
Pleasure craft confirmed. No apparent hull damage.
The "Glory-maru"... MJG-15041.
Requesting owner information
Boarding the vessel.
Hello. Anyone here?
No one on the flying deck.
No sign of life. Some personal effects.
No traces of an incident. Perhaps a fall overboard?
Vessel's vacant. We'll prepare a tow.
Tokyo Bay Aqua-Line Aqua Bridge
.
Tokyo Bay Aqua-Line Aqua Tunnel
,
Wait, wait, wait!
Prime Minister's Office, Chiyoda Ward
.
Fifth Floor Hallway
,
1st report from intelligence and research.
The Aqua-Line has sprung a leak.
Water's pouring onto the auto lanes.
A liaison office is up, and an emergency order issued.
And the PM?
Arriving in 28 minutes.
I need info... downstairs.
Yes.
First report confirmed at about 8:30 a.m.
Leak in the Tokyo Aqua-Line tunnel, near the 2.5 kilo marker.
Seawater entering from a fissure in the tunnel ceiling.
Crisis Management Center
.
Several cars involved.
Hamanami Coast Guard personnel are caught in the steam cloud in the bay.
Executive Meeting Room
,
Aqua-Line's closed both ways.
Coast Guard is issuing alerts.
Rando Yaguchi, Deputy Chief Cabinet Secretary
,
Status, Mr. Koriyama?
Koriyama, Crisis Management Supervisor
.
5 confirmed collisions in the tunnel.
Earthquake damage?
Oki, Deputy Director (Japan Meteorological Agency)
We're checking.
Any relation to the sea eruption?
Not enough info to say yet.
We have helicopter footage!
Yusuke Shimura, Deputy Chief Cabinet Secretary (Ministry of Defense)
,
An underwater volcanic eruption?
If so, it's anomalous.
,
Coast Guard 691 reporting continued steam eruptions.
Tokyo Bay Aqua-Line Wind Tower
Japan Coast Guard Super Puma 225 MH691
,
The churning water prevents undersea visibility.
We'll need a unified initial response
Let's reorganize.
FDMA disaster force is in place.
3rd Regional Coast Guard HQ has sealed the bay.
No sea or air access.
A coastal evacuation advisory has been issued.
Umihotaru Parking Area
,
Please evacuate the premises immediately!
Follow police instructions and evacuate to Kisarazu!
Tokyo Bay Aqua Line Aqua Tunnel
,
Holy crap!
Tunnel's leaking!
Watch your head!
Cool! A slide.
Aqua Tunnel Evacuation Slide
,
Stay calm.
Heading to first aid.
Aqua Tunnel Evacuation Passage
,
This place is awesome.
My feet hurt.
Awesome! I'm getting scoop footage.
What? What's that noise?
Something's up there.
This is bad.
It's freaking me out
What's that? Something's here.
Crisis Management Center Conference Room Stairs
.
The PM has returned.
Fifth Floor Hallway
,
Aqua-Line rupture is unconfirmed.
Prime Minister and attendants
,
Never mind the details. Any fatalities?
No.
Then leave it to the guys below.
There's secondary disaster risk.
I've canceled your meeting. There's a briefing in five minutes.
Understood.
Fifth Floor Office
,
What are the cases for it being some undersea thermal discharge?
Briefing for the Prime Minister
.
Sekiguchi, Minister of Science
An unidentified nuclear sub meltdown?
Hanamori, Minister of Defence
,
Impossible. The bay is too shallow for a submarine.
Yanagihara, Minister of Transportation
,
We believe it to be magma steam.
A new undersea volcanic eruption.
Excuse me, Minister Yanagihara.
The epicenter is shallow and appears to be just steam.
We're confident it's not volcanic activity.
Really? Then tell me sooner.
A new, large hydrothermal vent?
That must be it.
A vent directly above the tunnel?
Past geological surveys rule that out.
Kanai, Minister of Disaster Management
,
An oversight, perhaps?
Prime minister.
Something's on the sea floor.
Seiji Okochi, Prime Minister
,
Some "thing"? Like what?
A colossal creature. There's even footage online.
Preposterous. A big whale spouting?
The sea is boiling. What creature has a temperature over 100 degrees?
Kono, Minister of Internal Affairs
,
We've been scouring online videos.
We've yet to find any conclusive evidence.
Azuma, Chief Cabinet Secretary
,
Time is a wasting. How about a process of elimination?
Right. A new volcano or a large thermal vent.
What else could it be?
Then let's plan our basic response.
Can we hold a cabinet meeting, Mr. Prime Minister?
Of course.
Let's move to the main conference room.
Yaguchi.
You'll have to toe the line on their decision.
Don't stir things up.
Shouldn't we consider every possibility?
Hideki Akasaka, Aide to the Prime Minister (National Security Officer)
,
It's good to be a rebel, but think of the guy who got you here.
Got it? Word of advice.
Fourth Floor Conference Room
,
All those injured in the tunnel are receiving care.
Conference regarding the Tokyo Bay Aqua-Line incident
,
Fireboats and helicopters are mobilized in Tokyo Bay.
Satomi, Minister of Agriculture, Forestry and Fisheries,
is absent on a trip to Australia.
,
Satomi, Minister of Agriculture, Forestry and Fisheries,
is absent on a trip to Australia.
They stand ready to respond.
Regarding to Tokyo Bay coastal region...
...we're at evacuation preparedness level.
Due to possible debris and ash,
we're grounding all flights out of Haneda until further notice.
Forgive me. Correction.
The grounding of all flights out of Haneda
is unavoidable to ensure citizen safety over economic concerns...
Later
As for the undersea volcano-induced tunnel flooding.
fortunately, no toxic gasses have been detected.
Teams from the Archaeological Agency and the Coast Guard
are en route to conduct a thorough investigation of the cause.
Eruption activity is reportedly dying down rapidly.
Is it over?
No big deal, I guess.
Mr. Prime Minister. I beg to reiterate...
...the presence of a large marine creature...
...as a possible cause.
Yaguchi. This is no place for jokes.
This is a ministerial meeting. Minutes are kept.
Don't make mockery of it.
With no time frame for restoration,
we can expect those losses to swell.
Sorry! We must suspend this meeting.
The television. Turn on the TV!
It's unbelievable!
I've never seen anything like it.
What was that?
A tail?
Yes, It's a tail.
Yaguchi's joke may be a serious thing.
Let us adjourn this meeting.
All ministers, assemble in the Prime Minister's office.
So what the hell is it?
For now, we only have "Giant Unidentified Creature."
We're making a list of biologists and scholars
from universities and research organizations.
We'll hold an emergency summit
to figure this thing out.
Make haste. We need to know.
Yes!
Mr. Prime Minister.
Perhaps we should focus on our response.
Yes, of course.
Yes, but this is unprecedented.
I think the choices are simple.
Do nothing. Let it go.
Or capture it, exterminate it, or just chase it off.
Kabira, Minister of Finance and Foreign Affairs
.
I vote for extermination.
I concur.
Hayama, Secretary of Economic Industry
,
Look at the costs incurred already,
with the tunnel,
the grounding of flights and indefinite closing of Tokyo Bay.
I, too, favor extermination.
The sooner, the better. Right, Defense Ministry?
Matsumoto, Supervisor of Defensive Operational Policy
,
We've prepared for a wildlife-based threat before.
But never with Self-Defense Forces using weapons in Tokyo Bay.
Why blow it up? Can't we just chase it off?
Academic circles and environmentalists
are already calling for it's live capture
as a valuable new species.
No, extermination's the answer. A few torpedoes?
The use of weapons requires careful examination of options.
I, too, side strongly with the option of live capture.
Start gathering intel on the unidentified creature quickly.
Extermination, capture and expulsion.
Hiraoka, Deputy Chief Cabinet Secretary
,
Who are you addressing?
Vapor cloud spotted near the Tama River!
It's moving?
It's alive, isn't it?
Tama River mouth, Tokyo Bay
,
The creature's off Haneda Airport Runway D,
entering the Tama River!
Report of flooding on the Bayshore Expressway.
Not again!
Forget capturing it.
Anzai, Prime Minister's Secretary of Internal Affairs
,
Sir. Biologists are starting to arrive. Only three so far, but...
Fifth Floor Reception Room
.
Emergency Academic Conference regarding Giant Unidentified Creature
Dr. Shiga, paleontologist
,
It's indiscernible from TV images
whether it's some dinosaur relic
or a species of whale.
Dr. Yanagi, marine biologist
,
It seems to be a never-before seen aquatic species.
But I can't say without an examination.
Dr. Hanawa, biologist
.
First is whether the footage is real.
If I were to rush to judgment based on unverified evidence...
...I'd lose credibility as a biologist.
The conference is wrapping up.
Fifth Floor Secretary's office
.
This is ludicrous.
Asahi Bridge on the Nomi River, Ota Ward
.
What a waste of time that was.
I agree.
Damn their status. Get me someone who knows something.
Yes, Sir.
Shimura, any ideas?
A smart Environment Ministry friend
from college, but she's low ranking.
Fine. Call her.
Hiromi Ogashira, Ministry of the Environment Deputy Chief, Wildlife Division
,
Serpentine with auxiliary ambulation.
Gills make it aquatic, but has legs like a lungfish.
If it has legs, can it come on land?
Yes. It's a possibility.
Really? What then?
Frankly, we haven't determined which agency it falls under
Our scholar says that fin-like feet...
would be crushed under the creature's weight.
So coming ashore is physiologically impossible.
It's already supporting its weight.
Is that so?
What's your view, Environment Minister?
Kikugawa, Minister of the Environment
,
Forgive the deputy chief's poor decorum.
But as your experts concluded, coming on land is very improbable.
I see.
Sir, considering the damage wreaked thus far...
the sooner we hold a press conference to calm the public, the better.
But Sir, If I may.
Please take care to give only verified information.
Understood.
Prepare my uniform.
New Nomi Bridge, Nomi River, Ota Ward
.
First Floor Press Conference Room
,
The Aqua-Line and Tama River have sustained significant damage.
The creature is currently moving up the Nomi River.
We're yet to identify what sort of creature it is.
But we don't expect it to come on land.
Should it beach itself in the shallows...
we believe it would be crushed to death under it's own weight.
I repeat.
There is no danger of the creature coming ashore.
Please set your minds at ease.
Sir, excuse the interruption.
It has?
Kamata, Ota Ward
.
Hurry! Hurry! Run away!
No danger of coming ashore, huh?
Underground Access Hallway
,
Now what? I've just been proven a liar!
You weren't supposed to go off script!
I needed to reassure the public clearly.
We're asking the experts how it came ashore.
Screw them. What's happening out there?
Sir, we need to set up an emergency disaster control headquarters.
Understood.
Conference regarding Emergency Disaster Control for Giant Unidentified Creature
,
This cabinet council is now adjourned.
Let's get to work.
Fourth Floor Hallway
,
So much red tape.
Every action requires a meeting.
That's the foundation of democracy.
Even to hold a press conference?
We have set up emergency disaster control headquarters.
to combat the large unidentified creature that has come ashore.
We are crafting a full-scale response to secure citizen safety,
including coordinated evacuation
with Tokyo federal government agencies...
The creature's heading toward Shinagawa.
At a speed of about 13 km per hour.
It moves slowly for it's size.
It can trample through Tokyo in 3 hours.
The city is dense and brittle.
We're looking at enormous damage.
We must exterminate it now!
It's a densely-populated area. We must evacuate people first.
Have MIC and MILT set up evacuation zones and transport.
Tokyo Metropolitan Government Building
.
Disaster Control HQ, Ninth Floor
,
We've got orders from the PM to conduct evacuation measures.
Kozuka, Governor of Tokyo
,
What took so long?
Nothing in the first response manual applies here.
Just expedite an evacuation plan on the fly.
We've never drilled for this kind of thing.
Tahara, Vice Governor
,
A city-wide evacuation will cause a general panic.
Citizens will have to self-evacuate.
Kawamata, Vice Governor
,
We'll make every effort to control traffic.
Onchi, Superintendent General
,
They must leave their vehicles quickly and obey signage and police.
Highway Fifteen, Shinagawa Ward
,
Traffic signs are out of order.
Please leave your vehicles and follow police guidance.
The Tokyo Government has ordered a full evacuation of Shinagawa.
All residents are required to evacuate immediately.
Hurry dear!
At this rate, the city will be in ruins
Contact the Public Safety Commission.
We can request Self Defense Forces for pest extermination.
And use of weapons?
Interpreted as an armed attack under Article 76...
Self-defense troops can use force.
This doesn't qualify as an armed attack.
Article 76 stipulates "by an aggressor country or equivalent."
It's no time for semantics.
Only the SDF is equipped to respond.
That means soldiers engaging in urban combat.
That will give the Prime Minister pause.
We need an integrated response that involves both...
military force and civilian evacuation.
Declare a state of emergency.
Right now, our only extralegal measure
is mobilization for defense.
Only the Prime Minister can decide that.
You're talking...
a declaration with no precedent.
We'd be mobilizing the country for war.
The police can't handle an evacuation of this size.
But if we mobilize...
there is a likelihood of collateral damage.
I don't want that.
Can we get the US to kill this beast under the Security Treaty?
No. Our government and SDF must move first.
Even under the Treaty, the US can only provide support.
We're facing a living organism.
Aggravating it might only lead to more damage.
Yes, it's an organism.
That means we can stop it.
Unlike an earthquake or a typhoon.
Protecting citizens is our top priority.
It's a tough decision, Sir, but to prevent further calamity...
...your authorization is needed.
Right this instant?
Are you serious?
Time is precious. Your decision.
Moments ago, the Prime Minister...
declared a national state of emergency...
calling for the first ever mobilization of the Self Defense Forces.
And the first post-war military action since World War II
As an emergency "pest extermination", the order preempts direct approval.
Tokyo Metropolitan Government Building A (Ministry of Defense)
,
Nerima 1st division has been dispatched at Tokyo's Request.
Underground Command Room
,
They're tasked with guiding rescue and evacuation efforts.
But they're not equipped for battle.
Atsushi, Chief of the Ground Staff
,
Attack helicopters are the most expedient.
Contact Kisarazu base.
Ozawa, Chief of the Air Staff
,
Shall we deploy F-2's from Misawa?
No. Any civilian casualties could destroy the SDF forever.
Hamada, Joint Staff Commander
Let's minimize firepower.
Kitano, Chief of the Maritime Staff
,
But we don't know its strength.
I think we need to be ready.
Yajima, Joint Staff Deputy General
,
I agree. Let's recommend an integrated, 3 force operation.
Call the PM.
The joint force will be lead by the Eastern Army.
The goal, extermination.
With ground troops focused on evacuation...
Zaizen, Joint Staff General
,
Rapid response helicopters will be our primary attack force.
Sir, as it's in the city, some elderly and infirm may remain.
That's why I can't make a decision without an inspection.
Under such conditions, a little collateral damage is unavoidable.
Sir, it's not easy.
But we need a decision.
Understood.
Ground Self Defense Force Kisarazu Base, Chiba Prefecture
.
This is a risky, unplanned mission. Call for volunteers?
No, standard rotation. This is what we signed up for.
Fourth Anti-tank Helicopter Unit, Second Flying Squadron
.
Ground Self Defense Force AH-1S Attack Helicopter
Kisarazu lift off 13:08. ETA 13:20. Over.
Underground Access Elevator, Prime Minister's Office
,
What a relief. The creature may be big,
but this ought to do the trick.
Maybe we can rebuild the town with it's carcass.
Minister Yanagihara.
Wishful thinking and armchair theories
by the old Imperial Army in the last war
led to 3 million Japanese lives lost.
Beware of unfounded optimism.
Kitashinagawa
.
Please watch your step. Remain calm.
Get away from here quickly!
Local evacuation centers are useless.
Tell us where to send people!
The creature's progression has stopped!
Stopped?
Why all of sudden?
Incredible.
It's evolving.
Shinagawa Shrine
.
Kitashinagawa Station
Yatsuyama Rail Bridge
.
Attacker 1, this is CP. Over.
Copy CP, Attacker 1. Over.
Head to holding area 2 to await further orders.
Ashida, Second Flying Squadron Commander
,
Attacker 1, copy.
Second Flying Squadron Gunner
.
It's not like we were told.
CP, this is Attacker 1. Target differs from report.
Attacker 1, hold your position. Await instructions.
Resident evacuation is complete.
Understood.
Minister, we're ready to open fire.
Mr. Prime Minister. On your command.
Very well. Go ahead.
Attacker 1, commence fire on the creature.
I repeat, commence fire.
Copy CP. Commencing fire.
Target straight ahead. Aim for the head.
Distance 300. Ready, aim...
Hold your fire!
Why aren't they firing?
Ground Self Defense Force OH-1 Scout Helicopter
.
Civilians near the line of fire!
Fourth Anti-tank Helicopter Unit, Kisarazu Base
,
Civilians present. Can we fire?
Joint Task Force Central Command, Camp Asaka
,
Civilians present. Can we fire?
Ministry of Defense HQ, Central Command Post
,
Civilians present. Can we fire?
Crisis Management Center Conference Room, Prime Minister's Office
,
There are civilians. Can we proceed?
Can we proceed with firing?
Mr. Prime Minister!
Abort. Abort the attack!
Civilians must not receive fire!
Attacker 1, abort attack. To holding positions. Over.
Copy CP. Abort! Holding positions!
The creature is again on the move.
Breaking through the expressway, is headed towards Tokyo Bay
Ota Ward
.
All flights are canceled.
New fire outbreak in Shinagawa.
Most train lines running.
Pledges of support from overseas...
...more supplies and aid workers...
The Tokyo Exchange is open as usual...
The bullet train is operating shuttle services from Shin Yokohama.
Scientist envoys from France and other nations have arrived.
The creature has not been spotted in the Uraga Channel.
So the search zone is expanding.
The casualty count is up to 100 as a result of...
Fires in Ota Ward have been put out.
Disaster Management Minister Kasai leads an envoy
to survey and assess the damage.
Giant Unidentified Creature disaster site, Ota Ward
,
Government Damage Assessment Team
Giant Unidentified Creature disaster site, Ota Ward
It was only ashore for about 2 hours, and look what it did.
No.
We had as long as 2 hours to mount an initial response. Disappointing.
It was a surprise. Can't be helped.
Everyone did their best in the circumstances.
Don't get smug, Yaguchi.
It's time to meet the press. Mr. Minister, this way.
Understood.
Sagami Bay, Oshima Island vicinity
.
Maritime Self Defense Force Takanami-class destroyer Onami DD-111
Rotary Wing Patrol Helicopter SH-60K
.
Dipping sonar
We believe it submerged to the sea floor off Kanaya.
We're strengthening surveillance...
and patrols around Chiba and Sagami Bay.
But if it's hiding in Sagami Trough, detection's moot.
Who knows where or when it'll emerge?
How are preparations?
GSDF Camp Asaka, Nerima Ward
.
Joint Task Force Central Command
,
Once spotted, a rapid land strategy at water's edge will be difficult.
We'll need multiple plans
Yamaoka, Eastern Commander
for a landing point encounter and expeditionary pursuit.
Samejima, Eastern Director of Defense
,
I'll get right on it.
Coordinated artillery, tanks and F-2 scenarios.
Third Floor Entrance Hall, Prime Minister's Office
,
Defensive operations lean heavily on the Kanto area.
Cabinet Press Conference
,
The metro area has to take priority.
Looks like a 5th floor order.
What about the regions?
13 million people, GNP of 85 trillion yen.
That's 17% of the total.
And in the Kanto region? 40% and 200 trillion.
Seems like a prudent strategy to me.
Protecting a country isn't easy.
Deputy Chief Cabinet Secretary's office, Fifth Floor
,
They've set up a special response team in the PM's residence.
Fujinose restaurant, Akasaka District, Minato Ward
,
And I hear you were appointed its bureau chief.
You're rising in the world.
Rando Yaguchi, Deputy Director &
Cabinet Minister of State for Special Missions
,
Rando Yaguchi, Deputy Director &
Cabinet Minister of State for Special Missions
I want you to pick the team. You know bureaucrats.
Shuichi Izumi, Vice President of the Liberal Democratic Party
,
I'll round up people who'll speak their mind to the PM
Yeah. People with balls.
I'm Tachikawa.
Takeo.
Ready, lift.
Second Floor Conference Room
.
Giant Unknown Creature Crisis Management Headquarters
,
I'm Rando Yaguchi. We'll operate as a flat organization.
Forget about titles and seniority.
Speak freely here.
That's it.
I'm nominally in charge, but we're a crack team of...
lone wolves, nerds...
troublemakers, outcasts...
academic heretics and general pains-in-the-bureaucracy.
So do your thing.
Mori, Ministry of Health, Labor and Welfare Bureaucrat
,
Here are the basic specs.
Find out what you can.
Is this all?
Yup. We have to fill in the blanks.
If you have info, please share it.
Yesterday's "council of experts"...
were too baffled to conclude anything.
Hazama, Johoku University biologist
,
I put together a simple profile.
It's shown us 3 configurations.
More mutations coming.
There's more?
Yasuda, Basic Research Promotion Division Chief
,
We're analyzing a sample of its body fluid at our lab.
Pass some to me. I'll get outside help.
The US took all the remaining samples.
Sodehara, Joint Task Force Lt. Director General
,
On-site remains are being burned due to stench.
Komatsubara, Foreign Policy Director
,
Under American pressure, I hear.
Then we leave the analysis to you.
And from Behavioral Biology?
Behaviorally, it just seems to move.
Can't determine intellect.
I think communication with it is unlikely.
Tachikawa, Director of Nuclear Power
,
Simple question. What's its energy source?
It needs an enormous amount of energy.
Not just to move, but metabolically.
Oxygen conversion in its digestive tract wouldn't be enough.
All that energy.
Nuclear fission?
Sense of humor, Ms. Ogashira?
That's impossible.
Yokosuka Bay, Kanagawa Prefecture
.
A US carrier is leaving port?
We heard that Yokosuka City's radiation monitoring alarm went off.
I'll check with the Nuclear Regulation Authority.
Monitoring Department, Nuclear Regulation Authority, Minato Ward
,
I have orders not to go public yet.
But radiation levels in the metro area have risen.
Like a leak somewhere? A reactor?
Negishi, Nuclear Regulatory Authority Monitoring Manager
,
We've not found a leak at any of the nation's reactors.
Then where's it coming from?
Is that possible?
This data shows radiation spikes matching the creatures path.
Look here.
See?
Miss Ogashira was right.
Sorry.
"Why's the radiation meter reacting?"
This information is already spreading publicly.
Contact the Chief Secretary Cabinet.
Chief Cabinet Secretary's office, Fifth Floor, Prime Minister's Office
.
This is trouble.
The PM needs to call a press conference.
Morito, Secretary to the Chief Cabinet Secretary
,
Without proof it's radioactive,
we might end up stoking public fear unnecessarily.
It's not enough of a spike to warrant evacuation.
There are no legal grounds to it.
It's still a matter of radioactivity.
The sooner, the better.
That's right. I'll meet the press.
Let me talk to the PM.
Schedule a Prime Minister's briefing. Five minutes.
Japan-US heads of state conference call
,
Yes, President Ross, I understand. Thank you.
A lot of unilateral demands.
Typically American.
An Assistant Deputy chief to the US President.
wants a secret meeting with the PM.
They move fast.
Yeah.
He just left Yokota Air Base.
Foreign Ministry's in a uproar.
I hear his aide made an appointment with you.
With me? Why?
Kayoco Anne-Patterson, Special Presidential Envoy
,
I read your administrations reports.
I need a person I can work with.
Someone with an interesting history. That's you.
I'm honored, but I think you want Prime Minister aide Akasaka.
He turned me down already.
I need a favor that won't stain my record.
I want you to find someone.
Who may that be?
A man who foresaw your creature's appearance several years ago.
Interested? We know he landed in Narita 7 days ago.
Goro Maki.
Japanese. Former college professor.
I hear your intelligence agency is first-rate.
What's in it for us?
A trade. We gathered intel you might want.
But let's keep it bilateral, okay?
Just US-Japan, so, win-win.
Understood. Let's get to it.
Thank you. I rushed to Yokota straight from
a party, so I didn't have time to change.
Where's Zara?
Kayoco Anne Patterson.
She's very young.
America admirably values performance over age.
And she's Senator Patterson's daughter.
The one behind the Kern Agreement. Formidable.
A mixture of talent, pedigree and coattails.
Not really your type, I suspect.
Nope.
If she unabashedly uses her father's connections...
...she's the political type, like Yaguchi.
Tokyo Central Government Building Two, Chiyoda Ward
.
Commissioner-General Secretariat, National Police Agency
,
Searching for an individual at a time like this?
For Rando Yaguchi.
I owe a great debt to his father.
As many agents as you need.
Sawaguchi, Commissioner's Secretariat
,
This is his profile.
Motobe, Criminal Affairs Director
,
A rebellious elderly professor once expelled from Japan.
Although a biologist, he worked at a US energy firm.
Interesting old man.
A red flag?
No. Just locate him.
The NSA or CIA will take it from there.
Discreetly, I hear.
His last whereabouts.
My grandma's country sure works fast.
But he's gone missing.
The Coast Guard found his boat adrift at sea.
Ms. Patterson.
Were you looking for him? Or this?
Yeah, that too.
"I did as I pleased. You do the same."
His last words?
Confirm the contents?
No need.
I trust you.
Special ink. Can't be copied.
I'll take photos to share with my team.
Godzilla?
That's right. It's the DOE's code name. "Godzilla".
He gave it an English name.
Gojira.
What does it mean?
I got one hit.
On Ohdo Island, where he's from, it means "God incarnate".
A violent one. I hear that's why he put "God" in the name.
In Japanese, the name read "Gojira."
"Gojira"...
...you say?
Who cares about its name at this point?
It's just as well it originated in the US.
Now we know what to call it.
The government is unofficially calling the giant creature "Gojira."
National Diet Building Gardens, Chiyoda Ward
.
Goro Maki?
Ex-biology professor at Jonan U.
Find out who he was.
You'll get an exclusive when the time's right to go to print.
That's a promise.
Hayafune, Freelance Journalist
,
Yes, I know.
Sixty years ago.
So this is all about unregulated dumping of radioactive material.
Don't tell me...
Gojira fed on these.
Yes.
That's the DOE's conclusion.
They sent requests to various institutions
to analyze the containers.
Dr. Maki was the main figure.
Suddenly, an ancient species of marine life
found itself surrounded by radioactive waste.
And rapidly mutated into an organism that could withstand it.
That's his Godzilla theory.
But it's body lengthened when it came ashore.
Yes.
It can suddenly mutate, from sea organism to land.
This new Godzilla surpasses anything I imagined.
This is all the information at my disposal.
What comes next...
Personal service.
What Dr. Maki left behind.
I can't make sense of it.
It's not a molecular array. How does it relate to Gojira?
Perhaps an analytical table of structural layers.
Dr. Maki intentionally left out some final data.
We now have the complete version.
Do you mind if we analyze it?
Sure.
I'm bad at Japanese honorifics. Can we go informal?
Okay, then tell me...
What does the US want with Gojira? Study or exterminate?
That's for the president to decide.
Who decides in your country?
Prime Minister's Signature
.
Cabinet Approved Victim Relief and Reconstruction Bill
Fourth Floor Hallway
,
Finally a cabinet decision on the relief and recovery bill.
The Gojira bill, too, will be an interagency nightmare.
Lack of precedent will cloud orders.
Expect a lot of passing the buck.
Second Floor Hallway
At least the security bill passed easily.
Foreign Ministry muscle, under US pressure.
The US wants to use its Gojira info as a diplomatic card.
Let's pray our crafty Aide Akasaka can handle the White House.
Results of the disaster site analysis.
.
Gamma rays match no known elements whatsoever.
It's incredible... Gojira, is it?
Its body harbors new elements.
This is why the US Dept. of Energy moved so quickly.
Let's take this data with us. Call the PM.
Understood.
More troubling complications.
So...
...how much do we say?
Having fully analyzed substances recovered from Gojira's path...
...radiation of 0,5 microsieverts in the stricken area.
Thanks for the food.
Yes, thank you.
Even with the information the US shared,
I feel gridlock coming.
Yeah. Riken's report had impact.
Gojira has eight times the genetic info of humans.
It'll take years to sequence all of it.
Gojira's the most evolved creature on the planet.
Capable of self-mutation. Not generational.
That trumps human intelligence.
It's still mortal. It can be killed.
I sure hope so.
That's what we're here to find out.
Any clues into its behavior?
It just walks
Why did it suddenly decide to return to Tokyo Bay?
I got it.
Cooling.
Gojira has something of a nuclear reactor on its body.
Its fins are heat vents, meaning it has a blood-cooling system.
So it retrogressed to sea creature temporarily
to adjust its body temperature after mutating.
Maybe our only hope is to shut down
its internal cooling system.
Forcing Gojira to do a reactor scram to stay alive.
Rapid cooling may not kill him, but could immobilize him.
Machida, METI Manufacturing Director
,
Like administering a blood coagulation drug.
Is it possible with Gojira upright?
We'll examine practical methods.
Perhaps a compression pump.
Takeo, MLIT Disaster Management & Transport Safety Deputy Director
We, the health ministry and METI,
will gather the necessary coagulant and equipment.
Submit it to the PM as the "Yaguchi Plan."
Understood.
Name aside, let's get on it.
"Godzilla is God!"
"Save Godzilla!"
Good morning, Tea?
Thank you.
Thank you!
I think we all could use a break.
Deputy Chief Cabinet Secretary's office guests
,
Everyone is collaborating voluntarily.
They don't go home to rest, not even when they are asked to.
And if they do, they come back early with warm food for everyone.
It's very inspiring.
None of that jurisdictional infighting among ministries.
Just people working together.
A lot of outsiders have tirelessly volunteered their time, too.
You're right.
There's hope for this country yet.
Truly.
One question, though.
When did you last change your shirt?
To be honest, it smells a little rank.
Really?
A shower would do you good.
Gojira has resurfaced in Sagami Bay!
And it's coming ashore!
Cape Inamura, Kamakura City, Kanagawa Prefecture
.
J-Alert! Broadcast that Gojira has come ashore!
Primary alert over Em-Net transmitted!
This is Kamakura Disaster Prevention.
This is an emergency evacuation order.
A colossal-sized, unidentified creature has come ashore.
Everyone is urged to evacuate the city immediately.
Repeat. Evacuate immediately.
Please follow the instructions of police and fire personnel.
The Prime Minister.
Gojira is moving towards Kamariya.
Am I crazy or has it gotten bigger?
Beyond expectation.
Different face and body.
Yes. His size has nearly doubled.
Gojira's evolved into it's fourth form.
This will be disastrous.
Yokodai, Isogo Ward, Yokohama City, Kanagawa Prefecture
,
Citizens, take refuge indoors!
This area is under curfew.
You are in the designated evacuation zone.
Your attention, citizens!
Gojira expected to reach Tokyo in three hours.
Tsukuda, Minister of Justice
,
Why's it coming here again?
Ogimachi, Kawasaki City, Kanagawa Prefecture
.
A direct armed assault on its body
runs the risk of releasing radioactive material.
Preventing its progression into the metro region is top priority.
I hear it lives on radioactive material.
If it attacks a nuclear facility,
it'll spell a worse disaster.
Prime Minister.
We must stop him now.
And we don't want to be viewed overseas as timid.
How goes your Yaguchi Plan?
Regrettably, it's not ready yet.
Give the order and the SDF will do its job.
The declared state of emergency is still in effect.
You have...
...the power to order the attack.
Sir.
I know.
Commence.
Yes, Sir.
Contact command.
Yes.
The order's come through.
Assume unrestricted weapon use.
We are to do whatever it takes
to keep Gojira out of Tokyo.
Operation B if it rises at Kanagawa.
Make Kawasaki the primary battleground.
Miki, Eastern Army Deputy Chief of Joint Staff
And Tama River as the absolute defense line.
Good luck.
Air Self Defense Force Misawa Air Base, Aomori
,
Taxi to holding point B1, Runaway 10.
Runway 10, cleared for takeoff.
Mitsubishi F-2 Fighter Jet
Ground Self Defense Force Kisarazu Base, Chiba
.
Attack formation reports 5 miles west.
Ground Self Defense Force Tachikawa Base, Tokyo
.
P0304 embark from Tachikawa 15:36.
Maruko Bridge on the Tama River bank, Ota Ward, Tokyo
,
Tanks and artillery deploying at Maruko Bridge.
Roger. Ready to attack.
Please succeed.
Tamagawa Sengen Shrine, Ota Ward
,
Eight minutes to target contact.
We're really engaging on a live fire?
Relax. Just like in the drills.
Operation Command Post, Tamagawa Sengen Shrine
,
Target contains radioactive material.
Pinpoint your attack on the head and legs.
Saigo, Operation Field Commander (First Regiment)
,
Ready all battalions.
Target approaching. ETA in three minutes.
1st to 4th chopper squadrons arriving.
GSDF Anti-tank Helicopter Squadron
,
C01, this is CP. Over.
Copy CP, C01 over.
C01, this is CP.
P01 in flight over Musashi-Kosugi, holding at BP1.
P02 to P04, behind towers.
Standby at Holding Area 2. Over.
Musashi-Kosugi station vicinity, Kawasaki City, Kanagawa Prefecture
C01, ready to engage at PP1.
Target distance 1,200 meters.
Roger. Maintain position. Over.
helicopter reconnaissance complete.
Total area evacuation confirmed.
You're sure this time, Koriyama? No stragglers?
I must trust the report from the field.
The target advances.
Sir, authorize the use of force.
I authorize the use of force.
Order is confirmed.
Commence firing.
Commence Phase 1.
Commence fire. Repeat. Commence fire. Over.
C01, copy. Commencing fire.
Togawa, Fourth Anti-tank Helicopter Squadron Commander
,
Ready... fire!
Autocannon direct hits, ineffective.
Switch to Apache 30mm. Give it a shot.
GSDF Rotary Wing AH-64D Apache Longbow
.
3rd squadron in reconnaissance. Report on effectiveness!
3rd squadron engaged. Target fine. No effect.
16,000 rounds of machine gun fire.
Not even a scratch.
Get HQ and the PM.
The Commander request permission to use missiles.
It's a dense area, but we've no choice.
I hereby authorize the use of all...
...necessary weapons.
C01, switch assault to missiles.
When ready, fire them all. Over!
Roger! P01 to P01, change weapons system to missiles!
Target straight ahead 700 meters.
Ready... fire!
Launch all missiles! Give him hell!
All direct hits. But no visible damage sustained.
Even missiles don't work?
What is it?
Its skin is too tough to pierce.
We'll shift to Phase 2.
Commence Phase 2 of the operation.
Commence fire. Repeat. Commence fire.
GSDF Type 10 Tanks First Tank Squadron
Roger. This is Tiger 1. Commence fire.
,
GSDF Type 10 Tanks First Tank Squadron
Type 10 tanks, aim for target's legs. Concentrated barrage.
Ikeda, First Tank Squadron Commander
.
Commence fire now!
Distance good. Fire!
Direct hit! Keep firing!
Target speed has decreased!
Good. Commence artillery fire!
GSDF Type 99 155mm Self-propelled Howitzer
.
Time on target 10, 9, 8...
7, 6, 5, 4, 3... Impact now!
All hit target. Fusillade. Fire!
GSDF Type 96 Multi-Purpose Missile System
.
Target is entering the Tama River!
Tell Gotemba to commence attack.
GSDF Camp Fuji, Shizuoka Prefecture
.
Multiple Launch Rocket System M270 MLRS
Target has halted!
Move to Phase 3. Start the aerial assault.
Type 10 tanks, shift to Phase 3.
All tanks to new positions. Repeat...
Cleared for attack.
Fire,
ready...
now.
Bombs away.
Laser on.
Target is turning northwest. Repeat. Northwest!
It's turning away?
Is it working?
JDAM 2nd wave.
This will finish it.
Yes!
Murasaki, Second Tank Squadron Commander
.
Tanks retreat!
Evacuate!
Target has crossed into Tokyo!
ACP, C01... Choppers out of munitions!
Munitions exhausted!
Tiger 1, this is 40. Visibility zero.
This is Tiger 1.
8 squads out of ammo.
3 tanks severely damaged, 2 crippled. Over.
Forward command post destroyed! Target's breached the defense line.
Defensive position has collapsed.
Yamamoto, Joint Task Force First Commander Joint Staff Vice Chief
.
It's still within artillery range.
Let's continue!
No. Those wards are not fully evacuated.
I'm afraid that's all we can do.
Understood.
Operation suspended.
I'm sorry we couldn't even halt it.
Don't lose hope. It's our job to protect the people.
An offensive isn't the only way. Speed up evacuations.
The operation failed. Gojira is on the move again.
The SDF's full power was futile.
Incredible self-preservation ability.
If standard weapons worked, we wouldn't be here.
A perfect organism surpassing Man.
Meguro Ward, Tokyo
.
Target is entering Meguro Ward!
Let's petition US troops for aid in taking it down.
From the American ambassador.
The USAF confirms bombers on their way.
US Air Force 509th Bomb Wing B-2 Spirit Stealth Bomber
.
Submit a formal cooperation request.
I'll meet with the ambassador.
I'll hold a press conference on the subject.
We've requested aid by US forces in Japan
In fighting Gojira based on the Japan-US Security Treaty
The proposed US bombing zone.
It's this large? It'll be worse than Gojira.
We'll need to evacuate people underground.
Atagoshita Avenue, Minato Ward
,
The US military will launch an attack on Gojira.
Evacuate to subways and underground arcades!
Sengaku-ji Station, Asakusa Subway Line
.
Don't push!
This residence is in Gojira's path.
The SDF failed to stop it.
The US military may also.
Are you saying evacuate from here?
Yes. Other key functions, too, must go immediately
to a secondary facility in Tachikawa.
The US strike is about to begin.
I have a duty to stay and monitor its execution.
I can't abandon the citizens to make my escape.
Mr. Prime Minister. You can leave because you've the nation to protect.
Please evacuate.
Tokyo city hall is still functioning.
For now, let Governor Kozuka take charge.
Understood.
2 helicopters will arrive on the roof.
We'll go by car.
Okay. Go ahead. It'll take some time.
Traffic will be murder.
We'll meet later.
Okay. I'll crawl if I have to.
A mandatory evacuation order has been issued. Please vacate at once.
Sotobori Avenue, Akasaka, Minato Ward
.
Gridlock. Traffic's not going to move.
The strike is coming. We need to get everyone out.
So that's Gojira.
The strike will occur ahead of schedule.
US Air Force Massive Ordnance Penetrator (MOPII)
.
Roof heliport, PM's Office
,
MOP II bombs struck on target. It's confirmed bleeding!
Iki, Ministry of Defense Secretary
.
This may work!
Way to go, USA.
Sir. The helicopter is arriving.
A2 Exit, Akasaka 5-chome Station, Minato Ward
,
Take it easy! Underground!
What's that glow?
GSDF Rotary Wing Eurocopter EC-225LP Transport Helicopter
.
Gojira's back seems to be glowing. No further details.
To do what?
Nobody around.
Get inside Deputy.
Highway 16, Fussa City
,
There was an emergency call from Japan's airbase.
US Ambassador to Japan
.
8-2 number 1 seems to have been down.
US Ambassador official vehicle
,
But there's no way. That's impossible!
Godzilla. Truly a god incarnate.
The target is shooting some unidentified weapon from the front.
Bomber 2 and Bomber 3 will circle in from behind.
Payback time. Roger. Payback.
Transporting the PM and 8 others to Tachikawa-
Hamamatsucho, Minato Ward
.
Shimbashi, Minato Ward
Ginza Fourth Street intersection, Chuo Ward
.
Toranomon, Minato Ward
Kasumigaseki, Chiyoda Ward
.
Nagatacho, Chiyoda Ward
Tokyo Station, Chiyoda Ward
.
High levels of radiation are projected.
People are urged  to remain indoors for at least 49 hours...
How much radiation has Gojira released on Tokyo?
Don't wait for the government. Decide here.
I hear radioactivity is high.
Will they distribute iodine tablets?
Nuclear, biological and chemical response teams are being deployed.
For decontamination and rescue.
The Prime Minister, Cabinet Secretary and 5 ministers have gone missing.
Police headquarters and 2 ministries remain intact.
Homeless city refugees are estimated to be in the millions.
Government officials are hoping to avoid a political vacuum.
Party members are selecting an acting Prime Minister.
,
With the PM Residence in danger, government headquarters...
Tachikawa Wide Area Disaster Prevention Base, Provisional HQ
are being moved to Tachikawa city away from the city center.
,
Deputy Chief Yaguchi! I'll call back.
Mr. Izumi.
I'm glad you're safe.
To think that going home on Friday saved me.
You're injured. You all right?
Sorry. Bandages are in short supply.
That's okay. No big deal.
Tokyo is directing fire and rescue.
No Internal Ministry.
,
Let the police handle refugees.
Special Disaster Bureau Provisional HQ Operation Room
,
They'll survive one night.
Rumors will fly, so get a jump on the press.
Provisional HQ Staff Room
,
I need information. Where's Gojira?
Inactive near Tokyo Station. Who knows why.
Radiation levels?
The Nuclear Regulation Authority personnel are busy getting readings.
Gojira's dripping radiation from its mouth...
but only trace amounts.
Hisamatsu, Nation-First Party Deputy Chairman Public Secretary
,
Its plume blew out to sea...
but contamination is widespread.
The hard-hit wards are uninhabitable.
On top of being contaminated.
Well conditions are pretty grave...
We lack manpower, materials and legal infrastructure.
They're all dead.
The Prime Minister, Chief Cabinet Secretary, everybody.
Don't go to pieces!
We'll make do with the survivors!
Yaguchi...
Calm yourself first.
I'm sorry.
Who's the acting PM?
Evacuation center (Unoshima Elementary Gym), Kazo City, Saitama
The ruling party has named Agriculture Minister, Yusuke Satomi
as Acting Prime Minister.
He will head a provisional emergency government...
Evacuation center (Nishi-nakamachi public center), Isesaki City, Gunma
,
quickly naming a new cabinet...
to fill the political vacuum.
Giant Unidentified Creature Response Task Force HQ
,
So a man with factional seniority,
and whose loyalty made him a minister,
is now the Prime Minister.
I hear it was foisted on him by the party secretary.
Who wants responsibility at a time like this?
Director's Office, Special Disaster Bureau Provisional HQ, Tachikawa City
,
Some disturbing movement near Tsushima Island.
Kazakoshi, Executive Secretary to the Prime Minister
,
I suppose we'll have to wait and see.
Can the Foreign Ministry act?
Katayama, Acting Foreign Affairs Minister
,
We're still getting up and running.
At any rate, just try to avoid unforeseen surprises.
I'll let the ambassador know.
Yusuke Satomi, Acting Prime Minister
,
The noodles got soggy.
I knew this job wouldn't be easy.
Satomi is a hard man to read.
Whoever the PM, our job is to keep the ship afloat.
We need an emergency legislation.
We're only 30 kilometers from where Gojira's sleeping.
I'm not worried about that anymore.
This country's good at quickly picking a successor.
You next?
No way.
I'm thinking 10 years.
If Japan's still around, run for office.
I'll support you... in exchange for a party secretary post.
Akasaka was at Yokota, so he was saved.
A politician needs strategy and luck.
Now he's Chief Cabinet Secretary.
You could be more ambitious.
The Disaster Bureau is a unique path, though...
You're practically in charge.
Rando Yaguchi, Deputy Director, Cabinet Minister of State for Special Missions
& Giant Unidentified Creature Unified Response Task Force HQ Bureau Chief
,
Rando Yaguchi, Deputy Director, Cabinet Minister of State for Special Missions
& Giant Unidentified Creature Unified Response Task Force HQ Bureau Chief
No, I'm here to take the fall, if needed.
Akasaka's a shrewd delegator.
You're the next new aide to the PM on a career track.
What's wrong with that?
Why'd you become a politician?
Because it's just friend or foe. I like the simplicity.
Bureau members have arrived.
Special Disaster Bureau Provisional HQ Office
.
It's great to see you all.
Over half of our team has returned. Thank you.
Our hearts are heavy for those we lost.
Let's do it for them.
We'll fill their positions.
While we struggle
with the loss of colleagues and loved ones.
We can prevail!
For our countrymen.
I ask you to pour heart and soul into completing our work.
I beg you.
Let's get to work!
Tachikawa Wide Area Disaster Prevention Base
.
Preliminary conference room
How's the freeze plan going?
Private companies are working on 24 blood procoagulants...
using silica, thrombin and other agents.
One of them should work.
How about samples?
Hiromi Ogashira, Ministry of the Environment Deputy Chief, Wildlife Division
,
We've asked GSDF to retrieve some living cells for us.
GSDF Nuclear, Biological and Chemical Reconnaissance Vehicle
.
Roger that.
Samples retrieved.
I'll send them to BSL4 labs.
Good
Remainder to any P3 level lab, public or private.
These are government-classified substances.
We need diverse info on Gojira.
No change to radiation levels. Below 1 Sievert.
Roof of Kabukiza Tower, Chuo Ward
,
He's a quiet sleeper
It's storing it all up in its belly.
GSDF Central Nuclear Biological Special Weapon Defense Unit Eleven
,
Shift change.
Yaguchi.
Arriving in 5. Secure us a meeting with the acting PM, will you?
Is that right?
Yes. There's a movement centered on China and Russia,
to take Godzilla from under the control of the Japanese government
and put it under the control of international organizations.
Many countries are aligned with that opinion, too.
However, as for the US government, we strongly hope
that Japan and the US can perfectly control Godzilla together.
Hideki Akasaka, Acting Chief Cabinet Secretary
(Former Aide to the Prime Minister)
.
Hideki Akasaka, Acting Chief Cabinet Secretary
(Former Aide to the Prime Minister)
Ok.
From the government point of view,
it is for that reason that we would agree to a 2-plus 2 cooperation.
However, as army experts will remain as the  backbone of the government.
We have to respectfully decline your offer
to remain at the center of decision-making.
In place of that, we will...
A US-Japan Gojira research coalition?
The more knowledge, the better. Lets clear some space.
Nice to meet you. I'm Rando Yaguchi.
US Godzilla Joint Research Team
.
From GSDF's latest unmanned surveillance system.
It froze soon after the attack.
Same as the D2 simulation.
Richter, Joint Research Team Leader
,
Just as I thought...
It appears that Godzilla has something like a built in phased-array radar.
So it can instinctively intercept approaching objects.
US air strike grounds, Minato Ward
.
GSDF First Special Weapons Defense Unit
,
Squad 2, this is CV1.
5 minutes from point zero. 10 minutes remain. Over.
Copy that, CV1.
Cross-referenced field data with Tsukuba's...
this may be how Gojira plans to propagate.
Rapid colonization all over the world.
So not only could it evolve to a smaller size...
it could sprout wings capable of intercontinental flight.
Let's go
And that will mark the end of the human race.
Before that happens, using our nuclear wisdom
is the only road for salvation for mankind.
Are you serious?
Tama Monorail Operation Base, Tachikawa City, Tokyo
.
The Defense Secretary thinks its best to hit Gojira...
with a thermonuclear blast.
And the White House?
A report cites a 13% chance of Gojira landing on the US west coast.
The UN Security Council has set up a multinational Gojira strike force.
The US is serious.
Afraid so.
They say Gojira has to be hit with a nuclear missile.
The Pentagon's already moved to set explosive yield...
and burst level for a B83 warhead.
To be dropped on Tokyo?
I was ordered to evacuate.
I see.
So it's highly likely.
Yes.
But I'm not leaving.
I won't see a third bomb...
dropped on the country of my mother, and live through it.
Japan-US heads of state conference call
,
Certainly. We'll act accordingly, President Ross.
Matsuzawa, Minister of Foreign Affairs
,
Certainly, we'll act accordingly that way, President Ross.
Well, you heard it.
That country foists some crazy things on us.
That is certain.
But this goes too far!
I agree.
Call the Chief Cabinet Secretary.
Yes.
The UN Security Council has passed a resolution...
for a US led force
to exterminate Gojira.
As party to the resolution and participant...
our nation will be under its command.
In other words...
I'm going to need a special law...
vesting the Prime Minister with full powers.
Authorizing...
the use of a nuclear weapon on Tokyo?
I didn't want to go down in history for anything like this.
Tachikawa Wide Area Disaster Prevention Base rooftop
.
From here on, Gojira comes under US led, UN jurisdiction.
Post-War Japan is a tributary state.
"Post-War" extends forever...
You mustn't give up.
No creature can withstand
the million-degree heat of a nuke.
As a sure method of extermination, it's the right choice.
We're on the edge of a breakthrough...
with our freezing method.
Your plan still has too many unknowns.
Plus, all countries have pledged their support.
to a complete rebuilding effort if we sign on.
If we can't kill Gojira with certainty...
...we lose the world's trust.
We must put our fate in the UN's hands.
My job is to think about what to do for Japan
after Gojira has been destroyed.
Right now the damage is limited to three wards.
They can be rebuilt.
The city's economy is in a free fall.
If bonds and stocks continue to plummet...
The nation with go into default.
Japan needs international sympathy and funding.
Scrap and build, huh?
To save the country.
There's no other way.
Yaguchi.
This is the reality. All else is just a dream.
A thermonuclear bomb?
Dropped here?
We just gave the UN its sanction.
Unbelievable.
How do we know it hasn't made itself immortal?
The choice is incinerate with a nuke; or freeze with a drug.
Yes, that is a choice. But not a good one.
Man is more frightening than Gojira.
The UN coalition will of course give time for evacuation.
That's our window for finishing.
We got something that worked well on the samples.
Now comes production.
To freeze all of its blood...
we'll need 672 kiloliters of coagulant.
I'm securing facilities as we speak.
Can we make it?
We have to!
Don't give up. Don't abandon this country.
Ask every private chemical company you know...
to open every line possible.
I'll send all pertinent data.
Ask everyone to finish production by tomorrow.
We're getting broad cross-checking.
Spreading knowledge works.
Logistics for police and MLIT to ship the coagulant.
I'll do that.
I need METI to coordinate pump makers.
If we agree to buy them...
Shanghai will give us 3 tank trucks.
We need 5 more wheel loaders, any size.
Ambassador Lansing
just reported coalition projections...
that Gojira's energy beam...
will be restored within 360 hours to previous levels.
Shuichi Izumi, Acting Special Advisor to the Prime Minister
,
Matsuzawa, Minister of Foreign Affairs
The creature is likely to resume activity in 15 days.
I see.
US Forces Japan Yokota Air Base Command HQ, Fussa City
,
A charter home will be leaving in an hour.
All remaining staff, prepare to leave immediately.
Cartland, US Army Colonel
,
The start time for the nuclear strike against Godzilla has been decided.
Countdown will begin in 5 minutes.
Paine, US Forces Commander
So it's too late to turn back now.
Lansing, US Ambassador to Japan
,
Japan has been given a two-week grace period in order to
in order to evacuate remaining residents.
That may seem long for the Allied Forces, but it's too short for Japan.
Evacuation means uprooting people from their beloved homes.
Don't make it sound so easy.
Agreed.
Evacuating 3.6 million people? Preposterous!
We don't have the manpower.
Not to mention millions more in neighboring prefectures.
The governor protests the sacrifice of Tokyo.
This is a national decision, not a municipal one.
Relocation selection and approvals can't happen in 2 weeks.
The moment Gojira resumes activity...
the strike time will move up unconditionally.
Regardless of collateral risk.
A thermonuclear warhead will be launched from a sub at that time...
as per the coalition decision.
What bull! Easy for them to talk about far-off Asia.
If it were in NY, they say the same would apply.
Evacuation bus depot, Taito Ward
.
Central Expressway, Hachioji City
Port of Yokohama, Yokohama City, Kanagawa Prefecture
.
GSDF Kisarazu Base, Chiba Prefecture
Over 3.6 million Tokyo refugees evacuated to locations nationwide
Showa Memorial Park, Tachikawa City, Tokyo
,
Land prices are soaring in west Japan. Food is short.
Kanto area companies and shops are shuttered.
City's full of the unemployed.
The yen's plunge reflects investor fears...
...except from those profiting from it.
People come in all forms.
You have information?
I do. It's my job after all.
How about printing my article a day prior to the bomb drop?
New Gojira material.
In exchange, we can control the announcement timing.
How's that?
I understand.
The professor loathed the radiation sickness that took his wife's life.
He hoped to render radioactive materials harmless.
If that's possible, so is the creation of a new material.
He must have feared the military.
That explains his redacting the DOE data.
He hated radioactive materials.
And maybe anyone involved with it.
Including Japan, which left his wife to die.
Then he leaves his data and writes, "Do as you like"?
Strange person.
So what did he do in the end?
Good meal.
Solve the chart yet?
Not even with help from a cryptographer.
Anything from the US?
I wouldn't rely on them right now.
We regard it as important for a multi-tiered approach.
It resembles a mandala more than a chemical schematic.
Or working backwards from the solution.
He was a little twisted.
I'm even baffled by its simple lines.
Why did he put it on paper, not data?
Perhaps it's meant to be folded.
With a body like Gojira's...
old radioactive waste must leave it hungry.
No doubt.
Crooked teeth. It can't even prey on nuclear waste.
Origami.
It's not eaten.
We grasped the entire pattern.
The new information came from making folds.
We focused on radiation as its energy.
This is a molecular chart for converting elements in the body.
Element conversion molecules.
The unknown radioactive isotope is the proof.
Say hydrogen or nitrogen entering the cell...
where it's converted to necessary molecules.
Gojira's a mixotroph with an organ that converts decaying heat.
A bold but viable hypothesis.
It can live anywhere there is water or oxygen.
Like an ascetic surviving on mist.
So Gojira's is both a threat to mankind...
but also poses a revelation of limitless potential.
But then the blood coagulant may be ineffective inside its body...
killing the Yaguchi Plan.
Possibly. So what now?
we raise certainty of working.
First, analyze this structure, then a way around it.
I'm having supercomputers run parallel analysis...
but the results are days away.
We've only got 10.
I asked MEXT to use their global connections.
Burghead Computer Science Laboratory, Germany
,
Call from Japan.
They're requesting parallel computing.
We can't.
This is a closed system. We can't risk our data being stolen.
Come, come. Where's your trust in your fellow men?
Tell them we'd be happy to do it!
Supercomputer cluster
.
We've solved Maki's riddle!
Here.
Incredible.
It's not the cell membrane itself.
But an extremophile configuration that inhibits cell membrane activity.
This inhibitor could keep the blood coagulant viable.
There's still hope.
It looks good.
Okay.
Tachikawa Wide Area Disaster Prevention Base rooftop
,
I get the feeling Goro Maki anticipated this.
Maybe releasing this destructive God as a sort of test...
on mankind, this country, we Japanese.
"Do as you like", including the use of nuclear weapons.
Maybe so.
"Do as you please", huh?
But...
that's hard to do in this country.
It is.
By oneself.
Sir, we're ironing out the last kinks on the Yaguchi Plan.
We ask your approval to deploy it.
Yes, but Izumi.
A UN resolution is already passed.
Some say that the US seeks a quick resolution
to bury their knowledge of Gojira.
We know that!
And you know our country's condition.
But Sir...
...forcing one country's sacrifice for self-gain is deplorable.
So you're saying...
...act unilaterally on humanitarian principle.
Perhaps it's time we did as we wanted.
You're right.
So, where do I affix my stamp.
GSDF Reception Room, Tachikawa Wide Area Disaster Prevention Base
,
"A strategy to administer a coagulate"
"to freeze and thus render the creature immobile."
It's long-winded.
What do we call it?
Operation "Yashiori", after the sake Susanowo used to put a hydra to sleep.
Very well. We'll run it in 5 phases.
Asaka is working on details.
Vehicle operation...
and explosives drills have already been conducted.
We're execution ready.
Many thanks.
No need.
It's our job.
Countdown's at 2 days.
Damn.
I still need three days to make enough coagulant.
Can't the countdown be suspended?
Who in the Security Council can we get to help stall?
Not China and Russia. Too geopolitically close.
How about France? Nuclear country. They'd be interested in  the biology.
I have a back channel I can use.
Please.
I'll try the Euro Bureau Chief.
And I the Foreign Minister.
We need 24 more hours!
Chartered plane, US Forces Japan Yokota Air Base, Fussa City
France has petitioned to interrupt the countdown.
,
Chartered plane, US Forces Japan Yokota Air Base, Fussa City
China and Russia are opposed, but we're maintaining silence.
,
Cussing, US Official
China and Russia are opposed, but we're maintaining silence.
That's because it isn't just hardliners
at the nucleus of Washington and the Pentagon.
Japan has grown up enough
to have international trade deals on the sly.
Dangerous in another opportunity for personal growth.
Our friends are progressing with an effective deep freeze plan.
I think this country is betting on it.
And you're rising that bet also, I see.
Nuclear weapons are a deterrent.
I've been trying to advise Charles against it.
But it goes against the flow of the mainstream.
And you and I must bear the risk of retaliation.
Me, I'm ok.
But you, with your fastidious career,
and the Patterson name, mud will stick.
And your dream of becoming President in your 40s will disappear.
Hey, Kayoko!
Good luck.
Yeah.
Science Museum roof, Kitanomaru Park, Chiyoda Ward
,
A joint US strategy?
Science Museum First Floor
.
Raise the chance of success.
Can our independent commands be coordinated?
You've made friends.
Lots of Air Force and Marine volunteers.
Even drones if you need it. What do you say?
I'm in.
But there is no guarantee of them coming back in one piece.
Of course. I'll bill the Japanese government later.
SBPCPC Kanto Chemical Plant, Tsukuba City, Ibaraki
,
We scraped together enough inhibitors.
Quickly send some tankers to pick them up.
Port of Kisarazu, Kisarazu City, Chiba Prefecture
.
Material and coagulant is shippable and operation ready.
Give HQ the green light.
GSDF HQ, Tachikawa Wide Area Disaster Prevention Base
,
Won't you reconsider accompanying the front line troops?
A political decision may be needed.
And time will be critical.
Too risky. Policymakers can direct from the rear.
You want to be PM in 10 years?
Got to make sure the country's around in 10 years.
we've got the young talent, public and private.
Like you. We'll have leaders.
You've kept me going. Thanks.
Nonsense. Thank Akasaka's mentoring.
Good luck.
Save me Party Secretary.
GSDF Heliport
.
Operation Yashiori, private sector cooperation
GSDF Special Machinery Company
.
In this Operation Yashiori...
there's a high risk of acute exposure to radiation heat.
I cannot promise that all will be safe
But your work will matter!
Our country's greatest strength is found in the field.
The SDF is the last fortress able to protect the country.
We place Japan's future in your hands.
Godspeed.
Roll out!
Yes!
Operation Yashiori Forward Command, Science Museum rooftop
.
Northwest wind, 2 meters.
Plume should blow out to the bay minimizing impact.
All platoons standing by.
The US attack drone squadron...
in designated holding pattern.
Tanba, 32nd Infantry Regiment Commander
,
All systems are go, Chief.
Awaiting word from Tokyo of evacuation completion.
We've only got one shot at this. Going ahead.
Tell local governments to enforce curfew order.
Roger. Alert Kanto area municipalities.
Have them issue a 50-hour indoor confinement curfew for all citizens.
Roger.
Train car detachment, passing zero point.
Commence Operation Yashiori.
Phase 1 diversion, begin!
N700 Series Bullet Train (unmanned)
.
Diversion success!
Train blasts effective! Operation, Phase 2.
Begin aerial assault!
USAF Fifth Air Force 309th Intelligence Squadron
,
Copy. Contact US Forces.
Command, this is Bravo 1. Target in sight, engaging.
USAF Unmanned Combat Air Vehicle Squadron (first sortie)
,
Copy that. First wave airborne, engaging.
Target discharging photons from dorsal fins.
Gojira's taking down the drones as planned.
1st sortie demolished.
We wear him down.
Keep it discharging until it's spent
2nd drone sortie, all destroyed.
US Forces Japan, Yokota Air Base runway
,
3rd sortie commencing attack!
Target moving to predetermined coordinates.
3rd sortie destroyed!
Contamination zone is growing.
Radiation exceeding permitted amount.
If we stop now, all will be lost. Continue the attack.
4th sortie destroyed!
We can't let up. Launch the 5th sortie.
Target has stopped discharging its beam from dorsal fins.
GSDF 32nd Infantry Regiment, Third Bomb Squad
.
How can it do that?
5th sortie destroyed.
Kai, 32nd Infantry Regiment Third Company Chairman
,
Godzilla plume is double the intensity.
Hang in there. Launch 6th sortie.
Volume's decreasing.
Matsui, Communications Platoon Leader
,
Target's flame has ceased.
Nogi, 32nd Infantry Regiment Lieutenant Colonel
,
Target luring to Kill Point 1 complete.
Begin Phase 3! Stationary blasting!
Fire!
Radiation at expected value.
Fixing target at Kill Point 1.
Start Phase 4. Guided blast.
US Navy Aegis Destroyer Fleet Huey, Boso Peninsula, Pacific Ocean
.
RGM-109C Cruise missile
Target down!
Kill Point 1 fixing complete.
Launch final phase. Special crane platoon.
Murayama, First Special Crane Platoon Leader
,
Roger! 1st platoon forward!
First Special Crane Platoon Wheel Loader Group
,
Crane Platoon 01, Hydra-slayer 01, move out!
Deploy Cranes 12 to 14 to battle positions behind BP2.
Concrete Pump Truck Group
,
Deploy Cranes 12 to 14 to battle positions behind BP2.
First Special Crane Platoon Wheel Loader Group
Hydra-slayer 01, Crane 11 and BP1 in deployment zone. Over.
Crane 11, Hydra-slayer 01, copy! Standby with engines ready.
Deploy outriggers! Approach BP1 and commence injection!
Crane 12 and BP2 deployed.
Hydra-slayer 01, Crane 15. All vehicles deployed.
Engaging hook up. Over.
Crane 15, Hydra-slayer 01, copy.
Tank Truck Group
,
Stay at outer operation range.
Start injection!
Inject coagulant!
Initiate all pumps! RC operational!
Okay, raise output pressure! Target the mouth as much as possible.
20% of supply administered.
Dosage to target exceeds 30%!
Crane Platoon 1 has been annihilated.
Dosage is working! Target is slowing!
Now's our chance. Send all train bombs!
Unmanned train bombs (E233 & E231 Series trains)
.
Gojira's fallen!
2nd platoon roll out!
2nd and 3rd platoons forward. Freeze the bugger!
Second and Third Special Crane Platoons
.
Kikuchi, Second Special Crane Platoon Leader
Administer all at once!
50% of supply administered!
First 20 tanks are running out.
Got it. Switch tanks to 21 and above!
60% of supply administered!
75% of supply gone!
We've passed the projected coagulant minimum.
90% of supply administered.
100% used. Critical point reached.
The target's skin is stiffening!
Please work.
Did it work?
The target has resumed activity!
Full evacuation now!
Change positions! Hurry!
Abandon attack and quickly evacuate to holding area!
Chest area temperature has dropped to -196 degrees.
Gojira...
has been completely silenced!
Operation Yashiori is terminated.
Thank you. All were remarkable
We were down to under an hour.
Too close for comfort.
But we owe it to the PM convincing France.
Morelli, French Ambassador to Japan
Excuse me!
Look at this survey data.
Gojira's new isotope has a half-life of 20 days.
It'll be halved in a month, gone in 2, 3 years.
That's good news for Tokyo residents.
Thank god.
GSDF Nerima Base, Nerima Ward
.
Good work.
The Satomi cabinet will be resigning en masse.
In line with your scenario?
It wasn't mine. This was all PM Satomi's scenario.
The capital and government are in shambles.
Good opportunity to rebuild it right.
Once relief and reconstruction bills are passed...
it'll dissolve for general election.
To resuscitate Japan and 3.6 million metropolitan refugees...
we'll need a brand new cabinet.
This country rose up through scrap-and-build.
It'll be done again.
The countdown was merely suspended.
But it'll restart when Gojira begins moving.
3,526 seconds to launch.
I'm amazed you allowed that.
I had to keep the world satisfied.
Now Japan... no...
Mankind, must coexist with Gojira.
You shared the data with France.
With France and the whole world.
I broke a promise, but regret nothing.
I like your by-any-means approach.
So...
you'd better not quit
When I'm US President,
you'd be ideal as my Japanese counterpart.
Your Japanese puppet, you mean.
The fact remains that casualties were high.
Accountability comes with the job.
A politician must decide whether to own it or not.
I myself choose to own it.
Well, as Maki said,
"Do as you like."
But now's not the time to quit.
Things are still far from settled.